<Blog>

<date>27,November,2002</date>
<post>


       
      yay! it changed! :) i think i get it now. you have to post/publish something  new  for the changes to take effect. aaaaaaaahhhhhh.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,November,2002</date>
<post>


       
      i've been trying to change the template for my blog for the past few days and i've been unsuccessful. it's very frustrating. i was able to do it once, but then when i wanted to change it again, it didn't work anymore. i did everything the same as that first time. it doesn't say anywhere that i can only change templates ONCE! does it?  sigh.  i better go check.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,November,2002</date>
<post>


       
      i have a dilemma. after a really long while, i've recently gotten back in touch with my old flame. let's call him D. he's been sending me these really sentimental "you're special" or "miss you" or "glad i have you" type of sms messages. yesterday he asked me to check out his band's website and sign the guestbook. i found his pictures on the website and  OHMYGAWD  he's still as cute, maybe even cuter, than ever!  haaaaaaaayyyy . i had this really hot sexy dream about him last night. i dreamt that i was in a dorm and he came over. at first we were talking and then we were flirting and then making out. after i got all hot and bothered, i leaned over to him and whispered "i want you". and then we got into this huge hot tub and i started singing  dilemma  (nelly/kelly). we did some heavy foreplay in the tub and then we got out and started looking for a bedroom. then my mom and dad suddenly was there so we had to sneak around and finally got into a safe room where nobody would find us. it was all cozy and perfect. we were undressing each other and then sort of fell onto the bed when... i woke up. all sweaty like.  WHEW!  my sister thinks i'm stupid for even thinking about that guy still. she never liked him. she *loves* my boyfriend now. she feels like he's her real older brother (i'm the eldest, we don't have a  kuya   kase ) and he really does treat her like she's his own younger sister. he's very protective and caring. my boyfriend really is a great guy. but D is SO cute. i know D will always be my crush. i've had a crush on him since i was like 8 and now i'm in my 20's but when i see him i still feel like i did when i was 8... so maybe that's all there is to it. a childish infatuation that won't die. i guess i could never really love him the way i love my boyfriend now. but be with him one night?  OOOOOHHHH  *slap* naughty girl... bad! bad! hahaha but really it's only in my head. i could never... EVER.  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,November,2002</date>
<post>


       
      you'd think this was easy. damn. i don't know where to start. this is SO weird. it's like talking in front of a million people.. or  trying  to.. and i was never really good at speaking in public. speeches make me nervous. i start sttutttt..stt.. stttuuttuuttttuhh.. uhmmm.. *deep breath*... stututtering! HAH! ok why did i start a blog? because i'm a bum right now and i have nothing better to do. i wonder if a lot of people actually spend their precious time reading these things when it's so easy to start one. i think people usually would rather listen to themselves talking than hear others. i myself am a listener though. each person i know has told me at least one deep, dark secret that *supposedly* no one else knows. and i'm about ready to explode with all these secrets.. but unfortunately i am also a woman of my word and i cannot divulge any of it in this blog... weeeeell... maybe one or two. hehe. anyways, lately i haven't been able to sleep at night. i stay up and just   worry   (about anything and everything) and miss my boyfriend. 2 nasty habits i've got to kick. i have to admit though, missing my boyfriend all the time seems to be unavoidable. and anyway if i stop missing him when he's not around, would that mean i don't love him anymore? i miss him SO bad. that said, i think i'm almost ready to go to sleep. at the start of our relationship, he would call before he goes to sleep when we couldn't be together (of course, after a year and a half, i'm lucky if i get a call twice in a week), anyway he used to tell me that he doesn't miss me so much because he gets to be with me in his dreams.. he says that in his dreams we're in a place that's all green and cool - lots of trees, green grass, all kinds of plants, beautiful waterfalls - he says it's kinda like that island in jurassic park. one time, a friend of his heard us talking about this and asked, "are there dinosaurs in your dream too?". it stopped being romantic after that and he stopped talking about it. LOL.. :)      
     

    
</post>

<date>01,December,2002</date>
<post>


       
      fuck pms. i hate being so hormonal. i went into a rage a while ago because my boyfriend kept bugging me to have dinner and i was watching my fave show on tv and i already told him to just wait a few minutes til the show was over. but i know that's not really what's bothering me. i was annoyed because a few days ago he told me that i always have to get what i want. i know it's true but it just doesn't seem fair coz i  know  that he's the same way. like when  he's  watching a game, i have to call him a thousand times before he'd come to the table or even just respond.  sigh.  and then finally he'd come to the table and sit.. where he could watch the game while he eats and totally ignores me. and do i complain when he does that? no! it seems like i always get the bad rap whenever we have an argument. i'm the spoiled brat. i'm too emotional. i'm being irrational. when he's the one who has the communication capabilities of a cave man! i just hate fighting so much and i'm so tired and moody i just went all quiet on him and let him go home without talking about it. he's supposed to come over tomorrow but he probably won't. but i'm not gonna beat myself up over this one anymore and i'm not gonna cry anymore. i'm not perfect.. and neither is he!  oh god... i miss him already...  pms sucks.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,January,2003</date>
<post>


       
      D's been texting again and it's gotten worse. he's past "i miss you" and "you're special" and he's now gone into "i love you" and "i'll always hold you in my heart".  sigh.  what is up with that? he knows i have a boyfriend. he's implied that he has a girlfriend, although i can't be sure coz i don't really talk to him or even text him back. i avoid it as much as possible coz i don't want to encourage any more of his mushy sentimental messages. maybe he's just being all christianly. he's the church type. maybe it's like bretherenly church love or something. i don't know. i don't even see him anymore. he's crazy. can't say i'm not flattered though. hehe. oh and all of a sudden, out of the blue, his sister starts texting me too telling me that she and her big brother (D) are planning a party, sort of a reunion, for all of our old friends, people we used to go to church with. she says i HAVE to go. hmmmmmmm.. interesting. whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaat???? :) LOL!
     

    
</post>

<date>10,January,2003</date>
<post>


       
      whaaaaaaaat???? :) i haven't been able to post anything since the holidays started. things were ABSOLUTELY chaotic here but the noise has died down now and i'm back to my old routine - tv, tv, and more tv. meanwhile, normal people in the normal world are back at work or at school.  i don't know if it's just me but it seems like the more i stay at home, the more i don't want to go out. i'm turning 23 at the end of the month and i'm still where i was when i was 22. i don't want to get into a beat-myself-up mode coz once i start one of those.. well it's hard to get out of it but i can't help it. i'm restless, i'm embarassed, i feel useless, worthless, and insecure coz i don't have a job. it's been almost a year since i graduated and i'm still nowhere. i quit the first job i ever had after a month coz i felt like the people were mean to me. or maybe i was just having trouble adjusting to a work environment. maybe it wasn't the right job for me. who knows? my mom thinks i'm just a big softie or a coward maybe. i've always been the girl with the big potential but what's potential when there's no motivation, no drive, no passion, no determination, no courage, no strength behind it. i'm afraid those things i lack and how to get them is one thing i don't know. in college i thought i knew everything. i went to the best university in the country and before that, to one of the best high schools in the country. but no one can teach you what you want or tell you what your purpose in life is. and that's just it. i'm on a big plateau going round and round but not really getting anywhere coz i don't know where to go. I DON'T KNOW WHAT I WANT. i know what i DON'T want though. i don't want to get stuck in a job where i'm not happy. happiness is such an elusive thing. like right now, some people might actually think i have a great life. i mean, i get to choose between a big house or a condo to slug around all day in. i have a great car, good food, nice clothes, bags, shoes, big screen TVs, a cellphone, a laptop - everything. and i don't even have to pay for any of the miscellaneous expenses that come with those things like cellphone bills or gas money or repairs. i have typically everything that generous, loving, wealthy parents would give to their child. it sounds like i'm bragging but i'm not. i'm not proud of the way i'm living my life right now on this damned plateau. i'm totally miserable because i can't just be this. a slug! a clown! a sidekick! i go around and cheer people up or make them laugh. i run a few errands for my parents. but mostly, i'm furniture. that's the most use that i've been to anyone. this can't be all there is to me or for me. i just don't know what i want to do. when i'm alone, i think so much. i worry. i stress. i plan. but nothing happens. they all stay in my head all jumbled up. i can't make up my mind. maybe because most of my life i've been given things before i ask or before i even want it. i don't know how to want or how to make a decision because i'm used to having things served to me on a silver platter. what do i do? it's like i have everything and i have nothing. it doesn't make me feel good to still be living off my parents like this. i know they have money and they don't complain but still it doesn't feel right to me. i want to make my own money, buy my own things, earn my own living. i guess that's another reason why i don't go out much. unless it's an absolute necessity, i avoid asking my parents for money. sometimes i don't even have money to buy a pack of cigarettes so i have to bum off my sister all the time and sometimes she gives me these looks.. it just diminishes me.  *deep breath*  anyways..  like i said, it's hard for me to stop once i start talking about this. i guess that's why i started EVE'S PLATEAU coz my family, my boyfriend, and my friends are probably gonna sew my lips together if they even suspect i'm gonna start talking about all THAT again. in real life, people always think i'm such a happy-go-lucky laid back person most of the time. they probably wouldn't believe i'm really that bothered with something. usually they think that i just like to bug people with petty things. petty things! it's not trivial to ME! hey, it's my LIFE after all! anyways they always tell me i'm  makulit .   uuh.. whatever! :p  (by the way, i was thinking of changing the URL to just plain "eves.blogspot.com" coz i thought people might have a hard time remembering or spelling "evesplateau.blogspot.com". i mean it's kinda long, but then again a person who can't spell P-L-A-T-E-A-U probably won't be interested in a blog that has it in the title.. right? so the URL stays!).
     

    
</post>

<date>28,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
      sometimes i find my sister totally despicable and at those times, i despise myself for loving her as much as i do. i know i'm not perfect but please spare me the "judge not thy neighbors (or in this case, thy sibling) lest ye be judged yerself" crap because nobody really knows what it's like to be her sister and to live with her besides me and i'm telling you, it's hell or if ever there's anything worse than hell, then that would be it. i would pity anyone who has to live with someone like my sister. sometimes i wonder why she doesn't just move out and end our suffering. she goes around with this "the world is against me" attitude, but it's more like she's against the whole wide world. she likes to go around thinking that she's a victim when she's really responsible for 99% of the crap she finds herself CONSTANTLY in. and then she thinks she has the right to hate the world and everybody in it, especially me, because she's so oppressed and pressured and treated so so badly. fuck that. she cares about herself and nobody else. she doesn't help anyone with anything. when she rarely does, she expects to be canonized a saint. she thinks our whole family owes her something, only she and God knows what, so everything we do for her is simply our job or obligation and deserves no thanks. sometimes she just blows up in your face because she's annoyed by everything or she thinks you did something wrong. she is the first person to judge me and put a magnifying glass to my every fault. and still SHE thinks I'M the one treating her badly when i've always tried to understand HER and be there for her. she's never around for the family not even for me. we're all there for her. everybody thinks she's so strong but really, she survives because she runs away from everything. she gets drunk, she takes drugs, she has sex with whomever, she locks herself up in her room. really, i don't know how she can even be called a part of our family. she's a ghost. she is bitter, cynical, and envious. she is ungrateful. she is the worst kind of bitch there is. she slept with my friend's boyfriend and therefore, *I* ended up losing HALF my friends and getting hated and my reputation getting ruined because I covered up for her. but did i stop asking her to join me in my nights out or did i stop introducing her to other friends? NO. but just last week she tells me she stopped inviting me to go out with her and her friends or sometimes even her and MY friend because last time we went out, i kept whining about my boyfriend not being there. wow. i'm such a loser just because i happened to mention that i missed my boyfriend and i deserve to be excommunicated from her nights out. not that i care. but it just irks me that she could be so self-righteous to.. my god.. words fail me. not that i'm saying that i'm some angel but at least i try to be. she revels in her evilness. she's dark, she's poetic, she's depressed. damn that. she has a car, she's pretty, she can ask for money whenever she needs or wants it, she lives in a nice house, goes to a nice expensive school, has great parents.. damn. she's really got a lot to be angry about doesn't she? she is a lost child and i've just about given up waiting for her to grow up. maybe she is a tiyanak. in filipino folklore that's a monster that takes the form of a an infant. i don't know if she'll ever stop blaming me or unloading her trash on me for everything that's wrong in her life. it's sad really. this isn't even half of it. she's so pathetic sometimes she gets so damned hard up about looking cool and together and superior that it in itself is pathetic. i don't really know what she is to anybody. she's only a daughter and a sister to her family because she happened to be born into it. but if i had a choice, i really think i'd choose somebody else to be my sister. she's not a sister to me in the real sense of that word. we just happen to have the same parents. but i try to be one to her. at the most, she's been accomodating at times when it works for her. i guess she's just that way. maybe she'll never change. she complains about love and men but i don't think she has it in her to love and to share a life with someone because in her world, there's only room for one.. herself. if she doesn't change or even try to, i don't think she'll ever be happy and then she'll continue to blame me and envy me for the rest of our lives. i can't live with that. i wish she could just be someone i had to put up with on social occasions and don't actually have to live with. maybe then we could at least like each other.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
      my room looks like a junkyard. just thought you needed to know that. LOL.  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
      i just found out that D is getting married in december. so what, right? well a couple days after i found out, i dreamt that i met his fiancee and she was really ugly. in reality, i haven't met her but i don't know what my dream meant. did i want her to be ugly? is god telling me she's ugly? is that ugly girl in my dream actually the subconscious dream-state incarnation of me when i was with him and do i therefore see that version of ME as UGLY? i guess there are a thousand and one ways to interpret that dream, freud would have a field day. but if i'm to be truthful, i guess i have to say that when i found out he was getting married, i felt the tiniest tug in my heart. i can't describe it accurately. it wouldn't be right to say that i was hurt or disappointed or jealous.. but i was undoubtedly  affected . i guess in the back of my mind, i had always believed that i was the love of his life and that he would spend his life pining away for me living as a bachelor infinitely and desperately hoping that he would one day have me in his arms again. haha. guess i was wrong. i'm an intelligent girl with the heart of an idiot. just because he was the only one i could imagine spending the rest of my life with (that was before i met the love of  my  life) doesn't mean he felt the same way for me. see, i  know  that but my heart seems to think otherwise. oh well. hey, i have a job now. does this mean i'm off my plateau? we'll see.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      the thing that i wrote about my friend at the end part of my last post was totally unwarranted. she did not deserve all that i said and i am the worst person for having said things the way i did. but i will not remove the post because it will serve as a reminder for me the next time i feel the itch to bring down a person so freely with a simple flick of the wrist. i am a jerk, a bitch, an idiot. once again, my insecurities have gotten the best of me and i am so ashamed.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      i was awake half the night because a bunch of mosquitos wouldn't quit munching on me like i was a buffet. i couldn't get up and look for the mosquito spray coz i was SO sleepy and i couldn't keep the blanket on coz it was too hot. finally, towards day break, i guess the little fuckers got too full and their wings couldn't carry them anymore so i finally got some sleep. today was a generic day. meaning, eat, sleep, tv, eat. i miss my cute boy so much.  it's holy week so it's 3 days of no work/no school for most filipinos. some people see this as a chance to go home to the province to see their family and friends, others take trips to the beach, out of town, or out of the country, while some people choose to simply stay at home and get some much needed R&R. most people though still observe catholic traditions that are actually the reason for these holy and sacred days, that is to commemorate (did i spell that right?) Jesus Christ's last days as a man who walked this earth up to the point where he ascended into heaven. i'm not catholic so i don't really know all of the rituals and traditions but i know one is to hold sort of like prayer meetings in one person's home where the devotees gather and spend all day reciting some prayers/chants/songs. all day. nothing but chanting, prayers, songs and such. i was painfully reminded of this as i was awakened early this morning by a group of people's voices coming from my neighbor's house, the one right behind our house. my room, unfortunately, is at the back part of the house and so i am at hearing range. and just a while ago, after observing my own ritual of watching star trek voyager at midnight, i went to my room intending to go to sleep when i was greeted by the sounds of chanting, prayers and songs. so here i am. it's not that i look down on other people for being devoted to their religion. i'm just... well, not able to sleep. it's their right though. i just hope tomorrow they hold the meeting at the house on the next block.   i miss my cute boy. i often find myself daydreaming these days about my boyfriend proposing to me and us getting married. i daydream about my wedding day, about life as a wife, as a mother, and as a sister- / daughter- / cousin- / relative-in-law. i worry, i get excited, i get anxious, i laugh and i cry about it. like i'm ally mcbeal or something. and that's not good coz it's not always endearing to be hopeless and crazy. it doesn't help that everywhere i turn people are getting married - people i know, people i don't know, people in tv shows, people in tv show reruns, people in movies, people in "made for tv" movies, people who are old, people who are too young, people who are big, people who are small... i mean little, people of every color, race, and face. is it bad that all i really want is to be a good wife and mother as well as an awesome woman with or without a career? people put so much emphasis and importance on women having a career these days. it may be important to some people but not to all people. i don't think it's a nod to feminism if women start acting like they have something to prove. because we don't. if i don
     

    
</post>

<date>14,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      okay i am probably not pregnant. i got my period. it was lighter than usual though and i heard some people got their periods and still turned out to be pregnant. i get nauseous sometimes but there are lots of other reasons for that. earlier today i got nauseous when i smelled my handwash gel thingy and it never did that before but then again maybe it was just coz i was in a moving vehicle and the driver was satan's prodigy. he drove into the potholes and bumps with a certain disturbing silent glee. sigh. i don't know anymore how to distinguish between wishful thinking and instinct. i TOTALLY thought, felt, sensed, and knew that i was pregnant and maybe that was only coz i really i wanted to be. i'm torn between wanting to take a test so bad just to be sure (maybe hoping to be surprised) and feeling so desperate at the thought that it might be another negative result wanting to save myself from the grief. why is it that human nature causes us to want something that we know or think we can't have? uncertainty again. hello, my friend.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      i think i might be pregnant. i missed a pill a day after i had sex... with my boyfriend, of course. i have this nagging suspicion that i am. but it's like i think i'm pregnant every month. my friends don't believe me anymore coz of all the false alarms i've had. something i would never admit to them and even to myself was that those other times, deep inside, i felt like and knew that there's a big chance that i really wasn't pregnant. i wasn't surprised to get my period those other times, not really, just disappointed i guess. i've wanted a baby ever since i found out that i might not ever have kids. i have PCOS (polycystic ovarian syndrome) and my ex-obgyn told me that i might become infertile if i don't get pregnant  soon . told me that with a little taunting smile and in a horrifying matter-of-fact tone. in one breath, she sentenced me to a life without children. i love children. i even majored in child development in college. but after what that obgyn told me, i distanced myself from children. i used to hold and play with any baby around. but now it just hurts too much to be close to them knowing that i might never actually have any of my own. since then, i've heard and read lots of more hopeful things about my condition and my new obgyn is a specialist in infertility and she tells me that i have nothing to worry about. still, that monstrous doctor's voice won't go away. so even though i know that this is not the best time for me and my boyfriend to have a baby, i really would be happy if we were blessed with one. anyways, unlike those other times, i have this feeling... it's a kind of certainty... like my body's letting me know something is there... we'll see...
     

    
</post>

<date>01,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      it's labor day tomorrow. one day vacation... yay. it always confused me why on *labor day*, people don't celebrate *labor* by, it should be obvious enough, *laboring*. oh well. too bad GMA - the president (who is terribly fond of declaring holidays) - probably couldn't justify making this a long weekend. we've had a couple of long weekends since she became president. usually in a situation like this where there's a working day sandwiched in between a holiday and the weekend, she'll go, "what the hell, forget that one miserable working day! let's have a long weekend!" maybe not exactly in those words but that's pretty much what happens. a lot of people criticize her for this, mostly people who are paid on a "show up and work your ass off or you get nothing... NOTHING!!!!" basis. i don't blame them, they have a point. but i, personally, am with her on this one. i mean, we have gone through a lot because of ERAP. i think we deserve some much needed R&R... if not for what we've been through, we might need to be ready for what we'll be going through if the elections next year present us with another monster/president and greedy idiots/senators. we might need to prepare for another rough ride... maybe rougher than ever. if you live in the philippines, even if you don't follow political news religiously, if you merely catch the news while surfing channels, you'll KNOW who and what i'm talking about. mr. kingping. *shiver* he's SO creepy. i'm glad there are still people brave enough to go up against a guy like him, like rosebud and that cop guy even though he took back the stuff he said at least he got it out there, who come out in the open, even though it might mean losing their lives and the lives of the people they love, to try to uphold the truth and everything that's right and pure in this world. sigh. i don't really like thinking and talking about political issues (don't get me started on the bush franchise), it's so depressing. the whole world is going to pieces... give us another long weekend! it's summer vacation and we need it now more than ever! :) sigh if only the world were as easy as a sunday morning... or a sundae on a sunday morning!   enough of politics!   my boyfriend and i usually spend weekends together. sometimes he stays until midweek. no matter how long we're together, when he goes home, i miss him instantly and therefore i call him or go to see him even before a day has passed. i don't do that all the time but my calls and trips to his house are peppered throughout the week. it's torture for me because i end up looking like a sick pathetic puppy dog chasing him around and that's no fun for ME even though i'm happiest when i'm with him. confused yet? well it's torture for him because he has other things to do and he seems not able to do "things" when i'm around... understandably, of course. he's a very caring guy and he feels very guilty when i'm with him and he has to leave me somewhere while he's painting the fence, hauling wood, blocks, garbage, etc, driving for everybody in his neighborhood (he's that nice), etc. he has A LOT of "things to do", believe me. his family and friends depend on him so much. it's like they can't breathe if he's not around. not that i begrudge them the presence and service of their son/brother/cousin/friend/etc. it's just that... i don't know. i'm haunted by paranoid scenarios like... we're married, my first pregnancy, i'm due, my water breaks, i panic, i can't find him, nobody's home coz it's LABOR day, my family and friends are at the beach, so i wait for him... for hours, i can't take the pain anymore, i finally decide to go to the hospital by myself, and i end up giving birth in a smelly cab with a smelly driver with greasy hands. but hey, at least the fence looks nice. *shudder* i know he'd rather that i'm home safe and comfortable and able to do "things" of my own when he's busy. and heaven forbid i get my hands dirty, helping him out is out of the question. so last weekend when he said he'd be busy with "other things to do" this whole week, i resolved not to call him or go to his house to give him the space everybody always says i oughta give him. so there.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      whenever my boyfriend goes home after spending a day or two with me, i can't help but cry. i'm always always afraid that one day he'll never come back... that one day he'll just stop loving me and stop wanting to be with me. i know if it's gonna happen, it's gonna happen. but god i pray it doesn't. i can't imagine me not dying if that happens. maybe not physically but spiritually. my heart and mind will just GO and i'll end up a bitter old shrew or an unhappy wife in an unhappy marriage to someone that's not him. god help me. i think i'm going crazy.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      i don't know if i should break up with my boyfriend. part of me wants to because i feel like i'm not getting my fair share in this relationship. another part of me feels like we can work this out. i don't know if i have the strength to work this out though. it's so hard to get through to him. his greatest effort at making up is simply showing up and saying "i'm sorry" but then nothing changes afterwards and we end up fighting about the same thing over and over again. my friends tell me to hold on. they think we have such a great thing going. i used to think that too. now i just don't know anymore. he always breaks his promises, he says one thing and does another, he never calls, and he can't stand talking about "the relationship". it's like everything is black and white for him but i'm swimming and drowning in a sea of grey. i know people say you shouldn't look for a perfect relationship because it doesn't exist. you're bound to have problems with whoever you're with. but how do you choose what you can live with and what you can't live with?
     

    
</post>

<date>29,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      he's always busy. he doesn't have time... not for me it seems. when i call he's out or sleeping. when i get to talk to him, he's busy. what the fuck, right? i'm gonna get tired of this shit soon and leave his sorry ass crying in the gutter.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      my stars or the planets or the moon or whatever heavenly (or hellish) bodies ruling my destiny are all in disarray. it's like they went on lunch break and decided not to come back to work, go hide under cosmic rocks instead to drive me crazy. hey!!! come back and make my life great again. almost all my friends are gone either to the united states of america or to the disunited states of friendship, the republic of bitter resentment, and the islands of envy and gossip. my boyfriend went out with his EX (but not on a romantic date, on a friendly group get-together thing with friends but still..) behind my back and so now i hate him and i can never ever trust him or be comfortable with him ever again. i will always have this nagging feeling that he's hiding things from me. he told me to my FACE that he wasn't planning to tell me about it and he didn't see why he needed to. i threw at him every bad word i knew. i was SO mad but i wish i hadn't cursed him out. part of me is glad i did and thinks that it was a long time coming but part of me fears that he will never look at me the same way again. i realized and finally accepted that we are so different it's surprising why we're still together. we have such different ideas about love and fidelity and equality. i feel like he's thinking that he's "putting up" with me. that he's always right. that he has the upper hand. that i will do anything for him. i hate feeling like this. i hate being last on his list. i hate being stepped on and ignored. i'm going to get gorgeous and get famous and rule the world and never look back. sigh. 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      sad sad day. i was at my uncle's funeral earlier today. i never really knew him that well but he was always nice to me during family gatherings and stuff like that. i was surprised to find myself crying when he was about to be put into the ground. maybe it was sadness over life's end or sympathy for those grieving around me, those who knew him and loved him. it's hard to be in a place like that and not come face to face with your own fears about death - your own and your loved ones'. if dying is not just the extinguishing of life, if there is a next life or an eternity or a paradise or a heaven or hell to transcend to, i wish there was a better way to do it. like maybe through inter-dimentional portals or space travel or eating candles and matches or metamorphosis or simply clicking your heels. *sigh*
     

    
</post>

<date>04,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      i would LOVE to lock lips with johnny depp. god, is he the greatest kisser ever or what??!?! i was surfing channels earlier and i chanced upon "what's eating gilbert grape? (me! me! ooh oh pick me!)" on star movies. it's actually kind of a depressing movie so i wasn't really planning on watching it for long, i only wanted to stare at hottie johnny for a while, but then KABOOM.. kissing scene! and man johnny depp doesn't disappoint. the kiss was oh so tender but oh so sumptuous and passionate.. the kind of kiss you have right before a hot and hurried kind of loving.. yum. *sigh* i want him... here... NOW.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      he was late AGAIN, he didn't call AGAIN, he made me cry AGAIN, he effortlessly hurt my feelings AGAIN, this is all because of his family and/or friends involving drinking and/or going somewhere AGAIN, and for the first time, i broke up with him. oh and i also caught him lying again. god how many times has he fucking lied to me? i've caught him only a few times but he probably did it countless times before. i hate him for that. i hate him for making me feel like he doesn't love me and that i can't compete with his friends, that he doesn't want to be with me, that he'd rather drink EVERY freaking time. he hurt me so much. he'd also rather SLEEP his stupid ass off rather than talk about our relationship and work it out. i was so pissed i stormed into the room and said " AYOKO NA ! (I GIVE UP)" and gave him back the ring he gave me. he, on the other hand, responded with a snore. oh, i hate him. if i thought it was bad a few weeks ago, well it just got worse. i don't have a boyfriend, i'm probably about to lose the business, and i'm breaking out.. eek! 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      last time i tried to post, blogger went all buggy. i hate that. and just when i had some real good things to say too. hope i remember what i said. here goes..  shakespeare's sonnet CXVI  Let me not to the marriage of true minds Admit impediments. Love is not love Which alters when it alteration finds, Or bends with the remover to remove: O no! it is an ever-fixed mark That looks on tempests and is never shaken; It is the star to every wandering bark, Whose worth's unknown, although his height be taken. Love's not Time's fool, though rosy lips and cheeks Within his bending sickle's compass come: Love alters not with his brief hours and weeks, But bears it out even to the edge of doom. If this be error and upon me proved, I never writ, nor no man ever loved.  i first heard this sonnet in the movie version of jane austen's novel "sense and sensibility". i was touched then by the beautiful words and the emotion in it but i never really understood what it meant until now. love is an "ever-fixed mark". it cannot be altered or removed. my friends tell me to just get over him. him that i loved with every fiber of my being. how can i? throw it away like a piece of trash. i can't. i will always, always love him. even if i never see him again. even if i end up spending the rest of my life with someone else. i will always, always love avel. he is an ever-fixed mark on my heart and soul. i've never been so sure of anything in my life.  i miss him everywhere everytime everyday in every way. i miss his kiss that never failed to make my knees go weak, his smile that always made my heart skip a beat, his smell that made me heady, his touch that gave me a fever, his embrace that made me feel so safe, his laugh that was like the sound of life itself, his face that was so beautiful to me, his hands that were the gentlest in the world, his cute ass that he's so self-conscious about, his love... i miss him so bad it hurts all the time. it's never not there. i feel so bad that i gave up on him. i hurt him. i let him go. he has every right to never talk to me again. but i have every right to wait until he does. don't give up on me, love, just because i gave up on you. please. i'm just waiting.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      i watched the last episode of joe millionaire last night. i hated that show at first because it was just stupid but i have to admit that the last episode was really *kilig*. although it seems too perfect i'm tempted to think it's all a set up, ya know. setup or not, it was a great ending. it was like a modern day fairytale. it was ugly at times but at least in the end the disney princess ended up with the prince charming. i was rooting for zora because i think neither sarah nor melissa would have even given evan a chance if they met him in the real world and knew right away that he was a construction worker. maybe evan sensed that. then again, i don't think the producers would have allowed evan to pick the bondage princess (sarah) even if she was really the one he wanted. on the other hand, i felt that evan was gonna pick zora coz she's the only one who hasn't jumped into bed with him I THINK and she's sort of a mystery. guys always fall for that, ya know, like a "conquering new territory" thing. sigh. do fairytales still happen without the aid of tv producers? what about miracles? maybe all that's been happening to me is a message from wherever or whoever.. "get real! this is the real world. life is not fair. love rarely overcomes anything.. or comes at all. money comes before everything. not all people are basically good." i get like this, all cynical and sarcastic, whenever my heart gets broken. but it was never shattered like this before. maybe that's why it's so hard. i loved avel so much. i still do. when you really, really love.. how do you just stop? how do you move on? i just want to be with him. that's all. is that too much to ask? that's all i want.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey i think my banker likes me. lolz. at first, i thought he was gay (i still kinda think he is), but he has been giving me looks. the other day, he said "you look really good today". then today he said, "is mr. lazarte your husband or your father?" (coz i have a joint account with my dad). heh. my sister says "maybe he was just being nice?" way to give my self-esteem a boost. lolz. whatever. anyways like i said, i can't even consider having a new relationship right now. can't even imagine it although i feel like crap waiting around for someone who might not ever come around, someone who might have forgotten me in one click, someone who might not even care anymore. life sucks. and love.. well, love STINKS.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      the poem below was emailed to me by one of my old high school friends. it kinda hit me right where it hurts, ya know? lolz. but what's new? what ISN'T wrong in my life? what DOESN'T hurt me and make me blue? these days, i'm lucky if i can smile at least twice in 12 hours. oh well..  ------------------------------------------------------------------------- THE BLAME  If you see me walking the road with someone else It's not because I like his company It's because you're not brave enough to walk beside me.  If you hear me talking about him all the time It's not because he pleases me It's because you're too deaf to hear my heartbeat.  If you feel me falling with someone new It's not because I love him But because you're not there to catch me if I fall.  If you feel lost, I too am nowhere I too don't know where the road is going Are we gonna cross each other's path Or just completely turn around? Will we just let go of what we had Or go to the place where love is bound?  Don't let me walk with him It's you I want to walk with Don't let me talk of him It's you I want to talk with Don't let me fall for him It's you I want to fall in love with. -------------------------------------------------------------------------  THE ANSWER  When you thought I wasn't brave enough to walk beside you I was behind you every step of the way Still filled with awe because of the beauty that stands before me  When you thought I was too deaf to hear your heartbeat I didn't want to assume anything And I was afraid to lose our friendship  When you thought I wasn't there to catch you It was because you never gave me the chance You never reached the bottom, you've already grabbed a branch  If you feel like you are nowhere, I too am lost I too don't know where the road is going Are we just going to turn around, Or are we gonna cross each other's path? Will we just let go of what we had Or go to the place where love is bound?  Don't let me walk alone I want to walk by your side Don't let me talk of something else It's you I want to talk with Don't let me fall for someone else It's you I want to fall in love with.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      if you're not for me then why does this distance maim my life? i don't know why you're so far away but i know that this much is true.. i hope you are the one i share my life with and i wish that you could be the one i die with and i'm prayin' you're the one i build my home with.. i hope i love you all my life is there any way that i could stay in your arms? coz i miss you body and soul so strong that it takes my breath away and i breathe you into my heart and pray for the strength to stand today coz i love you whether its wrong or right and though i can't be with you tonight know my heart is by your side.. i don't wanna run away but i can't take it i don't understand.. if i'm not made for you then why does my heart tell me that i am.. (if you're not the one)
     

    
</post>

<date>10,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      i'm going to extremes to prove i'm fine without you but in reality i'm slowly losing my mind underneath my constant smile gradually i'm dying inside friends ask me how i feel and i lie convincingly coz i don't want to reveal the fact that i'm suffering so i wear my disguise til i go home at night  and turn out all the lights and then i break down and cry.. so what do you do when somebody you're so devoted to suddenly just stops loving you and it seems they haven't got a clue of the pain that rejection is putting you through do you cling to your pride and sing "i will survive"? do you lash out and say "how dare you leave this way"? do you hold in vain as they just slip away? (breakdown)  i hate that i can't stop thinking about him and wishing he'd show up one of these days. i have enough to think about. i have to collect payments for the business and people don't have the money to pay. or just don't want to. my dad is breathing down my neck all the fucking time. god i need a break. PLEASE. my luck or whatever is just spiraling down a vortex of darkness. maybe i should buy a lottery ticket, i might just win with all the good luck i've got coming to me. that is, IF there really is equilibrium in this world. but life is never fair. i won't hold my breath. i've realized how much he meant to me, what he was in my life. i've had shitty times before but they never seemed this bad because he was always there to support me and get my back and fight for me. he was always there helping me in big and little ways. he was my stronghold. now i feel like i'm carrying such a big burden alone. i can't help but feel like things would be so much better if he were around. but who knows? the last few weeks before the breakup, he was actually more of a burden than a relief. i think that's why i was pushed to the edge. when i said that i give up, i didn't mean i give up on him. i was just so tired of all the bad things happening. it was more of a "i give up. life sucks. give me a break." and that's exactly what i got. be careful what you wish for. sigh. i don't know how he can stand this. if he really loves me, how can he stand it? how can he stay away? does he know how much i need him? probably not. does he care? how can he just let it end like this? what is he thinking? is he giving me time? is this actually what he wants? what's keeping him from running back to me? pride? fear? hate? anger? lord help me. is there still hope? i told my friends that i was feeling better these days. but that's not completely true. i'm just as down as i was before or maybe worse. i just know now how to put on a facade and wait quietly and cry internally. i just don't SEEM that bad anymore. i can smile. i can laugh. but only on the outside. deep inside, nothing's changed. if he feels half as bad as i do.. he'd come to me right now. right this very second. but why don't i? why can't i? i love him SO much, maybe even more now than when we were together, and i miss him SO bad it's killing me.  how can you just walk away from me when all i can do is watch you leave? you coming back to me is against the odds but that's the chance i've got to take. but to wait for you is all i can do.. (against all odds)  love of my life, you've hurt me. you've broken my heart and now you leave me. love of my life, can't you see? bring it back. don't take it away from me because you don't know what it means to me.. (love of my life)  maybe nothing lasts forever even if you stay together. i don't need forever after. it's your laughter that won't let me go so i'm holding on this way.. did you know? could you tell? you are the only one that i've ever loved. now everything's so wrong.. (my favorite mistake)  can't nobody do it like you. every little thing that you do stays on my mind.. well i thought i could just get over you. but i see that's something i just can't do. from the way you would hold me to the sweet things you told me i just can't find a way to let go of you.. (officially missing you)  i wake up to shadows touching your pillow looking for a trace of your smile and that's when it hit me.. you're no longer with me.. i crave your touch. i crave your lips. i miss so much the excitement of your kiss. and since you're gone, my heart won't behave. it's your love that i still crave. and just the thought of never waking up with you again always turns me inside out.. how could we let it end? (crave)  baby, help me.. coz without you my whole world is falling apart.. and i'm going crazy.. i need you to come back home.. (can you help me)
     

    
</post>

<date>10,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      i've started letting myself face the probability that he might never come after me. he might just let me go just like that. even though it hurts like hell, i can't keep lying to myself. he said it himself, he can live without me. he told me that right from the start. i can't and won't do anything about it. i admit that the only thing keeping me from going down on my knees and begging him to come back to me is the thought that he might think less of me for it and lose any respect he has for me and then eventually stop loving me. but i guess that is enough. i'd rather lose him this way, with my dignity intact. as one of my friends said, he might be the love of my life but he's not my whole world. i have to believe that i can live without him too. i have to...
     

    
</post>

<date>08,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      have you ever missed someone so bad you actually literally physically feel like a part of you is missing? these days, my worst times are when i miss him so much i feel like vomiting from my stomach feeling like a blackhole even if i've just eaten. my best times are when i'm in front of the tv and my brain is numbed or when i'm with friends talking my heart out (and their ears off). my grandma says i'll be over him in 3 months. if that's true, if love has an expiry date, then it should feel better and better as the days go by.. but it doesn't. it feels worse and worse. or maybe it's like cheese, you never really notice it's starting to expire until the last few days before the deadline. maybe even a few days after. haha. can't manage the tiniest hint of a smile right now. insomnia is getting worse. blackhole is getting bigger. head is pounding harder. it's like my body is as broken as my heart is. i'm going stark raving mad. i wanna move on but i can't. i wanna hold on but i can't. i wanna SLEEP for pete's sake!!! but even in my sleep, i find no rest. my dreams are as restless as my life is..
     

    
</post>

<date>29,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      i'm sorry but i just can't take it anymore. i never understood the saying "misery loves company" as well as i do now. i never felt it as much. because i was never really miserable, no, not until i found love and lost it. now i can't take seeing people in love. i find myself cursing at those people who write testimonials on friendster about their boyfriends or girlfriends saying how happy they are, how in love they are, how wonderful it is when they're together.. because i'm miserable, i'm in love but can't be with the one i love, i had it wonderful too but then it ended! it hurts!!!!!! and i'm so scared. i'm scared that i'll never find love again. i'm scared that i let my one chance go. i'm terrified at the thought that he's gonna end up with someone else. someone simple, pretty, thin, submissive, and dumb.. someone who can never love him as much as i do. someone who can never understand him the way i do. someone who isn't me. how can something that feels so certain be so vague? how can he not be the one for me when every fiber of my being aches for him? my soul calls out for him.. my heart is dead without him.. my body is restless and can only find peace in his touch. how can i take back what i have already given? my love, my time, my life? when you give someone your everything, what happens when he goes away? you're left with nothing but questions and longings. you are drained. how can people expect you to just up and go on with life? he's never coming back. i have to accept it. i can't wait forever. it seems impossible but i will just have to learn to go on and find some way to recharge myself so that i can love again someday.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      excerpt from kahlil gibran's  the prophet :  when love beckons to you, follow him, though his ways are hard and steep.  and when his wings enfold you yield to him,  though the sword hidden among his pinions may wound you.  and when he speaks to you believe in him, though his voice may shatter your dreams as the north wind lays waste the garden.  for even as love crowns you so shall he crucify you. even as he is for your growth so is he for your pruning.  even as he ascends to your height and caresses your tenderest branches that quiver in the sun,  so shall he descend to your roots and shake them in their clinging to the earth.  like sheaves of corn he gathers you unto himself.  he threshes you to make you naked.  he sifts you to free you from your husks.  he grinds you to whiteness.  he kneads you until you are pliant;  and then he assigns you to his sacred fire, that you may become sacred bread for God's sacred feast.  all these things shall love do unto you that you may know the secrets of your heart, and in that knowledge become a fragment of Life's heart.  but if in your fear you would seek only love's peace and love's pleasure,  then it is better for you that you cover your nakedness and pass out of love's threshing-floor,  into the seasonless world where you shall laugh, but not all of your laughter, and weep but not all of your tears.  love gives naught but itself and takes naught but from itself.  love possesses not nor would it be possessed;  for love is sufficient unto love.  when you love you should not say, "God is in my heart," but rather, "i am in the heart of God."  and think not you can direct the course of love, for love, if it finds you worthy, directs your course.  love has no other desire but to fulfill itself.  but if you love and must needs have desires, let these be your desires:  to melt and be like a running brook that sings its melody to the night.  to know the pain of too much tenderness.  to be wounded by your own understanding of love,  and to bleed willingly and joyfully.  to wake at dawn with a winged heart and give thanks for another day of loving;  to rest at the noon hour and meditate love's ecstasy;  to return home at eventide with gratitude;  and then to sleep with a prayer for the beloved in your heart and song of praise upon your lips.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      i'm SO broke. my dad's business that i was managing is now going under and i haven't been getting my salary because my dad has enough problems paying our pending liabilities. it's not that he told me not to get any money anymore but i just felt it wasn't right. besides, i'm not doing anything other than following up on collections. i'm about to start a new business with my friend but we're still in the early stages and i don't have anything saved. anything i had went to my everyday expenses. i can't get a job because i'm still held up in the old business and i need to devote my time to the new business. i can't even begin to imagine where i'll be getting the capital i need for the new business. i was planning on asking for a loan from my dad but i can't do that until i have all the details organized and we haven't even begun searching for a supplier or a manufacturer or whatever. i have like thousands loaned to a couple of friends and my ex-boyfriend but i don't see any of them trying to pay me. i don't think i can depend on that. :( waaah. i might actually have to go out and get a job. it's such quel. i wish i could have men give me $50 to go to the powder room and $100 to visit someone in jail like holly golightly in breakfast at tiffany's! but i'm not near as pretty as her. damn.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      i had another nightmare about my ex. in the dream, he finally came over.. but it turned out that it was only to take away our daughter (we don't really have one in real life). he left a note that said that he was going to be in jail because he was found guilty of fraud or something like that. the note also said that there were these women who have been visiting him in jail and that they were his soulmates. i woke up. i couldn't breathe and i started crying almost automatically.  :(  i was chatting with this guy who's been dropping hints about wanting to go out with me and he finally blurted out that he likes me and wants to go out with me and so on and so forth. i was caught off guard because he said that he just broke up with his girlfriend today and then he asks me out. i'm worried that maybe i had something to do with his relationship ending but he said that he's been wanting to break it off for some time now. anyway, i was at a loss for words so he said, that's okay, i'll talk. and then he starts to talk about things like how he thinks a girlfriend should be, what she should and shouldn't do, how she should act, etc. then i just start crying (he doesn't know). i didn't know why at first but then i realized that i missed my ex so much and that i'm not over him yet. i was thinking of how different he is from this new guy. i was thinking of how much better we got along. i know it's not fair to compare because i've only known this new guy for like a few days but.. he was going on and on about RULES. what the f*ck? my ex never ever told me what to do unless i was driving too fast or something crazy like that. but other than that, he never told me how to live my life like telling me how many sticks of cigarettes i can smoke in a day and this guy was. what's worse, this new guy doesn't make me laugh. my ex and i used to laugh all the time. we just had *it*. if he's not the one.. i don't know who is. i think that my ex and i were very deeply connected. fundamentally, we understood each other and we were made of the same stuff. he IS my soulmate and the love of my life. the things that i thought were wrong were surface problems that any couple in the whole world could've had. but the things that were right were rare and special. and now it's gone and it's all my fault. and it's all his fault. i don't know. maybe i'm wrong. if we were so right for each other, if we loved  each other so deeply, if we did have something so special, then why aren't we together now? why can't he or i bridge the gap that we have between us? maybe there is someone else out there for me. maybe we just haven't found each other yet. but it's definitely not this new guy. sigh..
     

    
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      okay the guys are just pouring in. it's raining men.. HALLELUJAH!!!! lolz. i don't get it. just these last two days, i've already had like four guys asking me out or making a move on me. what the hell, right? the powers that be are trying to tell me that i'm a good catch and there are lots of good catches out there for me. BUT AM I READY? still.. HALLELUJAH!!!! IT'S RAINING MEN!!! AMEEEEEEEEEEEEEN!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      my friend asked me if i was doing okay. i told her that i'm functioning like a normal person LOLZ and i don't cry all the time anymore. i can smile and i can laugh. but that's all on the outside. inside, i'm always crying and eternally sad even when i'm happy. i asked her if that made any sense to her and she said it does. i'm so glad i have friends, good friends. if not for them and my sister and my mom, i think i might go crazy. i miss him still. i love him still. all the time. even when i'm not thinking about him. even when i'm hating him and remembering how badly he treated me. god help me. but now i understand that i'm equally responsible for everything that went wrong, if not moreso. because i let him treat me like crap. i let him go on disrespecting me because i didn't respect myself. i didn't value myself. we got into a viscious cycle. he'd do something that hurt me and then he'd come over and say sorry and then we'd end up in bed. no matter how much i yakked on about him being wrong and hurting me, i always ended up forgiving him and even REWARDING him for what he did by sleeping with him. it's like i trained him to be the way he was, to treat me the way he did. the message i was giving him was, "hurt me, it's okay. all you have to do is show up, say sorry and let me nag you a bit and then i'll forgive you and even give you some awesome sex." i feel so stupid. i gave him everything no matter what he did to me. i degraded myself. i belittled myself. i don't deserve that but how can i blame him? how could i have expected him to respect me and value me when i didn't value and respect myself? i presented myself as a thing to be used. "here i am, use me. i am your ATM, your sex toy, your shock absorber, your car, your fortress, your sounding board, your wall, your bodyguard, your voice." i felt so grateful that he was with me. deep inside, i felt like i didn't deserve to have someone love me so i was stepping all over myself trying to please him, to serve him. i screwed myself in other words. what a dreadful thing it is to be so consumed in self doubt, insecurity, and self loathing. i screw up my life over and over again. everything is so twisted and distorted in my head that i am just totally lost. i know that i made such a big mess of everything and now i don't know how to fix it. if i go to him, i will be surrendering the one thing that i did right which was to stand up for myself. besides, what would i say? where would i start? how can i admit my part of the problem without owing to it all? on the other hand, if i wait for him, i might be surrendering our love because i know that i had done something wrong but didn't do anything about it. i am sure he knows that. i'm sure part of him understands that it's not all his fault. it's kept him from coming back to me on bended knees. only right. besides, i was the one who wanted to give up. why should he beg me to try again? i screwed him up too. but he knows what he did to me too. so, really, who should make the first move? i don't know. there is something stopping me and there is something stopping him. so far, neither he nor i are budging and there's no indication that things will change soon. so maybe that's that. this might really be the beginning of the end... i just have to live with it.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      my friend and i are going into business. we're thinking of doing clothes for full-figured women like the local stores "tubby" and "maxi" but we're not calling our store "robust" or anything like that. i think it's insulting. they don't call the normal-sized stores "stickthin" or "emaciated" right? it's so unfair that when you reach a size beyond 8/10 here in the philippines you only have a couple of places to go to for clothes and they're all very pricy and the choices are very limited AND the brands are very politically incorrect. hehe. aren't you glad i can talk about something other than my ex-boyfriend who has been haunting my sleep lately. i've been having nightmares for two straight nights now and it all involves him being with other girls while we're broken up and us getting back together but then me not being able to stand it because he fooled around while we weren't together. the nightmare the other night did not involve any girls, only my ex-boyfriend's confession of having slept with other girls, but last night there was a skinny little bitchfriend clinging onto the love of my life. grrrrrr. she was young, skinny, and very very annoying. i'm glad that i don't have any psycho genes or i probably would have turned into miss texas chainsaw massacre and chainsawed her ass to hell in that nightmare. ugh. so much for not talking about my ex. anyway, you all have to buy clothes from us... or else... whirrrrrrrrrr whiiiiiiirrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr... LOLZ.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      okay, i exaggerated a bit. i'm not in love with H. i like him a lot. but i also like T a lot. i think they like me too but not in any serious way. that's okay though. i don't want a serious relationship right now. after the dramatic love exravaganza with my ex, i really need a break from the soap opera life. i'm having a lot of fun right now. parteeing a lot. going out with different guys. spending time with my friends. life is good. hehe.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      last friday, i went out with a guy i used to date in college. we just got back in touch through friendster after 4 years of no contact. he turned out to be a total psycho. i remember back in college he was a bit too mushy and sentimental for me. he was gushing over me after one date. well, multiply that by 4 years. damn. he was crying by the time our date was over last friday and he didn't want to leave. the sex was great but it's not worth it. he kept telling me that i'm the best he's ever had, that i'm so special, that he's addicted to me, that i'm one hell of a girl, that i changed his life in one night, that he'll give up everything for me! i was totally freaked out. damn it, i never thought being good in bed and being so cute and irresistible could get me in trouble. heh. now he keeps calling me and i'm afraid to answer the phone. i make people tell him that i'm not home or i'm sleeping. my friends tell me to just be straight with him. tell him to leave me alone. but i'm afraid he's gonna start stalking me if i do that. i wish he could just take a fucking hint. he texted me last night telling me that he'll NEVER let me go. i am SO scared.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      he loves Her. i am not Her. they share a passion for poetry. that is all there is. there is no more. but i want more. choose me. love me. let me make you happy. well that didn't work for julia roberts in my best friend's wedding. maybe i should make my own monologue. my own plea for love. in my own words. maybe i should write him a poem.. you know, no one is more passionate about poetry than i am. really.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hallelujah! i'm alive! i can write poems again! after a couple of years of some major blockage, i'm baaaaaaaack. thanks to my inspiration, mr. H and to my muse, ms. X! mwah mwah mwah! and here it is..   Peak  I awaken to darkness Day has left me The Night beckons Dark arms enfold me As I lay quietly Waiting for this, Ah Ecstasy. Bliss.  I enter the realm Of dreams Not through The Gates of Sleep But through A shortcut A secret path That leads to A hidden door Known only To those fearless few Who answer without Question the Night's Invitation To those insatiable few Who long intimately To know the Night's Endless Depths  Where love flows Thick like smoke Where light dances Like fairies trailed By magic dust Around and around Cool to the touch Where time and space Melt into one Where you and I Become angels We fly, we fly High into the sky Where the sky Is the earth Where the earth Is the sky  Ah. Ecstasy.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i was reading pablo neruda's poetry last night while listening to pm dawn. i almost went crazy. i think i'm starting to like someone. but we can never be. this is for him...   Being So Not For You (PM Dawn)  Why can't I keep you from the cold? You seem to know the different faces No matter what road you travel on You go through the darkest places I can't tell the angels it'll be good for you Wanting to say blessed be the darkness For bringing the light through But I'd be lying to myself  I had no right Bringing you here Knowing what I know Feeling the way I feel I had no right  Being so uncontent baby Being so confused Being so not for you  You're in love with all that you don't know It animates your expectations What's the easiest way to hurt a man? Give him all he's ever wanted Trying to tell the angels I don't know what to do Convincing myself to believe All the sadness has purpose too Makes me hate this  Then you ask the angels to make you a better you Dream all you want 'cause all the light you occupy They will try and take it all from you
     

    
</post>

<date>16,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      coelho's "the alchemist" says that everyone has his own personal legend. it says that when you're little, you know what that is, but then as you get older and people start to tell you what you are and what you aren't or what you can and can't do, you get jaded and you stop believing and you lose track and you become unhappy because your only real purpose in life is to achieve your personal legend. but it doesn't end there. when you start to forget, the cosmos gives you omens to help you back on track and guide you. but then if these omens are not heeded, they fade away. i wish i'd read this book before, whenever it was that i should have been heeding omens. now i don't think i get them anymore because maybe it's too late. my only chance is to think back on my childhood and maybe REMEMBER what it was that i supposedly KNEW to be my personal legend. but the thing is, even when i was little i wasn't sure what i wanted. i don't remember ever really being sure of one thing. one instance stands out. i used to hang out at my dad's office and i'd play with the typewriter. i distinctly remember writing this one poem about things that i wanted to be. i don't remember all of them except for a few. astronaut. chemist. archaeologist. i don't think any of those are my personal legend though. if it is, then i'm screwed coz i'm never gonna be any of those. science is just not my thing. i get headaches just thinking of high school physics or chemistry. i'm getting them now. argh. as for being an archaelogist, my body just won't allow it. i'm very sensitive about where i sleep and i can't stand public bathrooms and my skin gets really weird when exposed to too much heat and dust. i wouldn't last a day out in some desert sleeping in a tent and bathing in a stream littered with animal crap. i would end up dead or very near a nervous breakdown. i know that sounds very "prima donna" but it's true. when i'm feeling particularly macabre, i torture myself with the thought that i'm gonna die young because it seems i have nowhere to go, like beth in "little women". when i'm feeling particularly optimistic, i revel in the thought that i'm just so full of potential and my talents are so varied that i could be anything that i wanted to be and all i have to do is choose. painter. psychologist. writer. musician. thespian. businesswoman. athlete. a thing of beauty. world's greatest lover. inspirational speaker. mistress of culture. pop icon. archaelogist. thinker. philanthropist. treasure hunter. princess. warrior. prophet. revolutionary. the list goes on. death or the most impossible decision to make. these seem to be the only roads ahead of me right now. either way, i just come right back to where i started. i am eve and this is my plateau.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i told another friend about my latest escapade and she gave me the "i don't know what to say" reaction which is better than the "i can't believe you did that" thing but in a way still makes me feel a bit judged. although i don't think she was judging me. maybe i just feel guilty. but why should i? as i said before, it's my life, it's my call. then again i guess i'm just looking for someone to be on my side and obviously no one is. that's okay though. c'est la vie. right? it was a carpe diem moment and that's my philosophy right now. carpe diem!! so kudos for me! LOLZ. it's weird but other than my friends tsktsking and giving me their "BAD GIRL!" looks and speech, the aftereffects are actually quite positive. it helped me get over my ex in a way more than 2 months of friends and family support, books, meditation, self-help exercises and a plea for insanity ever did. sex is truly a wonderful thing. i remember this guy i exchange emails with told me that more than the support and love of my friends and family, i shouldn't forget that prayers really helped a lot. i told him yeah, of course. LOLZ. i wish i could tell him now that "you know what i found really helped? SEX." it invigorated me. just like vitamins but for funner. my friend said that a similar thing happened to her and she felt bad and realized that she loved this other guy even more. but with me, it made me realize that there are so many more men out there and i could have so much more. MORE SEX!!! WOOOHHHOOOOO! LOLZ. crazy. what i mean is that i now know that my ex is not the only guy out there and he's definitely not the only guy who will ever be attracted to me. it's even more than the sex thing. there's also the very real possibility of a relationship and that makes me happy. there will be other guys to love and have relationships with. other guys who will love me. yipee. so all i can say is... NEXT! =)
     

    
</post>

<date>04,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hope everybody had happy holidays. mine was fine but it made me miss the ex more. yet i feel somewhat better because i felt the love and support of my family and friends. :) yey it's a new year! :( damn i'm turning 24!   new year's resolutions: -lose weight -start dating non-dysfunctional men -get healthy -think about considering to ponder the idea of quitting smoking -update wardrobe -drink more water -read more -save money -PARTEE HARD  birthday wishes: -money money money -that he remembers  i haven't been dreaming about the ex. but i've been dreaming a lot about  a lot  of sex. what could that mean, i wonder? i'm always scared that i'll become a nymphomaniac (or that i'm on my way). sometimes i think that i like sex too much. or maybe that's my mom talking. even if my life right now is so opposite to what i thought it would be when i was still an updstanding clean-living wholesome girl, my mom's lectures on decency (her version of it) are still branded on my brain. of course they don't come up while i'm in the throes of passion or while lighting a cigarette or while peaking on X but aftwerwards.. which is worse i think. more disturbing still is that after everything i've done, which is to say everything that everybody else does, my friends still see me as this good girl. i don't know why. it baffles me sometimes. they say, "how could you? i never thought you were the type who could do this or that!" i know my friends are worried and i appreciate them saying so but i wish they'd just cut out the "i never thought you could" part. it's like i let them down or something. why is it so hard to believe that i'm capable of " bad " behavior? because i'm not mean when i don't have to be? because i smile a lot? because i'm friendly and outgoing? because i don't cut down other people? because i don't say FUCK every two seconds? because i don't sleep with every guy that comes along? no, i'm not out to destroy my life and everything around but yes, i'm human and sometimes i just want to LIVE without fear, without regret, without anything holding me back and without having to hear people say that "i'm not the type" as if i've lived my life for sainthood and blew it in one shot. man! i mean what's life without taking a few risks? we all take risks all the time anyway. crossing the street could be fatal. even if i end up regretting some things, that's okay. because i'm the one who's gonna have to live with the consequences of my actions. my choice, my risk, my gain/loss. i do things for my own reasons, not because i'm this or that type. i hate being typecast but it's not like i set out to prove people wrong either. :P i'm sorry to disappoint anyone who thinks they know me so well they can predict what i'm gonna do next. i don't think anybody really knows anyone that well.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "I will have poetry in my life! And adventure! And love... Love above all! No, not the artful postures of love, not playful and poetical games of love for the amusement of an evening... But love that... overthrows life! Unbiddable, ungovernable, like a riot in the heart... And nothing to be done, come ruin or rapture." - Shakespeare In Love 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      the impossible has happened. the ex is history. i adore Pi. i am enamored. i am amazed. i am SO IN LOVE. again! dear god. i'm so scared that i am headed towards another huge pothole and i wouldn't be able to hit the breaks even if i wanted to because the thrill of the ride is just so envigorating. i feel like meg ryan in city of angels, riding on a bike with my eyes closed and both arms stretched out - i know it's stupid and dangerous but it just feels so good, i can't stop. i'm just praying and hoping that a truck doesn't come around my corner. keep your fingers crossed for me! =)
     

    
</post>

<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i still miss the ex. i still love him. lately, i've found myself crying over him again. maybe i shouldn't be in a new relationship when i'm still feeling so hung over from my last one. but i'm also starting to fall for Pi.. like for realz now! he's so good to me. he adores me and i feel like he'll never hurt me the way the ex did. i still get a little nauseous whenever he goes into misty-puppy-dog-eyes mode and starts professing his deep love for me in that shaky melodramatic soap opera tone of voice. i easily get irritated whenever he does things that the ex would never do (like comment on my eating habits) or whenever he doesn't do things that the ex would always do (like make me laugh). i know i shouldn't be comparing them. it's not fair to either one. i just can't seem to help it. i'm trying though and i think i'm getting better. i want to love Pi - really, i do - as much as i loved the ex or maybe even moreso. i just don't know if i can learn to do that. can you teach yourself to love the way love taught you? can love that is learned over time be greater than love that overcomes you in one night?
     

    
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "Suddenly, quietly, you realize that - from this moment forth - you will no longer walk through this life alone. Like a new sun this awareness arises within you, freeing you from fear, opening your life. It is the beginning of love, and the end of all that came before." (Robert Frost)  "The only people for me are the mad ones. The ones who are mad to love, mad to talk, mad to be saved; the ones who never yawn or say a commonplace thing, but burn, burn, burn like fabulous yellow Roman candles exploding like spiders across the stars." (Jack Kerouac)
     

    
</post>

<date>15,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      haven't been able to post for a while. my sister's been hogging the computer again. i need to move out SOON. grrrr.  i think i may have damaged the good reputation that i have carefully built up through the years. i went to centro and halo last friday wearing a ratty shirt and slippers! i could have pulled it off if i was maybe catherine zeta-jones, but i'm not! damn it, i'm not! i tried to act like i didn't care anyway. i think it was successful in that no one tried to kick me out or ask me to sweep the floor. i was invisible at best, an annoyance at worst. i think that could have put a scratch on my good social standing but i may just be able to repair that still.  i have a new boyfriend. guess who it is. it's mr. psycho. he turned out to be not-so-psycho after all. but then again, sometimes i still wonder... lolz. okay, okay. maybe he is a little weird, kind of mushy and really clingy. maybe he's a bit gay sometimes (i.e. he acts gay, not that he goes for guys). maybe i don't love him the way i loved the ex. maybe we didn't get together under the most pleasant circumstances. maybe he's not really my type. maybe i'm just on the rebound. maybe he's just on the rebound. maybe we're wrong for each other. but i couldn't say no. he cooked me pasta and named it "X* VALENTINE SPECIAL". he kneeled and asked me, "could you be mine?" and i said yes. he shouted "she's mine, world! i love her so much!" out the window. it was the most romantic night of my life. i cried. there were candles and blueberry cheesecake ice cream. sprite in wine glasses. annie lennox's cover of 'waiting in vain' playing in the background. i couldn't say no. it was perfect. sigh.. happy valentine's all!  *X = my real name of course  the only thing that was sad about last night was the thought that my friends couldn't share my happiness because they don't like Pi (my new boyfriend). like i said before, we didn't meet under the best circumstances. he had a girlfriend and we had an affair while he was still with her. but he's not with her now. i don't think it should be an issue anymore. but then i guess my friends are afraid that he'll do the same thing to me. i understand how they feel but i wish they could get to know him so that they'll understand everything and see that he's not some womanizer who bounces from girl to girl. and even if he does end up cheating on me and leaving me for another girl then so be it. i've survived worse things. i just want to be with him right now. i hope my friends appreciate the fact that he left his girlfriend. at least i know that it wasn't his intention to keep me as a mistress. he says he loves me and i tend to think that he's proved that somehow in more ways than one. i'll tell more later. my sister's hounding me to get off the computer so she can use it. loser. i'd let her squirm in anguish but i have to call Pi too so..  TO BE CONTINUED...
     

    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      my sister is a fucking bitch. just thought you should know.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      my best girlfriend, my soulsister, is with H now. i'm happy for them. love you hunny! and i really mean it. i know that i said i was in love with H for a while there but i think i was simply overcome by admiration for him. his poetry stirred my soul and i mistook it for love. then again, maybe it was. i believe that there are different kinds of love and some do not need justification. some people you just love from afar and you wouldn't have it any other way. you're not supposed to. i don't know. all i know is, there isn't even the tiniest bit of bitterness or jealousy in my heart. maybe because i can't imagine being in a relationship with H in the first place but even if i could, i love my soulsister so much that i cannot begrudge her any happiness she might find. she deserves it. she's had it really tough. she got pregnant. the guy who got her pregnant ran away. her one true love cheated on her the second time around. her parents split up. she took in her mom. her mom doesn't have a job. she lost her car because her dad wouldn't give it back to her after she crashed it. her son got pneumonia. the bastard she loves doesn't give her the time of day. those are just a few examples. this entry wouldn't end if i were to name everything that's gone wrong with her life. but despite all that, she hasn't become cynical and mean. you know how people who go through difficult things end up becoming the kind of people who give other people a difficult time? well, she's not one of them and that makes her even more magnificent. she's such a tough little cookie. she not only survives the pitfalls that life pushes her into but she always comes out with her unfaltering grace and benevolence intact. sure, her friends have been there for her but not on a day-to-day basis, of course. she's never had anyone to really share her life with. someone to share each of her joys and sorrows with. someone who will take care of her and protect her and appreciate her completely. i have long prayed, no, demanded, from the powers that be that she find that someone. i tried my best to fulfill that role as much and as long as i could but i know even my valiant efforts fell short of what she truly deserved. i could only do so much. it's not like i can marry her. hello?! i'm a straight woman. anyway, i'm just happy that she finally has someone. that's all. maybe there is a god.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i have a tagboard! yay! the 2 or 3 people who come to my blog can now leave me messages. lolz. it's futile, really, i think 3 is actually a high count. in truth, i know of only one friend who comes here religiously. pathetic, right? it's my own fault though. i know these ALL-ABOUT-ME blogs rarely ever get cyber-traffic. who, other than my circle of friends, cares about my lovelife? nobody. you think i didn't know that? well, i do. so there's gonna be changes around here. i have things to say and i will be heard, damn it! you just wait..
     

    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
           You are the ravest of dance parties, a must for the all night rave! Exciting company you make people feel sexy, sensual and generally ecstatic. You make people feel close, at one with each other but can also make people feel nauseous and anxious. If you spend a lot of time with someone they tend to hallucinate, they can't see clearly and feel like they are getting carried away with you. When you spend way too much time with people you fuck up their brain, heart and liver. However, after spending a whopping wonderful night with you, the next day people get depressed thinking of you and how much they miss you. They get love sick and don't want to eat, they can't sleep, they feel sore in their muscles and can't concentrate for very long as they dream of when they will spend an exhilirating time with you again on the dance floor at the very next rave party. Fortunately for people, the more they see of you the more they realize how bad you are and eventually they don't see much of you anymore.    urlLink If You Were A Drug, What Would You Be?    quiz by  urlLink raven ritings  
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      love again. i never thought it was possible to be this insanely happy, i said to Pi the other day. it is SO true that love is SO much better the second time around. well, at least for me, that is. i never thought i would love anyone as much as i loved the ex. Pi proved me wrong. i love him SO much. maybe more in the last few days than i ever loved the ex in the whole 2 years and 7 months we were together. things just really feel right this time. we fit so perfectly. he is my match in every way. i love him. I love him. i LOVE him. i love HIM. I LOVE HIM!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      my hair has totally gone wild. and when i say "wild", i mean screeching-monkeys-in-the-jungle WILD. it looks like there's a bird's nest clinging to my skull.. a bird's nest that was chewed by a llama and then spat out.  this is what comes of not learning from your mistakes. it all started when i was seven years old. i had really long, straight, smooth, silky, black hair but then my mom had it permed. why? it was the 80's! hello?! goddamn it, we should have just skipped that decade. but then again, the 90's would have been the 80's. oh well. let's not go there. as i was saying, my mom got my hair permed and since then, i've had my hair relaxed, straightened, treated, cellophaned, "hot oil"-ed, colored, waxed, "henna"-ed, creamed, ironed and most recently, rebonded (which is really just ironing but with chemicals). each of those treatments came with promises of beauty and renewal but they all just added to the accumulated damage in the end. each time something new comes along, i'm foolish enough to believe that it will be different from the others. something inside me says, maybe this is it! the holy grail of haircare! the answer! the ONE. but no, they never are. well the downward spiral stops here. i have suffered enough bad hair days to last me forever (you can say i'm having a bad hair lifetime). so from now on, i will go organic on my hair (as much as possible). i will mix up a batch of my own all-natural herbal shampoo if need be. whatever it takes. i've learned my lesson. let this be a warning to you as well. unless live birds laying eggs on your head is the kind of thing that ties in with your image, i suggest you be good to your hair.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hello, i'm still alive. i know, i know. it's been ages. i just haven't had a minute to myself the past few weeks. Pi has been living in my house since he got evicted from his boarding house (the owners are renovating) and we've been spending every waking hour together. i can barely find time to go to the bathroom alone. it's fun and stressful at the same time. just like the summer heat.. oh so lovely and yet oh so sticky. speaking of summer, we (Pi and i and some friends) were supposed to go to puerto galera this weekend but chie just texted to say that most of our friends have to work this weekend so we're cancelling it. that means the 3 hours Pi and i spent scouring the malls for a new suit for me was all in vain. and i was so ready to spend 3k++ at marks & spencer (the only place that had close-to-decent stuff.. apparently, landmark's and rustans' summer theme is TACKY). thank god i thought twice.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      so i found out that i'm royalty. hah. hail! hail queen eve!!! okay that's stretching it a LITTLE. the story is, one of my grandaunts did some research recently on our genealogy and found out that we're directly descended from spain's duke of alba. no, she's not a few screws short. yes, we've got the papers to prove it. lolz. the next question you might be asking is, which one? well, i don't know. i never asked about the details. i was too busy jumping up and down screaming "i'm a princess! i'm a princess!" and planning a visit to my royal relatives in spain. frankly, it doesn't even matter. the important thing is.. i'm a princess! not just daddy's little princess. not just Pi's princess bride. not just a spoiled brat acting like a princess. but a real princess! i knew it. the only down side is, it's gonna be tougher now to find a job. i mean, so far i've only gotten offers from call centers. i can just see it now..  "thank you for calling x, inc. this is the princess of alba speaking. how may i help you?"  that's just not right.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My bestfriend Kate and I have decided that we need to lose weight once and for all. We need to be at our most fabulous now that we're getting older. We've lost that edge, you know, youth. We're halfway through our 20's and we've gotten to that point where you need to really put an effort into being and staying beautiful. LOLZ. I wish I had listened to my Mom and started earlier. Now, it seems like double the effort because I have half the energy and the stamina as I did maybe 5-8 years ago. Anyway, for that extra push, we decided to bet on it. Whoever reaches their goal in weight loss in 6 months wins. Kate hasn't given me her terms and conditions. I gave her a pretty tough time with mine. I hope she doesn't say she wants my car or something like that. Ooh, I'm getting hungry. Grrrr. Kate left me a message on YM saying, "hey eve! if you feel like bingeing, think of this: i worked out for 2 hours last night. hehe." Damn. I haven't even gotten close to thinking about going to the gym. I *need* more motivation! Eek! More updates later. Wish me luck!
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Being an adult sucks. I complain a lot about my sister still being in school and I always preach to her and tell her she should hurry up and graduate already. I mean, she is already 23 but she says she has one more year to go before she graduates. But if I were being honest with myself, I'd have to say that I'm really jealous. I wish I was still in school. Then my biggest problem would be getting good grades and that's it. Sometimes it bothers me that life could bring me down so fast and so easily. And I actually have a pretty easy life compared to other people's. So I cannot help but come to the conclusion that I am weak. One little flint thrown at me and my world crumbles. I don't want to be like that. I want to be like those people who can stand tall and firm through raging storms and violent seas. How do I do that though? I have no idea. At times like this, I just want to curl up and sleep until the dark cloud passes. This time though it seems like it's never gonna pass. It feels like one giant wave after another coming at me. And I'm drowning..
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's official. I've become my mother. I always wondered why my mom was so high strung all the time. She would always tell me, "You'll see. You'll understand when you become a mother." Now I know what she means. Oh boy, do I know. I mean, I'm only in my first month of pregnancy and already I'm feeling it. I can't get thoughts of bad things happening to my baby out of my head. I feel like I could lose him anytime and it paralyzes me. Oh by the way, for those who didn't get my last post, THIS is what it's about. Yes, I'm pregnant. According to the doctor and the ultrasound, by around 5-6 weeks. And I'm freaking out because they didn't see a fetus in my ultrasound, just the sac. They said not to worry. Maybe it's too early. They told me to come back after two weeks. This is gonna be the longest two weeks of my life! And I haven't even started to think about when and how I'm gonna tell my parents about this. On top of all that, a lot of physical discomfort - vomit-inducing nausea, ovewhelming fatigue, extreme mood swings, frequent trips to the toilet, increased body heat, insane cravings, unwavering sleepiness - is the setting in which all this stressful worrying is taking place. This can't be good for my baby. Okay, there I go again. I think it's worse for my boyfriend though. I'm probably driving him stark, raving mad. Poor guy. Oh, and a couple of my close friends still don't know about it. I was thinking of how I was gonna break it to them. I was thinking of surprising them like a couple of weeks from now when my tummy is noticeable, I would just show up. But I'm worried that it might seem a little cruel. LOLZ. It feels like it would turn out as a practical joke rather than a pleasant surprise. I'll probably just email them after I get my second scan and attach the ultrasound pictures or something like that. I know they'll preach but in the end they're there for me and they'll be happy for me eventually. Just like my mom and dad (I hope). When things like this happen to me, I'm amazed at how people make me feel enveloped with their love and support. In the midst of all the chaos, I find peace in the love of my family and friends. At times like these, I feel like I'm the luckiest girl in the world. :)
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I got a positive on an HPT last night (I can't even utter the words so for those of you who don't have a clue what an HPT is, sorry). And on the eve of my mom's 46th birthday no less! Forgive me, mother, father, for I have sinned. How do I begin to explain this to them? My loving, generous, TRUSTING parents.. who ushered me into this world with great expectations and high hopes.. who sweat, bled, and wept through the hardships of life in order to give me everything my greedy little heart desired.. Oh, God, I'm reeling. The world is spinning. I feel like vomiting. Literally. Morning sickness, hello, good EVENING, what are you doing here?? Wait! Maybe the pharmacist gave me the wrong test. Maybe it tested sanity rather than *that which cannot be named*. That would make oh so much more sense. The thought of getting strapped into a straight jacket is more comforting right now than the visions of my future wardrobe consisting of extra lose flowery dresses and super stretchy pants. My world as *I* know it is on the brink of utter meltdown. Somebody, PLEASE, get me some crackers!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       guess who's getting married. hehe. it'll be in august.. of THIS year. how can anybody put together a wedding in a month, you say? i know *I* can't do it. thank god for my mom and her network of friends. next, people are probably gonna be wondering why we are getting married. i know it seems like we're getting married because i'm pregnant and it seems like we have no choice. my mom keeps telling me that i don't HAVE to get married if i don't want to (followed by a string of prophecies of hardships and sufferings that will occur as a consequence) but i know it'll make things easier if i do. i know she wants me to and even though i haven't told my dad yet, i know that he's gonna tell me that i'm bringing shame to our family name if i insist on staying unmarried in my situation. at first, i was fighting the idea in my head. of course, i can't voice my protests since i have lost the right to be a brat now that i've committed THE worst sin any daughter can ever commit. but then i started to realize that i might just be rejecting the idea because it's coming from somewhere else instead of from myself and it seemed so unromantic to have my mom and my aunts and uncles plan my wedding for me and practically propose for my boyfriend. things are happening so fast, i barely have time to stop and ask myself whether i truly want this. i realized that i do want HIM but i was uncertain about wanting this big change.. this strange, new life. i realized that it was natural to have those doubts because i'm about to go somewhere i've never been. it's a little scary (i.e. it's a whole lotta scary). i may be making the biggest mistake of my life but so what? i always have a choice. so am i sure i want to get married? i still can't say i'm 100% on that. this is what i'm sure of so far.. i love him and i do want to spend the rest of my life with him, i just wasn't expecting the rest of my life to start this soon.     
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      the ex has been haunting me these past few weeks. first, his friends started adding me in friendster. well actually they're also MY friends since i got to know them and hang out with them quite a bit when the ex and i were together. they're officially HIS friends though because they all live in the same neighborhood, grew up together, went to the same schools and stuff like that. you know what i mean. i actually thought i'd never hear from them again after the breakup and that really made me sad. but apparently, i was wrong. they like me! they really really like me! :) eheh. needless to say, i'm happy that they aren't mad at me for leaving their friend and breaking his heart. and yes, i did break his heart after all. i'm finally getting some justification and validation. the ex started writing daddy-O, one of our friends, and for the first time since the breakup, he's pouring his heart out to someone. unfortunately for him, daddy-O's wife is MY close friend and staunch ally. and daddy-O can't keep anything secret from mommy-O. in other words, i've read the actual letters. he talked about how his life now seems empty, he expressed his regrets, he even said that he envied daddy-O's life as a husband and father. regret and envy are two things that the ex never felt. he was proud of that. he told me before that he hated people who envy and pitied people who had so many regrets. now he knows how it feels. i think it did him good though because he's talking about trying to change for the better. if only for that, i'm happy. after all this time -- all the miscommunications, all the struggle to extract from him even the tiniest hint of emotion, all the fights and misunderstandings, all the uncertainty and unanswered questions -- knowing that i was and am missed after all and that the 2 years and 7 months we shared did matter to him.. that, my dear friends, is closure. it took all this time for him to finally say it. he really loves me. he just didn't know how and that was what i needed from him to keep me holding on. ironically, now as it turns out, that is all i needed to get over him completely. so there. peace at last. the only thing i wish now is for him to find his happiness too.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I had my second ultrasound a few days ago and it is confirmed. There is life growing inside of me. We (me and my boyfriend) were even able to see the tiny heartbeat. It was SO awesome. I've never seen anything so beautiful.. and scary. Part of me feels resentment sometimes because the morning sickness deal is really nothing to laugh about. Sometimes I feel like I just don't want to do this anymore just because it feels so awful. I mean physically, it's really awful. Sometimes emotionally as well because I have to go through all these new feelings. Spiritually though, I don't think there can be anything more amazing than this. This is as close to heaven on earth as it'll ever get. Being part of the whole circle of life thang. It's humbling really and yet ultimately fulfilling. Now, if only I can make my mom and dad look at it that way. I've been toying with the idea of writing my mom a letter. I know I'm being chicken that way but hey, come on.. this is really hard. Any of you have better ideas? Please feel free to give me your suggestions.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The wedding is in two weeks. I'm really excited but a lot of weird things have been happening. We have an old Filipino superstition that says the closer an important occassion comes (e.g. birthdays, holidays, weddings) the more you should avoid leaving the house and traveling around. They say you become accident-prone.. but that's if you're significantly involved in those occassions. I mean it doesn't work if you just *know* someone who's celebrating her birthday in the next town over. You have to be at least a member of the celebrant's immediate family or a close friend, if not the celebrant herslef. Now I'm not ordinarily a superstitious person but in the last few weeks, we've had a car accident, two physical accidents (my mom tripped and sprained her foot and my grandma tripped the next day but fortunately didn't get hurt that bad), and just a lot of turmoil. My life is like a telenovela, a soap opera. I've heard that a dozen times from other people and I've only recently started accepting it. I don't even think there's a soap opera who can trump my life story. I guess that's why I never got into the whole telenovela bandwagon. It all just seems to pale in comparison to the drama of my life. What am I talking about? Well, for one thing, my dad wants to bury my cousin for harassing my mom because she had to tell him to leave the house he thought belonged to his mom (my aunt, dad's sister) but the house actually belongs to a corporation (comprised of my dad, the president and major investor, and three of their brothers) where she embezzled millions and therefore angered my dad and forfeited her rights to the house and the corporation. And that's just the frosting on the cake. A very very thin layer of frosting. There are other layers, not to mention a whole cake the size of Texas under that frosting. Oh there's too much to tell. Don't worry, I'll try to sprinkle some stories every now and then. Just don't expect it too often because it takes a lot out of me. Too much emotional stress. Anyway, inspite/despite/over and above everything, the wedding is on and we're all looking forward to it. After all, you know they say every cloud has a silver lining. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>