<Blog>

<date>31,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Some small kidz are playing fireworks here. yeah, cny's eve. In the previous years, we children used to stay up late at night to watch television programmes. Well, i'm here now chatting all the way. Reunion dinner isn't really reunion dinner this year. hmp, last night i slept around 5 something in the morning, struggling to finish up my physics folio. Anyway, i wasn't that sleepy at that time, and at least, it's done now, i guess. Still there's the group work to be done...  
     

    
</post>

<date>30,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      i'm just plain bored. Tomorrow, it's going to be an even boring day. Today, i feel like an ediot again. nahh, my feeling always changes. These few days, as usual, i have been throwing tantrums at everyone. Woke up this morning and the first thing came to my mind is 'what am i going to do after this'. Did some work but slept alot. Searched a little on the net for information on the physics project, and got some useful information, if i have not mistaken. hm, i'm still thinking whether to follow my friends to mines or not... haven't made a decision till now, i hate making desicions, haha..   
     

    
</post>

<date>28,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      yes, at last i get to publish posts again. Tried a few times to get in just now but to no avail. Today, is just like any other days, but of course, there's still a little differences. It's the last day of school before the cny holidays, and yeah, i'm expecting a boring new year. Well, without my dad at home, we couldn't visit any relatives which stays far away. My mom doesn't know the way. Only if my cousins are going, then MAYBE we'll just tumpang like one of the previous years (this is the second year i'm celebrating cny without my dad at home). Tons of homework, but i don't know where to start first. Stayed back for ?, nothing, anyway, it came to my mind that i don't have anything to do at home, so why not spend a little more time in school. hmm... really sad and dissapointed that my dad went back to china to work. Last night, at last, he gave me my pmr reward, in the form of money, as usual. Well, he didn't give me just like that, he told my mom to put 'em in my savings account. 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I guess, umm, dad's waiting to board the plane right now. Well, time flies, one week is gone, and he's flying back to beijing for work. sigh~ at first, i didn't know whether to follow him to kl sentral or not, i'm afraid i will cry. I really enjoyed it when we were in pangkor. Hopefully, we can go somewhere else this coming may. when we're apart, we will only know how to appreciate the time we had together. Supposed to stay back for sports practice today, but didn't. During the last period, had some bad gastric pain, and of course, decided to go home and rest instead. Mrs lee sent me home, ate some instant noodle, and went to bed. When dad woke me up, i didn't realise that it's already dinner time. We had our, ahem, advanced reunion dinner and my appetite wasn't there at that moment. That's what will happen to me after taking gastric medicine.   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      haa... pkbm training today. In fact, i marched like a jerk - for some reasons, ??? Mom fetched me home. After that i followed mom and dad to mid valley. Came back home and had a small barbeque. All in all, it's not that bad, just tiring, especially after pkbm. Imagine marching under the scorching sun. A very busy day, my cousin and her children are now in my house visiting too. Dad is flying back to Beijing tomorrow night. sigh~ :( yeah, boring cny approaching!  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      ah, just came back from pangkor. Overall, it's so-so, well, not bad. The sea tour was marvelous, where we get to snorkel, the land tour isn't bad, just that the routes they use is nightmare - up and down, and several 90 degrees, even 360 degrees turns. That friday, i wore my school uniform all the way from smkbts to p. pangkor. I really enjoy the sea tour. That was the first time i went snorkeling. And, i really like it! We jumped in the sea which is full of colourful fishes, big and small, swimming around. wow, i even get to touch a life sea cucumber and a life coral too. I brought along one big stack of books, well, obviously, homeworks. Didn't manage to finish all of them though. Still have one essay to be done which is need to be handed in for english tomorrow. ah, snorkeling is fantastic! i'll never hesitate to do it again!  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I've been far too careless this few days. This afternoon, when i was frying an egg, my finger accidentally touched the frying pan. ouch, a patch of 'melted-like' skin now. Yesterday, i banged my forehead at the pc when i was bending to take a piece of paper. Now, even when i frown, i could feel the slight pain. Last holiday, the standing fan's blade slashed my skin and i accidentally closed my mom's car door with my finger inserted in it. Luckily, i didn't crack my finger nail. Went for mr. lee's add-maths class in the evening. Today's teaching is bit confusing, but i'm working hard on it! I've been publishing posts daily so far, but i won't be posting any for tomorrow and saturday. Well, short holiday in pangkor and i'll be going there right after school tomorow. 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Today isn't just the same as other days before this, i guess. Sometimes i think staying in bts just isn't my channel. Dad came back from china today, and he's going back one day right before the school holidays. Just imagine how's the auspicous festival is going to be like without the bread-winner at home. B-O-R-I-N-G! What to do? work is work. After school, a few of us had a meeting with pn faridah hanum. I was chosen as the cheif editor for bulletin pss. In my point of view, maybe i deserve it. However, i'm not interested in holding any posts. To me, positions in the organization chart aren't important, except for positions in exams of course. Being ordinary is good enough. Well, don't know why i was dumb at that moment and didn't protest it. Maybe, giving the post to someone more compatible is a good choice... 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      man, enuff frustrated for today. For sports practice, we did shot putt and 100 metres sprint. After it was all over, i was really not feeling well. hm, a little nauseated i guess. Futhermore, i was really lethargic and was reluctant to walk to the bus-stop. While waiting, loke stopped by, and offered to drive us home. Didn't follow him anyway, wen chin denied to do so. hehe, so we were there, sitting beside the big drain, hoping for the bus to arrive soon. Soon, it started drizzling, and the raindrops become heavier. Eventually, we sat a cab home. Stopped at the al-amal restaurant, because wen chin is going for tuition. That time it already stated to rain cats and dogs. I ran, mostly walked home and arrived home drenched to the skin. I quickly took a bath as my dad always says take bath as soon as possible if u get caught up in the rain. The electricity current broke off a few times, and, my youngest brother hid the paper that mrs lee asked me to type. If i lose it, i'm dead meat. He made me panic that i searched the whole house so many times. Somemore, it was dark at that time. Two times i was typing on the pc, and both times, something went wrong and it was left unsaved. Had to do it all over again. Say, i better get a punching bag to punch out all my anger. Yesterday, mom said she saw foxy, our house dog which accidentally ran out of our house and didn't return at the playground. She tried to catch up with the lady with foxy but when she came down from the car, the lady was nowhere to be found. hm, i've been thinking about this since then. Well, it a pure breed wired-haired fox terrier and i guess, it's sort of a waste to lose him. Before this, everyone who came to my house called it as 'toy dog'. I just woke up just now, after sleeping for quite long. 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      This morning we had to line up like soldiers. As usual, boring speech from the pengetua and when it's pkbm day, there is his real funny commands. haha, i giggled when he shouted, i guess, some of the teachers in front had noticed me. Yen nee was beside me, she was busy joking about the teachers and so on. In class, i have been laughing alot, especially during est lesson. BUT, i laugh alot doesn't mean that i'm happy. haha, right towards the end of the lesson, some of us were thinking whether to stay back for pkbm marching or not. Many looked out to the sky, hoping that it'll rain. Finally, we decided not to stay back and instead, do our biology work in the evening. By the time pek mun and i walked out from school, the bus had already left. Fortunately, may jie's father was the another alternative. Came home, play, sleep and not long after i woke up, may suddenly came up my stairs. I was shocked at first, didn't know that she was already here. Then, melisa came followed by pek mun. Off we start to do our group work and we ended around 7 something. Hopefully, mr. lim won't ask us to redo a new piece.  
     

    
</post>

<date>19,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Piano lessons, nothing much. Came home, did some work and started to play worms world party. haha, the addiction is here again. Bout 8.30 loke came, followed by tam. Back to school work. Again, didn't completed it, maybe it's 80 percent done. They went back at 10.15, with loke walking back home. hm, second thought i still have some school work to be done. hehhe 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Another dental appointment this afternoon. Today i got my braces removed, at last. Now, i have to wear a retainer instead for another year. Maybe because it's my first time wearing it, i'm still not used to the feeling. It's hard for me to chew and i can't really pronounce some words out properly. Just now, loke and tam came to my house to do our physics group work. However, didn't manage to finish it up and they went home at 10.30. The whole time loke was busy playing with my hamster. Most probably, we'll continue our work tomorrow night.  
     

    
</post>

<date>17,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      ...second post of the day... Events happening at night are more meaningful. First, jarrod called me from russia, well, juz a few minutes chat, bills are not cheap. I'm glad we're keeping in touch. Just now, had some chat with afiq, now with izyan. Both of them are leaving bts for boarding schools, in some peoples opinion, brighter future for them there. :(, although i have other stuffs to ponder on, this takes it all for now. They're among my first few close malay friends. Thank God, i managed to get their autographs today. They gave somewhat touching and sad goodbyes. Afiq took photographs with 4 science 1 and a few teachers, he said to me that we'll meet again if we get to enter the quiz perdana sejarah like what we did in the previous year. hey, till we meet again!  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Wasn't feeling that well this morning again. The whole day my hands were cold like ice. Came back from school today with lots of question marks in my head, as usual. Weekends are here again and i'm thinking how to spend them. School ended at 12.30 but the bus only came at 1 something. When we went up the bus, there were few spaces left for us to sit. For the first time, we chose the last row right behind where three of us - me myself, pek mun and wen chin can sit together. Sitting at the back is, well cool! We were joking when the bus suddenly came to a bump on the road and our bums went floating in the air for a moment. haha, i laughed till my stomach crammed and wen chin was busy observing edward when there's another bump. Had some sports house meeting today. They made some changes this year and students were swapped from one team to another. Pkbm day is on monday, which means we going to line up like soldiers in the morning. Now, i have to stay back on monday, tuesday and wednesday, three days in a row. Futhermore, i don't feel like sitting public bus alone too, that's the problem. Well, we'll see how it goes in the time to come.  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Right after pn. siti ainon let us go off today, me and a few classmates which are sitting the school bus rushed out to catch up with the bus. Went to universal for tuition today. Just because i'm late, i didn't get to sit with my friends. Anyway, i didn't inform them that i'm coming today and maybe they're quite suprised to see me there. As usual, mr. lee's teaching is full of jokes that made us laugh our heads off. His class is good, only that sometimes he explain things very fast. The class ended later than it's supposed to be and when i walked home it's already drizzling. 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Another sleepy physics lesson today. Sitting right at the back so couldn't really hear what the teacher says. When i came back, i was really sleepy. In the evening, i went to tasik permaisuri with tam. Supposed to bring some  hydrilla  leaves for a biology experiment and we've to scoop them up from the lake there. By the time i reached home, mom's already at the dinning table eating. Having some problems with my braces again, which is kindda irritating. Hopefully, mom can make an dental appointment tomorrow.    
     

    
</post>

<date>14,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Somehow another awful day for me. Went to school, came back from school, ate lunch, slept and dinner is going to be ready soon. Got to know that dad won't be able to come back during cny. :(, yet another boring cny at home! Actually we planned to go to pangkor during the holidays, rooms were booked, money was paid. Most probably, mom's going to push forward or postpone the stay, or maybe, just cancel it. Till now, i still couldn't spot where my watch is. hm, mrs. lee read out my piece of essay for the class to listen today. Got back my book, and the pages were shinning with red inks, and, a dissapointing 29/40 score. Can't blame it, that's what you'll get if u only mention 2 main points, 'garbage in, garbage out'. 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      ... wasn't feeling well in school the whole day. First lesson for est today and first time of the term we went back at 1.40. Helped out mrs. lee a little at the end of the lesson, after that she asked me whether i would like a lift home. Thank God i chose the right choice to follow her back. When we came out of the school, the surrounding was all empty, which means, my bus had already left. Just read another email from faraway friend, jarrod. Got some of his advices, i guess they make sense too. hm, i'm mixed up. Mom's birthday today, we went out for dinner and i footed the bill. haha, couldn't get any cake coz dad's not here. Anyway, i earned some money working during the holidays and nothing wrong spending them right?  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Woke up late for piano lessons this morning. As usual, when i'm sleepy, i perform badly. Lots of mistakes when playing the ornaments part, eventhough i've practised that piece many many times. The teacher told me to repeat some parts a few times too. Gone beserk and simply played out the melody. kekeke, forgot how to do my theory, in fact, piano theory from grade 6 onwards is really boring. Supposed to write out the voice part of the melody and whatever crap it is. Anyway, just some careless minor mistakes in my answers. oh yah, got my certificate for grade 6 pratical also, i almost forgot about it at first. Came home, did abit of work, print out some articles for est, and sleep! Mom went out for a wedding dinner and we kids just stayed at home and watch tv, that's the tradition.   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Weekends are here and it's a good time to rest. Slept for don't know how many hours, but it seems more like hibernation. Continued reading my story book and just dozed off. The computer man came to repair the printer today, and had to pay bout 160 bucks for the printhead. Went to mc donald's for dinner and after that, we went to pasar malam. Nothing interesting there, i don't really like night markets though. Didn't saw any friends there except loke. Guess it's because i went there too early. Overall, my day was really really boring.  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Not really in the mood today, but laugh alot in the bus. There're little kids in the bus, mostly from sktm, my primary school! Some indian gal, wondering what my braces are. They stared at me and asked a few questions. man, i hate being the centre of attraction. Anyway, gonna get the braces off in... another week. If only my mom is not working tomorrow, i would have asked her to push the appointment to tomorrow. There isn't really any major homeworks today, which is sort of annoying. When there is, they come in big bunches at a time. Now the weekend's here but there aren't any asignments.  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      It's a suprise there's no asignments from teachers today. Maybe it's rest day for us. I came back, had my lunch and went to sleep. Slept late yesterday, and was reluctant to wake up this morning. This afternoon when we're in the school bus, wen chin, pek mun and me myself joked among ourselves and laughed our heads off. In the bus, wen chin was busy counting the number of humps we went through on the road. If i've not mistaken, there're about 20+ of them. hehe..
     

    
</post>

<date>08,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      homeworks. My group was abit confused about the biology presentation. Manage to ask a few friends through the phone and finally understand what mr. lim meant (i guess?). We're supposed to present them on mahjong papers tomorrow and i heard that who did not complete his/her asignments will be kicked out of 4 science 1. That's the main motivation that made us did our work. Had some gotong-royong cleanning up the library after school today. It was really tiring as there's dust everywhere and just imagine how big is the library - including the media room. When i came back, i wasn't feeling well. Just ate some maggie and slept till 7 something.  
     

    
</post>

<date>07,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Slept quite late yesterday. The cat pushed the hamster's cage again and the pine shavings were scattered everywhere. Had to use the vaccum cleaner to clean them before going to bed. Quite a number of homeworks today, especially biology, i don't even know what to do. Anyway, this can't be compared with my brother. He came back yesterday and complained that he has four homeworks to do on the first day of school. Suppose to attend the accounts tuition today, but decided to start next month cause my friends aren't going and i'm kindda lazy at the same time too. Haven't started my homework, maybe later, i'll take a nap first, hehe.  
     

    
</post>

<date>06,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      *yawn*... first day of school today. It was fun at first, had a new bus driver, and we joked among friends about her. hahha, during assembly, those who got straight/almost straight a's were called out to the stage to shake hands with the pricipal. As promised, cikgu syed alwi also gave us our rewards for getting 'a' for living skills. Kind of bored, no teachings today. However, i'm sure there're tons of homework awaiting for us in the time to come. Well, i believe that is no honeymoon year for us. Feel bit 'different' in class too, duno... After school, went to work for a while and walked back home at 4 o'clock. Hopefully, i could get my salary tomorrow.  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Last day of work today. Tomorrow school's gonna reopen. This holiday i got my first ever working experience, which is sort of good. But second thought, i regreted working. Wasted my precious time which i allocated for reading. Now, the holidays are all over. Wonder when i'll have the time to continue reading my story books. Woke up at 6.30 today and i have to drag myself to get up, and have to wake up one hour earlier tomorrow. It's great that school's reopening and i don't have to be feeling bored again at home. 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      man, real fed up with this blog thingy. Got crashed down for days, only manage to publish blogs today. Well, new year's here, bye 2002. I've learnt alot throughout the whole year. Time flies, it's gonna be my fourth year in bts. It feels like i've just entered form 1 yesterday. Resolutions? nahh... i don't have any specific resolutions, there're tons of 'em in my mind. My resolutions change from time to time. I've always thought of becoming the best writer, but i guess it'll be in my dreams. hehe, another piano exam next year (i mean this year), passing it will push me to grade 8. In other words, another tough moment...    
     

    
</post>

<date>28,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      An english monthly test today. Supposed to write an essay. The title doesn't really suit me, so i didn't do that well. In fact, at the same time i was having a gastric pain, again. Didn't take any gelusils nor rest too. When i reached home, i imediately took some medicine and ate my lunch. Only managed to finish half of my food, and slept. I'm still thinking whether to go to sbs, thinking thinking. If i do transfer there, i might be happier, but if i remain in pes, the adults will be happier. 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      school is bad today. Didn't really enjoy it since the first day i went there. During biology, there's this shocking diagnostic test. Don't care much bout it either. The funny thing that's worth a laugh is that: when we're in the lab, a kitten suddenly appeared from nowhere and everyone shouted like mad. One gal shouts and everyone joined. nonsence. Halfway through est lesson, some science equipment fell and a thermometer broke. Don't know, i suppose the mercury spread all over the floor too. Some even tried to play with it. man, i thought mercury is poisonous. hm, nobody was helpful enough to tell the lab assistant till the end of the class, i followed pek mun and she informed them about the broken thermometer.   
     

    
</post>

<date>26,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      For the past few days, lots of the unexpected happened in bts. More of dissapointments caused by the sidekman and his 'minions'. Chinese being accused for being racist, and lots of blames pouring from day to day. What we care. kampate!! As usual, sms-ed alot today. That's it if it's not prepaid. How much i've spent i don't know. Wait till the bill arrive and soon my parents will take away my h/p. Guitar lessons? I'm thinking to taking them. Guitarists looks cool. Anyway, i haven't really decided whether to learn guitar or not. Yet another decision making. heck, that's what i hate.   
     

    
</post>

<date>25,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Up to now, my homeworks aren't done, monthly tests next week, and i'm still playing. Really can't deny that i've changed. What will my exam results gonna be, we'll see. Today isn't a good day either. Well obviously, there's no one single day that is perfect. I'm waiting. haha, as usual, played alot today. Now, i'm addicted to the football game on ps. Alas, finished metal gear solid, say, it's a real good game...    
     

    
</post>

<date>24,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Initially, didn't think of posting any posts for these few days, no mood. Anyway, pek mun gave me the idea that i will have alot to write about today. So, i'll just write out some crap here. Ahem, went to bukit jalil stadium for some peace rally today. Reached school around 4.15, eat up our kfc, and off we went to the stadium. Traffic in bukit jalil was really congested, luckily the journey back to school was slightly better. Nothing much there, lots of yelling  - 'we want peace', and the place was real crowded like anything. What that decorated the whole place was those banners, some even written with foul language. Only around 9 something, all the vip's and vvip's including dr. mahathir arrived. To cut the story short, there's some performance from a few local artiste, long speeches and plenty of yellings. I didn't really like it either, crowded, smoky and there's those disturbing malay guys there. Well, reached home around 12 am, half asleep but here i am now, hooked to the internet.    
     

    
</post>

<date>21,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      long delayed blog. Today isn't entirely a good day either. It has been 'nightmare' to me since mrs lee left bts. First, the shock of my life i got, next the changing school matter. Pes isn't really like what i had expected. Well, i've talked to my parents about transferring to sbs, they object straight away without any further negotiating. What a dissapointment. On the phone, mrs lee advised me to remain where i am now. Good, everyone's against me, so i must as well obey them. The next day, dad says 'stay at least one month first'. By then, if i'm still not used to the school, they'll transfer me out. hm, i'm in two minds now i guess. I have a group of friends in sbs, but i don't want to make anyone unhappy. Now what? Sometimes being naïve has its benefits. What for think so far that'll drive us nuts? nahh, till then, just see how it goes... 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      *sigh~* gimme a few days break. Don't know what i should write about now, so just hold on and wait till i have the mood.  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      hoiyoh, first day in pes and my very first experience in a single-sex school. Girls there are sort of  gila-gila , but they're quite friendly. Managed to enter the best class, but didn't quite like it too. Too crowded and noisy. hahha, weird too, senaman pagi during every morning assembly. First time me and pek mun are experiencing it so we laughed like mad. Today as we walked everywhere, we became the centre of attraction. Without any badge and hey, i look funny in the pinafore. Got some information from some 'spy's in bts about today, where there's a new replacement for our english and est teacher, which is our class teacher too. bah, got to know that she's a real nasty fella, likes to boast about herself aquiring her phd and compares herself with other teachers. Wasted i wasn't there. If she were to bombard me with questions, i will surely answer back in a very 'special' tone. More and more students are planning to move, even the guys. Today, school life in pes isn't that bad, just that i'm not used to it yet. Still, i have bts blood in me.  
     

    
</post>

<date>17,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      ahh~ tomorrow, i'll be wearing my pinafore with white shoes and socks to pes. I'll definately miss my libarian clothes. Today, i wasn't concentrating at all in class, skipped some classes too and went around searching teachers for autographs. One satisfaction is, i finally screwed up enough courage to apologize from pn. rosma. Autographs, autographs, autographs. Chatted a little with the teachers, the best one is surely with mr lim. ah, definately, i'll miss him and his class too. kekkeke, i've no idea how's tomorrow gonna be, all i can do is to wait and see. Mixed feelings, not happy, but sad and scared. 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Another piano lesson today. A very bad performance from me. Went to switch on the pc right after i woke up. Just wanted to try out a game my brother borrowed. So, the whole day, i've been playing red alert 2 on the computer. heck, tomorrow might, i mean will be my last day in bts. For the first time now, i felt that i made the wrong decision in changing school. Before applying, i was so sure i jolly well told everyone that i'm sure of leaving. After my application was approved, i felt the other way round. Now i realised the reason i wanted to shift isn't strong enough. Anyway, what is done is done. I'll try pes first.   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Dental appointment at 12 noon today. Again, there's a little difficulties fitting the upper retainer. Anyway, wore a 'temporary' one and have to attend the next appointment this coming friday. Chap Goh Meh today. Ang pows i've collected of course is not as much as last year's. By the way, i don't really need the money though. It's just the fun of collecting them. Many stalls were not open in pasar malam. Don't know whether it's because of this occasion or just the rain earlier on. Anyway, i don't really like night markets. Just too bored at home...  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      alrighty, i'm writing friday's post on saturday. Again, went out the whole day. Slept at 2 the previous night and was forced to wake up at 7 something in the morning. Don't know what's the rush though. Just in a day, all the transferation process is done, which i didn't expect in the first place. Still there's something to be done in bts. Most probably, monday will be my last day in bts. If given a chance, i would want to extend it for another few more days. Well, honestly, mrs lee leaving bts is the saddest part of my school life so far. In the afternoon, went to leisure mall. Before joining my friends, went to buy school uniforms, shoes etc. Then, it's time for the friends gathering. Those who tagged along were: halijah, izana, izyan, kiat hwa and tam. Ate at swensens, forget of the price because it's only once in a blue moon. Halijah and izana went back right after the lunch, wheares, the remaining four of us walked around the shopping complex. hm...  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      aiseh, some stupid matter kept bugging my mind. Spent hours on the internet just to occupy myself and i wore my pyjamas the whole day. hah, lazy eh? Winamp crashed down, again. So gotta download it again. Nothing much today, yet another boring day.  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      bored. Of course nothing eventful happen today. Piano class at 9 in the morning, and i woke up at 8.50. In the afternoon, tam came, we chatted for a while before going to sktm's mrs lee's house. We walked there, as she stays not far from my place. Sat and chit chat a little, then we went back to my house. Nothing much, tam went back around 5.30 and i took a nap before dinner.   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      MAYDAY !!! managed to woke up at 6 o'clock sharp this morning eventhough i slept late the previous night. Got ready for school and took down a big pile of books from the cabinet above. When everything's done, it's already almost time for the bus to arrive. Don't wanna elaborate more. Wait till i have the mood... 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       gomen nasai , forgot to post updates yesterday. Anyway, was busy downloading songs too. Went to school today, the usual monday pkbm lining up and a boring, crappy speech from the hm again. Supposed to stay back for pkbm but played truant. In fact, all the chinese gals didn't stay back. Mrs. lee sent me home, and tam sat for a while in my house. Well, talked a little of 'senses'. Nothing really major though.  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      yo, went out the whole day. Supposed to attend a piano lesson replacement, but just told the teacher i couldn't make it. In the morning, went to edmund's house. Don't know what luck i have nowadays. On the way to tam's place, my mom's car was knocked by some saga car. Luckily, the damage isn't that serious. Kelly, wen chin and i had no choice but to wait for tam's mother at the roundabout. Reached edmund's house late than planned. Those who went there were: (guys) ching, chris, edward, loke and (gals) kelly, tam, wen chin and me myself. Played 'truth or dare', most of the guys, busy playing counter-strike online and ps2. Well, chatted alot, spilling and revealing own secrets i guess. Left edmund's house at 4 something, took a bus to tam's house, where edward and kelly went back to taman midah. Sat there for a while, ching and loke walked to lm, then the remaining four of us went to the taman midah pasar malam. 90% of the stalls aren't open, contacted kelly and we walked to wen chin's house. Her house is crowded with people, her uncle's family if i've not mistaken. We went in her room she brought us some alcoholic drinks, i drank too eventhough i'm not good in it. We talked and chatted there all the way. Then, it's time to go home. Edmund phoned his mom and told her to leave the house at 10, wheares i called my mom around 10 something but the phone was engaged. Tam offered a ride so just  tumpang  her car. Overall, it isn't bad...    
     

    
</post>

<date>07,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Got up really late today. Nevertheless, still managed to reach school in time and got in my line. Came home from school, logged on to the net, sent an email and slept. I left my pc on, to listen to some songs i've downloaded. Another boring weekend is here again. So far, i don't have any plannings, but might be going out tomorrow. Homeworks, there is, plenty. Don't care bout it though. hah !  
     

    
</post>

<date>06,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Again, i was really sleepy in school and today, i also got the shock of my life. ..., oh yeah, i'm thinking of stopping tuition too. Too lazy i guess. I always believe that if we really put in effort and work on something, i'm sure we shouldn't have any major problems with it. Same goes as studies. Well, form 4, i don't know.  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      *yawn*, was really reluctant to get up this morning and was very very sleepy in school. I'm going to take my afternoon nap after this. Yesterday, slept around 2 o'clock, just to complete my history work. Questions in upper forms is definately different from pmr. Got to answer in long long answers in essay forms this time. It seems like no matter how long i write an answer, it'll never end. Luckily, mom sent me to school this morning. Well, get to sleep for a few more minutes extra, only.  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Just had another late bath. Bad, bad day. Really stressed out right now, and, still a big pile of homeworks, mainly history. This morning was good,  pakpak  (dad's brother) came to visit our house. hm, didn't see them for quite long already, and the whole family seem very friendly. :) After lunch, went to leisure mall to lepak with tam. Just a walk before going back to homeworks. When we're satisfied, mom came and fetch us home. Help up tam to do some work, her physics folio! In fact, there's plenty of work, with some editing here and there. Then, she went back for dinner. Next, is to do the group work. I insisted them (loke too) to come at 9 be'coz i was really lethargic at that time. Took a nap, didn't sleep well though, alot of phone calls coming in for me. Just a short short nap and they arrived at my house. oh yah, i helped tam to print out her folio first before starting the mahjong work. Finally, they just went back about half an hour ago, and bla bla bla... hmmp~ 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      ah, just came back from a dinner in my grandaunt's house. The house was packed with people, we even have to take turns to eat. Well, we took turns according to generations, where the elders and young ones (my generation) get to eat first. And, as usual, every family get to  da pau  back the leftovers. On our way home, with my aunt in mom's car, again, it suddenly started raining cats and dogs. But, as we almost reach cheras, there's simply no rain at all. Odd weather for this year's cny, eh?    
     

    
</post>

<date>02,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      comments ?! so, what's cny? It's just the second day of the celebration and my family stayed at home the whole day, without any single visitors, being couch potatoes. I day-dream alot, watching how time flies. Read an 'suprising' email from dad yesterday, and another one today, weird! Apparently, the first one was about me, being hot tempered for the past few ?, weeks. Well, it's true that i do feel regret after every outbursts i've done. Nevertheless, i just couldn't screw up courage to apologize. hm..  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      oh well, slept quite late yesterday and was forced to wake up at 8 something. The usual  bai nian  every year, first stop is to visit my grandfather. Went home, not long after that, my uncle came to my house. They sat for a while chatting, while i was in upstairs, busy doing my maths homework. After that, off we went to do some visiting. Well, the adults have them planned already. My aunt sat my mom's car, to direct her the way, just like one of the previous years. Visited quite a number of places, some of the ppl, i don't even know how they're related to my family, a distant relative i guess. Every house we entered, the first thing we did was shook hands and wish each other happy new year. At night, there was this pot luck dinner at my orthordontist granduncle's house. We used to do this in the previous years, but those were for christmas. However, last christmas he was in australia attending his son's wedding. So instead, we had the gathering on cny. All in all, today isn't bad. But of course, it isn't that fun too without my dad here with us.      
     

    
</post>

<date>31,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      last day in pess... oh well, although i was there for only a month, i got a few of the teacher's autograph. they are - pn. prema, pn. azwana, pn. nik hasni, pn. shikin and pn. yong. i didn't get to know them that long, so it's hard to decide on which is my favourite one. however, first thought, i suppose it's pn. shikin, my chemistry teacher. as for friends, i didn't take their autographs as my book is supposingly full, instead, i asked for their contact number and so on. for the first time, i stayed back in school till 4. most of the time, chatting with see man and stephanie. when i reached home, i was really tired. received an sms from conrad, informing that he's backing out from the literature class. hm, i informed mrs lee then, bla bla bla. anyway, those in the group are: edward, joanne, loy yang and me! didn't get to sleep in the afternoon, and i'm really sleepy right now. 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      ahaha, long delayed. lazy maybe. went to school today, as the timekeeper for a debate. the participants were from smk(p) jalan ipoh and smk(p) air panas. Well, air panas won, the opposition team! oo yeah, the title for the debate was 'this house believes national service should be made compulsory for all school leavers'. definately, i disagree... haha, teacher in-harged for today was pn. hasnita (duno who's that), and pn. azwana (the datin). hm, pn. azwana teaches me est, well, she seems nice and friendly. :) all in all, it was great. the way and the style of their debates. i like the ending part of the government team. quote it here "actually, this debate is just like a game of chess, the opposition team made their first move and we made our last move, checkmate!" unquote. anyway, monday will be my last day in pess. oh well, a desicion is a desicion. i shall remain and stay put there. hm? 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      monthly tests update! biology - 40 marks, unexpected. chemistry - 70+. hm, stayed back till 2.15pm today for choral speaking. I'm not sure what purpose is it for, i think it's some sort of competition. Anyway, we have to present it on next wednesday and we only started pratising today. First practice isn't bad though...  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      heck?! ponteng piano today and went for a bts gathering at lm. Guys: chris, conrad, edmund, jacky, wai kit. Gals: Kiat hwa, may, melisa, pek mun, yen nee, tam, theresa, and me! -hope i didn't miss any. First, we went to the cinema, apparently, late for any shows. So, instead we went to fireworks. Conrad, yen nee, theresa and me myself played bumper car. I remember the last time i played that i was still a little kid. bla bla bla, all of us spilt up walking around with our own group eventually. As usual, i was with kiat hwa and tam. Well, went to memory lane, a&w, popular then watsons. When i was in popular, conrad sms-ed me and call us to join them bowling. Off we went there, and met them all. Not all bowl though. Before going home, i went to tam's house while kiat hwa tagged along as she's going to tumpang my mom's car later. Chit chat, my mom came, dropped kiat hwa at the lutheren church and EOS! All in all, so-so... 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      moral - 40 marks. whaha, only managed to get the passing mark. Physics test yesterday... hm, i think some mistakes here and there, and some questions don't know how to answer. oh well..  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      School again... got back my history and maths test papers today and had my bm test too. The bm test was tough, don't know how is it gonna be. Anyway, my history score was a satisfaction, although i didn't got the highest score. Maths was terrible, i'm almost at the bottom i think. That's bad. hm.. 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      School is '   ', what word to fit in i don't know. Anyway, had my monthly test already. For add-maths, i think i'll fail this time. Out of 6 questions, not one single one i know how to do. English essay, a dissapointing 22/40 score. what the heck, i think the teacher didn't really mark the language, more of grammar i see there. argh, what does school mean to me now? Last time, i love school days so much i never want to miss any. Now, school holidays are really a treat to me, and i really appreciate the weekends break.    
     

    
</post>

<date>03,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      To transfer or not to transfer? ah? i don't know ler. Gimme some time to think. Futher thinking, maybe we should have remained in bts earlier on. By the way, if we gals didn't made the move, the guys wouldn't budge as well. Now, all of us split up, some here, and some there. Thinking of the past, i miss those happy times when all of us were in bts - how much we laughed when we're in the bus, those 'bual-bual kosong' among 4 science 1. Thinking of those malays who have left for boarding schools - wana, izana, izyan, afiq. ah, miss their everyday jokes. Teachers? of course. Suppose u ppl can roughly know who they are. Always late regretting, i agree. *sigh~*    
     

    
</post>

<date>27,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      'majlis budi dan bakti' - at last, the day i've been looking forward to. not really because of the reward, it's predictable that we will not be receiving the amount of money we deserve. well, woke up around 7 this morning. when i was still upstairs changing, kelly and wen chin already arrived. my mom sent us to school, just as we were about to enter the hall, en. mustapha came and commented on our dresscode which is '?' damn! i don't know, i doesn't seem anything wrong to me. without negotiating, we were told to wear blazers, got to borrow them from prefects. well, it was wen chin's shirt which is not suitable. phew, escaped, luckily not me. anyway, wen chin swapped clothes with kelly, as she was not receiving any prizes. as expected, long and borinGG speech from the vip and hm. i wasn't really concentrating but i think the hm's speech is trying to convey some message to us. first event was the pmr rewards, the academic, followed by co-curricular i think. we librarians also got to receive a cert, nothing much about it. after receiving our prize, there was this kodak moment and everyone were calling us for snapshots. haha, not bad, i like it. towards the end of the ceremony, we got to chat with pn faridah, and oh well, 5 months pregnant, tam was busy talking about the baby. after that, me, kiat hwa and tam went searching for mr lim. we even walked to the lab. haha, finally caught him at the canteen eating. the guys were there too. some chit chats, ate some mee (yuck!), and back to mr. lim again. we got to chat a little with en ghazali too, he told us that he didn't got his transfer because the hm didn't approve it. kesian..! i reached home around 12 and bm class was on 2. overall, it's great, i enjoyed meeting old friends again - afiq, halijah, izana, izyan, ...etc. and the best thing, talking to former teachers - en ghazali, mr lim and pn faridah. 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      bla bla bla, didn't update for a long time dy. this morning woke up at 9.30 and realised there's a sms from pek mun, supposingly it's about the bm class. yeah, bm tuition at 11.30 today. woo, that's kindda early for me. anyway, all of them came. first, it was edward and jeff. then, loy yang came. after about 5 minutes, jiho and pek mun arrived. oh well, pek mun said there's a bad news that the bm class will start at 12. she wanted to use my pc for a moment so i brought her upstairs while the guys were downstairs chatting. apparently, pek mun wanted to save some fonts in a disket and i also lend her a cd which, i think there're some fonts in it. after that, all of us sat around the table, chatting while waiting for cikgu abu. *sigh* he came 1 hour later than planned, which is 12.30. ah, got to know that he went to eat first before coming. nothing much after that. see man phoned me a few times, first to ask about some homework, then, she asked me whether i would like to join her to pasar malam. i suggested to phone stephanie as well, but the plan didn't came out as planned. i went out with my parents, the same goes with see man (i guess?). maybe next week we'll plan properly and call steph as well. 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      school as usual today. for est, the teacher had some small game. we were divided into groups of fours and fives and is given a piece of mahjong paper and a copy of nst per group. supposed to find for the word the teacher mentioned and we were given 1 minute for each round. well, my group, which consists of conrad, edward, jeff, wen chin and me myself (bts!) managed to score 14 out of 15. didn't expected that we were rewarded too. supposed to meet her in staff room at 1.10 to collect our gift and during the second recess, off we went to search for her place. ahha, chocolates, that's it. all of us laughed as we didn't expect it too. anyway, better than nothing. conrad and i took a piece as i was bit hungry at that time. school ended at 2.30 and i reached home around 3. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Left house for school around 6.15 this morning. well, wen chin didn't come so i sat next to conrad, joining the other bts guys. nothing much, school ended at 1.50 instead of 2.30 because the islam students are having PAFA. anyway, went home, ate lunch and slept until 7 something. luckily the literature class was postponed to wednesday.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      hm, applied to be a librarian last wednesday. not really applied for it though. application was closed and they already elected the probationers when i first entered. luckily, the teacher accepted.. had a meeting on the same day, mainly to elected the office bearers. tam was elected as the chairperson, whereas i got the post as the treasurer. hm, i think it's temperory. today, there's a breifing on the oral tests. school ended at 11.55 and the traffic was really congested.  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      first day in sbs, my third secondary school. gosh, never thought that this will happen. changing school twice! anyway, today isn't bad, each class has 4 computers plus a television. and, the school is really big, doesn't look like a school though. school ends at 2.30 but we had recess twice. hm, i'll update more about this later. 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      argg... slept at 4 am last night, and just woke up a moment ago. been chatting all night long. right after i phoned mrs lee i straight away logged on to the net, and that was 10.30, and chatted all the way till 4 am. all chris's punye pasal, hahha, just jk. anyway, was so fed-up with him, bad words just got loose from my mouth. hm, maybe 'hand'? hahha, at the same time, downloaded some songs, from soft ones to DISCO types. addmaths class yesterday, was a little afraid while on the way walking to the tuition centre recalling the snatch-theft that wenchin experienced about a week ago. as usual, class was full of crappy jokes, adding to loyyang's 'dirty' jokes. anyway, it was fun chatting to pekmun beside me at the same time. piano lesson replacement tonight, argh, nvm, pratical exam is just around the corner. *yawn*, still sleepy now, feeling a little nauseated..? 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      ujian lisan bm today. mumbled a little, and the results, 9 marks out of 12. oh well, considered good. luckily only cikgu mazlan was there, not with pn sharlina. hahha, no p&p the whole of today, all we did was walk from one class to another, yapping and playing around. it's suppose to be a gotong-royong day, but since there were not many windows in our class, the main job is just to clear the rubbish and dust the computers. oh yea, was given an opportunity for a training to enter the memory technique grandmaster championship, but didn't took it. :-/ just lazy. tumpang kiat hwa's car home today, since i didn't have any transport. school holidays is starting tomorrow. no planning... heheh  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      alright, for almost a month i did not update my blog. so, how's life? well, so-so, life still goes on. exam just ended today, hurray! but the worst thing is lisan bm first thing in the morning tomorrow, and the coming piano exam next month! c'mon, where's my break? holiday is near, well, no planning. dad will not be able to come back, as well as that we not able to go to singapore for holiday. hm, my exam? argh, fall sick on one of the days, again! man, it's like a curse. 2 1/2 hours for most of the papers, yet kept rushing to complete the answers. Got back my maths objective paper today, well, not bad. But i've no confidence in my subjective part. Wasn't feeling good when doing it, so even there's plenty of spare time, i didn't bother to check my answers once more *tak larat!*. anyway, h-o-l-i-d-a-y ! 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      juz for gag, Cyrus says: fuck u ar ¨»'o'«¨  meOw says: shuddup la ¨»'o'«¨  meOw says: u fuck salah orang §hiÑîCHï»¿~ says: lol Cyrus says: yalo should fuck leng lui ¨»'o'«¨  meOw says: tahu pun 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      k, it's already one month since i entered sbs. well, not bad. the best thing was, the friendship between us (bts fellas) became closer. although there is still some *questions* in my mind, heck!, but well, friends! in class, i laughed alot with wen chin, even the teacher noticed me today. loyang, with his dirty jokes, haha, they make us laugh too. anyway, mom bought a webcam and cd writer today. a suprise actually, i only asked her to enquire about the price of the cd writer but suddenly the pc man came today along with it. cool, i tried experimenting with them already, even sent 2 pictures to my dad. :)
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       FIRST VISIT TO BTS!  well, well... went to visit bts today. around 10, edward came and fetch me along with jeff, loke and wen chin to the school. as we reach there, we noticed edmund was already waiting inside his mom's car and chris was already inside the school. well, got permission from he security guard and luckily he was those friendly kind. got in, and the first teacher we bumped into was mr. jeya. arg, an unhappy welcome. he gave us some unwelcoming lecture saying it was a stupid action to leave the school bla bla bla.. next, pn. rosma. don't know what message she was trying to convey either. haha, went upstairs and head straight to mr. lim's lab, which where we thought was the safest place. nah, tough luck, he had a class going on. went to the staff room instead. found en. ghazali, ah.. he's nice. shook hands and we talked about our school life in sbs. walked around the staffroom, managed to chat a little with pn. mordiana, cikgu k.a., pn. mordiana, pn. siti ainon, pn. izan and even ms. jane! suprisingly, she was nice to us. well, that's more like it. after all that, me and wen chin then decided to find mr. lim. off we went to the science lab again, and there's mr. lim. heheh, well, my main purpose of visiting the school is just to find mr. lim and en. ghazali. blablabla, around 12, we finally decided to go to leisure mall. went there by cab, ate mc donald's, went to speedy, popular, watsons... pooh, finally, show at 3.45. charlie's angles. the show isn't bad, just a little... ahem ahem! hahhaha, really tired now, and literature class is on 8 tonight!   
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       TWO WEEKS IS UP!  woke up around 5 something this morning and sent dad to kl sentral. when's the next time he's coming back? don't know yet. no plannings today, if only dad's here... well, went to bkt jalil club yesterday. swam for about an hour, then went to play basketball.  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       HAPPY OR SAD ?!  had been going out almost everyday since dad came back. yeh yeh... during school days, dad picked me up and we went for lunch with mom. yeh yeh... but, dad's goin back to china on sunday. aww... went to mv (midvalley) juz now, main purpose is to buy my brother's birthday present - a pair of rollerblades. again, after siva's class, came home, change into fresh clothes, and went there. ate shakey's as dinner. and, i'm having a sore throat at the same time. after that, we walked to toys'r'us to buy the rollerblades. good thing my feet can fit in too. hahhaha...  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      piano exam yesterday, guess i really screwed it up this time. had butterflies in my stomach before that. don't know what sort of butterflies are those, i was like 'hyper-nervous' at that time. after it was all over, i felt a little relieved, maybe. mom bought me for lunch at dave's deli. came home, and tuition at 5. came home, again, and mom and dad were already outside waiting for me. i rushed in the house and change into fresh clothes and straight away we went to leisure mall. bought the 9.15 tickets for the hulk. as there's still time, we went to eat dinner and dad bought me my advanced birthday gift - a discman! initially i was going to buy it using my own savings. hahha, bought a dance pad too, which is for the play station. anyway, after all that, it was already time for the movie. a real nice show. packed with all kinds of feelings - sadness, anger, and even humour. it's really a great show, just the ending is a little... well, i don't like those endings. haha...   
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      siva's at 5, and literatrue at 8. bah, luckily school ended at 11.55 and i slept b4 going for tuition. tomorrow is gonna be another busy day. going to tam's house, bm tuition, and going to lm too. haven't decided which is first, hehe. oh yeah, dad's coming home tomorrow, yehhh! better get a father's day gift tomorrow. well, reach here around 11 pm. so, by the time he reaches home, it'll be already midnight. got back my chemistry paper today, the thing i fear of most (for TODAY). next week, it'll be my english, which is gonna be bad, and my moral. argg... 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      extra piano lesson just now. on the way to school today, saw mr. lim's van on the way to town. too bad he was driving fast and my mom's car was far behind. argg, what a waste! haha... more exam papers today, hm... my greatest nightmare now is piano!   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      literature class just ended, first day of school, as expected, most of our exam papers are already marked. aww... don't wanna comment about the results here, hahha.     
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      haha, played final fantasy till 5 am last night, when other ppl are getting up for a new day, me and my brother are just going to bed. woke up in the morning, continued to play again, until it was time for tuition. hahah, first time going to siva's today. didn't really know where the place is, only that it's near my cousin's house. well, edward called half an hour before tuition and asked me whether i need directions (duno whether it was edward or loyyang, both have the similar voice). anyway, told them to come to my house first and as it was still early, i invited them in. 5 minutes to 5, we started walking to siva's house. didn't know that the 'classroom' is that small either. hahah... anyway, his teaching isn't bad, just that i don't have any idea what is it all about, coz i've never learn it before...     
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      bz-iest day of the holiday: piano class in the morning, dental appointment at 3.30, lm after that, and bm tuition at night. luckily slept quite early yesterday (maybe, hehe) at 2 something. haha, woke up around 9.30 today, didn't took my breakfast as i didn't have the appetite. maybe it's because of my bad throat. went for piano at 10, came back at 11 and played the playstation. dental appointment, arg, i don't know what was the dentist doing but it kindda hurts. got to know that the two wisdom teeth which are sprouting out might need to be extracted, arggghh... anyway, went to lm after that and was just in time for the movie - finding nemo! hehe, second time watching it. feeling bad again at the cinema, especially after eating some popcorns. right after the show ended, rushed home for dinner and around 8, cikgu abu came followed by loy yang and pek mun later on. hm, i'm thinking whether to go to frim this saturday...    
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      wohoo, record for this holiday: online till 4.30 am last night. didn't slept in the afternoon and had tuition before that too. hm, played literati online, and as usual, download songs (ff8). chatted at the same time too, and when i was about too offline earlier on, ooishin invited me to a game of pool. accepted her offer, as it's nice to get close to a new friend. played a few rounds, but only managed to win twice. last moments before sleeping, i read a magazine while lying down. by the time i really asleep, it was already 5 i guess. anyway, woke up around 11.30 this morning, no breakfast, and played the playstation for a while. nth much for today, i guess?  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      btw, slept around 3 something last night, as usual. woke up 11.30 in the morning for piano lesson. the lesson ended around 1 and straight away we went to my aunt's church's funfair. nothing much there, full of people and rushing at the same time too. bm tuition will be on 3 and our aim is just to finish up the coupons. anyway, reached home in time, ate up the foods, and a moment after that pek mun called saying that cikgu abu will not be arriving so soon. oh well, again. practised my piano, and loyyang called asking whether the bm tuition is on. bla bla bla, back to piano and loyyang arrived after that. well, only two of us there, with me wondering whether jeff is coming. we chatted a little, played the cat, and at last, abu arrived, then pek mun. class started, and ended at 5.45. went out for dinner at 6.30, and now i'm here, hooked again to the net =). long, long day... 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      1st lepak for this holiday: went to lm yesterday. well, those who went were pek mun, wen chin, me myself and also edward, being the only guy. afterall, the main purpose for this outing is to watch FINDING NEMO. took a cab around 12.30 from my house to lm, first thing we did was purchase our movie tickets. edward requested for the centre seat but we got the side one instead. as there was still time till the movie starts, we went to browse at the books in popular while edward went to fireworks. met up just in time the for the show and there's still time to buy our popcorns. all in all, the cartoon was really good, perfect i would say. all through the show, there're some sad parts and it's full of humour. all of us laughed alot throughout the show. i couldn't remember what time the show ended, but after that we went walking around the mall, to popular then to wrapz, we were curious to taste that newly-opened restaurant's food! kindda interesting and tasty. after all that, we later proceeded to the opposite building to walk around. nothing much after that. at around 6, my brother called and to me to search for them in popular. well, bid farwell to my friends and straight away went to popular. mom bought some books and went to chicken rice shop. i didn't ate dinner as i was still feeling bloated after eating with my friends. a little more shopping and off we went home. really had fun 'loitering' with my friends that day. oh yeah, 'finding nemo' is really a good show. go watch it! most probably i'm gonna watch it for the second time, this time, with my family =) 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       HaPpEe BuRtHdAyE !!  happe burthday to me! whehehehe... couldn't celebrate because of the monthly test, which is going to last till this wednesday. cut my birthday cake last night. tirimasu, not bad... mom gave me my present yesterday. receive a few from friends today, hey... tq tq, ppl! 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       StresSeD weeK aGaiN!  yesterday conrad invited me to pasar malam tonight. too bad i can't go, dinner tonight with my cousin who just came back from america. last night, again, conrad invited me for a movie in klcc. lizzie mcguire. i suppose he's so desperate to watch it. too bad, mom dun let, monthly test on monday. :'( maybe i'll go with conrad the following week, that's if the cinemas are still showing it. oh yeah, few days ago, saw mr lim's ny van on the way to school again. i suppose, fourth of fifth time. as usual, his van was ahead of mom's. hahha... hm, took off the speakers from the old pc juz now, brought it to my room and plugged it to my discman. whehehe, not bad! 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       ATTaCk OF THE GASTRIC JUICE  second gastric pain of the month, this time, is during mr lee's class. as usual, took medicine (the bottle is goin to be empty soon) and took a short nap. alright, getting a little blurr now, can't recall what else happened throughout the week. oh yeah, first time playing truant, not for school lessons, but for koko. edward and i hesitated initially, after judging the pros and cons, we eventually decided to just head straight home. outside the gate, met weng chee, form 1 junior. well, she asked me aren't i'm suppose to stay back. :-/ juz replied with a 'shh...'. hahha, edward saw his bus on the way, but decided to accompany me later on. afterall, his bus will only reach his house an hour later. walked to the taxi stand, and to our suprise, wen chin and conrad was there too. apparently, conrad was having a bad flu. couldn't stay back, and edward and i tagged along.  ahem! as for today, edward, ern li, wen chin and i went to j. jusco. wen chin and i went to purchase some key chains, while edward and ern li went elsewhere, i suppose, to choose my birthday present. :) haha, did received two presents today, and also two e-cards: from dad and loy yang. around 1.30, we took a cab and went to leisure mall. luckily the traffic was not congested! had lunch, shopped a little, and bla bla bla. met another sbs-sian there, a junior also. came home bout 4, and kindda late for siva's again (luckily not the last one to arrive!)  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       HARRY POTTER  alas, finished reading harry potter and the order of the pheonix. a really great book i would say. read it until 4.40 am last night, and finished up the rest just now. hm, even shed some tears, well, u know which is the sad part. :'( went for piano today, performed pretty ?, badly.. lots of things in my mind to think of. 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       ...  oh well, long time no update. had been kindda busy, mood? down, messing up with projects and the mountain of homeworks. as we got our respective id's for the pc in school, logging on to the net is a favourite pastime now. went for duty on thursday, nothing to do, on the pc. obviously there're tons of mail, some fella sending those junk mail to every student. ern li and wen chin have been busy dating, oh yea, pn. G scolded our class today, the main point i guess was because many didn't hand in their projects.   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       woHoO  went to j. jusco after school by bus. hm, nice seeing ern li and wen chin... siva's at 5 and came home with a bad gastric pain... aiyoo...  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       phew~  well, stayed back for pbsm today. thought of playing truant at the first place, haha.. conrad wasn't present and edward didn't stay back. as it was only me alone in group 2, i decided to duck in group 1, without informing the teachers. arg, anyway, off i went to join my opposite group, leaving ooi shin, qiu rong and kian ming behind. felt so awful right after entering the class. luckily the teacher didn't recognise me!  
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       STRIKE !  piano lesson today. hmp, shirley teacher kept asking me how was my piano exam. oh my, all i was able to say is 'duno'. well, she gave me a smile and man, i felt so guilty at that moment. :/ anyway, played hanon's and czerny's today. hanon, which was really hard, and teacher had to support my hands while i played throughout the whole piece. after piano lessons, we went to bukit jalil club. tried bowling today. won once and lost once. enter the gym after that and played a little basketball with my brother. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       HOMEWORKS !  i've a real mountain of homeworks today. mod. maths, bm, science reports, history, est, bla bla bla... stayed back for extra-curricular activities this afternoon. interact and volleyball club. nothing much though. volleyball was really tiring. all we did was just run and run. felt a little nauseated on the way home, but still managed to log on to the internet when i reached home. haha..  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      muahaha.. got back my moral paper. first time in history i failed a subject. oh well, so? again, suppose to stay back for pbsm today, but didn't. lazy, in fact, everyone is. walked to 7-11 after school, then as usual, took a cab home with conrad, edward and wen chin. 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      oh my, oh my, things are getting far worst. my studies, deteriorating... and i'm still repeating my bad habit of getting hooked to the net. hm? self-control is what i need now. anyone can giv me some? hahha... hahha... hahha...... 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      aa he hem..... woke up in the morning with a bad sore throat, arg, flu, muscles are still aching too. didn't want to go to school at the first place, but changed my mind. in school, had some minor gastric pain... 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      arghhh~~~ woke up this morning and could hardly move a single muscle, as expected. went to martin, came home and played the dance stage, again. anyway, played just a while then gave up. muscle ache. went to klcc with mom in the evening, main purpose was to change my swatch skin's battery. saw alot of nice nice and beautiful watches there... hmm.... walked around, didn't shop much coz no money, besides the limited time we had. had a drink in san francisco coffee before going home though :) oh my, i'm sneezing alot now... 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       arg, lethargic  woke up early this morning... pek mun arrived around 8.45 and off we went to the mamak restaurant to have breakfast. chit chat a little and as there was still a long time till it reaches 10 am, we decided to head to my house first. few minutes to 10, loy yang phoned and said that they're going to the court already. pek mun and i got our racquets and we walked to the badminton court next to the playground. played for quite sometime, among the ppl were: edmund, edward, loke, loy yang, pek mun and me myself. bout 12 something, we went to the same mamak restaurant to have lunch again. this time, edmund footed the bill. hehe, nth much after that, pek mun came to my house while waiting for her mom. played the dance stage several times, pespired alot again, then went to club at 4.30. 1 whole hour of badminton, AGAIN, this time with my cousins. next, was a game of bowling. phew~ to cut the story short, came home, went out for dinner, pasar malam (also with my cousins). all in all, it was great, really exercised alot just in 1 day!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       worst presentation!  nth much happened today actually, in fact, we only studied two subjects as two of the teachers didn't enter. for english, my group, was the first choosen to present the topic on land pollution. oh my, it shouldn't be like this. i did the typing and designing, and also most of the talk. apparently, i was like the back-up speaker. my oh my, nobody dared to step out to speak, in the end, i was the one to explain everything. however, i appreciate those who gave a try to speak, i really do. man, really got the fright out of my guts. pn. g did asked many questions, anyway, i was somewhat ready for all those. i don't really blame her though, i think it's more like a test for us. however, i was really dissapointed with some of my group members (not to mention who here) who did not contribute anything or put in any single effort on this task. obviously, teacher wasn't happy nor satisfied with our terrible job, and a re-do next wednesday! 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       oh no!  arggg... things are getting worse. bad mood in school, really terrible and disgracing marks to face. sigh~ the worst was chemistry and modern maths. didn't managed to get any marks that could satisfy me so far, addmaths and bio wasn't that bad though. oh my, what a disgrace! i better pull up my socks and buck up! 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      well, stopped blogging for quite some time. sigh, life is somewhat a little crappy these days. got back some papers, and none is satisfying. :(  
     

    
</post>

<date>31,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      woke up around 7 in the morning, nothing much (which is worth sharing) happened during the day, only that mom brought us out in the evening. went to leisure mall, first thing we did was to purchase the movie tickets. lord of the rings: the return of the king. the most anticipated trilogy, yeah! it's amazing, especially when they battle. the number of warriors and all that. well, there were some touching parts too. great movie overall. the movie started at 7.20 and ended around 10.35.  look, with just a blink of an eye, it's almost new year. blink, blink, and blink, gosh, how time flies. i can still vividly remember the moment when everyone was fearing of Y2K. i can still remember the day i first entered form 1. wow, one more minute till new year. when the clock strikes 12 it'll be a whole new year!  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      again, brother woke me up early to play RO. i gotta stop playing that game... took a short nap around 10, and received countless phone calls. hm~ plan didn't work out perfect, we were suppose to go to leisure mall at 1 pm, but there were some minor problems. after so much of negotiating, i wonder how much i spent sms-ing, loy yang's mom finally came and fetch loke and me to leisure mall. had mc donald's for lunch, then went to buy the tickets. wanted to watch lord of the rings initially, but unfortunately the tickets were sold out. nvm, might be going with mom to watch later. anyway, we bought tickets for 'colour of music'. i think that's the title, starring miriam and tony leong. not bad i'd say, some laughters here and there. well, outline it's a love story. after the movie, all of us went to tam's house, and then waited for loy yang's mom to come fetch us home.  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      shawn woke me up 6 o'clock in the morning to play ragnarok, of course i did coz he was going to help me tank. i'm trying to lvl up my merchant... hm, enough of that, i went back to sleep at 8 and woke up around 11. had curry 'hor fun' for breakfast then went to universal for biology tuition at 12.45. gosh, i was totally lost after missing 2 classes. sigh~ luckily i could recall some of the lower form facts. it helped somehow. came home, played ragnarok again then went out at 4.30 to bukit jalil club. as usual, 1 hour badminton. i'm kindda lazy, hehehe... had some light snacks after badminton with cousins and their family, then went straight to pasar malam. well, that's for today. 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      well, i don't really celebrate christmas, not to the fullest, so it's not really boxing day for me... all i did was staying at home, playing RO... this game is real addicting, i'm trying not to play so much... coz i've alot to catch up in tuition after i missed so many classes ! 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      woohoo... woke up this morning with my christmas socks hanging on my bed. i've guessed so, hehe, some pratical treat mom used give us kids for christmas - chocolates! yum yum, without dilly-dallying, i got up and peeped what's in it, 4 bars of kinder bueno. yummy, although not as much as the previous years, but good enough. i had an extra gift too - a 0.3 mechanical pencil which i requested from mom (i broke my old one in beijing). i can't really remember what i did after that, coz i'm posting this on the 28th! just changed the date u see... anyway, went to granduncle's house in damansara jaya after that. is it jaya or heights? i forgot, hehe, doesn't matter. christmas dinner, well, he organises dinners every christmas. it's great, especially when u get to gather with relatives. but this time, two of my uncles' family didn't come. nvm, still sufficient ppl to joy up the night, i guess, hehe.  adults chatted among themselves, while me and my cousins sat outside and had our 'youth conference', lol! chatted alot and also played with my granduncle's new puppies... man, they're really adourable. went home around 10 something i guess... well, that's it ! 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Came back not long ago from KLIA, and i'm really dizzy right now.  This was what happened today: The plane was to depart at 8.45 in the morning. Dad woke us up around 5 something, had sausages and chocolate drink for breakfast, got ready, and we left the apartment at 6.15 sharp. The taxi driver was already waiting for us downstairs. Traffic was pretty smooth, of course, it was so early. Reached the airport in half an hour time. Dad paid the taxi driver and we went in to check our flight's counter and so on. As there was still time, we sat at the sofa there to kill time. Proceeded in after that, well, parting from dad is always not easy, but, hm~ Anyway, dad says he's going to remain in the airport till we reach the boarding room. :) Well, lots of prosedurs after that, including filling in forms, and checking in our luggages. Dad called mom's handphone a few times too, just to check whether everything was alright. The dreadful 6 hours flight from beijing to singapore was kindda shaky. Landed at Singapore Changi Airport at 3 o'clock, and off we went to do a little shopping as the gate won't be open till 4 o'clock. Well, flight from singapore to kuala lumpur wasn't that bad, luckily it's just half an hour flight, i was already feeling sick at that moment. Came down, mom bought DOM for her friend, and we went to claim our luggages. 3 checked-in luggages this time, instead of only 1 when we came. Heheh, i was seeing things spinning around me that time, dizzy! Aunty Linda and Yan were already waiting for us at the arrival hall. Headed straight to Burger King to have dinner. I ordered mushroom swiss burger plus fries but only managed to eat half of the burger. :-/ Right after i reached home (home sweet home), i ran straight to the pc, but didn't sit long there, i wasn't feeling well u know, took a bath, then went to bed. Zzz...  Ahem, i'll just sumarize a little of what i experienced throughout the whole week: It's winter in beijing, leaves fall during autumn and right now, all the trees are bare. Guess what, even birds' nest are visible on trees. It seldom rains there, which is why the atmosphere is dry (unlike malaysia, which is 'panas dan lembap'). Arg, it didn't rain even once when i was there, that's why i didn't get to witness snow falling from the sky! Well, due to the dryness, lips and skin crack very easily, which is what i'm experiencing now.  One thing which puzzles me is that, there's this electromagnetic current everywhere. Simple things we touch eg. the taxi, door knobs and even ppl's finger could give u a minor shock. I usually hesitate to touch the escalator's handle there, well, just in case. Maybe u can figure out why by refering to some theories in physics eh? Wind there is really strong and chilling, when i get really cold, my fingers will hurt at its' tips and so does my toes. In Forbidden City the other day, i kept demanding to go back earlier as my ears were pain. hm? One note: nothing is free in beijing. You even need to pay to enter a temple ! 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      woke up at 10 something, had breakfast, then laze around. not much plannings today, anyway, went out during lunch time to a few bookstores, i chose a book which costs 20 yuan, then had lunch at a restaurant nearby. hm, i ordered a bowl of beef noodles, but didn't ate the mee. wasn't feeling well that time, sigh, the noodles look delicious though. haha, did a little shopping after that, mom brought some more souveniers, while denzel got his wallet which he demanded earlier on. came back, not long after that dad and mom went to the supermarket while we kids stayed in the apartment. mom prepared the dinner tonight, right after dinner, i took dad's camera and snapped a few pictures around dad's apartment. ;-) 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      hoho, wore 4 layers of clothing today, including thick thights, a sweater, an overcoat and the usual wind-breaker. dad woke me up really early today, bout 5.30 in the morning if i've not mistaken... scrambled egg for breakfast and we all went out at 7. this time, first destination was to huai bei skiing resort. well, went there along with another malaysian family, hehe. the whole journey took almost 2 hours. superb, the whole thing was great. the whole place was covered with ice and yet i was sweating when skiing? haha, rented skiing equipments including the boots, snow blades and also the ski poles. yup, through out the whole game, me and shawn  didn't fall even once. haha, we were so proud we boasted to our parents, mom fell a few times. :-/ after it was all over (2 hours was the duration), we got up the cab and the driver brought us to tour around that area. it's quite rural/remote over there, unlike the city which is progressing pretty fast. we stopped at a few scenic spots, snapped some pictures at the entrance, and it was time for lunch. can't remember what's the restaurant's name, but i guess it serves sichuan food. yummy, best local food so far... we headed straight home after lunch, another 2 hours journey. dad paid the taxi driver right after we reached century towers (dad's apartment), rmb 750 altogether, including yesterday's whole day trip. dad says it was reasonable. =) moreover, he was friendly. we rested at home, i tried to take a nap but at last didn't, went online for a moment instead. went out again around 6 for dinner, planned to go to an indonesian cuisine earlier on, but got to know it's closed for renovation when we reached there. well, went to a wubei restaurant instead. there was some performance there, quite interesting. food was just average. walked over to the shopping mall after dinner, bought a few things, and came back here again.  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      pizza for dinner again!! all because of little denzel! well, had fried egg with bread for breakfast, then went out at 10.30. first stop was summer palace, again, didn't tour the whole place. it's huge, man! the lake there is so wide, but frozen right now due to the temperature. wind today was extremely furious, could almost lift me up! i was chilling from top to toe then. we didn't have proper lunch today, just a few taiwanese sausages in summer palace and some instant noodles in the zoo. beijing zoo was our next destination. such a sad state that the zoo was not proper maintained. got to see giant pandas there and later bought some souvinear. most of the animals are kept indoors. haih, didn't visit the whole zoo again, missed out the aquarium, lions, tigers..... after that we went shopping, bought some more winter clothing, then had pizZa for dinner. hm, came back to dad's apartment around 7 something... that's all... 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      woke up and had sausages for breakfast. went out after that to the bookshop. cds there are real cheap! bought an original linkin park meteora for only 20 yuan (rm 10). well, spent alot of time in there, the bookshop has a total of 6 floors. should have chosen more cds... haha. we later had kfc for lunch, then continued shopping again till dinner. as for dinner, we went to pizza hut (little brother's request). arg, if i continue eating lots of heaty food i'm gonna get sore throat again. we later went to watch acrobatics. tickets were pretty expensive, 120 yuan (rm 60) per person. but i guess it's worth it. man, the show was fantastic! 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      had western food for breakfast. after that went to forbidden city. wind is pretty strong today, very, very chilling. it's dry over here, even my finger's skin cracked, ouch! back to the tour, well, it's a very huge place, didn't manage to tour the whole city coz of the weather. but i can say it's nice. came straight home after that, and had instant korean noodles for lunch. went out again around 5.30 pm after that to visit my grand-uncle. gosh, as usual traffic was really congested. took quite a long time to reach our destination. hm, went to the restaurant next to the his apartment later on, grand-uncle ordered lots of dishes, and his daughther footed the bill. next, we went to his apartment, clappers are installed in every floor, with just a clap, the lights will be on. chatted and chatted, then came back to dad's apartment around 9.30 pm. ;-) 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      right now, i've no idea wat's happening to my blog... well, had bacon with egg as the start of the day. went to a few shopping malls after that, bought quite some stuffs, new year clothes for little brother, trousers for mom, and some tid bits. had japanese noodles for lunch today, and mushroom soup, croisant and coffee for tea time. went to a yunnan restaurant for dinner, food tastes 'special', but average. hm, nothing much, went back to the apartment after that. 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      was forced to wake up early this morning, we were supposed to follow a local tour to a few tourist spots. first spot was to a jade carving factory. nothing much, just got to see how jades are carved and so on. next was the great wall of china. there're snow everywhere. nice, but it'll be slippery if stepped on. gosh, whenever the wind blows, we'll surely chill. jaz walked till one point then we turned back. toes were numb, fingers were hyper numb! (even with protective gloves) went for lunch after that, well, satisfying enough i would say. after all that was 2.45 pm and we went to the ming tombs. didn't visit the whole place though. next stop was some traditional chinese clinic. just spent a few minutes there and after all that, it was the end of the tour. came back to apartment. rested a while, then went out again for dinner. pizza hut. haha, went to the supermarket after that. hm, i kindda observed the price of the fruits sold there. one shocking thing was 1 whole durian costs 128 rmb (64 ringgit). dad bought us some ice-cream too! heheh...  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      started the journey to klia around 6.30 last night. well, left siva's class an hour earlier and right after i left the class, i got non-stop missed calls from both conrad and edward. haha, what more, of course i played with them too. after checking in our luggage, we finally had our dinner in the food court, together with aunty linda and cousin yan. as expected, flight was delayed due to the weather before this. it was almost midnight when we reached singapore change airport, and the next flight to beijing will be at 1 something, am! went a little shopping in the airport, and the sales guy there was rather rude. bought some nougats and candies and off we went to the boarding gate. journey from singapore was boring, 6 hours! i was yawning non-stop but just couldn't sleep. slept for bout 3 hours anyway, later on woke up to watch csi on the mini screen. temperature in beijing was approximately 2 - 5 degrees celcius. dad was already waiting for us at the arrival gate, immediately we went to purchase some bottled drinks from the vending machine nearby and get a cab to dad's apartment. hm, nice apartment, friendly security guards i would say. went for a shanghai lunch and did some shopping. sad to say the shopping mall was crowded with customers. besides, i was so tired at the moment after the long flight. came home after that as dad suggested that we all should rest first. slept, woke up around 5 and went out for shopping and dinner. guess what, dinner at mc donalds. haha, but mc donalds here is different from those in malaysia. did alot of shopping before that, my brothers and i got a new wind-breaker each. mom got a new pair of shoes and a new set of hat and scarf. went for a stroll later on before taking a cab home. my, it was winding and cold! even with gloves my fingers were numb. all in all, today is considered a tiring day!  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, as u can see, i'm posting this pretty early today. It's because i won't be able to do this at night. I'll be on a plane, to where? Beijing. Woke up around 9.15, and noticed there were incoming sms-es. Yeah, from conrad. :) I replied then straight away went down for breakfast, again, i didn't finish 'em all. Haha, took my medicines with some tasteless barley drink. No added sugar that is. Hm, luggages are already well-packed. Maybe there're still some things to be brought there. As for me, i'm still packing my giant pouch-bag which i'm bringing along. Equipped with my discman, i suppose i won't be that boring in the plane. One note, i hate sitting in airplanes. Y? Everything is bad in there. The smell, the food! And i'm air-sick. Too bad isn't it. Hopefully i'll be able to publish my next post tomorrow, in my dad's apartment. Well, provided if he allows me to use his laptop! 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      woke up early, piano lessons at 11. had lunch - a piece of bread chucked with tuna, and a few spoons of mushroom soup. still no appetite! completed my addmaths homework, oh well. walked to tuition around 4.40, mr lee didn't teach today, his son took over. nothing much happened, i came home and ate dinner, then surf the net while chatting with ern li. chatting with edward right now. argh, mood isn't good. well u know y edward! hehe...
     

    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      sigh~ woke up in the morning with a stinging bad sore throat. had a piece of bread for breakfast then took panadol. wore my jacket for almost the whole day, well, i just hope to get well as soon as possible. why? cause i'm going to beijing soon. it's winter right now, and it'll definately be freezing cold. played pc again, but later did a little addmaths. couldn't finish all the homework though, i was a little too tired at that moment. lunch was served later on, and i a few spoons of porridge was satisfying enough for me. went to bed, woke up, and felt totally awful. argh! played pc, and between that, joanne did sms and later phoned me, asking mainly about our tuition stuffs and so on. continue playing the pc until mom called for dinner, again, i didn't manage to finish up my meal. went to the doctor at around 8 o'clock. this time, mom is gonna make sure that i finish up all my antibiotics. (well, i didn't finish mine before this, and now i'm sick again!?)
     

    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      gosh, i just reached home from a whole lot of tiring walk. first, i was busy dreaming when i didn't realise i was already an hour late for siva's class. in the end, i decided not to go or else i'll be the laughing stock of the class. (not actually class, but siva himself) at around 1.10, i quickly rushed out to meet edward and loke to go for the next tuition which is in pudu. this time, we had no choice but walk to the bus stop in front of the main road. man, just from my house to the bus stop takes more than 15 minutes. reached the bus stop, there were empty places, luckily. well, unfortunately then, there were no place in the bus and i had to stand. traffic was severely congested as well, and it took a long time to reach our destination. suprisingly, the teacher came in late, and to our dissapointment, he ended our class early too! what the... the bus we sat home was also full, no place, traffic was still from bumper to bumper, and my bones are about to snap standing in there. agaiN, we had to walk for 20 minutes. i didn't bring any water, and i regretted it. my throat was as dry as the desert. thristy, lethargic, and about to faint, i had no choice but to continue walking. bla bla bla, at last i'm at home now. by the way, right after steping inside my house, i quickly reached the fridge to help myself with a glassful of chilled water. phew~
     

    
</post>

<date>06,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      i'm actually writing this past midnight, just changed the time :p. well, bio tuition and piano lessons today. nothing much, just that i didn't practise enough so i performed really bad. didn't follow mom to club for badminton, no mood... supposed to have dinner right after that with my aunty and cousins. mom came back after that and brought us to pasar malam. first, saw conrad... next was a surprise, chi wei. first time seeing him in taman midah with the fact that we live quite near each other. didn't do any revision today, bad bad... 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      It's 5th of december, next friday will be 12th, and i'll be spending about 10 days in beijing with dad and mom and bro... heheh, the holidays are gonna end soon. sigh~ oh well, woke up pretty early in the morning, did a little add maths and played RO, again. my normal daily routine. bla bla bla, lunch, nap, and tuition. nothing significant happened. today is rather a boring day isn't it?  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      lol, how long was it since my last post? and what a surprise, almost everyone is having their own blogs right now. i remember when i first started, the only person doing blogging was edmund. well, today isn't entirely a good day for me. woke up in the morning and felt kindda nauseated. apparently, i was having a fever and chilling the previous night. dragged myself to wake at last, and only later realised that RO will be under maintainance till 12 noon. argh, checked my inbox, and connection is at snail's speed. here's what i hate most, i had connection problems later on and the pc cannot be connected to the internet. went for tuition at 4.30, and well, it's back to mr lee's cracking jokes (i guess?) hehe, came home, had dinner, didn't really eat much today coz of my appetite. went upstairs after that and checked the modem's connections while browsing through the manuals. i was kindda ratty then, so fed up with it. FINALLY, with a few clicks of the mouse, i'm back nice and connected to the cyber highway! played RO with brother, then did a little tuition work. =)
     

    
</post>

<date>16,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Whoa, just the second week of school and homeworks are piling up till mountain high! Group work for moral, biology, bm and english altogether. Gosh, what's more? 1 est essay and 1 bm essay to be handed in on monday! Well, having a bad flu right now, it all started with a minor sore throat earlier this week, then had flu later on, then cough.    MONDAY  I couldn't really remember what actually happened, but during est we had this group activity. Those who were in my group: edmund, loke, loy yang and me myself. To get the ball rolling, ms. chiang demanded the group leaders to go to the front. Hm, all four of us didn't want to be the leader so we were there pointing our fingers to one another. Unexpectedly, ms. chiang suddenly pointed at me and said the rose among the thorns will be the leader. Argh, no choice, but it doesn't really matter. The whole activity went on kindda crappy, with the whole bunch of jokers in my group u see...    TUESDAY  13th january - mom's birthday! Treated my family for dinner, shawn was supposed to foot half of the bill, but nvm, understanding sis he has here, lol. Enough of crapping, in school, we had our first club meeting for this year. Guess what, i entered chinese society. It wasn't my choice actually, all my friends decided to enter, and i just followed suit, instinctively. Nth much, my spoken mandarin is long decayed, so i didn't speak much...   WEDNESDAY  As planned, it was the meeting for sports society today. This time, i insisted to join chess club, and my friends followed suit. Hehe, had extra class after school - physics and chemistry. Reached home around 5 after that, and i was really sleepy. Arg, english tuition at 5.30. Took a nap after dinner...   THURSDAY  Next, meeting for PBSM today. Was told to collect the physics homework, well, did that before school ended, not all handed in their works though. Right after the bell rang, i headed to the staff room in the second floor and put the papers on pn. norehan's table. I hope i did things right...   FRIDAY  Today, eh... Meeting for sports houses. I'm in amethyst, purple house. Lucky me i have friends accompanying me including conrad, eolanda, kiat hwa and lee wun. Hehe, went to martin after that, came home, had lunch, rested a while, then it was time for siva's. Siva's at 5 today, so didn't have much time to rest. I was late in fact, overslept a little. 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's hard to describe how school was so far. Life has been rather crappy this whole week. Had insomia almost every night, thinking too much! Anyway, it takes more muscles to frown than to smile. So, smile when u're happy. And smile when u're sad. I tried my best u see... Well, there are times when things were silent, and if i'm sad, tears will start to well up my eyes. Hey, but stop! No way i'm going to cry in school without an acceptable reason.  Things are surely different in a different class with different friends. I can vividly remember those days (last year) when i sat with wen chin, and buzzy in a group. Laughthers 24/7. I can recall when we were having fun imitating elyn. Haha, but again, HEY, it's a new start. No tam, no wen chin this time. My closest friends will be kiat hwa and lee wun. Guys, loy yang the great sifu will be there, right? Lolz... So, alas, here it is, form 5:-   MONDAY   Let's see what i can recall. Oh yeah, woke up really early, and left my house at 6.15 am. 6.15! That's too early! No negotiating anyway, Denzel's first day in standard 1. Well, when i arrived, the tarmac was kindda empty, not one of my friends is there yet. Took out my chemistry work book and did a little revision, best way to kill time in a fruitful way yeah? Soon, one by one and in groups people start arriving. Got in our lines, mazlan gave a speech, with a few cracking jokes too. Great, we were informed about the locations of our classes after that, 5 Angsana will be on the 3rd floor. Permission to use elevators, please. Haha, that will not be a reasonable request for the teachers. Miss Chiang came in a gave us some exercise, suppose to list down words related to EST, hm, just reeled off whatever i could think of that time. Nothing really worth sharing, school ended at 2.30, and i came home by taxi. Waited really long, it was almost 4 o'clock when i reached home and tuition was at 4.45! Darn, i was so sleepy and we did karangan. Humph~   TUESDAY  Couldn't recall what happened, kekeke... Came home, mom told me that mrs. lee called and informed class will be on wednesday.   WEDNESDAY  What happened in school? Forgot, hehe... I was so sleepy that i quickly finish lunch when i came home and took my afternoon nap right away. Slept until 5, which is when i saw joanne outside my gate! Ran upstairs and changed, and make a phone call before resuming my lessons ;-)    THURSDAY  Sigh~ sat taxi home today with edward and loke. Apparently, everyone wasn't in the mood. Edward wouldn't bother to joke around, i wouldn't bother to look at them, and so on. It was pindrop silence apart from the sound of the traffic. Hm, what's the point elaborating on this? Enough.   FRIDAY  History tuition in martin at 1.45. I wasn't really feeling well today. Bit nauseated. Didn't finish the food i ordered. Wasted. Sigh~ First few minutes of the class was bit dreadful too. Wasn't feeling so good. But after that was ok. Came home by taxi with wen chin. Some good laughthers along the journey. Hehe, reached home, slept, and woke up when it was almost time for siva's. Feeling bit tired, but had fun during his class. Well, lessons ended at 8, and porriage was for dinner. Didn't finish my meal, no appetite, gosh~  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've posted one post but I guess i didn't really publish it pretty well... now it's no where to be found, took quite some time to wrote it - all about Chinese New Year. Dad went back to China this morning, flight was around 8 something in the morning if i've not mistaken. Mom woke me up about 5.30 in the morning, got ready, and dad drove us all to kl sentral. As usual, we didn't go in the building. Well, all of us hugged dad goodbye and that's it.......... Dad will be coming back in either May or June...  
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yeap, i participated in the kuiz perdana held in an agama school yesterday. it's my second time participating, and i believe i did better the last time, that was during form 3. well, joining the quiz cetainly brought back lots of memories. the other time i went with afiq, hazwana and kien pong, it was kindda fun. so does this time, basically, i had a great time joking with the gals and mr loga. oh yeah, my team consists of jamilah, see man and sulastri. one note, yesterday when mr loga was tuning the radio, it accidentally aired a chinese channel which made me and see man laughed. the other time when i went with en. ghazali, he accidentally tunned into a tamil channel and i laughed along with my fellow mates. gosh, what a click! the quiz started around 9 (if i've not mistaken) and ended at 12 sharp. mr loga offered to send us all home but see man and i decided to get back to school as we weren't prepared. hm, if only mr loga told us sooner... well, obviously we didn't win the quiz, but there's no use crying over spilt milk! 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      a crappy day 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As uve said it edward, its indeed a special day. The thing is, Ive never expected it to be this special. Actually, I wasnt really in the mood in the morning. Yet another librarians gathering after assembly, and this time, we (seniors) were assigned to teach/guide one/two newbie (probates). Well, good thing Ive got a rather dependable form 4 librarian, Mah Chong Ken if Ive not mistaken. Have been seeing him around helping with the library stuff these days, seems to be pretty capable! As usual, the so-called short meeting took almost one whole period.   Happy things happened in class, lazy to elaborate more here. Was informed about the seminar which is going to start at 1 and ends at 3, and that means changing of plans. Went downstairs during recess (I wonder when was the last time I did that) just to phone my mom along with kiat hwa. Lee wun and wen chin joined after that. Later after that, before going down to the music room for the biology seminar, mr. loga called me and informed that class will be at 7.30. Well, later that night, I found out that it was a ploy. Haha, but never mind yeah   The seminar then ended at 3 oclock. It was a really long talk. At that time, I kept looking at my watch, hoping for it to strike 3. Mom came and fetched me home after that, and on the way, I was told to collect the cake. Whops, something happened in the cake house. Sheesh not going to mention it here. Got home, had lunch, fixed the severely out-of-shaped plastic shelve and went to sleep. Tired. Tuition at 7.30 (or 8 ?). 7.30, mr. L came and not too long after that, kiat hwa, followed by edward, lee wun and wen chin came. Then jeff. Next, surprise!! Celebrated for about half and hour, and it was back to lessons. Wow, that made me really elated++ !!  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Whoa, spent the whole day attempting to activate gprs. Even phoned hotlink 3 times just to solve my problem. Anyway, at last, i was able to connect, also with the help of those in LowYat Forum. Yay, now i'm able to download stuffs... &nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Woke up early this morning to follow my mom out along with brother. Of course there's a purpose for this... hm? First stop was mom's office, she always insist of parking her car there if we were to shop around that area. Reason? she has the season parking card. Apparently, today isn't a working day, so there weren't that many people in the building. As there is only one chair at my mom's place, she initially ordered me to stay in the meeting room, alone. Tried that once, and i don't think i wanna be in there alone again. Well instead, mom got a chair from the seat nearby and that solved the problem. Sat there observing the place for a moment, then read the newspaper, and after that browse through the stack of catalouges placed in one of the shelves. Mom did her work, and after half an hour or so, it was time to go. As we went out, i noticed there were some people inside the meeting room. Phew~ Good thing i didn't enter or i might be chased out? Walked to Wisma HLA, and had breakfast in Coffee Bean. Ordered a breakfast set which includes toasts, scrambled egg, sausages and coffee. Taste was quite good. Was later forced to finish up my meal faster, so, although i was already bloated at that moment, i just quaff down the remaining coffee. Mom went to shop for clothes after that, and i just tagged along. There was once when mom was trying out clothes in the fitting room, the lady in the shop together with her friend continuously bombarded me with questions. One of them said i have baby face - yikes, that sounds familiar, some one did tell me that before. Another said that i'm very tall. She then asked me to stand up and she started comparing heights. More questions, and i just wince a little as i'm not that fluent in cantonese. Hehe, at the same time, i was hoping for my mom to come out fast. Anyway, the two ladies were friendly, just that i'm a little... reserved. ;-) ... Came home, went for biology tuition and following that, piano lesson at 4. That's not all, badminton from 6 until 7, don't really favour it though, but after being foisted so many times, i decided to just go for the exercise. Saturday is always the busiest day, when i don't get to even touch my school homework at all. I've been rather busy for the for the past few days, helping out with the library here and there, entering class later than usual as well. I wonder if i'm marked 'LP' - lewat perhimpunan every morning, better check that out. Well, i was asked to collect 2 ringgit from every librarian the other day, and not all paid on that day too. Luckily loy yang was there to help. What more, thursday&nbsp;was also bad hair day - both figuratively and literally. I actually never expect the hairdresser to cut my hair this short. In school, i was again not perfectly in the mood, been thinking about lots of things lately.    
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Started the day with a really bad mood and yup, the following hours didn't went on perfectly either. Scoured around the shelves today to search for my list of vocabulary but it's no where in sight, guess i'll have to make a new list. Attempted to practise my piano but the house was just so noisy that i gave up, wonder how am i going to endure such a cacophony. Mom drove me to tuition at 1 and well, i guess my attitude towards everyone during the class wasn't pleasant. Oh well? Came home, had lunch and rested for about half an hour or so before going for piano class. Went to leisure mall at night, and as already expected, spiderman 2 tickets were sold out. Proceeded straight for dinner, then to a little shopping, and it's time to get home. bOring...  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      mood was a bit ok early this morning but it sort of slowly deteriorated. received a msg from mrs jeya today, before opening it i was hoping that it is to inform that class will be cancelled. ops, but it wasn't. it says "class tonight at 8pm". sigh, i'm gonna get more scoldings for not completing my task, one time after another. *wink*  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>