<Blog>

<date>24,January,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Oh yeah, and I've noticed that a lot of the gallery is buggered. Bugger.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,January,2003</date>
<post>


       
      This weblog is ALEX FORDs fault. It was his idea! Feel I must point that out.  This must be as boring for you to read it as it for me to write it, but in case anyone is checking I'll update it now and then, and it'll make a good diary-thingy sorty thing for me.  Anyway todays highlight was my NEW TYRES ARRIVING FROM GERMANY! YES! Ordered late Monday, despatched Tuesday, delivered Friday. Can't wait to fit them and sort out my bike, then get down to Betws!
     

    
</post>

<date>22,January,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Whoo, scary...  Just looked at the hit counters and I've been getting hits even before I've launched the pages!  Even had a 'dodgy' entry in the guest book. Will be deleting it shortly.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,January,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well, at last, it's all uploaded and finished.  The delay was because I thought Tripod dtp was down - it wasn't - it was because ftp is blocked from the PC room closest to the Chaplaincy!  Update on me - well I'm back in Bangor, course-less and job-less. In no hurry to get a job either. Just taking each day as it comes.  Doing lot's of exercise, which is good, but my knee has started playing up, which is bad.  Ordered various odds 'n' ends for my bikes. Can't wait to get them back on the road - especially the mtb!
     

    
</post>

<date>12,January,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hold on a minute - I'm still here! Decided not to go back today. Will go tomorrow.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,January,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well, apart from optimsing the photos, my site is officially finished! All pages complete, hit counters in place & working.  Think I'll 'launch' it tomorrow from Bangor.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,January,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Yet another too-late night update! Just watched The Shining for the first time. Very good film.  Had a typical little episode this morning: my dad was out, and I drove my mum into town, and when I arrived back at the house - realised I had forgotten to get the key off mum! Quickly drove back into town. My mum was meeting my sister and luckily (predictably?) she was late, so I just managed to get there in time, and get the key.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,January,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Right, got the galleries up and running! Well, apart from optimising them :-(  Been reading BM a lot. Wish I could afford a new bike, but I just can't right now. Did pay (one of) my credit cards off today -  after  the payment date - £20 fine! Ouch!
     

    
</post>

<date>09,January,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Made rapid progress on website tonight. Gallery menu page now live and Ally gallery fully functional!
     

    
</post>

<date>08,January,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well, after a lot of fiddling and a rather steep learning curve, I've managed to get the first gallery up and running! The Proxomitron is running well, too. Time for bed.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,January,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Just downloaded and installed a little program called The Proxomitron. It kills ads and pop-ups, and limits access to my computer. It seems to speed page loading greatly. Top little program!
     

    
</post>

<date>07,January,2003</date>
<post>


       
      First attempt to upload a gallery... and it's a total failure!
     

    
</post>

<date>07,January,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I remember that one of the effects of Prozac is that it reduces your inhibitions and makes you more playful. In fact that's how I feel when I'm really happy. And you know what? I'm beginning to feel like that again.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,January,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Trying not to get too excited about this (don't want to get my hopes up!) but my dream job has just appeared on the Bangor Careers service:  Cymru Prosper Wales Graduate Placement Programme 2002 / 2003   Job Title: Environmental Administrator  Company: South Caernarfon Creameries Ltd, Pwllheli, Gwynedd  Placement Details: Minimum of £180 p.w. / 12 weeks   Basic Purpose of Job   The basic purpose of the placement will be to set up an Environmental Management manual and Environmental Management system within the company.   Knowledge, Skills and Discipline Required   &#61558; A graduate with an Environmental background  &#61558; Welsh speaking would be preferred  &#61558; Driving license  &#61558; Computer literacy (including word and excel)   Got to give it a shot! Don't speak Welsh, and I hope they don't automatically give it to a Welsh speaker over me, but I am ideally qualified for it!
     

    
</post>

<date>07,January,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Radio 4's Midweek had the author of a fascinating book on this morning: a study of ‘lucky’ and ‘unlucky’ people. Apparently there’s no paranormal or otherwise explanation of luck, it’s just the way people think. A simple test is to imagine that you're in a bank raid, and that you are shot in the arm. How do you feel? An unlucky person may think 'how awful, trust me to end up in a bank being robbed, and get shot'. But a lucky person would think 'thank goodness I wasn't shot and killed'. One person in the study even thought 'great, I've been shot in a bank raid, now I sell my story to the papers!'.  It seems that luckniss comes down to a way of thinking. Lucky people see the best in everything and see set-backs as challenges. Unlucky people are much more pessimistic. (The authors studied how frequently 'lucky' and 'unlucky' people won money on the lottery, which is a game of pure chance. It was 50/50.) I suspect I have the 'unlucky' way of thinking. Someone like Sarah or Irene definitely have the 'lucky' way. There's lessons in this for me. Got to get hold of that book.  Was thinking about what it would be like if the course had gone smoothly. Realised that I'd be part-way through my first morning in Grango, that horrrid prison of a  school. Instead I'm at home, still in bed. So maybe it's not that bad.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,January,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well, been fiddling around finding out how to block banner ads. I could block all the ads on Tripod quite easily, but I reckon there's some code in the ads that checks to see if it's being blocked, so I'll leave them for now. They're hardly a problem anyway.  Found Sarah's original homepage just now. It was made three years ago, I think she's forgotten it's there. Felt a little weird reading it.   Watched GoldenEye this evening. I'd forgotten how good that film is. urlLink  
     

    
</post>

<date>07,January,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Finally summoned up the courage to phone Janet, my university tutor, to ask for a complete written report covering why I was thrown off the teacher training course. I suprised myself with how nice I was on the phone to her. Politeness itself. I'm glad I've got it done.   Can definitely feel the Prozac kicking in now. It's a strange feeling. I feel that still got plenty of things to be depressed about, but now I'm simply not depressed.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,January,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hmm, a quick test to see how/if this works
     

    
</post>

<date>28,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
      BAD NEWS  Poofus the hamster just managed to reach my trousers the bars of her cage last night, and ate them. £35, and I'll have to replace them as 1. They were very good and 2. I only have two pairs of trousers now.  Plus the wind blew my lovely slate barometer and glass boat from Venice down yesterday. Over £30 together. But kinda symbolic; both were bought when I was with someone I no longer see.   GOOD NEWS  Went with Helen to a photo shoot today! It was a with a local professional photographer, and bizarrely his studio his Llandegfan village hall, where I used to help with Cub Scouts. Helen remained dressed this time (it was for a modelling agency portfolio), but it was the same place where she did her nudes and, gulp, *bondage* photos the other week! (for her boyfriend for Valentine's) But I actually spent the time preparing my Sports Science lab tech job application - deadline is in two hours! 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
      The club was great!  Well, it wasn't a club, it was a flashy wine bar, in the old cellars of a big hotel. Helen was the one and only dancer, but she was fantastic. She enjoyed herself and had over twenty quid tucked in her knickers! Overall, she made £80 last night. All right for some!  Well, I said Helen was the only dancer, but that's not strictly true. There was supposed to be a guy dancing with her, and although he turned up, he chickened out. Pussy. However, I'd brought along my mate Andy, who has a great body and is a good dancer. After a quick word with the management, he was off! He wears thongs all the time, so looked the part. He was also pissed, having consumed a bottle of red in preparation. But Andy & Helen, together, were great. Helen brought along her blonde near 6' Danish friend, Carina. Helen, Carina and I all get along very well... Other people came too, including a Greek couple also from Helen's corridor, another Greek lass and of course Ruth. All round, it was a fantastic night, and we didn't leave until well after midnight ;-)  Looking after the hamsters is great! The cages nearly fill my tiny room, but they're such fun. Got to give them back later :-( We've spent hours playing with them in the Chaplaincy! Sandra, a German resident, particulary liked them. I let her keep Pretty one night in her room! I think she's missing her best friend, who went home to Germany today. It's nice to cheer someone up. Did her washing up with mine, too.  Oh and, Helen has asked me to drive her to a 'glamour' photo shoot tomorrow... she says I can stay and watch... :-)
     

    
</post>

<date>25,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Today, or rather this evening tomorrow and a bit of Thursday, I'm looking after about half a dozen hamsters.   Oh, you want to know why? OK. It's cos they all belong to my friends who live in a student halls, and tomorrow there's going to be a room inspection (and pets aren't allowed), so I'm keeping them in the Chaplaincy in the mean time. There's Pretty, the daddy who lives by himself (as Syrian hamsters should) in one cage, Poofus, the mummy, with three beautiful babies in one big cage, and Rascal, a black baby who now belongs to my friend Ruth and lives in a seperate cage too. The babies will need seperating very soon or they'll start breeding!   I'm going to a pole-dancing club tomorrow! Weirdly, this is because of the hamsters. A girl on my friend's corridor had a hamster who suddenly started churning out babies, so we went round to have a look and go 'ahhhhhhh' etc. I got talking with the owner - Helen - and became friends. She's a psychology student, but also extraordinarily good-looking (not that being a psyche student and being good-looking are mutually exclusive!), and a glamour model! She's just got a job as a pole dancer, and starts tomorrow. I'm driving us there. Should be interesting! Helen currently has three of the baby hamsters but gave tw others to my friends on that corridor.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Had my first ride on a scooter today. Got up to whole heady 60mph! Was great though. Rode pillion, and went to Llandona beach on Anglesey, with me giving hand-signal directions!  Less good was the weekend. I've been very ill and mostly in bed, shame as some people I know from  urlLink OUTDOORSmagic  were up in Snowdonia to climb Tryfan, and I sorely would've like to have gone with them.  Need to insert a bit about the strength testing I did in the week following the peace march. I was a guinea pig for a sports science honours project, and it involved me being strength tested on a KinCom dynanometer and then having to do 150 bicep curls to damage my left bicep! Then cryotherapy - 15mins of my arm being submersed in 15deg water! Blood test too. Tested everyday until Thursday. Interesting stuff. Good to see in Sports Science dept. The girls doing the project were nice too.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
      PEACE MARCH  Probably worth saying that I went on the peace demo in London on Saturday Feb 15. A 600 mile round trip from Bangor! But a fanstatic time:  We left Bangor at 5.30am, and I spent most of the coach journey down asleep, though on the occasional moments when I did open my eyes the view sun rising over a frosty England through the big windscreen of the coach (I had a front seat) was glorious, until I fell asleep again. Later on, I read UN resolution 1441 and Hans Blix's report, to be as fully informed on the situation as possible. Clearly no case for war.  We disembarked and joined the northern branch of the march just south of Euston station.I don't know London at all and got a bit confused as to where we went. I know we broke away from the northern route and cut through Soho (sex shops! woooh!) and maybe Mayfair, and joined the main march by going down New Bond Street a few hundred metres before it went into Hyde Park (which wasn't remotely full at all, actually).  We missed Picadilly and Eros (not that I know what that is! Statue I think) but considering I met a woman I know from London entirely by chance (1 in 750,000!), and then had a really good chat with some other people on the coach back, then nevermind. Good, in fact.  The Bangor group - strangely and inexplicably - made no attempt to stick together. Some of the people in my little group got bored with the gridlock and cut through the back streets - which were pretty empty. It was quite fun to have our own little mini-march though!  But then I split away on my own before we reached Hyde Park, as I was bored of following others and having to constantly stay in sight. Freed from checking everyone's position every ten seconds, I could really appreciate the mood, the atmosphere of the crowd. Something very special indeed.  Oh and I had my own home-made 'Free Palestine' placard. I made it in the Chaplaincy on Fri night after coming back from the PC room, when I found a blank board and some paint in the kitchen. Quite proud of it! While wondering around Hyde Park I saw a lot of people looking at it and smiling.  However it was only attached to my stick by duck tape as I couldn't find any glue or nails, and it blew off as I was talking to Anne in HP and hit me on the nose!! I now keep it as a souvenier in my room.   Found the coach in Park Lane by joggging from one end to the other scanning for it as I ran!  All in all a fanstastic day. Maybe our government will ignore us, but at least we stood up to be counted for what we believed in.   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
      UPDATE whoo hoo  Um, my bike is now a nice trick-looking (get me and my hip cool terms! er...) black rigid mtb. Can't actually ride it though as I'm being a guinea big for a muscle-damage expt, which hurts as much as it sounds like it does.  Um, made friends with a pole-dancing glamour model who likes to show me her pictures. oo er missus... Go running with her every other day. She's a real laugh. I'll also be driving her to the club she works in in Beaumaris (weirdly enough... new trendy club under the Bulkley Arms) where she's invited me to watch to her. She makes twenty quid an hour though - I'm not jealous, much, no...  She also has a family of baby hamsters, which is how I met her.  Oh, and she has a boyfriend :-(  Who doesn't live here :-)  Um, also met lots of other cool new people, and have developed a tendency to fall asleep in the afternoon.  Other than that, can't think of much else for now.
     

    
</post>

<date>31,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Coo, no update since Tuesday... well, not been missing much. Going to bed too late (4am!)/getting up too late (4pm!!), not good. Feel light-headed when exercising - think I've been lying down too much! Took recycling today after clearing a lot of junk out of the Chaplaincy last night (at 3am). Over five sacks of paper!
     

    
</post>

<date>26,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Went to circuit training on Tuesday - damned hard work, Tom had us running sprints in the 'warm-up'! Walked back with Natasha and Beth. Made a change from always driving. Was rather suprised when Cecily asked me if I wanted to go to the beach today! Obliged, but with some trepidation.  Anyway, this moring Cecily and I drove to Abberfraw beach. We spent a long time discussing relationships, opposite-sex friendships, a little bit about Islam and what life's like in Florida (where she's spent some time). Cec was actually very nice, after treating me so coolly for the last few weeks. She'd somehow got the idea that I fancied her, which makes her run a mile. She's rather wrong, bless, but a nice girl. Glad I had the chance to talk to her.  In the afternoon I was dog-tired having only had five hours sleep last night. But still drove Ruth Louise and Kieron down to Church Island. Funnily enough, it was my first time to Church Island after leaving my ex, just as visiting Aberffraw this morning was the first time since, too. Climbed some trees and a rock outcrops and sat in a big yew tree to read an excellent book I found in the Chaplaincy. It's called 'The Arabs - a Short History' and was first written in 1943 with this (revised) edition published in 1953. It's facinating, written before all the troubles of that region kicked off. The Arabs really are a great people and, afterall, Iraq is the cradle of human civilisation. So much to learn!
     

    
</post>

<date>23,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I've got my hamster back! I visited Ruth last night after leaving here and Sasha was fine with me. I couldn't bear to leave him, and Ruth wanted me to take him before she got too attatched to him!  Compared to his sister, he's much thinner, and much more active. I mentioned this to someone today and they said 'just like you then'!  Went to the Treborth Botanic gardens work day today. Had a lovely time gardening in the sun. In the morning, I pricked out lettuces, and in the afternoon I cleared scrub. Chatted to some new people - Jenny, who lives next door to Helen and can climb 5c (my best is only 4c!), and another girl who live in Emrys but I didn't get her name. Cute though ;) Another cutie was Mandy, who I've nick-named Lara as she was dressed like Lara Croft! She was a friend of Nicky, who was also there. Me and Jenny sat by the (incredinbly hot - the wheel barrow wheel started smoking!) bonfire and didn't notice everyone leave! So we drove home. Met Emma in the Chaplaincy and phoned Nicky, and we all went to Cable Bay. The setting sun was beautiful; it's reflection like a stream of lava across the sea. We paddled in the sea and climbed on the rocks a bit. We'd seen a woman do an amazing cartwheel-backflip thing, and so we had a go ourselves. I was rubbish and Emma didn't even try, but Nicky did a great cartwheel.   Cruised home at 50mph on the A55. Spotted Helen jogging to the Menai Bridge so crossed it to shout 'hello', then drove down & around under the bridge to show the girls the view. I got out with the engine running to have a go at climbing the piers a little way, and Emma jumped in the driving seat and drove my car off! It was very funny - she'd stop, let me catch up (I was running after her) and then drive off just as I got there!   All together a great day :)
     

    
</post>

<date>20,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      My sleep patterns have become shot to s***. Just as I was going to bed last night I idly flicked on the tv to check teletext the moment the first bombs fell on Iraq, and ended up watching ITV news until 5am. As a result, apart from short periods of wakefulness checking the news (looking in particular for the B-52s launching from Fairford) I slept through until 6pm! Just as the second wave of attacks started. I actually got up, quickly stuffed some food, water and milk down my throat and headed down for circuit training, only to find the place deserted... not sure what happened there! Anyway, now I feel like a pile of poo but will no doubt stay up far too late tonight following the progress of the war.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Been loosing a little sleep over Iraq, I will admit. I'm a very empathetic person - Concorde, TWA 800, 9/11, even the Estonia, nine years ago, all cut me up bad.  Slept most of the morning, and ached like hell after the monster session at circuits last night. Tom thought it would be a good idea if we went outside for the warm up, and we ended up doing sprints up hill! The equivalent of a good intervals session for me. And then we did the circuits! Amusingly, circuits is becoming something of a dating agency. Last week Tom asked Bethany out, as this week another guy asked the girl I'd gone round with out in that usual, falterting crap-guy, style! It's funny, I didn't mind at all. It must be the Prozac!
     

    
</post>

<date>18,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hopefully Saddam will just leave, probably at the last minute. But if he doesn't, noon Thursday is my bet for the bombers & tankers to launch from Fairford. Hopefully, they and the rest of the air attack only go for army command & control and Ba'ath buildings, and leave civillian stuff alone, and send in troops early to give the Iraqi army the chance to surrender rather than be killed by air attack. I desperately hope that happens.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well, this is it. We are on the brink of war.  I'm pro-ultimatum. I do not pretend otherwise. Yes, I went on the anti-war march, as I felt that an attack at that moment of time would be unjustified. But since then, Iraq has failed to co-operate fully. There is a lack of evidence to show he has no chemical or biological weapons. He has developed new ballitsic missiles and unmanned aerial vehicles specifically designed to deliver such weapons. It's clear he still has a weapons program of some description. Do not forget, unlike the US or other countries who have chemical weapons, Saddam has used his on numerous attacks on civilian populations in Iran and Iraq.  France would've had us given Saddam forever to disarm. That wouldnt work, we all know that. It's over four months since 1441 gave him two months to comply. It would have been wonderful for the UN to have presented a strong, united front against Saddam. But that has failed to happen, so other countries feel they have to go it alone. The previous resolutions clearly give a basis for war, as shown by various attorney generals around the world.  Let's have a look at numbers:  Against a war: France Russia China  Most of Africa  For: US UK Most of Europe (including Spain Italy and all the new members) Australia Japan  The worldwide consensus of opinion is clearly for giving Saddam one last chance. And that's what Bush has given him.  What about the past? In the 1980s, Iran was a greater threat to the world than Iraq. So the west armed Saddam, rather than directly attack Iran, just as we armed Israel to defend itself against the Arabs (without such arms, there may well have been a second holocaust in Israel). In hindsight, it was the wrong thing to do. But it was the right thing at the time. We're still doing it now; re-arming Afghanistan to protect itself against the remains of the Taleban.  And what about France and Russia? Iraq airforce is made up entirely of French (Dassualt) and Russian (Mig) aircraft. His army uses Russian small arms, tanks and vehicles, and Canadian-designed artillery pieces. His Baghdad bunker was built by a German company to a Yugoslavian design. Russia is the main investor in Iraqi oil. France and Russia have long-standing ties with Iraq, and their stance is no more than an attempt to preserve those links, and a desire to 'stand up' to Bush for their voters. Germany has been casting around for an international role for sometime, and as ties with France are renewed, it has chosen to side with them.   All these countries could've chosen to support the draft resolution with the 'key-tests', to be completed before a dead-line, that would have ensured peaceful disarmament. Saddam clearly wants WMDs, and is developing them, and has a track-record of using them. He needs to be stopped, and the new resolution was the best way. But sadly it did not get the international support it needed, forcing the allies to go it alone. The only loser was the UN.  As I said, I'm pro-ultimatum. War is not inevitable - if Saddam leaves, there will be no war. I agree with that position.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      A very important day - Blair Bush and the Spainish premier met in the Azores yesterday, and today they go to the Security Council to press for a resolution for the last time. Today 'is it'. I'm deliberatley avoiding news until about 10pm - or 5pm in New York. By then, the situation should be much clearer.  Bizzarely, I am continuing to vividly remember by dreams. I had a nightmare - very rare for me - last night. I dreamt that Helen was dying in hospital! I believe my brain cooked that up after watching 24 yesterday, where Paula, a nice character, died.  The weather is, once again, amazing! Sitting out on Mount Stella in the sunshine was lovely.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      The weather has been amazing the last few days. Hasn't stopped me being glued to the World Indoor Athletics Championship though. Great stuff. Went to Beth for an hour yesterday.  On Friday I watched Comic Relief in its' entirety!
     

    
</post>

<date>14,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Spending today in front of the box watching the indoor athletics, followed by Red Nose Day. Will probably spend the weekend watching the athletics too!
     

    
</post>

<date>12,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Argh, just remembered - my very lazy neighbour left some bags of rubbish outside her room, right next to my door. There was something disgustingly smelly liquid in them, and it's seeped into the carpet just outside of my door. As the chaplaincy is really old, there's always a strong draft coming under my door, so now my room stinks!  Tried pouring pine disinfectant and lots of hot water on the patch before I came. Hope that's cleared it, at least a bit.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Precis of the last few days...  Um, attacked by hamster, which hurt like hell. I've had enough of constantly being bitten, so Ruth's got him at the moment. Not sure whether to get another one or not. A bikemagic.com member kindly posted me half a headset, which Mike's Bike's is fitting for a fiver. Top stuff! Film crew came to the Chaplaincy to interview the vicar of Llanfair PG when Mabel Leysham was murdered. Interesting to see the enormous amount of lighting, reflectors and other kit they used, but a shame about the circumstances. Photographed kit I'm trying to sell with Sandra's digital camera. Lovely sunny day, took piccies on Mount Stella. Very pleasant. Did a small anti-war protest outside BBC Bangor. Only about 30 people. Filmed a little bit though, but don't think it went out on the telly.The Rowing Club did a charity 'Row across the Channel and Back' thing tonight. I didn't row, but watched and supported. Raised over £50 for Comic Relief!
     

    
</post>

<date>12,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Did go to circuits, first time in a while. Was a little dull, but it picked up - some games and stuff! And the stretching was relaxing. Gave two girls a lift home, one of whol I like the look of. Annoying, that very night, she'd been asked out for a drink by Tom. Grrr. And they went to the Greek, the best pub in Bangor. Grrrrrrrrr! Oh well. Oh and Ulrika was voted out of Fame Acadamey. Grrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr!!!  Today, read lots of interesting sports science on an excellent website. Off to fit new brake pads now.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Last night I watched Buzzcocks/Shooting Stars, then jogged to the Fridd PC room. It was almost empty, except for - can you believe it - Sarah, and two new friends of hers. When they logged off I actually sneaked outside before they could see me - didn't want to be seen as some Billy No Mates! But then I felt ashamed - usually I never worry about what others think. So I went back in and stood - well, sat - my ground. Later on I watched Fame Academy - great! - and then let Sasha have a roll about in his ball. He was vey energetic last night! He had a good roll around in the chapel, before I put him back in his cage and went to be myself. I could hear him running on his wheel for ages!  I'm very happy today - went to the little old Mike's Bikes shop in Upper Bangor, and managed to find a pair of cartridge brake pads to go with the Avids. Excellent! Had a hair cut too, and nice chat with the hairdresser. 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Sunday, Sunday, Sunday... just trying to remember...  Um, morning in bed, watched GP (suprisingly good!), walk to PC room, play with hamster, watch 24. A nice quiet 'recharge batteries' type weekend. And it was raining an awful lot outside.  Today, well, weights session this morning, walked to Halfords and looked at bike brakes, came back via another bike shop where I bought a quality Avid Rim Wrangler pad set (but only one, still need something for the back, and it was ten quid, boo), bumped into Little Louise and chatted for a half hour or so, then went to PC room.  Oh, the excitement!
     

    
</post>

<date>07,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Today's been a bit crap... didn't go to bed until past 4am (can't actually remember why), and didn't wake up until 10.20am. Went down to get some milk from the kitchen and ended up chatting to Will, Debbie and Emma for a while, and also stroked Sannai and was given some Christmas pud by Will (yummy!). It's been raining all day and it felt very cozy. I like rainy days... when it's sunny, you sort of feel under pressure to go out, but on days like this you can contentedly stay inside and potter about, or just watch the rain. But after breakfast at, er, midday, I feel asleep unti 4pm, then listened to Chris Moyles, ate some biscuits, and came here. Yay.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      First, what happened last night.  Only Helen, Carina Andy and I went, so I was worried I'd get bored(!). As it was the first how was a little boring, with me and Andy just wondering around looking at the pictures and things. There was absolutley *no-one* in the place - there was a public meeting on about the proposed marina development in Beaumaris that evening, so it wasn't suprising. After a while, we decided to round the local bars to try a get some custom. The management dropped the entry price to a fiver, which is much more reasonable. About a dozen people turned up after ten, and the night picked up then. Helen and Andy did some dancing, and, as ever, were very good. I had a nice chat with Carina on the sofa, and chatted to the manager a bit too.It isn't being the success they hoped, but it's early days yet.  Today, I woke up at about 8am, had breakfast, felt sleepy so slept until noon! I'd vaguely heard the phone ringing and looking at noon saw it was Helen, and gave her a ring. She was on the train to Llandudno! She'd been by Impact this morning with the offer of some work at a conference at a hotel after the original model was taken ill, and naturally Helen jumped at the chance - just the break she's looking for, and so soon! Trust me to miss out! Well, I stopped thinking that way pretty quickly. I'm so lucky to know Helen anyway! It was a lovely day, so I decided to finally get out and ride the Marin Trail. It was great - tricky and tough. But rather long. I cut it short, and rang Helen to see if she wanted a lift home as I was near(ish) by. She did, but I had an hour spare. I found the proper start of the trail, and on the map board saw I'd missed some of the best single-track towards the end. I decided to ride up it (very difficult) and then ride it down again! Great fun, but when I reached the car, I saw I'd only 15mins to reach Helen now. Oops! Was 15mins late getting to her, and just as I reached the station (our arranged meeting point), a drunk woman collapsed in the road in front of my car. Well, I guessed she was drunk, but with my sense of smell couldn't tell! But Helen smelt it straight away. She only lived around the corner, so I drove her home.  We spent a while wondering around Llandudno looking for a belt Helen had lost (belonging to Carina!), then I talked her into going to McDs. She only had a chicken sandwhich - she doesn't go there often at all. Driving home we had a light-hearted arguement about girls and boys and the attraction between them. Suspect that with her, much like with Hazel, sex appeal is the main thing.  After a nice bath and a trip down the pc room to update The Horse's Mouth, I was having a nice hot chocolate when Ruth texted saying I'd had a tiff with Helen! I'd had nothing of the sort! I went round to Helen (as I'd planned) to give her her the PowerPoint posters of her, and give her hamster carry box. She answered the door with no trousers on and panty-liners hanging out (er, nice). I kept her company while she packed (she asked me to). All seemed fine! Hamsters were great to play with, though Poofus had eaten a Gap sweater and a £70 pair of jeans, though they can be 'fashionably' patched.  Went round to Ruths after Helen went to bed (she has a test first thing tomorrow). Just not the same - hate to say it, but I simply much prefer the company of Helen. She's great! Going to miss her until she comes back next Wednesday.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Went to see Two Weeks Notice with Helen and Carina last night. Good film. Afterwards I let them use my bodyfat scales, which then made Helen (predictably) think she's fat, when she's anything but. However, on the way out of the Chaplaincy, we bumped into Said. Said made an off-the-cuff little speech that really put Helen's mind at rest, all about how she celebrate her plus points and not worry about her (non-existent) bad ones. Said was superb. I wish I could say stuff like that!!  Earlier on I'd been accused of mixing up the baby hamsters, resulting in Rascal getting pregnant! But there's no way I did it. I was very careful to avoid just that, and I never even took Timothy (the other black one) out his cage! So I have no idea how they ended up mixed up.  Otherwise, felt rather ill again yesterday, and slept for a lot of it. Again.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Had a bit o' fun yesterday afternoon. As I left the library I noticed it was five pm - just the time Helen finishes in the chippy in Beaumaris. I thought I'd drive over and suprise her - otherwise it takes her about an hour on the bus to get home. So I did. But I didn't know when she finishes or where exactly she works, but as Beaumaris is quite small I thought I'd give it a shot - well, it was a challenge! I parked opposite the bus stop on the main street. I didn't want to just sit there like a lemon, so I planned on waiting for only two songs on the Top 40. Just as the second song was ending, lo and behold, Helen appears! But she goes into the Spar shop. At this point I notice a Rolls-Royce parked in front, and a plan forms...  Quickly parking the car round a corner, I run back and wait opposite the Spar, behind the Roller. The plan is to wait for Helen to come out, quickly run round the front of the Roller, sit on it and ask 'wanna a ride home?', a la the Toyota Corolla adverts. However, the local lads are all hanging around on their FS Saracens outside the Spar, and soon notice me. At one point I thik I see Helen paying at the counter, so I sit on the bonnet of the Rolls. Minutes tick by. Helen doesn't emerge. Soon, one of the lads rides over and starts trying to poke fun at me. However he is exceptionally dim so it's not much of a challenge to rebuff him. He asks my name. 'Bob', I reply. What a dumbass. He thinks I fancy the girl who works in the Spar! I go back to leaning on the wall after he buggers off. Then one their older mates putters across on his moped, and asks if I've a problem. After asking him to repeat several times because his helmet is muffling, I inform him 'no, not at all', which leaves him rather flummoxed. He leaves too. After a while, the boys get bored and ride off. Thank god for that.  Anyway, I'm beginning to think the Spar has a second door I haven't spotted, so walk up a bit to see if I can spot Helen - she's reading the mags, naughty girl! Then it occurs to me that being a Sunday and all, the buses don't come very often and she's probably just killing time. I'd stil like to do my joke if I can though, so I crossed over to the bus stop. I can just read it without going in front of the Spar - next bus isn't for a half an hour! Then, because 'm so nice, I decide to creep on her inside the shop and make her jump. Just as I get to the entrance she turns round and come out. Cue me hidind behind a big column in the entrance, and walking round one side of it as Helen goes round the other! Then I creeep up to her at the bus stop - don't half make her jump! She's over the moon to see me! She's very tired - she worked at the chippy all Sunday and Saturday, then worked the bar in Verdis in the evening, so she's very glad of the lift. We agree to go running later.  When I came round to go for a run an hour later, she'd fallen asleep! She's very determined though - she got up and got changed (with me in the room! - but I didn't see any more than what I saw lat Wednesday, so it's hardly a big deal). We had a long run - 45mins - and my knee was agonising for the second half. It's a real shame - I love running with Helen and she loves coming with me. The pain stops as soon as I stop running and today it barely hurts at all, so I'll just grin and bear it for now. Don't think I can keep it up for long though. In the evening I watched 24 - superb - then went to PC room using Sandra's card, and surfed for MP3 proggies.  Today was a bit of a disaster - been very lazy. Spent the moring in bed fiddling around with CD rippers - few of them worked :(, but now I've got a good system to make MP3s with. Didn't even have breakfast until 11 - how lazy is that?? Napped and read (3001 - finished it) until about three, when I forced myself out of a kind of shame to get up. Went for a walk and saw the ponies in the field. Then cut the walk short after the ponies slobbered all over me to go home and clean it off :), then came down to the library, where I'm writing this (very long) entry.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Disaster - Bikemagic is down! What will I surf aimlessly for hours now?  Beautiful day weather-wise today. But the most exciting thing I did is buy a hamster cage and all the bits ready for me to have my own hammy! Came to £37 :( money I haven't got, but I want a hamster so much! Petsathome is such a cool store. Also got my laptop ripping ultra high quality MP3s - only takes a mere five hours per CD! - and printed out a lot of Helen's photo shoot on the colour printer. Looks good!
     

    
</post>

<date>01,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Today, I have mostly been, asleep.  Apart from giving the incredibly cute hamsters back :(  Got job application in on time yesterday. Fingers crossed. I feel I gave it my best shot.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      So many things have happened since I last posted! There was the Rumi magic concert, the chaplaincy bbq, and then this last week the picnic to the woods with the big rope swing and then our trip to Sea Zoo with Joanna, Gareth and Sandra, followed by that late night when it was hot. But now I'm home in Reading visiting my folks, and missing Sandra and Sasha my hamster like hell. I'm here for a few days, then I'm supposed to be going to Bournemouth to visit Ruth, before returning to Bangor on the 28th. But I desperately want to return to Bangor before then. I guess I have to go to Ruth's though, I've said I will and I've got some of her stuff, plus I'm giving her a lift back! Maybe I can get her to come back a little earlier though. Sandra leaves for Germany on June 6; so little time left. As it is, I hate it here in Reading, after Bangor it's big and scary. I'm afraid to go out the garden gate!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Bought a digital camera today! A Nikon Coolpix 2500, for just £150, from Currys. PC World nearly had me going all the way to Chester in search of the offer, until I remembered that PCW and Currys are part of the same company!  Also been spring cleaning the last few days. Cleared & cleared the area outside my room, and burnt (cool fire!) the boxes in the corridor.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Filling in a few blanks   Posted retrospectively, in June 2004...  I actually had a really good time good time down in Bournemouth, and was sorry to leave. (Highlights including sleeping in a campervan on their drive, going bowling, a top walk along the coast a day-trip with the whole of Ruth's family to a grand mansion house!) Back in Bangor I never really saw that much of Sandra again. She went back to Germany in June (a long haul back - her parents came to pick her up in their campervan!). I remember taking Joanna to dinner to the pub on Anglesey opposite the pier, before going on to Penmon Point. A fablous evening. I gave Sasha to Joanne to look after as she loved him so much too. He died in the night of 16 December 2003, and is buried at the foot of Bangor Mountain. I miss the little fella.  Around April 2004 I returned to Bangor for a few days staying with Ruth. The highlight of that trip was an evening with Joanna, again. We had a real heart-to-heart and with her input, came away knowing myself a lot better than I had before. (Other trip highlights include spending a whole afternoon just lazing in the sun on Roman Camp, a ride around Gwydyr, this time on my new suspension bike :)
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       lol I'm going 24hr racing!   There have been many teams wanting last-minute team-mates for  urlLink SSMM , a 24hr mountain bike relay race. A bit last-minute, but I couldn't resist. The closer was that the team who asked me are from the same triathlon club that one of the girls on the personal trainer course is also in!
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       lol I'm going 24hr racing!   There have been many teams wanting last-minute team-mates for  urlLink SSMM , a 24hr mountain bike relay race. A bit last-minute, but I couldn't resist. The closer was that the team who asked me are from the same triathlon club that one of the girls on the personal trainer course is also in!
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Why can't people accept success?    urlLink Someone's out to knock Lance Armstrong again , despite a total lack of evidence. Why do people feel compelled to do this? Are they jealous of success? What's the point of that. Lance was born with the gifts that he has - all of them, the physical abilities and the mental reserves he uses to tap those abilities. Pure luck.  For all but a tiny number of people, there's always going to be someone faster, fitter, cleverer, more successful. Don't let that stop you from trying to Be All You Can Be (copyright US Army, lol), but don't let it turn into something as negative as the need to always to try to knock those better than you.  Here endeth the Sermon ;)
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       What is it with   refs and umpires tonight? One made  urlLink one of the worst mistakes I've ever seen , while another looked like he  urlLink couldn't handle the pressure,  disallowing a fine goal.  With the England vs Portugal match, well, being honest, Portugal deserved the win, and they won even despite a dodgy decision. Good for them. However Sprem won with the assistance of the umpire's mistake. A shame; I feel she could've won fair and square.   Venus, by the way, really didn't seem to mind the mistake, or the loss altogether. Her calmness is a remarkable feature - she can keep her cool under pressure like no other. But on the other hand, she now lacks any sign of drive - she still plays with great skill, but has no hunger to win.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Yay!   Brake cable sets don't have outers long enough for disc brakes, do they? I didn't know that until five minutes ago. But I just cannabalised the outer from the Deore lever set and hoo-ray, powerful, reliable braking!  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       'ave it!!   Yeah! Royal Fail were one day late but never mind, I now have new Avid disc brakes, 185mm front and rear! Terrific! Not being hydraulic means no pupmp-up, no fade and nothing to leak. They just work. Only got to fit them now - how hard can that be?  Tell one thing though - I nearly fainted when I unwrapped the parcel. They came in a Hope Mini Mono box...
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       6pm in June   and we have to have the house lights on! On the otherhand, the garden needs it, the trails need damping down and hopefully now we won't have hosepipe bans later in the summer.  Personally, I love Wimbledon when it  urlLink rains . The BBC put some fascinating stuff on looking in and around the All England Club and its history to fill the time.  However one day this will be a thing of the past, as  urlLink Centre Court is to get a roof  in 2009. I don't think I'll mind too much :)
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I complained about the BBC - and won   Last September I saw a horrible news item (not in itself a problem), but I think the BBC mis-handled it badly. I felt strongly enough about it that I complained, to the BBC and also to the then Broadcasting Standards Commission.  The BBC replied first; oddly enough, they dismissed my complaint :). However, Ofcom (the organisation the old BSC morphed into)  urlLink disagreed and upheld my complaint ! Look for 'FINDING: BBC News, 2 September 2003, 22:00', near the bottom of the page.  This shows that if you feel strongly enough about something - complain. People are listening and, if it's justified, are ready to support you.   urlLink Complain to Ofcom    urlLink Complain to the BBC   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Bleep Test Two   Not far from me there's a short section of disused road in the countryside - about 30m long. Just right for doing a bleep test on, in fact :). I measured and chalked out a 20m course, then played the track I'd downloaded last week on my Minidisc. Last time, in London, I'd reached 10.8, but this time I only reached 9.7 before the first wave of nasuea. I'd also thought that my London result had been hampered by me chewing and ibuprofen ten minutes beforehand - leaving me feeling decidedly ill. Maybe it hadn't made that much difference after all.  I can think of a few reasons why I didn't do so well this week - I totally forgot to warm-up first, instead just going with the test (which starts at a very easy pace), and also I can still 'feel it' after weight-training yesterday. But I think the main reason I didn't do so well is that in London it was a proper test, with Caroline and several others, I'd been waiting a day to do it, and basically there was a lot of adrenaline in my system. That makes a big difference.  Today I rested until level ten started and then ran that, so I think I'll have had some training effect from doing it. It's hard on the body - acceleration, deceleration then a 180 degree turn; tough. I plan to do it at least twice more this week - then maybe I'll be able to pace Caroline next time we do it together ;). I think the key - at least for me - in this test is to resist the urge to be sick, and push on further. Challenging!
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Bye bye Forumulas - hello Avids   I've had enough of those old Formulas. Hopefully Windwave will refund me rather than replace. Whatever, I'm not using them again! Instead, I've ordered a bargain set of  urlLink Avid Mechanicals  - widely acknowledged to be among the most effective and reliable disc brakes. I ordered them from  urlLink Merlin , where my bike came from originally, in fact.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Into space - privately   I've known about the  urlLink X Prize  for years but never quite believed it would happen - someone would fly into space in a craft developed entirely privately. But  urlLink someone has . And they follow in the foot-steps of a  urlLink long list of other such pioneers . Great stuff.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       It's alright for some   I found out from Windwave - when someone finally answered the phone after five minutes of ringing - that their mechanic is on holiday, so my brakes won't be looked at until next week. Arse.  'suppose I could go for a ride and just drag my feet to stop. Or put a stick in the wheel. Or maybe not.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Back t'gym   Returned to Rivermead for the first time in five weeks today. Thank god, they've stopped playing MTV RnB (which just looped the same six songs over and over) for Q, which is mostly indie. Yay!  Made it at 11.59am, which is handy as it costs £1.80 from noon onwards :)  This is a different routine from my old 3x6 - quicker and, frankly, more enjoyable.   Squats  100kg 6 (well I just had to check I could still do it - felt good too!), 90kg 8   Wide-grip pull-ups  6,4   Db bench  18kg 11 (oops) 20kg 8   Db shoulder press  14kg 8   Cleans  3x3 30kg (that's a lot of threes)   Bent-over bbl rows  30kg 8   SLDLs * 60kg 8  A quick, effective whole-bod routine. I like :)  *Not sure if I should mention it, but when hurriedly loading the barbell for SLDLs, I idiotically hung 30kg on one side then took all the weights on the other end off - of course the bar flipped up tw@tting me in the face. Lesson learned!
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Zenith   A few minutes ago the sun reached the highest point it will rise to in the sky in 2004. I absolutely  nailed  home from the gym so I could be back in time to watch it outside with my radio-controlled clock in hand!  ...days getting shorter from now on...  ...not long to winter...  ;)
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       d'oh 2   A friend from my cycling club mailed me telling me what a great ride they'd had last Saturday. This was because at the monthly club meeting the week before I'd made the case for making the Saturday ride shorter and more fun-orieentated. I'm glad they have, but gutted to have missed it.  C'mon Windwave, fix my discs!
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       d'oh   Noticed at breakfast this morning that Shredded Wheat are supporting the  urlLink British Heart Foundation's  Big Red Fightback (which strangely isn't mentioned anywhere on the BHF's website) by putting tokens on the back of their cereal packets, which if you send in will lead to Nestle giving the BHF a £1 donation per token. Good stuff.  Unfortunately, there's also a the chance to win an instant prize with the packets - the chance to win a CAR, in fact...
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       ow   Just seen a replay on TV of  urlLink Ashia Hansen  tearing the tendons connecting her kneecap while triple jumping. As someone who's done something very similar I can concour that it HURTS LIKE ****!   Oh dear   We didn't do too well in the European Cup, the competition that Ashia was competing in when she was injured. The men's team were leading the competition after the first day but finished fourth after  urlLink one of the 4x400m runners tripped over his own leg .   Worse, the GB women's team have been relegated from the competition after finishing last, despite a few stellar performances including  urlLink Paula Radcliffe's 5,000m win .  
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Satellite   Every so often I have a peek at  urlLink this page , a weather satellite view of North East Africa, the Middle East and Southern Russia. All will be revealed ;)
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I'm now a gym instructor!   This past Thursday we had our practical gym instructor assessments, where we each had to teach an hour-long gym session one-to-one. We'd already had a theory paper - on which I'd scored 97%. For my practical I trained my sister, who'd never been in a gym before! Other people had helpers ranging from the occasional user to a personal trainer with five years experience! Using a newbie worked for me though - it allowed me to show off my teaching skills and was an insight into how unfit some people can be - I had my sis using level 0 on the stationary bike at one point - I didn't know it went that low :)  One thing I regret is how stressed I felt beforehand. I was in the second group to be assessed that morning so I chatted to the helper of another trainee while I was waiting. Towards the end of the hour she commented on how stressed I'd seemed first thing - talking nineteen-to-the-dozen - but I had calmed down a bit since. But I remember some other candidates - while maybe zoned - looking cool, and certainly not stressed. At uni - and since then - I'd become the same - calm and collected under stress. I  will  be again in future.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Always another way   I burnt Caroline (the Russian) a CD of the bleep test that I  urlLink downloaded  from the internet (and added a few choice songs too afterwards :) ). She was overjoyed when I gave it to her. We're going to use it to do our own bleep test in the sports hall when we're next in!
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       There is no spoon   A Russian on the course and I did the bleep test together earlier this week, but we both messed up, I made only 10.8 (for various reasons) and she 8.3. If it had gone smoothly she's have easily have beaten me but she had drunk too much water beforehand. She was pretty upset afterwards, as she really wanted to do it properly (she's in amazing physical shape). 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Personal Training   The course is held at the Central YMCA gym, just off Tottenham Court Road in London. The entire complex is underground housing a 25m pool, a 30m sports hall and lots of studios and classrooms. It's an amazing place and we have free run of it!  I commute by bike and train - cycle to the station in Reading, train to Paddington, then up Oxford Street duelling with the buses and taxis to CYMCA. A lot of fun! Probably only seven miles of cycling a day though. I'd make it longer but the days are so long - leave at 7.30am and lucky to be back by 7.30pm!  The course runs one week on, then one week off. Must be said, the off-weeks (when we don't go into London), are a little dull...  We've a great bunch of people on the course though. Couldn't ask for better! There's some 18 of us, roughly 50/50 boys and girls.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Time to say Hi again   I've been thinking about it for a while, and now I'm going to re-start my ol' blog!   First, I have to briefly bring you up to speed since my last post over a year ago. I stayed in Bangor job hunting until July 2003. I couldn't find a good job up there so eventually returned to Reading to work as a clerical assistant to the design department of  urlLink JET . It was an easy job, but a bit boring and certainly not going anywhere, so I went to work for  urlLink Momenta , working on an environmental issues helpline. Quite a good job and in the area I did my degree in, Environmental Science.  But after a couple of months I was made redundant :(. I had a wee think about what I really wanted to do and re-visited an idea I'd first had a year ago, while still in Bangor - training to become a personal trainer. With the help from some peeps from a forum I discovered  urlLink YMCAfit , and after a lot of thought started training with them mid-May and I'm now right in the thick of it! I should qualify sometime this autumn.   Sporty  wise I'm still happily mountain biking. I bought a cracking new bike last Autumn (which you can see on  urlLink my photo pages ) that's given me a lot of fun. I've been getting into cross-country racing this spring - a big buzz! Right now though, it's off the road as I've had to send the disc brakes back for repairs :(
     

    
</post>


</Blog>