<Blog>

<date>13,mars,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's ten to one here and I've just six hours of my Saturday night creating a layout for this bloody blog. No way in hell am I going to bed without posting atleast one rant to keep my fans content for the night.   So  urlLink  here's   something to wrap your meager little minds around. Oh and also  urlLink  this  . If you haven't heard of goatse man, well, I suggest you ask any younger to leave the room. Two links should be enough fresh content to keep the clones happy for the night. Time for some pepsi and sleep.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,mars,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tuesday at lunch time I received my 2 and a half month late birthday gift from my older sister who lives in Ontario. After serveral hours of attempting to install the new 7200 rpm 40 gig harddrive, i had ..er.. accidentally erased all my old data on my old hard drive, and still didnt manage to get the new one installed.  As a nasty side effect of loosing all my files, my music collection has been clipped some 200 and some odd files. 300 and some I had previously backed up to disk. Yesterday I was barely able to reinstall WinXP Pro and get back online, while I currently wait for my sister's roommate to drop me an email with instrucions on how to get the new hard drive in the right way.  My first exam starts in four days. Judging from the review the past week in class, I think I'll do farely well. Also, only 16 more days till my GameCube. Walmart is currently offering a deal where when you purchase a GameCube you receive a free 5 game demo disc; I hope this offer is available in my area. Its 12:51 (pm) here so I think I should get some sleep. I still have some more computer related setting up to do tomorrow.   This is where you stop reading. 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,mars,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      After two or so hours and a failed attempt of taking a shoutbox and some scripting savvy and making a personal blog engine, I decided it's probably best if I remain with  urlLink  Blogger   for the time being. Maybe if I get around to learning more php by the summers end I'll have another go at it, but as for right now, I can't be bothered.  After seeing it last night and it now being featured on  urlLink  Slashdot  ,  urlLink  TheOneRing.net   has a quicktime  urlLink  videoclip   of Gollum and Andy Serkis (actor who played physical gollum during filming) acceptance speech at the MTV Video Awards last night. I'm going to have to agree with slashdot on "No joking, this is probably the funniest acceptance speech I have ever seen."  Exams start next week and I am no whre near ready. I write math Monday, followed by science on Tuesday, English on Wednesday, and finally biology on Thursday. As an upside to all the blasted cramming I'll have to endur over the next week, I'm now glad to report I'll be receiving a GameCube for my gradding gift.   I've opted for the Wind Waker package versus the Mario Sunshine bundle. Many people were quick to judge the new look of Zelda as childish and ugly, but if Windwaker is able to live up to the quality of previous Zelda games, it will be a smash despite the new cell shadding type graphics. Enter the Matrix currently tops the list of planned games to purchase for the soon to be aquired Gamecube. I can not overly stress how much this game rocks my face.  Alright I'm done ranting.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,mars,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hot. Its way too hot. At least 100, and thats celcius. Im having a hard time just sitting here without passing out, but I'll survive.  Last exam over and done with today. All together 8 pages of biology. I thought it was gonna shaft me like my science, so I took half an hour last night to go over my outline and do a little review. All and all I think I did ok, finishing up in the normal hour and a half; guess I have to wait till grading now too see how much the review really paid off.  Once again its way too hot. Enough of this drunkey monkey hoo haw.  Sitting on a cornflake.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,mars,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alright harddrive update. Thanks graciously to the very skilled people in #windows95 on DALnet, I was able to sort out my problems and have my new 40gig drive up and running as a slave drive. I would have liked to get it as master and move my files over to it, using my old 8gig for music stoarge, but one thing at a time.  I just finshed writing my English exams just over 40 minutes ago, I think I actually did well. Considering how much I choked on my science on tuesday, I hope to woo my parents with a uplifted enlish mark to help secure my Game Cube.   Speaking of which, only 10 more days till I get it. I've been doing some handiwork here and there lately, so I'm happy to have nearly enough money to buy the Matrix Reloaded when I do get the Game Cube. First things first though, Windwaker has to be beaten. And for that to happen i'll be needing a memory card so I guess I'll have to dip into my matrix money. Not to mention my girlfriend's prom next week, so theres another slice of the pie gone. Oh well hopefully I'll have it all sorted out by July. Dam these western sandwiches are good.   Anyway back to mp3 whoring, so far 40 of my 200 deleted songs are back... oh the joys of 56k.  I stop typing. You stop reading.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,mars,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh bother, I just remembered something; I forgot to announce to the masses that I completed Wind Waker. Well not so much as completed, as I did finish the main quest. Kudos to sreid for navigating the last stretch before I took a break from packing to deliver the end blow.   The finishing cinematics are really something, much better then Orcarina of Time or Manjora's Mask, and the fact that you start a new quest after first beating the game. Nothing amazingly new in the second quest, mostly just change of clothing for characters, start of with the delux pictograph, and you gain the ability to read Hylian, but a nice little addon none the less. So all thats left now is the collection of side quest items, heart pieces and whatnot, and it will be another Zelda game behind me. I shant think I'll grow as bored with this one quite as quickly I did the others, the game is simply to large.  One peeve however is seems to lack the number of enjoyable minigames that were tucked in with previous Zelda versions. Wind Waker does feature serveral games in it, but none as addictive as ones in Orcarina of Time and the dark world shooting gallery in Link to the Past. What the game lacks in mini games it more then makes up for in side quests to keep the player content and involved with the game, which is always nice to see.  Now as Wind Waker fades into memory a new choice is presented: Enter the Matrix... yes or no. A month ago I would have clubbed myself like a baby seal if I would have considered no as an option, but after rewatching the Metriod Prime movie clips on the bonus disc, and checking out other games now out for the GameCube, I'm starting to question if I really feel like completeing a game with the style and size of Enter the Matrix. By the end of this week I'll have enough money to purchase it, so I supose the descision will be made then.  Thats about it I supose; as it will be a very boring and uneventful night as most of the chatters have gone to the grad party. *sigh* whats a poor nerd to do? Eat, yes eat. Left over pizza... exelent. Oh I managed to catch the end of Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles the movie last night, it brought back some very fond childhood memories.  Cowabunga. Hahaha, I made a funny!
     

    
</post>

<date>13,mars,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmm blogger got a new layout while I was gone, nice. Anyway, back after 3 days, and my headache is finally leaving so its all good. My little trip rocked the perverbial face.   First, prom. Nothing exciting to mention there, as most of the grads headed off to my cousins early to the party, leaving myself and my girlfriend, along with about 10 other stranglers behind. The party after the prom, that was good. Not gonna blurb about details that noone will read anyway, but I did wake up after 2 hours of sleep to find myself in a very cold and hard bottomed tent. The liquid refreshments from the night before made up for the pains the next day.  Today I had the pleasure of a pounding headache following me around, but a sinutab on the drive back home is finally putting that dog to sleep. All thats left now is a 8am wake up for grading day. Ugh, not looking forward to that. Not because of the grades, but because for some stupid reason they plopped grading day on a saturday this year. All I can say is: what. the. shit.  Nuts to your blinces, I'm going to bed.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,mars,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ooo, look at me! I'm Mr. Happy Man, I like to make people happy! And I live on a gum drop house on loly-pop laaaane!  No, not really. Actually im exhausted; 8 hours of Wind Waker will do that to a person. I swear the thing has a center of pure heroin wrapped in a delicious chocolate coating. Its addictive and I need help. Please, for the love of god save me from my wonderful new toy. Oh well, a fool and his gamecube are soon parted, and rightfully so. A three day break from the magical black box tomorrow for my cousins graduation and some visiting, then back home friday night for grading day marks the next day. Enough about me though, hows things with you? Dog still alive? Kids still not getting the fuck of your lawn? Yeah I know, same ol same ol.  ...but what aboot second breakfast? 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,mars,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Whoa buddy, lets settle it down there scholars. No, no lets not.  Friday night I had to work, just moving and setting up sound equipment. No big deal but I didnt get home till 4 in the morning so I'm still exhausted, 4 and a half hours sleep tends to do that to you, but money is money, and I'm glad I had it. I say had because yesterday I got a pleasent little surprise when I got my gamecube a week early. Unfortunatly the save card and players guide for Wind Waker came to 52 bucks, so my money left me as quickly as it came.  Now for my official game review deal.  Anything bad said about the graphic style of Zelda Wind Waker can go burn itself. The new cell shaded style the producer implemented fits perfectly for the game, in addition to the sound, which is also phenominal. Im not even a forth of the way through the mian quest and I can tell already the development team really went all out for detail and game immersion. The environments are massive, and completly interactive while the AI is far more diverse then previous games. Another improvement is player control, adding the ability to crouch and crawl, along with "sidle" along narow ledges. Swordplay is also more advanced, more varying attack combinations make for more energetic fight scenes.  I could go on but there is so much more ot the game then I feel like typing out. I highly recomend everyone with a gamecube to go out and buy this game. Those without gamecubes should buy one just for the fact of getting this game. This game gets my personal best of 10 thumbs up, along with super fantastico rocking my face award.  ...Seek... help.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,mars,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Maybe inspiration wasnt as hard to find as I previously thought. So this is the new layout, I might tweak some alignment here and there, but I'm pretty happy with the look as a whole now. I orginally planned some over lapping images, but I changed my mind and realized the whole process of uploading images to a free host and stuff would have been just a hassel. So yeah, how about those pirates.  Well thats basically all I had to blog. My main rant I already did for today, so unless I end up doing something worth mention, or get bored again, I guess this is it.  Fuck fuck, mother mother fuck.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,mars,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I mean whos dick do I have to suck to get some explosions around here. I'll correct myself right now about the previously mentioned "Blogs of Interest" as they are actually titled "Blogs of Note". Grammatical error or not, I still hate the idea of them like a fat kid hates celery.  Now living in a time where even Joe Shmoe can post his ideas and thoughts to the world via such resources as the internet, I think the idea of raising a few such blogs into the spotlight to be shown as more important or more relivant then others is remarkably stupid. Who are a few such clones to deem that one persons life be more wrothy then an others, or claim that since one blogger says something a little differently, covers things a little diffently, or lives life a little differently, that it is a amazing development.  And maybe I'm wrong, maybe I myself am over-emphasizing, but the fact remains that there is nothing more special about one blog then another. Well, besides this one, but thats heartless spam of course. Just felt like getting it off my chest. Maybe if I can get some traffic and actually post some content that the masses deem entertaining I'll gain the goody goody gosh status of being on the front page with 8 other "Blog of Note". But for that I might actually have to do the layout I've been seeking inspiration over.  Jesus people suck.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,mars,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Didn't blog lately, because frankly, nothin happened. sreid got his NBA Street Volume 2 which inheirently rocks our faces, and we've been trying to school each other in that the past few days. Breagh came over today, so I've been in a pretty good mood since.  Me and sreid decided to walk to town today and see what was good at the theatres. We made it in there in about an hour and a half, which we thought was a pretty good time. Bought tickets to see The Hulk but then changed our minds and opted for Terminator 3: Rise of the Machines. It was a good action movie all and all. Lots of explosions, hot chick, all the good stuff. The only downside was certain plot twists where you really had to understand the first two movies or have been following along intentivly to really understand it.   Anyway that was cool and I got home round ten to twelve and decided to browse a little before I get some much needed sleep, lord knows I need it after the walk to the movies. Fuck fuck mother mother fuck its warm in here, another nights above the blankets I supose. It is summer but I hate when I end up kicking the sheets off halfway through the night only to be woken up an hour later when the temperature drops and try and remake my bed while in it.   Incase you didn't notice (which the few of you who read the blog probably did't), I added a hit counter at the top of the page to keep track of how many people I've actually managed to woo to my site. I just stuck it up there for now until I do a remake of the blog layout and find a better spot to put it. In the meantime be sure to spam out http://debian.blogspot.com to all your little friends.  > *sniff* *sniff* > DEFENCE! HOO HOO! DENFENCE!
     

    
</post>

<date>13,mars,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Canada Day! Bah, who really cares. Me and sreid played some 007 and went to Don Cherries for his birthday supper; the steak there was delicious. After coming home and reading about 50 different blogs I decided to really put some personal content up on the site and hopefully get more people interested in reading it more frequently.  Right now however it's 1:38am and I don't have the slightest of energy to start redoing a blog template. Not to mention I have to be up to mow grass tomorrow and spend no doubt several hours infront of the GameCube playing sreid's yet to be aquired NBA Street Volume 2. For the moment I'll be content if I can get some pepsi and about 10 hours sleep.  > The winking pirate. > Weeooo! Weeooo! We got paint! > I hid the other 3 in the mushroom soup.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,mars,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      One of the better Mondays I've had in quite a while. The morning was spent idling somewhat bordishly (if that IS even a word) on the net, then after lunch me and sreid headed to his house to burn some music. A few hours later my music collection goes from 450 to almost 1100 songs now. Oh but shhh, dont let the RIAA find out. While burning he and I set about completing more of his recently aquired Mario Sunshine for his new GameCube, and when burning completed we opted for a trip to subway where I selfishly delved into my Matrix money to keep my stomach content. We tried renting NBA Street Volume from the video store, but aparently there was a lock on his name, so we eventually ended in town and him getting 007 Agent Under Fire for his grading gift, or was his birthday gift, I dont know.  The game plays well and there are plenty of options to customize gameplay. We only played the multiplayer mode, but I expect the missions to be weel constructed too. I was glad to see the presence of AI bots in multiplayer mode, it really helps boost game value when you want to play a little skrimich but dont want to have to rely on a second human player for an opponent. I'll cut my review short there as I'm in the mood for a rant, bare with me.  If any of you little people out there reading this are also bloggers, and have browsed the random blog list on the main page of blogger.com, you have no doubt seen the Blogs Of Interest blogs listed there. Now correct me if I'm wrong, but when I see a list of blogs titled "Blogs Of Interest", one would come to the reasonable conclusion that these blogs would be interesting; they would be different, they would be something that I could enjoy to read each time they're updated. They lie! Now I'm not saying my blog should be put on this list, I'm not jealous or any close proximity by any sence, but I see nothing extra special about the serveral blogs I have looked over in the list. Call me a ass for thinking so, but I really think whoever decided these blogs were special, has some creativity issues.  Now I dont know if there is supose to be any certain honor amongst bloggers or what have you, but I feel like I have the right assigned to me by the wonderful freedom of speech to lay a royal smackdown on Matrix Essays in particular. I myself am a huge fan of the matrix, seen the movies, quote the lines regularly, bend spoons and dodge bullets on occation, but this blog, is uber poopoo. Thats right, Ive had to lower myself to the level of calling things "uber poopoo" to describe this blog. I've thought about the ideas the matrix represents, the messages it can convey under the actual screenplay, and the intellectual stimulus it can provide if really thought out, but this site takes it way too far. Explaining unforseen events by reasonable doubt is fine, but I think people who take the Matrix and bend it into the bloody bible of their life is truely pathetic in my views.  I didnt see anyone taking a copy of Ace Ventura and study it trying to derive connections to every possible segment of religion, humanity, and social issues. I know the movies have little to no similiarities, but thats what they still remain to be, movies. The matrix is a freaking movie, not some blasted 8th wonder of the world. It doesnt hold the meaning of life, a prophacy of things to come, or the Carmilk secret. Its a entertainment medium, end of story. Stop trying to pick it apart and guess what each and every frame of the movie conveys, and enjoy it for what it is, a well writen and well directed peice of flim. Neos, Trinitys, Morpheus', Oracles of the net, do me and many other people a favor:  Shut the fuck up.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,mars,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Not a bad bit of HTML if I do say so myself. Yup I finally gathered enough energy to complete a whole new layout. The layout itself is baised off an already made template at  urlLink http://www.1greeneye.net/ , however the one you see before you was hand coded, and my bets are if you look at their source code, its a hell of alot cleaner. But I mean, hey its a lazy Sunday night, so what else is there to do for those of us with no life. Thats right, twiddle our thumbs and hum hillbilly tunes to our keyboard.  Alright I could have sworn I mentioned in my last blog that I was going to the beach today, but I guess not. So I caught a little sand and surf. Well actually I caught alot of sun, and now the burn on my back prooves it. I'll be a nice brown by tomorrow, but I ended heading for the water before I roasted the front side of me, so I guess I'll be tan on one side, albino on the other. Dam sunbruns sure do make you thirsty.  Still no decission on Enter the Matrix yet, but I'm leaning towards it right now. I just wanna figure out if the two disks are for seperate missions or just one long continuous gameplay. I'm hoping each disk represents a character. Ive played as the man, but I want to see how or if Niobe is any different. I've seen the previews so I know you get to play as her on atleast on mission, but the possibility of two different story lines you could follow is just a hope I dont want to let go of.   Driving in my big blue truck.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,mars,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I neglected to blog yesterday, so I figure I might as well do it now.  Last night me and sreid walked to and from the movies. It took about a hour and 15 both ways, and I wasnt really tired from it I'm happy so say. We seen The Hulk, right now my opinion of it is pretty iffy. It was long, which was good, but too much of it seemed like useless story line trying to explain things. Despite bad reviews due to CG, the hulk himself seemed very natural. The action sequences in the movie were well done and I'm glad to say the acting wasn't as terrible as I thought it might be.  Breagh came over today, it was a great time, after some stuff the las tfew days the visit really helped things. Right now I'm getting ready to fetch another snack, and watching some movie with Jennifer Anniston. Dam shes mint. Anyway enough of this.  My raisin russian queen. And me, the super evil genious. Muwah, dam those fat kids.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,mars,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alright so I opted for sleep over editing the layout, like it matters.  I can't feel my arms; alright; I can barely feel my arms, my neighbour's lawn mower is too freaking heavy. Its like pushing around a wheel-barrow full of fat kids, and we all know how dam heavy fat kids tend to be. But I'm glad to say I'm 20 dollars richer for having done it, money which could be going towards a new game seings as how I now have around 70 some odd dollars. However since I am planning on a little trip next week I think the game shall have to wait, for how long I don't know.  And that's my cue to exit. I'll probably be blogging again when I get home tonight, for those of you who care. There are people who care right? Right?  Mommy?
     

    
</post>

<date>13,mars,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So yeah, more mods to be made on the layout, but definatly not another night up till 2 in the morning doing so. Blogger seems to be hopping back and forth putting new blogs in the blogs of note section; why don't they just make up there mind.  Anyways it seemed like a very short day today. Got up at 12:30, had breakfast, net, ect. Went down sreid's and played some NBA Street Volume 2 for a while, then came back here and did the same. Right now I'm more then a little bored and enjoying some very "educational" television. Oh well, I guess I'll edit the layout.  Now listen meow.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,mars,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Too tired to type. New layout. See you in the morning.  Irish.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,mars,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Added a shoutbox instead of my bio, which will go.. somewhere. Mowed a lawn, made some money, off to spend it.   Thankyou, thankyou, goto hell.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,mars,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pretty spiffy if I do say so. Another layout done and I think it looks good. I'll redo and add my bio to the whitespace on the right later on, right now I'm happy just to look at my finished work.  Oh and until I add it to the links collum, you should click  urlLink here . This has to be one of my all time favorite sites concerning people and things getting flamed. Maddox, you rookass.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,mars,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm back from my break. Actually I was back this afternoon but couldn't be bothered to blog. It was a good little trip all in all. Spent Monday evening at Breagh's; then Tuesday and Wednesday we hung out at the Marina with the peoples and her her house come the later hours.  I was planning to be home by tomorrow morning but Breagh was going to the mall today so I figured I might as well join her and get dropped off at the ol homestead on her way back. She got some clothes and things and we browsed the stores for a while then had some Burger King for lunch. She wasn't feeling to great so she stopped in at my place for a bit and had some Advil and rest. Now shes back home and I miss her already.  .  I got another layout coming along. I'm thinking I should begin saving my old ones to offer as templates. Which reminds me. I was offered a position as a html coder at  urlLink http://www.inxstudios.com  before I left the other day. Its a new site featuring graphic design and webpage development it seems. I met the creator of the site a while back, he saw my site layouts lately and was interested in me coding templates to be sold, so I guess I'll be doing that soon enough.  Tenacious D is good. Really really good. You should download pirated music of their recordings. I like short sentences. Hell. O.  Down. Syndrome. :(
     

    
</post>

<date>13,mars,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Haven't blogged in hmm, 6 days is it? Why? You know why, nothing has happened, obviously. I can't even recall any worthwhile events the last 6 days to use as filler... dam. Oh, Breagh came over yesterday, its all good. Other than that its been a pretty anti-social week, however I did wander out this evening to whoop sreid in a game of pool volleyball, go me ;D.   I hate those messenger spam messages. I'll offer several lines of glory and praise to the one who brings me the head of the fucktard who thought that Windows built in spam option was a good idea.  I'm really hungry right now, so I guess I'll loot the fridge. Jesus sunlight makes me tired.  Congradulations! ...       Your an idiot!
     

    
</post>

<date>13,mars,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Read  urlLink this . If you don't, your a evil terrorist bent on killing innocent Americans. Just read the articles, you'll get it.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,mars,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      That would make today, Sunday, right? Right.   So I embarked on a interesting little journey this weekend, start learning Visual Basic. Why? I have no clue. Outcome: it has since been deleted. Since then however I've nominated Perl to take its place. Try and learn Perl instead of VB? Yes its quite mad, I assure you, I'm very insane.  So hungry, so very dam hungry. Since I had to fend for myself yesterday with my parents gone to some dinner thing, I end up eating all the normal food in the house. Where does that leave me now? Hungry and unpleasent.  Oh and lets not forget about this little creation  urlLink clicky .  Shwing.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,mars,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well i have found a solution to the problem of integrating a biography or about section of myself onto my website; move  the personal stuff to blogger. hence i have divided #! /bin/debian into two distinct sections.   the first of which is here; by back from the dead blogger account which i have not actively used since last summer. this will give me a chance to post the more blog-ish type events which i feel like talking about, as well as being a page more devoted to myself as oppose to my other interests. think of this site as just one big about page section for my site.  the other half of #! /bin/debian would be the site currently residing on  urlLink http://debian.recile.net , which will serve as a somewhat e/n webpage to my multiple nerd interests, as well as any tidbits i feel like posting. it will cover the more public and external portions of my site, while this, the blogger, will cover the internal.  i still have work to do to the debian.recile.net site to remove sections of my bio and whatnot and redirect about links to this domain, as well as make a semi-official post like this one to give people the 411 on the existance of my blog.  hopefully this seperation of personal from public irected content will help me devlope debian.recile.net more while still providing me with a station for blogging which i orginally wanted. in the beginning all i wanted was a single personal webpage; but trying to mix content about myself as well as content relating to what im interested in wasnt as easy as i planned, and its so much more simpler to have individual sites for it now.  anyway i better get dressed or something. breaghs coming over later to visit; so i guess she gets to finally meet my sister. see how that turns out.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,mars,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      omfg  .. MORE LIKE DOUCHE-FIRE.. ahhhh THERMODYNAMCILA
     

    
</post>


</Blog>