<Blog>

<date>31,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       ...I feel sleepy...   I have to get to sleep earlier. I did las tnight, but I keep waking up really late. Okay, so I bought a laptop! I've been thinking about it for the last three days and whether I needed one or not. While I don't code anymore, I'd really like to learn again and a laptop allows me to learn that while I'm somewhere else other than my desk. Sometimes you just don't want to be stuck sitting at a desk for so long.   I purchased an IBM Thinkpad T40. Rated to be among the best of thin laptops right now, it is lighter, sturdier, and made of quality parts so I don't have to worry that three years down the road, it'll break...cause it won't. Although this comes at a pretty price, I think it's worth it if the laptop will last beyond three years.   
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       D'oh!   I just heard about Bob Hope dying. It is a sad thing, but he indeed live a full and happy life. It would be a great thing for people to live to that age and die peacefully.   I'm up for watching a movie on friday. I want to watch Pirates of the Carribean. I heard it's really good. 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Bob Hope died   How sad. :( But he did live a long, full life.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       No LAN party this Friday....   Sorry, no LAN party this Friday, hon. Let's go watch a movie with the tickets I bought. It has to be 2 weeks old though. I'll let you pick. Then eat somewhere in my coupon book. What do you say?? :)
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       I win! (or we win...either way, I won!)    I win! Yes! I finally won at Warcraft III. Of course, Paul was helping out...but still...I won against the computer! For the first time, I was able to build an army (air force is more like it) and support the main horde that Paul was building. I've decided to go Night Elves though. Building two groups of bird archres and chimeras takes A LOT of resources...and I have to make sure that my base will not be attacked while I'm building that primary force. I'm trying to figure out the build order myself...and how fast I can build the two air groups that I need. I've been thinking about building two of each Ancient of Wind and Chimera Roosts...but that would take more time....almost the same time it would take with just one of each building.   I've been thinking of going through the campaign for both the original Warcraft III and the expansion. it seems pretty easy since I've been thrashed around by the computer so much. I'm really liking this game now...and to think before I really didn't like it at all. I guess my opinion will change once the computer kicks my ass again. I'll hate the game, I'll love the game.   There's nothing like seeing five chimera dragons flying towards an enemy base...
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       The Comic Strip...   So Alex and I have been working on comic strip ideas for a long time now. I think we have enough ideas now to release a few out into the public. The problem is, they are all in black and white. What with Alex's wrist problems, he can't spend the time and effort to color the whole strip...let alone hundreds of them that we're planning to make.   We have some really funny ideas though. Some of them poke fun at us, me, or just Alex, but it's all in good taste. We have one where I'm telling Alex about a new game I got and how I think it's the "greatest game I've ever played!" and, of course, he has a tired look on his face. Switch to the next screen, I'm playing the game and have a huge smile on my face. Then it's switches to another screen where I'm showing Alex another game, and now I'm proclaiming that this game is the "greatest game I've ever played!" So it switches to another screen where I'm playing the game, but behind me are hundreds of boxes of games that, of course, I think are the greatest games I've ever played.   It's sort of exaggerated. I really don't think every game I buy is the best one I've played, but I've told Alex about enough games that he remembers which ones I think are really great and stuff. We have so many other comic strip ideas floating around that I have to write them down in an MS Word document in order to keep them fresh in my mind.   I'm thinking we should do tshirts based on the characters as well, but that comes later. 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Why can't I win?   Okay, I believe when I say that when I play Warcraft III, I have to practice a bit...get to know the game. I usually pick up things pretty quickly, but this, I don't know. I haven't won one game since I got it, and the only game I've won was when Paul was right there beside me, helping me out from getting my ass kicked! I know I'll get better (I hope), but how long should it take?! I guess I'm just impatient.   Janet hasn't called me yet. I guess she called my parents and told them they were here. I don't know, I wasn't too interested. I haven't been as enthusiastic about studying my N+ stuff recently. Maybe it's because I'm in a chapter right now where it's EXTREMELY boring. Installing network devices. Like I don't know how to do that.   I'll come help you in the backyard sometime, honey :) 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Loooooong post...   That was a really long post about WCIII. Very interesting. I read all of it. Haha!! :) Understanding it is a different story. Haha. Love you.  Anyways, I wonder when they are going to announce the job. I hope I get it. Hoping, hoping, hoping. I would love to go somewhere new.  Hey... if Janet calls you maybe we can go out with her on Sunday. Or maybe Saturday night... but I'll have to freshen and change my clothes, cause I am sure I will be stinky by the end of the day. Oh, maybe we can go to Roscoe's Chicken and Waffles for a late lunch after our Downtown trip.    :)   Yummmmy  I want to work in the back yard, Edgar. I loooove the backyard. I can't wait for the pool guy to come on Friday. Then on the weekend we can really get started on the area around the pool. Oh, do you know my parents will be building a sandbox. Isn't that cute. It's gonna be next to the doll house. And I can't wait to fix the doll house. It's gonna be so much fun. I also can't wait to have a BBQ. It will be so coooool. You should help us Edgar. Oh, do you know what else I did on Sunday?? It is soooo Father of the Bride moment. I carved my parents and mine and Meryl's initials in the tree in the back. It is facing the new patio. It's so cute. I have LD and MD with a heart. (that's mom and dad) Then I have LD and MD below.. that is Meryl and I. We have the same initials. I asked my mom if I could put your initials too, but she said not yet. Haha... what if I don't marry you. j/k Then I said well, we will have to chop the tree down then. Haha!! I know in my heart that we will be carving your initials next to mine. I can't wait :)
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       ...and I lose   I tried my strategies in Warcraft III about 20 minutes ago. Suffice it to say, I still got my ass kicked...but I lasted a bit longer this time :) Maybe I am learning. I think I have to make more units though...the computer just had SO much more. I must play again. This is really getting bad. 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Warcraft III: Micro Management and Focus Fire   So I bought Warcraft III and the expansion recently. I played the game last night for about 10 times. All 10 times I got my ass kicked severely and thoroughly by the computer on the EASIEST level. All 10 times I sat there wondering what I did wrong. There has to be something. No way do you go up to a horde of enemies and not stand a fighting chance against them. Then, after the 10th time of losing and getting pissed beyond belief, I went on a hunt to find ANY reason of what I might be doing wrong in this game. I think I may have found it.  According to some Warcraft III strategy websites, there is a process known as micro or micromanagement. Apparently, you are suppose to manage each and every single individual if they come under trouble. Additionally, there's another technique known as "focus fire." This technique allows you to concentrate all your firepower on a single unit in order to kill it faster and get on to the next unit. Now, of course, what I am thinking that goes along with this is Unit Selection and that is where strategy comes in. If you do enact focus fire, which unit will you destroy first? The Hero? Likely, but somehow in my mind, that doesn't seem like the smart thing to do in certain situations. Ranged units? That would be good. I think out of all units, those with the capability to have a ranged attack do the most damage. But still, something in my tells me that just attacking those units would not be effective. Melee Units? Well, maybe. A big maybe. They are the frontline of any force in the game. If you focus fire on one melee unit and keep on destroying their frontline, then their ranged units will kill you instantly.  I've been thinking that maybe separating the ranged and melee units into two separate groups. The idea is two fold really. I'll have control of my range attacks and have more of them (12 per group) and I'll have direct control of my melee units and also have more of them. But the problem there is where the hero will be placed with...the ranged or melee units? Does it matter? I'm also thinking that if I do have ranged and melee units in separate groups...I would be able to fire on the ranged units so the same damage is dealt to that side of the group as I'm doing to the melee enemy group with my own.   It is confusing, to say the least. I never knew this version of Warcraft would be so...intrinsically involved. You must handle each unit differently and must keep watch over the hero at all times, as he is the catalyst that keeps the groups going. The only thing that I'm unsure about right now is the build order. What do I build first? Barracks or Hero spawn? I wish there was a way where I can build both of them at the same time, but then my wood intake would suffer...and if I made more workers to get lumber...I'd run out of available units to train because I would have no one building farms.   What I could do is assign all five first to gold, build four more, one for wood, two for barracks and hero spawn, and another building a farm. After the barracks and hero spawn is built, have one start more harvesting of wood, while the other building a lumber mill. When the farm is built, have that guy start harvesting wood as well. By that time, I'll have to build another worker to build stuff.   Seems like I understand everything...but I have to be more aggressive in my offensive tactics. I see so much more of the enemy than what should seem normal...sometimes I think the computer is cheating. But I think it has to be that way because of the nature of online combat in Battlenet. It's rush to be rushed. I think that's what really turned me off on Warcraft III early on. I hate being rushed to build a base and quickly form a strategy of attack. I hate having no time. But it can't be helped. The computer is not going to wait for you...and neither will a human being *sigh*
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Star Wars: The Old Knights of the Republic   I bought Star Wars: KOTOR for $37.99 at Best Buy (of all places). They were able to price match the amount of the sale from Frys. They even tried to call up Frys (because I didn't have the price listing with me) and they said "Fuck it" and gave me the price. I'm so happy because this game is seriously awesome! I spent almost 6 hours this weekend going through the story and checking everything out. When this game comes out for PC, it's going to be so awesome.  On another note, Luigi came by on Sunday. It was good seeing him again. 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
        No bangs!!!   Errrr...I don't know about the whole "bangs" thing. I sort of don't like them. I think you look real good right now, but that's my opinion. Bangs...I don't know....they're sort of "red neck" looking on the wrong person. No bangs for YOU! lol j/k! 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       I need to eat the right stuff?   Well, that's true. I need to start eating the right foods. I just ate a donut...and it made me feel good. I guess I do need those vitamins. Expending all that energy on exercise probably made my body go through changes that it couldn't handle (cause I didn't have the right vitamins or didn't eat the right foods). I should've thought of that...but I can start right away.   On another note, Star Wars: Knights of the Old Republic is only $37.99 at Frys today!!! It's only for Xbox...but I'm thinking about getting it. Not a bad price! I need to catch up on buying games anyways, since I've *cough* borrowed *cough* a lot of copies from my source. Time to give something back, you know? It's bad for your karma if you pirate games for so long without giving back to the community.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       It's Friday!!   Woo Hoo!! I will try really hard to get out of here on time. Not likely exactly at 1:15pm cause I have to close my batch. 10 minutes later not 15 minutes. :)   Is it pay day yet?? I know.. next week.  I miss you, Edgar!! I can't wait to spend the day with you later... and Meryl, Haha!!  Hey.. I think I want to cut bangs again. What do you think?? Not like a lot like a bowl haircut, just a few wispy bangs. I dunno, gotta think... but I do know that I will be getting a trim soon. Gotta ask mom.  Remind me to ask mom about the vitamins. You should start taking them. Mom and dad were talking about you today. Cause mom saw you at lunch and said you looked tired. They were just saying that you should start eating more veggies and fruits. That you are not getting the right foods in you. But you will hear that later. Haha...  Ok, it's 8:04am, gotta get my desk together. :)  MwahMwahMwahMwah!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       When you can't play a game...   I experienced a weird sensation last night. I couldn't play any game I had on my system. I also didn't want to fire up any consoles to play games either. I wonder what that means. Oh well, I'll be getting Warcraft III today with The Frozen Throne expansion, so that should keep me busy for awhile.   I can't wait to see the backyard! The little hobbit hole you guys made for yourself (while quite small) is really cool. I can tell that the backyard did look really good once before, but you're right...when you have a business, you have precious little time for anything else.   I've been having trouble sleeping. I find that it takes me 30 minutes to go to sleep (or at least, feel like I'm going to sleep). Maybe I should take those vitamins that you were talking about. I exercised yesterday and that felt really good. Consequently I feel really good right now...but I think the vitamins would help out a lot.  
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Hello   Hi sweetie~pie!! How are you doing?? I am pooped again. Working outside is tough. I was sweating like it was raining. :P I can't wait for it to be done. Mom and Dad said they are going to finish half the backyard including the pool then start doing the inside, like getting the wood floors finished and redoing the tile in the bathrooms and kitchen. Then painting and redoing Meryl and their rooms. I think my mom will be pulling up the carpet in their bedroom and putting in woodfloors. Then after they finish that they will finish the back part of the backyard and fix up the cute doll house in the back. I'm really happy my parents are doing this now. It's easier since they don't have the restaurant anymore. That was simply impssobile to get anything done. That's when everything went kapoots!! Anyways... I have to straighten up the house and then do some personal grooming cause I smell!! :) I love you, Edgar!! Talk to you soon!!  Oh, don't forget tomorrow we will watch T3, maybe eat sushi and then I would like to go to Northridge mall. I want to see if they have any shirts that I saw at Topanga mall. They didn't have any sizes. Okie dokes!! I love you. Bye bye!!
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Working Outside...in Humidity...Yech   Hello there! Well, it's nice to know that you got a nice day off. I'm glad you did. I'm also glad that I got to see you today! Oh, I forgot to tell you thanks for lunch! That really made me full.   I think I must've talked to every employee in 21st Century today. Call after call after call when I came back from lunch. I don't think I mind though. I'm starting to think there's something wrong with my phone...in that it gives me the next call straight after the other with no time to prepare. Oh well...it's all good.  I think my jaw is getting better. I exercised for a full 30 minutes (not my regular hour). I thought I would take it easy at first and see if I could do the basics. No problem there :)   
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Nice day off   Hi honey... Meryl and I are taking a break from working outside painting the patio area. It's really looking nice. I am fullll of paint. I can never have a jon in painting. I'm sure it will all come out. Welps... I am gonna play some SIMS now. My dad went to pick up mom and then they are going to their fave store... Home Depot. Meryl and I will go back outside when they come home. Anyways... talk to you later. Love you!! Mwah! mwah!!
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Ehh...Jacking off decreases your chances of Prostate Cancer   Can you believe it? I was reading a report today that young and middle-age men who *ahem* "jack off" more can really decrease their chances of prostate cancer when they are older.   So much for going to hell, I won't get cancer!!! HA! 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       More tired than usual   Good Morning! Okay, today I'm feeling more tired than usual. I'm thinking it's because I stopped exercising. I feel...exhausted....and from doing nothing at all! I've decided that I'm going to run today (Thursday) and see how I do with my jaw. Hopefully, it's just the weight lifting that's the main cause.   I hope you have fun on your day off! I'll be here...studying N+. 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Early Good Morning!!   Hello baby!! It's 10:45pm and I just hung up with you. I will be signing off now. You will probably get this tomorrow morning. I just wanted to say HELLO. I will see you for lunch tomorrow. I hope you have a wonderful day. Wish I was at work... but then again, nah! Haha... Anyways. I will talk to you tomorrow. I will call you when I get up. I will probably sleep late tonight cause I rented a movie. "Real Women Have Curves"... I will watch that later. Okie dokie! Talk to you and see you tomorrow!! Mwah~Mwah~Mwah~Mwah!!~ I loooove you!!!! Mwah!!~
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Security Risks   Well, I'm patching up XP Pro right now. It's taking its sweet time though. Leave it to M$ to leave huge gaping security holes where anybody can take control of your system and resources. Of course, patching it up is a snap.   I like the way the backyard is looking. Your parents are really working hard on making it presentable and beautiful again. That's a good thing. At least you won't be baking under the hot sun (or weird humid rain) tomorrow since you won't be going to Santa Barbara.  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       No SB tomorrow...   ...because Sachi is in OC and she will not be returning til the weekend. Meryl doesn't have a key yet. Oh wells. So, I am going to spend the day with Meryl. God help me. We are gonna go for brunch, lunch... whichever. Then she will help me buy some capris. Maybe get our nails done. Do some planting later when mom gets home.  Oh speaking of planting, the back yard is looking great! Dad bought grass...like 5 pieces. He wanted to try it out first. He will go back tomorrow to buy more. It's really nice, Edgar!! I can't wait til we have our first BBQ in the new perty backyard! :) 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Two shower heads?   I'm glad you're going to be getting the fourth season of Friends! Then I can watch it after you :) So my dad installed two shower heads in the shower today. I'm confused really as to what each of them do. Apparently, one of them is for massaging and the other for "washing" yourself. I know...I'm still confused. They both spurt out water...so I guess it's just more coverage.   I think if we worked at different places, it would be alright...because by that time, we will be together. Have fun tomorrow at Santa Barbara!!! Love you.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       New Stuff   I am going to buy FRIENDS (4th season) tomorrow with the mula you gave me. Thanks :) Then I will buy Felicity (2nd season) some other time. I should check Amazon cause that is where I bought the first one and it was cheaper than Best Buy. Oh speaking of BB... I have to use my new ZoneRewardsCard. I have to give that to you cause I will probably lose it.  Gosh... I'm getting that sad lonely feeling... I miss you, Edgar!! I wonder how it would be when we don't work at the same place anymore. But I think that would be different because when that time comes we will probably be living under the same roof. :) winkwink~!! I love you, boo!!
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Duh!!   Yes, Chatsworth is still the Valley. It's the San Fernando Valley. It's a large area, Edgar. It's pretty much anything on the other side of the mountain from LA.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Earthquake weather!   I can't believe this! It was steaming hot a few hours ago and now it's RAINING?! It's only a matter of time before that big one comes. Dumb weather.   Live in the Valley?! Hmmm...I don't know...I'd rather live somewhere remotely close to work, but not in the Valley.   Is Chatsworth still considered "the Valley?"
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Weird weather!   It's sprinkling outside. At least it is a tad cooler. Still muggy and yucky though. Maybe we should move, Edgar. Hmm... I think we will end up staying in the Valley when we get married. Or at least me staying in the Valley and you moving here from Pasadena. It will be more convienent since this is where we both work. I do not want to commute.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Humid?!   It's not humid here! It's only dry heat! You can't take the heat!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Sushiness   Okay maybe. Remember, we have to watch T3. We've put that out for a long time. I hate parking at Sushi Mac.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Misc stuff....   Who else did you invite to our love forum?? Haha!! I don't see anyone else but us posting. That's ok.  I can't wait to have the day off tomorrow. I am pooped. The only bad thing is I won't see you, Edgar :( BUT, I will be back by 4pm so maybe you can have dinner with the family :) Can you eat my dad's famous Ravioli? Doesn't that sounds good?   The day off....Hmmm.... Not that I will be relaxing. I have to take Meryl to SB to her new apartment and schlepp some of her belongings. I hope the weather is nice there. I am sure it will be better than here. It is so hot, muggy and humid. 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Sushi?  I would like to eat some sushi this Friday, Edgar. Doesn't that sound good?? Can you chew? If you can't we can still go and you can watch Meryl and I eat sushi! Yum.  Ohhhh, and I will let you pick up the tab too!! :)
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Open Forum?  Ok... I guess this is an open forum now since I see Alex and Brixton's name?? So, I can't mention any of our personal relationship stuff... or be too mushy and lovey dovey with you cause that will just make Alex and Brixton and anyone else who comes on here throw up? Haha... too bad. I looooooooove you Edgar!! *mwah*mwah*
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       My Jaw   How do you write about something like this? You wake up one morning and BOOM! the right side of your jaw is hanging on for dear life. I guess a bit of a preface is in order. I woke up one morning to a certain grinding noise in my jaw. Of course, being myself, I didn't think anything about it because, at 24, who does?! We're invincible right?! WRONG!  TMJ Syndrome (I think it's Temporal Mandibular Joint syndrome) is what I have. It starts when you do something to your jaw (be it exercising or some other activity) that pushes the cartilage disc out of alignment with your jaw. So then when you move your jaw, you hear a grinding noise (which I learned is your jaw bone riding against the joint in your skull). To make matters even worse, there is a nerve that runs along that joint where the jaw can run over and cause extreme amounts of pain. This was my state of being last friday.   I think pain is defined by different levels. Suffice it to say, I have never experienced this level of pain before. I know all pain is annoying, but this pain was just more than that. I couldn't eat...at all! How annoying is that?! EVERYBODY needs to eat! Why can't I?! Whenever I tried to attempt to open my mouth last friday, I was delighted to experience pain on a level that reached supreme annoyance akin to being jabbed in the jaw with a syringe 20 times. Oh Oh Oh! Not only that! Ohhhh nooooooo! I had to wake up at 3:00 am in the MORNING on friday to take my father to the airport. So not only was I orally retarded, but I was fazed beyond belief due to lack of sleep. My LAN party (which was after hanging out with Liz-Ann) lasts from 6 pm to 3 am in the morning, effectively pushing myself beyond 24 hours.   Admittedly, it is a very stupid thing to do, but hey, I've never done it before (and even under the 600 milligrams of Motrin, which helped tremendously). I could not eat ANYTHING hard. I felt like an old man chewing on a stick of grass like a cow. It is amazing to think how severely incapacitated I was just because of the right side of my jaw. Albeit a very  important  part of my mouth, but still...you'd think it would last without any problem till I'm 65 or something!  ...and the fact that it happens to more women than it does for men does not bode well for my male ego (not that I've ever had one anyway).
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Gurgle   Do not eat Chicken Pot Pie if you're having stomach problems. You'll just get more stomach problems.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       It's Liz-Ann!!!   Hi Honey! It's me. I know you can see this. I'm studying right now. N+ is so much fun. Check this out  EEPROM is an acronym formed from  electrically erasable programmable read-only memory  and is a chip whose settings can be configured with software.   How is this relevant to networking? Well, NIC cards have EEPROM chips, jumpers, and/or DIP switches to configure. All NIC cards have MAC addresses that are hard-coded into the NIC at the factory and....  Boring.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Star Wars Galaxies?   Okay, so I've been thinking about this a long time. There's a certain curiosity towards a game that shows every single entity in the game as a real, living, breathing (maybe), human being. The whole concept is staggering to say the least. So many possibilities. Of course, some Sony executive had to go up and say "Well, we can capitalize on this phenomenon big time!!!" and who wouldn't?!?!   But this. Star Wars. It's Star Wars. They, in their most mystical fashion, can ruin (well, ruin more of what's already ruined) the single greatest licensing opportunity for a game.   Have they? I'm not sure. I never played the game. Suffice it to say, I have been thinking about it (50 bucks + 15 bucks a month). The whole "pay to play" scheme never really works for me though. How can Warcraft III, Starcraft, Counterstrike, and Battlefield 1942 among others are free to play? What's so different? Probably a lot. Probably not so much. It's all about the dollah.  I'm getting Warcraft III and The Frozen Throne expansion this week for a good price. I've decided to give it another chance since I was humiliated by the computer the very first time I played it. I'm not concerned. I'm willing to give it another shot.   Oh look! Another call from a person who doesn't know what they're doing. 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Unbelievable   Okay. So this is my first post. It's not bad so far. You know when you want to do these things (get stuff off your mind) and find a way to do it, then when you actually GET to doing it...you find yourself wondering "What did I want to say?" in the first place. You have the words, you have the medium, you have the audience (somewhat), then what's wrong? Absolutely nothing. It's like trying to answer a question you don't know the answer to and would not know any way possible to find out what the answer would be! How does that work?! Too many questions.  On the other hand, I'm at work right now. It's  urlLink there . I'm looking at my phone right now and wondering...why is it so huge? I mean, can't Nextel find a way to make these behemoths smaller? Not smaller as in Nokia "I can barely hold it with my two fingers" smaller, but at least a comfortable..  Uh oh...call coming.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      If I told you this was a test, would you believe me? I mean, you have no reason not to. 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Stories and such...   I've been told recently that I should become a writer. Whenever I would get a good idea for a story, I would think about for a good long minute, and then SOMETHING would come along to either distract my train of thought or otherwise. My idea for the story goes to hell and I never really complete it. The real problem behind this is my inability to focus on one thing for a long time (my work usually frowns upon doing that). I think I always have to be doing/thinking of something other than what I am currently doing, thus my mind is split such as the processor that governs our computers. The only thing that separates the my mind from a processor is the fact that it can prioritize the focus of certain tasks it is given. I have yet to learn that trait, or if I have, it is a poor implementation to what I want to do with my ideas (creatively speaking). It is easy to prioritize office/work tasks. I can do take without even thinking about it. It's when you're creating something completely out of the ordinary when your mind becomes utterly useless because you cannot focus on anything besides what's going on.   I'm sure it's a trait that, if I do start writing stories, I will eventually learn and do well at.   So it's my mom's birthday. I'm taking her and family to Parker's Lighthouse at Long Beach. She seems to really like it there. I don't know, when I've always gone, the food was overpriced for what it was, but if my mom likes it there, that's where we're going. It's funny, I think she's turning 53, but she doesn't look it. I guess there are some people that really look their age. Usually, it's attributed to all the bad stuff they have done to their bodies over the course of their life. Smoking, drinking, unhealthy eating, and other such vices can cripple the body when it becomes older. It's funny, but it's no wonder some old people are pissed all the time. They don't understand why they're getting older and weaker, thus they become senile. They want to keep doing everything for themselves, and while that's a remarkable trait, how can you do anything when you do not have the energy to do so. I've made up my mind that when I get older (significantly older). I will not drive on the streets (if it's called that when I'm 70+ years old). I will not attempt to adhere to my "old ways" and make an effort to see the good in what's current. I will stay in my house and take care of myself (even if I can not under my own power...I will attempt to do so), and if I cannot then I (would much rather kill myself) would seek the proper help. But the most important of all, I would spend my time finishing all the games that I have amassed over my lifetime. Even if my hands are old and gnarly...and can barely keep up to speed with the younger kids...I would still try.   Wow, thinking about all this makes me tired. So I go now.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Happiness is a warm T40   I know I know, it may seem that I'm talking about this laptop a bit too much. But that's just it! I love this laptop. It is seriously the single greatest laptop I have ever owned. True I have only owned two laptops before this (both of them Apples), but this is my very first PC laptop and so far, it has been an awesome experience.   You just called me, Liz-Ann...and now I've lost my train of thought. 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Saturday Morning...   Well, it is 11:35am and I just finished sweeping the front yard. It is much cleanier without all the leaves and small debris. I went to class this morning at 8am. It was a short 2 hours, just reviewing. Remember how I didn't go to class on Tuesday because I had to frantically finish my other classes report. Well I got back my test from last Saturday and to my surprise I recieved a B. He said the final shouldn't make much difference in the final grade unless you are border line. I think I am border line between an A and B. I have to do well on the final so I can snatch that A. I have class again at 1pm- 3pm. Can't wait...snoooze :)  My parents are working on Vanessa's catering. Smells good. I think Franz, her husband is picking it up at 3pm. Meryl is at Waffles. She will be home also at 3pm.  I read all your previous posts. I haven't been on here for a while. :) All that matters is I am here now. Right...  Bugoy is looking at me. It's cause I have his squeeky shoe toe. He loves things that squeek!!  I can't wait to see your new laptop. I am sure you love it already!! I am sad I dropped mine. There are sometimes I want to use it and it's not there :( oh wells... I guess I will buy one sooner or later.  I can't until the new program of Weight Watchers start. I think it is what I need to revitalize myself with the program. I am very excited about it. Also about Curves. I can't wait to enroll! Dawn and I will be checking in out after WW on Wednesday. Maybe that we can go on Friday so you can check it out with me. I would like that.  It is almost twelve and I have class in an hour. I am going to take a shower again and get my things together. Talk to you later. Love you!  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       So I wake up and...   I feel fine now. I can' t believe how bad am I without any sleep for two days (I don't believe anybody would be themselves without two days of sleep). Of course, I feel fine now. I'm trying to sort out all the things I have to do in my head. I have to get my credit card payment out. It's due on the 29th and today is the 23rd. I also have to move my car from the direct sunlight. That thing can get severely hot with all the heat. I have to clean around my room, make a file for 21st Century Insurance stuff.   Damn I forgot, I also have that Jury Duty notice. I hate Jury Duty. Now that they's making it mandatory (or rather THREATENING people with fines for not replying), I really think it's not fair for the public to endure wasting a whole day of their lives, waiting for their number to be called. I wouldn't want ANY government to take one day out of my life, possibly wasting my time (more than likely), without my consent. Forcing people to do something does not bring adequately suitable people for a task as serious as being in a jury. I don't want to do it. I don't want to be responsible for a decision the government should do.   end rant.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       T40 goodness   I love my new laptop! The high resolution, the soft and tactile keyboard, the lightning fast response times. I just can't get over how awesome it looks. This is something I feel was money well spent. I can't wait to show it to everybody! Liz-Ann is going to love it!
     

    
</post>

<date>21,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       The Midnight Shift   Well...9:00pm - 6:00 am is more like it. I have just survived the "midnight shift" and I am now attempting to finish my regular hours that I do on friday (which is 7:00 am to 12:00 pm). I will be dead tired. I can feel already in my bones. It seems as if another form of blood has taken over my body...to keep me functioning as I furiously type this post.   I was surprised to notice that I didn't fall asleep (somewhat) during my watch. There were times when I would dose off (especially around 3:30 - 4:00), but for the most part, I stayed awake. The incessant pinging of Unicenter helped tremendously in creating this state of mind. I feel as if I should be asleep...but, at the same time, have the energy to go on. I feel the fatigue deep in my bones. It's disconcerting to feel this fatigue when you know you have the energy to pull a few more hours. This reminds me of a saying...."the calm before the storm..." I attribute that quote to almost everything that requires expenditure with the risk of collateral damage. In this case, what I feel right now will be magnified ten times when I finally lay down and head off to sleep.  Word of warning (more for me than anybody else). Do not ever drink coffee again. I'm sure the toilet will appreciate it.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       ...and it arrives today?!   My laptop, which was shipped yesterday, has arrived TODAY (Thursday). I can't believe it.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Guess what?!   That "one" laptop shi.com had in stock was MINE! It shipped out today! Yay!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Staying awake   When you get older, you start to find out how that you can stay awake longer. Maybe it's when you're younger as well, but I highly doubt that...since energy is expended probably two to three times the amount of grown adults (depending on the amount of exertion you put your body through each day). Either way, the more rest you get, the better off you'll be during the day.  Conversely, the same could be said for the opposite. If you get too much sleep, but no activity whatsoever, then your body starts to slow down. Your immune system becomes lazy and weak. You must be wondering why I'm talking about all this. Well, for the first time, I will be doing a graveyard shift here at the help desk. It's going to be interesting, seeing as I will be the only one here from 9 pm - 6 am. I also find it curious that they shut off the fan and air conditioning units after 9 pm. I wonder why. People are still working in the building. It should be a concern that life support systems in every building have to be on for these people. I've been warned that it gets sort of warm in the 5th floor. I'm guessing it'll be no warmer than my room on a hot mid-day Saturday with just the fans running.   So it'll be a full day tomorrow (Thursday). 7:00am to 4:00pm (I can then go to Liz-Ann's house, take a nap and eat....I'll probably need to take a shower too...since I can't stand not taking one everyday). Then I come back to do a 9:00pm - 6:00am shift. I do get an hour break between 6:00 am to 7:00 am. Then, I do my regular friday shift of 7:00am - 12:00pm. After that, I will proceed to sleep 16 hours.   I've thinking whether or not I should go to the LAN party. I could go back home...get some rest and then head over. I don't know, I'm still thinking about it. I don't want to push myself too far. I know for a fact Liz-Ann and my mom wouldn't agree to it. But we'll see how I feel.   I just checked shi.com and they have ONE of my configured laptops in stock. I'm just wondering if it'll be shipped out to me. It better...cause I'm getting sick and tired of waiting. I have so many things that I need the laptop for...I really hope they send this one out to me (or at least, they will get more in stock so they will finally release the backorder on the item).  Warcraft III is starting to suck. I can't even create a goddamn custom game anymore within Battlenet. 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Just another day in paradise...   What the hell does that mean? Another day in paradise. It sounds like some sort of satiric irony. The saying does not sit with me well. This is no paradise. I guess it depends on where you are at the moment that fully defines the phrase when used.   So my T40 has not arrived yet. It's been (I think) a full two weeks since I've written on here and still no T40. I am getting antsy, so to speak. I can't find a reason why I need the laptop right now. I know I can wait a month for it...so why do I want it now? I'm crazy.   I recently bought a game called Eternal Darkness (for $15 bucks at Gamestop.com). It's a pretty scary game...but it is more interesting than it is scary. You lead a character that finds out her grandfather has been murdered and she has to find out who did this and why. But the story gets more convoluted as you go, finding out that her grandfather was actually studying occult magics and information leading to the paranormal surfaces after investigating certain secret areas of the house. You then proceed to read pages lost from a book made of human skin and bone (disgusting). You then lead the girl's ancestors at different locales towards finding the same book (during that time period) and finding out what happens to them. It is a really interesting game that leads you through different time periods of human history (and the way they speak latin during the Roman era is completely awesome). Overall, an excellent game for an awesome purchase price.  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Thanks baby for all the sweet things... BUT, why do you have my name in ( )... people should know I am your girlfriend!! Or do you have more than one?? DoH!!!  I looooooooooooove you too!! and you make my heart flutter also... like a butterfly!!
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       She doesn't post anymore...   My girlfriend (Liz-Ann) does not post anymore. She says she doesn't have the time. Whatever! ..... BUT... she is the sweeeeeeeeeetest, lovelist, prettiest, most greatest person is the whole world and I am so thankful and happy that she is with me :) She makes me a better person. :) She is so patient and kind. She makes my heart flutter!! I love her so much!
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Escaflowne, T40s, Star Wars: KOTOR, and maybe Warcraft III   Escaflowne is quite possibly one of the best Japanese anime series I have ever seen. It ranks up there with Cowboy Bebop and Macross as far as series go. Usually you will see a grouping of colors that the animators will use when producing their masterpieces, but in Escaflowne...you see every possible color in existence. It's never one color scheme that prevalent within the whole series, but a myriad of colors that keeps you interested (the story is excellent as well). The only thing that gets me is the "wide-eyed" look of the characters. Of course, this is characteristic of most anime characters, I think it was a bit over done for Escaflowne. Other than that, the series is excellent and ties in to one of the most interesting mysteries in the known world, the lost city of Atlantis.  You would expect an IBM T40 would be pretty easy to make, considering IBM is a huge corporation with manufacturing facilities of their own. I don't blame IBM for taking such a long time do produce my specific configuration. I know they have a huge back order to fill what with CEOs and executives alike purchasing these quality laptops for their own use. So it doesn't bother me so much to say that I can wait for a quality laptop to be built for my use. I'm just a consumer and customer, not a CEO or high profile executive. I can wait...or can I? Everyday that has past by, I've been wondering when I would get it. The ETA for everybody who has ordered this specially configured laptop is 8/14/03. At least, that's when my supplier will receive the stock from IBM, there is still a matter of shipping the item to me which could take another week or so. I hate backordered items. I hate waiting. Do I have patience? I'd like to think so, but only for certain people, things, events. An IBM Thinkpad T40 is something I do not have patience to wait for!  So I pass this really hard part in Star Wars: KOTOR. Pretty much had to sneak up on a ton of enemies and plant mines. I thought it was a pretty nasty setup when we started fighting. Everybody blew up in front of me when they ran over the mines. I'm thinking I have to do that for the infiltration mission I'm currently doing. Sneak in, plant mines, throw a grenade to mix it up and watch the fun. I'm not a jedi yet though...the only character in my game that has a lightsaber (and a dark force affiliated lightsaber at that) is Bastila. There has to be another way to infiltrate that whole Sith base without causing so much of a ruckus.  Warcraft III. There is one scenario map that has thoroughly pissed me off. You can only die once before respawning, you can only save once (apparently), and there is no way to go back in once you are dead. It sucks when you had a character that pretty much kicked ass but lose her to some stupid tank part of the map where you lose ALL your HP and abilities that would eradicate the enemies in there. Oh well. We'll keep trying to beat that map.  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
       
     

    
</post>

<date>20,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
       ...*doink*...   I'm going to begin most things that you leave behind and not update in the most banal and unoriginal fashion. *ahem* So I haven't written here in awhile. I must apologize though since this hasn't been updated in such a long time. Now, without further ado, let my rant materialize and rue upon the world chaos unchallenged and mitigate sorrow amongst ALL upon its wake!!! (not even Star Wars can get more epic than that).   I'm amazed at the vast knowledge of theatre my parents have acquired. As a reference to threatre, I am referring to the movies. Dare I say that they know more so of the subject than I do...and that's saying a lot (and also coming off quite condescending, but nevertheless true). They watch more movies now than ever before. It's not a bad thing of course. I enjoy a good movie every once and awhile, but I find there are more interesting things to do when in front of any sort of screen (such as what I am doing right now).   I'm not a big fan of TV. I usually never watch it unless I have nothing to do (which is someting that rarely ever happens). I find that I enjoy TV just when I'm about to go to sleep. My mind is hinging itself among the last vestiges of coherent thought, so I figure most of the crap of TV wouldn't affect me as I slowly vegetate and settle my mind in for the primal (carnal, or not) urge to fall deep into the slumber that my body requires. Disconnecting my mind from reality is a very hard thing to do. It's almost like you have to fool your mind into thinking that it needs sleep, so you coerce it with an apparent lack of cognitive realization of what's going on around you (i.e. closing your eyes) and attempt to figure out what those purple/green spots are and why they float around (which I have figured out after much research).  Specifically, when you close your eyes, I'm not saying this is for everyone, but you either see a purple/green spot floating around your otherwise pitch black vision or red/yellow spots doing the same thing. It's amazing because if you look hard enough, you'll start to see that the purple/geen (or red/yellow spots) start to show a fluid moving downward in the background. It almost looks like a cascading waterfall in pitch black darkness. This falling fluid, of course, is what keeps your eyes moist during operation...but the combination of that with the backside of your eyelid causes these wonderous colors to appear. It's almost as if you combine soap with something in the air to make a rainbow (I have yet to remember how that happens actually, at least I know there isn't a pot of gold on the other side).   I seem to remember wanting to rant about something else, but now I don't remember what. I guess I should end this with the fact that not everything in your life can be planned. Somethings just jump out at you and bite you in the ass.   
     

    
</post>

<date>31,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       The Darkness Within   That might've been a song by Metallica. I am yet again entranced by the lyrics of Coldplay. For instance:  "I awake to find no peace of mind, I said, how do you live as a fugitive?  Down here where I cannot see so clear.  and I said, what do I know? Show me the right way to go"  Now I'm not one for interpreting lyrics of songs (a lot of them barely make any sense), but there is something that hits a chord when I hear those lyrics from lead singer, Chris Martin. It is like something you can feel but cannot define. Something sad. There's a profound sadness in those words that I somehow relate to, but I don't know why.   But we never know, right? We never know anything. 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Star Destroyers and Waffles   Now, I'm not one for spending my money on useless trinkets that will provide no value to me. In fact, calling this thing a "trinket" is an an understatement.  At 3,104 pieces, this is the biggest Lego set I have ever purchased in my entire life. The finished product spans 3 feet in length and weighs a good 21 lbs. Maybe you're asking yourself, what does this have to do with waffles? Absolutely nothing!   There is a lot of repetition taking place in the construction of the Star Destroyer. One such repetitious act required me to create (16 times per frame) the details concerning the vents, shielding and turbolaser emplacements of each side of the star destroyer. It was a daunting task (one that I managed to finish last night) but the finished details on the side look really well...  I just noticed that whenever I delete a letter, the sentence implodes on itself. I hate that. What dumbass thought up that cool idea to delete everything after you delete something else. It's a forward delete. So if you keep typing on the affected part, it'll delete everything in front of that position.   I've been playing lots of Rachet and Clank: Going Commando and "trying" to finish Final Fantasy X. According to Andrew though, I'm not even half way through the game. Blitzball sucks the rear end of a scorpion! I hate that mini game with a passion! It needs to die a thousand different deaths with excrutiating pain!!!!!  *sigh* I feel better already.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       The Dark Side   It's December. December 3rd, 2003 to be exact. I don't know how the time flew by so fast this year. It's as if you remember that it was another Rose Parade, another cold night where you had to put on two pairs of socks so your feet don't get frostbite. 2003 (while we're still in it) came and went like the wind that blew a horrid life into the flames that torched Simi Valley. Now, after thinking about the blur of a life past this year, December creeps up on us. The end of a year that knew no length at all.   Of course, this is all hooked on to the fact that maybe we were all so busy, we could not stop to just...stop. Stop our lives to see what's around us and appreciate those things for what they are. To look at the person beside you and know that...time can stop for just an instant and when coupled with the ability to recognize this halt in time...I think this is where you find beauty in almost everything around you (except the blantantly obvious choices: death, destruction, famine, you know, those things). The air that you breathe, the sky that becomes blue after months of smog, the wind that lets itself known by whispering between trees. I wonder if other people ever think of this. I wonder if the people whom I see on my daily commute to work ever think about the beauty of the world around them.   But, oh well. Mostly everyone is so preoccupied with their own lives to notice the things around them. I know I sometimes am so absorbed with what I'm doing that I completely zone out of what's going on around me and focus on a certain thing (usually videogames). The question is "Why?" I don't know why.   On another note, you'd think that from a population of 3500 employees at my company, YOU'D THINK that the majority of them would be smart enough to remember a password. Sure you can go on vacation and isolate nearly everything from your mind, but jesus christ, a password?! Almost everyone in the company called on Monday (after the Thanksgiving weekend) to recreate their network, mainframe, siebel, NICE, ADRMVR, 3r/AWD, whatever passwords! I mean, it's not that hard to remember something like that right? Do you become so used to your job that you remember nothing else?! Why is it so hard to remember something that suppose to GET YOU IN TO WORK! I wish we could tell these people that it'll cost 5 dollars off their paycheck (and into mine) for whoever FORGETS and/or LOCKS OUT their user account. Hah! Let's see how many calls the helpdesk gets NOW! I bet our call volume would go from lots to almost nothing! Why...How....I just can't believe it! I would really be happy if they instituted this policy of paying to reset a password. They should do it with EVERY password-protected system accessed by people everywhere. "Oooooh forgot your password, that's too bad, 5 bucks from your paycheck and you get a new one specified by ME!!!!" hahahaha!   Oh, and lawyers seriously do not know ANYTHING about computers. It's as if they spent their whole lives learning how to argue that they can't type one single word. In fact, they argue with me all the time about what they supposedly did to "fix" their problem. Now I know why lawyers are so hated. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Le Super Metroide   It's good to "see" this game being played again on an SNES. A product of a bygone era of technology where videogames were actually "fun" to play.   Oh, I guess I'm being entirely too hard on the industry. Sure SOME games are fun to play now and then, but nothing can beat a good ol SNES game. 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
       what's...taters, precious?!?!   It happened again today. The bed was warm and comfortable and I did not want to go to work. So I woke up at 6:08 am. Mind you, this is very late. I have to wake up AT LEAST at 5:45 am to make it to work by 7:00 am.   I have been thinking about playing Disgaea again. I really should spend some time with those kind of games...but it seems like when I try to play them, I get tired easily of playing them. Disgaea, Silent Storm, Final Fantasy Tactics...geez, I'm even thinking of purchasing the sequel to Disgaea (La Pucelle: Tactics) which I know I won't ever finish.   But there comes a time when I think "...Someday, I'll have all the time in the world to finish all of my games...including the ones that take freakin 40 hours long!" When am I going to have this time for me to finish all of these games? When I get home, sometimes I'm so tired that I don't even want to look at the TV. Yet, there's an overwhelming urge to play through everything I have. It's quite a dilemma that I think I'll never be rid of. I'll buy new games and play, but never finish them. There are some exceptions (Rachet and Clank: Going Commando), but those games COMPLETELY enthralled me. I was so addicted to it that I couldn't stop playing for the life of me. I need games like that. The tactics genre has pulled me in a couple of times, but never like R&C:GC.   I'm almost done with Metroid Zero Mission. I think I'm at the last level (Tourian), but I don't think I'm suppose to be there yet. I don't have the space jump, power bomb, of most of the super missiles I need to defeat motherbrain. Plus those Metroids are SUPER HARD! I'm thinking there's another place I need to go to after Norfair. I'm going to have to ask Andrew.   
     

    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Chicken Chow Fun with Beef and Broccoli...Dragon Style!   I don't know what I said up there...but it sounds cool. I did not want to wake up this morning. It was one of those mornings where the bed was just perfect. The temperature was perfect and I just did not want to wake up. Of course, I couldn't call in sick because I had to go pay a bill at 21st Century (ironically, it was my insurance bill).   Oh wells...another day, another traffic jam.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
       A day in the life of...   It is ironic that I start writing this while I do my job. I know the few of you who read this do not know of the daily strain I submit myself to (or, in some rare cases, the lack thereof).   5:45am : I still have not gotten used to waking up at this time. Sometimes I wake up at 4:30 and wonder why I wake up at the same time every day.    6:10am-6:20am : I usually drink a cup of orange juice (everyday) and head out to the car which (depending on the weather) is freezing cold with frost on every window. After warming the car up for about 3 minutes, I pull in reverse and always hear the distinct grind of the steering column as it gives way to the previous night's freeze in its joints. I slip the gear into 1st and my car slowly and reluctantly starts another journey towards Woodland Hills.   6:30am : My car is awake now. It changes gears easily but doesn't want to be over-revved beyond the point of 5,000 RPM. Traffic around this time is not too bad...but I remember when I used to traverse this freeway during the 7-8am rush hour. You could almost wish everyone around you stuck in the same 5-10mph would just disappear.    7:00am : I park in the same place I do everyday since I was granted car pool status (even though I don't car pool anymore). The 2nd floor of the parking structure right next to the stairs. People usually park in the car pool spaces with no rideshare tag. Ooooh do the parking attendants get PISSED when they see no rideshare tag on your car. It's sometimes funny to see the red perma-stickers stuck on these idiot's cars who park in the car pool spaces. Those stickers cannot be taken off (without the aid of a hair dryer and REALLY hot water) without leaving some nasty glue residue behind on their window.   7:20am - 7:50am : It is usually quiet around this time in the office. I sit at my desk and comtemplate things such as the new games coming out this month, whether or not I'm going to buy any games, wondering if Liz-Ann is awake, and the most important, when is that first call going to come in. I think the question is, do I even want to answer it...   8:00am : The stampede starts. The herd files in to their cubicles and calls ranging from "...ooh...*embarassed*...I forgot my network password" to "The icon I usually use is not in the same spot as it was yesterday. Please move it to the place it was yesterday!!!"  Now, one would think that if you were hired by a respectable company, you would know about the systems used in this company. It does not take much to comprehend the basics of any computer. Just working with such things day in and day out would get you a knowledge far beyond the cattle that call the helpdesk nearly every day.    9:00am : The "stupid" calls die down a bit and everyone gets into their groove for working. The supervisors/managers make their daily inspections of the groups and chit-chat/bullshit with each other about things that do not relate to work at all. It is of no surprise me when they wonder why productivity isn't so high in the work place.    10:00am : Break time. Usually between 8-9am, there will be one person that will piss you off. Fortunately, after driving the 101 for almost six years now, I've learned the value of patience and just letting things go. People are going to blow off steam on things they don't understand. Am I to blame them for naturally being ignorant? No. I usually take my break with Liz-Ann, but over the past month or so, we have been busy during our breaktimes.    11:00am : This hour is like a void. Nothing really happens. The calls die down and the general population of then entire company shuts up and just works. It is during these hours where I develop for the website (from any hair-brain idea that the group decided to add to the website), web surf (yes I can do that here), or work on my C++ training. I really don't pursue the latter much anymore. I've come to learn that programming is something I may never be able to learn. I've learned bits and pieces, but putting it all together to make something cohesive is something that has eluded me for the past 5 months.   12:00pm - 12:30pm : Nearing lunch time. Liz-Ann always has something for me to eat, even though I never ask for it. The helpdesk usually argues about who wants to go to lunch first around 12:00pm, but I am never part of that argument. I stated that I want to go to lunch at 12:30pm and that's that. No arguments.    1:30pm : The calls start up again, but it's a different animal. They are more calm now than in the morning. Some of the people are even nice. MD Adjusters call about having trouble with DIR/REI and Pathways. Sometimes about printing/camera issues. We have a person that handles all that exclusively, so all the calls go to him without much of our involvement.   2:00pm : It slows down here again. I either find myself working on a special project for another group (that wants it yesterday) or just minding my own business. Unicenter pings out errors from over 500 servers in the company, so there's always something there to look for. Alerts are created for specific groups/technicians to look at these errors and take care of them. Sitting all day long in this chair sort of pisses me off. The chair is inadequate for people who just answer the phone and get up infrequently all day long. At least I try to help out the customer by going to their desk sometimes...but when I'm sitting down, I would like to feel comfortable so I don't get backpain! Unfortunately, managers/supervisors don't care about this until they find out they have to file paperwork for an "on-the-job" injury and worker's compensation comes into play. But I maybe ranting. I'm sure it's much worse in other places.   3:00pm : Another break. As usual, I sometimes go with Liz-Ann to take a walk around the building or just hang out at her desk. This is the hour before I go home, so I wrap up any work that needs to be done (usually calls from people that are still having the same problem) and just hang out until 4pm.   4:00pm : I leave work to brave the traffic ridden 101 freeway. You'd think at 4:00pm there would be no more traffic than there would be at 3:00pm, but nope. It all piles up at 4:00pm. Commuting. This is the single most tiring event of my day because I have to contend with people that are still idiotic and as stupid as people at the company. The only time this ends is when I am at home with people who are fit NEITHER of these descriptions. When I get home, it's like I enter the "anti-stupid" barrier and everything is okay. I also feel like this when I enter Liz-Ann's home as well...or any of my friend's places.   As you can see, this is a long post. It would be even longer if explained every minute detail of my job and exactly what I do. If you wish to know, then I'll post more later...but most of it is really very boring. In the end, I don't hate my job. I like certain parts of it (the fact that I get to work with computers) like working with really nice people who understand that THEY are the ones that called for your help. It is these people that I respect the most out of all the callers. But for the most part, the majority of them are sheep. It's almost unfair to take this elitism stance, but it's true.    5:00pm - 10:00pm : I just play games and try to enjoy myself as best I can before another day starts.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
       All Your Base Belong To Us!   It is strange how many people know the meaning of this. It's from an old SNES videogame that was horribly (and I mean axe butchering horribly) translated by our fellow Japanese. I believe the whole thing went:  In A.D. 2101  War was beginning   Captain: What happen?  Operator: Somebody set up us the bomb.  Operator: We get signal.  Captain: What!  Operator: Main screen turn on.  Captain: It's You!!  Cats: How are you gentlemen!!  Cats:  All your base are belong to us.   Cats: You are on the way to destruction.  Captain: What you say!!  Cats: You have no chance to survive make your time.  Cats: Ha Ha Ha Ha .  Captain: Take off every "zig."  Captain: You know what you doing.  Captain: Move "zig".  Captain: For great justice.   *sigh* You can see the whole .gif animation at  urlLink The Register .  Suffice it to say, it is interesting how this simple misappropriation of the english language has permeated most residents of the internet. People who know about "All your base..." don't even know it came from a horrendously translated videogame! It's an amazing thing to see people react to something as inane as this.   In other news, my significant other has gone ga-ga over the birthday gift of TiVo. She is a self-admitted TV junkie, so she can definitely appreciate the godly powers that are bestowed upon her once TiVo was finally connected. I have to admit though, setting up TiVo was NOT the "easy setup" that the manual said it would be.  To all those thinking of using a wireless network (specifically the Linksys WUSB11 adapter) on any TiVo system (40, 60, and 80 hour units), you MUST upgrade the firmware before TiVo can recognize the USB wireless adapter! I spent most of yesterday trying to figure out why the unit wouldn't recognize the USB adapter. It took two hours and some research on the internet to find out that after the initial setup (which requires two phone calls), you need to force an update to TiVo's service and download the 4.0.1b firmware. This specific software updates the TiVo unit to accept USB connections and recognize the Linksys adapter.   After much worrying though, TiVo finally works well and flawlessly I might add. Liz-Ann is going crazy over it (which was the intended effect). I'm glad she loves it.  Who me? No, I don't watch TV seriously enough to warrant purchasing a unit for myself. Although I have had my eye on a specific 20 inch LCD from Dell for awhile now. 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Photographs and Memories...   Indeed, many things to talk about. First of all, I would like to say congratulations. The one who reads this will know why.   I have been working on a special project for a group that I once tried to get a job for. I didn't realize until now that the job is so much more fun than what I am currently doing right now. I mean, come on, fixing problems over the phone and going to user's desks isn't the idea of fun. Users are a weird animal. Some of them possess no patience whatsoever. Not that I expect them to anyways. The real question is, would I be that way to other technicians if they came over to my desk? A rather hard question to answer.   In a complete change of topic, I recently (and I mean about three weeks ago) had one a most entertaining realization. I was thinking about high school (don't know why), and it dawned on me that I had many friends that were girls. I was always polite and nice to the opposite side of the sex, no matter what their race, creed, religion, etc. but it was not until recently that I realized that most of those girls were very physical in the ways they would communicate with me. Some would hug me just to say "Good Morning!" or some would touch my arm as I made an ass of myself (which I frequently did, both purposely and accidently, in high school) for their amusement. Now, if I were to take you back to my mindset back in high school, I could only tell you two things I was majorly interested in and completely enamored with. Videogames and computers. That's all. Nothing else.   The sudden realization came when I thought "wow, some of those girls were pretty good looking..." and BAM! It hit me like a side of salty lemonade across a bloody open cut: THEY WERE INTERESTED IN ME!!!  If you looked at me now (or at least knew me now), you'd be laughing, but I must admit I, at the VERY least, looked clean back then. THAT was a rarity as most boys my age back then did not shower nor knew the meaning of the word "soap." Neanderthals....  Then I realized something else. If I knew then, what I know now about girls...suffice it to say, I would've been a different person than I am now. I DO NOT regret this...AT ALL. Most high school relationships are immature at best and end worse than they began....but just thinking about it is really mind-boggling.   It's like you find that part in a videogame where you choose two paths. One can take you to an entirely different ending and another can make your main character someone no one likes at all, thereby leading you to an ending where your main characters dies in some fashion.   I have to repeat myself though (for the sake of Liz-Ann, who will read this). I DO NOT REGRET THIS INACTION AT ALL. It's fascinating to think about it, but I do not wish to go back to that period in my life and take advantage of all of their advances.   Nope, I already have the right one for me. I'm perfectly content and truthfully, I would have it no other way :)
     

    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
       ...the better of two evils...   Two hours before the last vestiges of a monday's past fades away unto complete ignorance. You read this now and think if there is any hidden meaning. Well, sorry to disappoint ya. There is none.   
     

    
</post>

<date>08,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Guess Who?   Hello honey. I am back. Wow, I haven't typed here in a while.  So far, this year is going by pretty fast...which is sad. Soon before you know it, we will be 25. Oh wait, that is you. You will be 25 this year. When I think of myself at 25, I have so many visions on where I thought I would be already. I know you are happy, which is good! Well, who knows, I have a whole year til then!  Love me.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Leaving Your Computer On   I have been thinking about this dilemma all weekend long and I still cannot decide what to do. Of course, I'm stress-testing my PC (so it will be on all week long), but is it really better to leave on your PC 24 hours, 7 days a week?  The opposite side says "there's nothing wrong with doing that." PCs are suppose to be on 24/7 and they would (I guess) last longer than one that was constantly being shutdown and restarted. I do not know the facts or validity of this claim, but it got me thinking. There are certain advantages when a computer is left on. First, you can download as much as you want (which is pretty much a given). Second, you don't have to wat for the computer to startup (then again, my computer in it's current configuration starts up within 20 seconds). Supposedly, when you turn on a PC, just like a light bulb that fries out during it's last days, power rushes through all the components in nano-seconds. If this is done constantly (everyday I suppose), then computer components will not last very long.  Now the disadvantages. I'm sure I will have to install Norton Anti-Virus software if I'm leaving this thing on all the time. Consequently, I will be subject to more danger that our glorious intarweb dispenses. Second, I have a shuttle for a PC. Shuttle XPCs are, for lack of a better phrase, freakin loud. The goddamn fan sounds like a jet engine. The good thing is that I still get good sleep despite this noise.   So what is the verdict? To leave it on or off all week long? I have doubts about the internal components slowly frying themselves from the heat inside the shuttle. I will probably have to research better ways to cooling if I plan to keep this up and have my computer last a long time. 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I want things that transform!!!   Holy Monkey! I just got a ship in R-Type Final that TRANSFORMS!! Into what?! I don't know. All I know is that is changes it's SHAPE when you speed it up or slow it down. How freakin cool is that?! Anything that transforms is  awesome .   
     

    
</post>

<date>06,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
       3:38 am   Why? Why am I up this late at night? I've decided to leave my computer on for a whole week to see how it does. Damn thing is loud...but I think I can sleep with the noise. Desert Combat .7 was just released, so I've been waiting in line at FilePlanet to download this sucker. It's been a good hour and a half since I clicked "click here to wait in line!"  Why put an exclamation mark after that?! Should you be excited about waiting in line?! I don't think so.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Servers that love to fail   Well, it's not like they love to malfunction. in fact, I don't think they try to "not work." It's all the human's fault. They tinker and install new "upgrades" that supposedly make work better, but in the end, the server with that critical application that everyone has to have up and running, 24/7, 365 freakin days a year, will eventually fail. Ha! and fail it did these past few weeks. In some weird way, this makes me happy.  Donuts and work. How synonymous are these two things? I'd say pretty damn synonymous if you ask me. Jesus, is synonymous even spelled correctly? Everyone loves eating donuts at the office. Every friday, it never fails. One of the three higher-ups would bring in one to two boxes of donuts (depending on how frugal they are) and the hard workers consume them with a lust unseen by the animal world. It's always a race to get the donut that you love to eat before it's snatched by that unsuspecting co-worker...WHO KNOWS that NOBODY loves that particular donut as much as you do!   Not that I eat donuts all the time. I don't. But when you get a hankering for one and find out that your favorite was just stolen from its nest only seconds after you finished up that phone call, you gotta be mad at somebody!  *sigh* Donuts. The proverbial bane of human existence. Donuts will be the catalyst of America's downfall. Aaaack...don't go into conspiracy theories. I hate assumption...why should I think of something that could happen right? Waste of time if you ask me.   UT2k3 has taken most of my night's time for now. It's rather entertaining to play a game that literally plays two to three times as fast as your brain processes information. Maybe it's because I'm getting old? I don't know. All I know is that I see things that were in one place and HALF a second later, they are someplace else....SHOOTING ME!!!!! I mean, come on! What the hell is that?!  *cough* Goddamn cough.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I remember my login!!!   Yes. A most exciting event. I remember my login/password for Blogger.com. Sometimes I can never understand why people call up and complain about having too many username/passwords to remember and suddenly, I'm complaining about the same thing.  Oh well...at least I recognize that I am complaining about it. First step to correcting a problem is recognizing that it exists.   There's a new format to the site. I'm trying to find something so people can post comments on a post and such. My sister could get a good kick out of that.   10:24 pm. Why does that seem so late for me now? 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Unabridged Anger   Why do some people have to be stupid? I'm guessing it's a genetic defect. Clients call the helpdesk all the time. It doesn't have to be a specific person calling, I basically know who calls the helpdesk all the time. Sometimes there are those people who just irk you. It's like they LOVE being idiotic and delight in making your day a living hell. If there's anything that pisses me off more, it's stupidity and ignorance.   First of all, if you're an employee of this most prestigious company, wouldn't you think that others would learn how to work with the machines that they use every freakin day?! Come on! It's not that hard to change a freakin password on the network! Shit, it's not even that hard to think of a password that you would remember! How come HR doesn't screen these people before hiring them?  "Do you have the ability to make your own passwords?"  "Uhm...well...I'm not certified, but..."  "Uh okay, we'll keep your resume on file and call you later."  That's how it should be. People who cannot make their own passwords and/or complain that they should keep the password they make forever and ever should be charged $5.00 for everytime they forget their stinkin password. I don't care if you don't know what to put for a freakin password! Think of something! Ooooh! Wow! There's an idea! Let's think of a word that you could remember day in and day out as you work at your cubicle for nearly all of your pathetic life. You don't think you would remember the single most important word that would enable you to make money and provide for your children, buy the things you want or pay a freakin mortgage bill!   *sigh* But of course, with the Security department, they charge employees $10.00 for a replacement of their lost badge. I say that's fair. The security of a password that you choose to access private company information should be held at the highest regard and careful scrutiny. It's company information! I would think that if this company held it's information priceless, then it would deem strict and financially punishing rules to enforce people to NEVER forget their passwords. I wonder if banks do the same thing if people forget their PINs.  But, oh well. People will forget and we will fix it. These people become lazy with the knowledge that they can depend on us to freakin change and/or unlock their password/account. Pisses me off. 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
       UH OH!    The Dante's Inferno Test has banished you to  the Sixth Level of Hell - The City of Dis!   Here is how you matched up against all the levels:     Level    Score       urlLink Purgatory   (Repenting Believers)   Very Low       urlLink Level 1 - Limbo   (Virtuous Non-Believers)   Moderate       urlLink Level 2   (Lustful)   Low       urlLink Level 3   (Gluttonous)   High       urlLink Level 4   (Prodigal and Avaricious)   Low       urlLink Level 5   (Wrathful and Gloomy)   Very High       urlLink Level 6 - The City of Dis   (Heretics)   Very High       urlLink Level 7   (Violent)   High       urlLink Level 8- the Malebolge   (Fraudulent, Malicious, Panderers)   High       urlLink Level 9 - Cocytus   (Treacherous)   High      Take the  urlLink Dante's Inferno Hell Test          
     

    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Ding Ding Dong   Learning Japanese. It's so much fun. I've always wanted to learn this language, but never really got the time to sit down and drill through it. I have to admit, it is hard to understand certain things (diphthongs). Oh well, time flies by when you're having fun.  Ninja Gaiden.  That's all I have to say.  I may quit playing console games for a little bit, get back into playing PC games since Battlefield Vietnam and UT2k4 just came out.   Oh my birthday is coming too...go me.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
       ?   Unknown error has occurred. He stares at the screen. The mass of jumbled code in error...jumping for recognition. He does not see. The screen is blurry. His tired eyes refocus to a wisp of dust that has been his companion for the last two hours. It has not moved. Neither has its relatives. Remnants of an empire lost. He rubs his tired eyes, but does not see. The white luminescent glow of a halogen lamp cast dark shadows. Fingers rested lazily upon his home. An instrument of efficiency and deft, but proved to no use upon the unknown error. It has occurred. He does not see. The air is still.  He stares at the glow from a lamp. A light so bright that brings severe contrast to his place of slumber. Black and white is the color of the room as the shadows stand at attention. Forever do they wait for him. There is no color in this world. He stares at the lamp but thinks nothing at all. He achieves what is unattainable for all.   He is on the outside looking in. The unknown error silently laughing at all who would choose to challenge it. The lamp flickers briefly to a power fluctuation. Everything changes for one second. One perfect second. He sees it now. Creased lines of recognition spread across his face. He knows. 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
       WHOA!   You actually posted here?! How'd that happen?   Oh and tell me the address of Tom's blog. I'm sure it will be quite entertaining to read.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
       The New Problem    urlLink Gentoo Linux   Hence! Let me introduce to you my new problem!
     

    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
         Tom wants to set up a new BLOGGER for him and I. He doesn't want to have an email trail when he talks about people here at work.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink penny-arcade.com :: View Forum - Games and Technology   I love this place. Even though I just a lurker, I rarely post anything. Check it out sometime. Some good people there...and funny too!
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       The One Who Is From Costa Rica   He shall come tomorrow. 11:45 pm is the time of reckoning. Beware. 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       A Happy Thought   I'm feeling better today....thankfully. Stress doesn't define me as a person. But more of a monster. Sure I can handle it, but someone will suffer, I can attest to that.   Apparently there are two GBA games that have gone under my radar (which I prefer because I love to be plesantly surprised).    urlLink Mario VS Donkey Kong    urlLink River City Ransom EX   Granted these games are remakes, but they bring back a time when things were simple and I didn't have to think so much (or think at all). The gut basic instinct of gameplay is presented on both these games. You should take notice (if you do play these games) that this is gaming at it's best (as far as gameplay is concerned). Best Buy has Mario VS DK for $24.99, which is a good price (better than gamestop's $34.99). Ten bucks cheaper is a good thing. River City Ransom is going to be a different story.   I think I've pretty much accepted my position (or lack thereof) at work. There's really nothing I can do aside from bitch and moan about it and I'm not really known for that. I still hate it (that much is true), but I resign myself to hoping that this is a temporary situation.  I must finish the Star Destroyer. I must finish reimaging my computer. I must finish La Pucelle and get back to Disgaea. I must read some more.   Lots of thing to do. 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Hate   Did I mention that, as of right now, I truly, utterly, completely, until I go back to my only job of answering tech support calls, HATE my job.   Today is about hate and the online community will know the extent of my wrath. Stupid, teenage, pre-pubescent, think they know-it-all, teenagers who play CS will DIE tonight. 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Anger --> Hate --> Suffering   I used to like my job. Slowly but surely, I am now starting to despise the very people I help everyday. Add the fact that I am now resuming the position that I had in Asset Management. Creating requisitions for product, request for quotes, emailing purchasing for purchase orders, and scanning, emailing, signing, filing maintenance/software/hardware contracts and/or invoices.  It's official. I hate my job.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Final Fantasy VII FAQ   Steph, this link will solve all your FFVII problems.  Also, the writer of this FAQ just died :(  He was a major contributor to GameFaqs. 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Weirdness abound   You ever have those times when you write a word, any word, and suddenly it's like seeing it for the first time? You start to think that it's spelled a different way than it currently is (which is correct) and start to seriously doubt if you knew how to spell that word at all!  I'm playing less of La Pucelle: Tactics. It's weird (post title). It seems as if I don't want to commit the time to play this game through. Don't get me wrong though, the game is great and I'm loving it. It just takes a LOT of time.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       The Swirling Maelstrom of Chaos   It is Monday. It's happening again. "People who work here and don't speak english" and "People who require a PhD to change a password." They have come together to make war upon my ideals. Why? Please tell me why do they do this? Why do they have to create this vortex of "stupid" around me?  *sigh* So in other news, I heard there is a way to post pictures in these blogs. I have to figure it out cause I'm thinking that would be heaps of fun...HEAPS, SAYS I!   The acquisition of music [that I like] has reached an all time high this past weekend. So far, all of it has interested me and has earned a place in my ipod.   I swear, if one more person calls me who cannot speak a lick of english or do not possess the complex faculties to change a password, the online community will suffer tonight.  EDIT: I hate it when people ask for my extension. Why do you need my extension?! So you can proliferate these four numbers, which serve as the only means to contact me, to people of below average IQ!?!? WHY?!   *runs away*
     

    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Links For You!    urlLink SuprNova.org   I guess I shouldn't be advertising this one...but if you ever want to get the latest demos or patches for new games and apps, no better place to get them but here. Ah! but you will need bittorrent which you can get  urlLink here    urlLink Culos!...what?   ...a link especially for Alex!    urlLink Hmmmm   ...Think I should?   urlLink Ahhhhh!   It's teh two headed monster!!!  
     

    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       People Who Cannot Speak English And Get Hired By Major English Speaking Corporations   First off, why? I think this is an important question. Why do people, who cannot speak english to save their life, get hired by predominantly english speaking businesses? Isn't the english language pretty much a requirement in America today? I'd like to think so. Don't get me wrong, I'm not trying to put anyone down and I'm not being racist against anyone who doesn't speak english. If I were going to Japan to work in a business setting, I would attempt to learn their language and writing system in order to communicate better in my work/home environment.   The second question I have is not directed towards the people who cannot speak english or speak it bad, but to the corporations who hire these people based on skillsets that JUST pertain to the job. Hey Corporate America, don't you think that speaking english CLEARLY and PROPERLY is pretty much a requirement in today's business setting? Not only a requirement, but a goddamn necessity?! We live in a country that is dominated by a specific language. It happens to be english (or whatever bastard dialec of english you speak). Just as I said earlier, if I went to Japan, China, Spain, India, France...I would work hard to make myself easily understandable to others. I think it is a courtesy that should be observed.   Now, I'm not trying to come down on those that are currently learning english, working hard at it, and pulling down a job at the same time. Consequently, I think that is admirable and I do not include such people [in my rant] who take the time (if they can) to learn a bit about the place they reside in and, at the very least, try to conform to standards of communication to make themselves representable.   I am, however, knocking those people who come from different countries (which I have absolutely NO problem with, mind you) and make no effort to properly observe and/or study the language at which is dominant in this country. That, out of many things, pisses me off the most. People that come here and do not speak english, do not make a concerted effort to learn the language in order to properly communicate, and basically live their lives here in complete and utter ignorance of custom.  I know that last part may have came off as racist and/or elitist. I get pissed because people from different countries want to come here and study very hard to learn english as a second language. I can name a LOT of people that are born in different countries and come here, learn the language, and communicate as if they were born here! That is something commendable...as it should be when one of us goes to another country (I would think to stay permanently) and attempt to study that country's customs and language.   I'm sure what I am ranting about is definitely in the minority. Nobody really cares about this as long as a person who cannot speak english can get his/her point across...be it sign language, drawing something, or pointing. I just can't get over the fact that businesses hire people like this. Shit, there are certifications for Microsoft products and most IT departments REQUIRE that you have this or they won't even give you a chance of an interview. Doesn't anybody think this should be the same for language skills as well?!
     

    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Testing Comments   Yet again, I am testing the comments section. Blogger just changed their whole interface...so there are a bunch of new styles and features. Yay for me!
     

    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Berries!   I am en route to monterey as I type this right now. It is friday, 7:14 pm. The sun is setting in the northern coast of santa barbara. Steph is listening to the cowboy bebop soundtrack and mom is wondering why we listen to this type of music. I'm getting used to typing on this machine. What with all the status messages I get for the servers at work, I'm always looking at the damn thing to see if anything important came in through email. Oh well, time to send this off and sit here :)
     

    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Dual Booting!   So yeah, why talk about this? Well, I'm currently thinking about re-doing my entire system. I'm thinking that if I use this laptop as my work computer, I could use the shuttle as a game/Linux test box computer for awhile (at least until I go crazy with Linux and want a completely Windows system again).   Gentoo Linux will be the culprit. I'm thinking of dividing the HD into 20 gigs for Linux and the rest for Windows. Depends though...if I like Linux then I may switch the HD space to provide more...but I'll hold my breath and see.  La Pucelle Tactics has shipped. Should be arriving May 10th. Yay!
     

    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Comments anyone?   The comments script has been activated. My sister's blog  urlLink site  also has this script. I'm pretty sure no one is going to leave comments for me, since no one really reads this...except dear sister and Liz-Ann. Oh and Alex. That bastard.   Post to your hearts content!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       sdarwkcab ton ma I   So,  urlLink gmail  is something that I'm looking forward to. I tried to register my name as an email address (not my full name of course) and I was prompted to create a username with six or more characters. This prompted me to become extremely sad as I was expecting to have edgar@gmail.com as an email address. Oh well.   urlLink La Pucelle Tactics  will be mine very soon. I have not even dented Disgaea and now I'm diving headfirst into another strategy RPG. Not a very wise thing to do, but I figure that if I could pass one level per day, I could make some progress into Disgaea. I heard you have to pull in some serious time to level up characters, but I feel confident that I can pass the game. It's a good thing La Pucelle includes a way to level up faster for more fast paced gameplay. While I would like to spend 100+ hours levelling up my characters, I'm pretty sure I have something better to do.   The  urlLink Star Destroyer  is still in construction. Tis another thing that I should be investing time into completing (being that it cost me $300). The question after finishing this behemoth would be the destination and/or resting home of such a large LEGO structure.  Linky Linky. I seem to like linking things. I had an extreme impulse to purchase  urlLink Super Puzzle Fighters  for my Gameboy Advance SP. After much deliberation though, I figured I'd stick to Alex's Puyo Pop for my puzzle game fixes. I may end up changing my mind though.  Aack! More phone calls! More later...  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey Edgar, while your at work you think you can get me on of those shiny cool pens that have millions of light and can scare a demon away?????  Please, pretty please please please please please!!!!!  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      1). I have to start on the NPC website pre-design for PHPNuke. I've been thinking about using my dad's old PC as a test server for the websites I'm going to be developing. I have to talk to him about that (it requires a clean reinstall of Win XP Pro).  2). I seriously have to stop spending money...like this week. Poor mode has been activated and I will binge on home foods and a week of videogames (when I go on my vacation next week).  3). I have to pass a game. I'm thinking it's going to be Painkiller (since it's so much fun), but I'm open to pass any other game as well.  4). I need to learn how to use MS Project and Dreamweaver MX soon. A lot of development really depends on the usage of these applications.   5). Research a replacement laptop for my irreplaceable T40. I love that laptop. 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I hereby promote Edgar to Lvl 2: Dark Mage Initiate
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I don't mean to prolong this conversation too much... but I think I should be heard out for a bit. It is true, like Youri said that we should have fun, and be happy with life, instead of wasting our entire lives trying to search for the meaning of it. But, you have to know, that many great events in history were carried out by a single man who went above and beyond the rest, who was able to look past the seemingly "invisible barrier" that was blocking the rest of the world.   If no one ever intends to find our purpose, why we are here, why we evolved, then we will never have the answers.  I am not saying that is necesarilly a bad thing.   I guess, after all, ignorance is bliss.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I can post here now... I could before but Edgar invitred me again, but it's okay!!!  Fear my wrath o weakling blogblogs! I will kick your blogbutts!  no...  Let's add some flava with a little craziness mixed into it.  fiddlediddlepoodle..  catch ya later.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Wow. I didn't know my 100th post was coming up (or passed...whichever)  It's cool that Andrew did it though. A fitting message for this blog's 100th post. I think this trail of words has really helped me realize a few things about myself and the job I do. I know sometimes I sound whiny and/or complain entirely too much, but at least writing it down sort of filters it all out of my system. I feel much better afterwards.   Today is Friday and that's always a good thing. 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well... I guess it will be me.   What can I do to make it special?  Let's see... oh I could start off by saying that Edgar is a great cousin, who single-handedly brought me to L.A (:D), and deserves a better job. I know he can do better, and could accomplish whatever he sets his mind to (for the unexistant god's sake, he's learning japanese!).  Now Stephanie is a different story. Always mad, cursing, and flailing her arms everywhere. Just kidding! Stephanie, another great cousin. Seriously, you guys are my favorite cousin's (well I only know about 3 others, lol, but they don't even keep communication). I like how you are so charismatic and cheerful, bringing up the morale!  Ok now this sounds like a yearbook signature.  Edgar, never lose this blog thingy, as it will be a living testament of your insanity!  Happy 100th Post.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Why indeed...   To answer your question, I really think there is no answer. The idea of God or any supreme force in the universe is sketchy at best and arguments to refute the idea of God become dependent upon our own belief structure in the "unknown"  I think that just the fact we believe an "unknown" could exist brings in the possibility that God and/or a supreme force in the universe may exist as well. I have been thinking long and hard about this very same argument. My personal opinion comes down to two assumptions.   1). Many (and I mean billions) believe there is a supreme being of immense power that looks over us. How can one refute the belief of many? There has to be a reason why so many people take an idea of a all-knowing deity to heart.   2). There is no supreme force. There is no God. When we die, we cease to exist. The universe is finite in our reality because we are not enlightened enough to believe and/or prove that the universe is forever.  Now admitting to these assumptions would bring in more questions, such as if there is no God, then why do we lose 21 grams of our body weight the EXACT moment we die? (supposedly it's the soul leaving the body). Who made this bible and why do so many people model their lives after it?  Questions. It's all about questions. If you ever thought why do we have a purpose in life, well, I think it's to ask questions. We live to question the purpose of living. Maybe that's the answer after all. If it is, then believing in the idea of a God would be much easier.   The problem with this and nearly every answer to the question of God is thrown sideways by the ignorance of organized religion and idiot religious fanatics out there who kill others for their beliefs.  Watch Dogma. If there was any movie that explained better, it would be Dogma. The message is there. I believe it.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I was wondering... why do we exist? I mean, if there, in fact is no god, then what purpose do us humans serve on this planet? All we are doing is draining up it's resources.  *Sigh*, I guess humans, or any life-form could be considered a parasite, since we depend so much on other organisms to live.   There has to be more than this... there has to be more than just living in a piece of land and earning some paper to buy things. I'm not saying anything about an after-life, but, if you look at it this way, it doesn't make much sense, does it?  Or maybe it does. Truth is, I shouldn't even be caring about stuff like this. I have a brand new computer to take care of.   I just wish I had more answers, that is all.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Many Things Of Late...   As the title suggests many things have happened. Some have ended a rather prolific time in my life. I never knew the death of Ronald Reagan could stir such emotion in me. It was like the final curtain call for the 80s. A flood of nostalgia gripped me firmly until the funeral ended. It was like watching someone you knew from childbirth just die in front of your face. It was almost as if I knew him. For me, he personified the pride and honor of the presidency of the United States. It was Ronald Reagan alone who made me feel proud and honored to be an American citizen. I know he may not have been the best president the U.S. has ever had, but the real question would be who? Who was the best president of the United States? Conflicting opinions for sure and I'm sure it's a question that will never be answered. Personally, I think Reagan came pretty damn close.  Work is work. Nothing I can really say about that other than the fact that it's getting worse. I realize that I am complaining and maybe I should just stop and try to find something that makes me happy about going there. I have options, I mean, it's not like I'm stuck there. But I guess it's just the politics of the place. The little arguments and disagreements, plus the increasing annoyance of some people's attitudes. There I go complaining again. I really do have to stop talking about work. I think I'll lay off it for a while. Talk about something else.  Alex and I will be doing some free-lance work for Stewboss and Paul's game server hosting company in the coming months. I hope it's something that we can easily work around in. I have to admit that I've never done this before, so it's going to be a learning experience. What I'm truly scared about is the fact that they might ask for stuff that we cannot provide nor even possess the technical knowledge to implement. Here's hoping that these people aren't looking for something revolutionary.  Sleep time then. I've been a post/comment-whore in other sites. Sorry about that. When I get my trigger fingers going for typing, I don't stop. 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       30 minutes in 3 seconds   The source of my frustrations these days stems from the fact that I had no say (whatsoever) in the decision to lend myself to the job I once occupied. The time I have available to myself is something positive that has come out of this. I can go to lunch whenever I want and take as much time as I need. But how do you weigh that against the work you're expected to do?   My previous job required that I would handle 1,642 pieces of paper each and every day. While the job does put your multi-tasking abilities to extreme practice, I view the job as a converter of such things. We convert most requests into physical products through monetary displacement. Cost centers, project codes, category codes, federal tax IDs, vendor specific payments percentages, split purchase orders through cost center and/or project code, invoice processing, amortization of invoice/purchase orders, rushing requisition/purchase orders through the system with no justification, the wait for managers/requestors to reply to their emails concerning their request and/or approval to process both requisition and purchase order, printing requisitions, po approvals, going down to purchasing and picking up purchase orders signed by a purchasing agent, scanning said purchase orders and associating them with referenced requisitions, contract scanning and synchronization with manager/vendor for signatures agreeing to contracts for maintenance/software/hardware/leasing etc, organization of said requistions, purchase orders, PO approvals, category manager/cost center proxy approvals, invoices, contracts, maintenance agreements for both software and hardware, contractor invoices and insurance contracts for their work to be processed, meetings with managers for them complain how the process is too slow and should be easier (all they can do is talk, it's what their good at), organization and live/real-time inventory count of all spare hardware/software and a running count of those borrowed and/or deployed permanently to specific users, salvage old equipment every month, keeping the basement organization within fire code, physically receiving shipments, physically retrieving desktop hardware and accessories, along with all this, keep up to date records of all transactions of the group (be it purchasing, invoice payment, deployed equipment, etc).  This...all of this...is what I've been temporarily charged with. Along with answering the inane and ignorant banter of our Harvard graduated user population for three hours every day, the rest of it is consumed with the above. 3 seconds is 30 minutes for me in this situation. I have no time to breath, no time to think, no time to do anything but the above. Along with the three hour helpdesk and 5 hour asset management support, I still have to administer to the CSC website and Support Magic (our ticketing system) plus train the rest of the helpdesk in the use of the new Blackberry system. I'm also assuming I have to organize/create training documentation for the one idiot that does not understand nor comprehend a device such as the blackberry because either a). he's lazy to learn about it, or b). doesn't care cause he cannot believe he has to learn about this! *enter sarcasm* Wow, isn't it enough that we have to memorize complex password change procedures!? *sarcasm leaves*  I think I'm too tired/exhausted to be angry. I don't think it makes sense to get angry anymore at these things. There's really nothing I can do and if I do say something...it'll reflect negatively on me (especially when review time comes around).  *sigh* My only solace is Liz-Ann and when I go home. Maybe now you know why I play games so much. Escapist tendencies galore.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       The Slowdown   I don't know why anybody complains about slow down in videogames. I think of it as a way to see everything in slow motion (which is cool now these days what with the whole "Matrix" craze). But I'd like to think that slowdown in videogames could be a figurative definition for my life. Sure it's sometimes fast paced during work, but once work becomes to much to bare, I slow down to a point where I can regain calm again.  Oh well.   Things to buy!  1). IBM Extended USB Keyboard for my desktop computer WHY?! Because I LOVE IBM keyboards!  2). Pay the car WHY?! Hehehe, that's pretty obvious  Darn! I really thought there was more to buy, but I guess less is better.  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       He came, He Saw, He went to Sleep...   Thou hast joined the ranks of the insane. Two new games have my interest purely on the fact that they are garnering excellent reviews. I would post links to the games themselves if it weren't for the Nazi'istic policies of web browsing that my company institutes.   I shouldn't be buying games because they get good/excellent reviews. I've been telling myself this. There's a good chance I won't get these games. I guess I'm just tired of the whole "play this cause everybody says it's good!" I remember when I used to buy games (with no prior knowledge of how good/bad it was) and loving it!  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I came, I saw, and I conquered.  :D   :D  :D  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Oh No! It's the invasion of the Buboy!!
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Lol! I don't think you suck. You get me sometimes. I don't really care whether or not you can beat me. But never let you pride get the best of you...and I think it did in your previous post.  
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      You can stick that "e" where the sun don't shine.    Oh, yeah why do I suck? It's not the matter of why do I suck, it's the question of, why are you making such a big deal out of beating me. ME, I've NEVER played Unreal Tournament, nor Unreal Tournament 2003, only VERY LITTLE Counter-Strike, and the only FPS game I actually spent time on is Halo, which, of course, I owned you.    Now you, on the otherhand, played all those games I mentioned and more. In fact, I don't suck, because when I played CTF online, I got 4th, then 2nd, then I made 1st place with a 50 point lead over EVERYONE else.    So, come home and I'll challenge you. If you don't chicken out because you're too busy watching those oh so funny videos you get at fazed, then I'll be waiting. 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "existence"   No "a"  You must ask yourself why you suck so much in UT2K4? You have to become aggresive. I hunt for you. I never, in my mind, think that you're hunting for me. You are the prey. I am the predator. Think in that mindset and you'll get more kills...maybe.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Haha very funny EDGAR, but isn't it even more funny that I beat you in every other game in existance?
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    BOOYAH! Andrew takes a hardcore beating in UT2K4!
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    I stole this from Steph's site. I had to show off your dormant, pretty legs. :)
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Ahh... the hotel :)
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      That was so cute! October will be right around the corner! :) I love you!
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Can't October 16th and 17th hurry up and get here?!
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    ...going here :)
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    ...with her...
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    ...but I'd rather be doing this
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    *sigh* I go back here tomorrow. 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Remember where this was taken, Edgar?
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Pretty garden!
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    You know Star Wars is coming out on DVD in September, right? Of course you know!
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey Edgar-man, nice pics and all, but I have to ASK. Any chance you can get me that Pen of Eternal Happiness any time soon? Because, you know, I am leaving July 31, and it would cause me oh so great sorrow if I left without that PEN!  Wahoo, ok it's late, so I'm going to play some PainKILLAH! RAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAWWWWWWR!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Wow, Liz-ann really made a comeback to this blog. All it took was to teach her how to post pictures :)  I think all of us are stricken with Affluenza every now and then. But yeah, there are those who have no control over this.   Andrew wants me to play games now.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Edgar... I think I suffer of the Affluenza Disease. There is a book that the same authors wrote about on this. I think I wil purchase it on Amazon. Check it out, hon. :)    urlLink Affluenza: A Disease of Overconsumption 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Meryl and Alex having a drink last Christmas!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    A fun night of good food, great friends and board games!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Edgar is so handsome!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Ahhhh... this speaks for itself!!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Edgar is in a deep thought!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Another GREAT pic of Liz-Ann!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    An amazing picture of beach near Sand City (still in Monterey). It's a great setting.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    a GREAT picture of Liz-Ann. This and the flower one from a previous post are frame material for sure!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Here is Edgar with BabyIndi! Yes... he looks a bit uncomfortable... but he'll be great when the time comes!!!! He's so cute!!! (the baby too, of course)
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Here is another future Abuela (grandma) in the making...
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Here is a future Lola (grandma) in the making...
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    My sister and Liz-Ann before we leave Dad's place at Monterey.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Here is Steph and Meryl at Christmas 2 years ago... wow, how time flies!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Here is me and Mrs. Feta. How pretty she looks. :)
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    This is at the Pier in Monterey!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Here is that picture I promised. Very post-card-ish
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Our second trip to Monterey with everyone in tow (Steph, Andrew, my mom and dad). This was taken at Carmel Valley. I'll post another pic of the place soon.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Here is LUCKY!!! She was the best doggie ever!!!! She is in doggie Heaven with Sarah! I miss her!!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Edgar is so darn cute!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Haha!! This is a funny pix. I made Edgar take off his socks and shoes and we walked barefoot on the beach. And you can see by his face that the water was kinda cold. Haha!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    One of my favorite pictures :)
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Making a toast to a shot of Tequila! Feliz Navidad!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    This is our 1st Monterey Trip together. We were having dinner at BubbaGumps. :)
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Edgar and Alex at Xmas time gazing in each other's eyes! Haha!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    This is us at Magic Mountain after riding Goliath. One of the worst days of my life. I am never ever going back to MM. You will have to drag me kicking and screaming. :)
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    This is a better picture of BuBoy! He is smiling!!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Here is my BuBoy!!! Soooo cute!!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    This is CRAZY BUSTER!!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    This is Grandpa!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Here is Yao-Ming!! My old doggie!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Here is the Philly I was talking about. That's Edgar's hand.. haha :)
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    This is us at Dave and Buster's in Ontario where Edgar loves the Philly Cheesesteaks! I will show you what they look like...
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Here's my pretty bear. Isn't she lovely? ;)
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    This is at Pea Soup Andersen's. We're so silly!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Oh, and this is our 1st ANNIVERSARY! March 10, 2002! Of course at Long Beach at Parker's Lighthouse. We had our first date at Long Beach, but we ate Tequila Jack's not Parker's.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Here's Edgar and myself at Guido's Ristorante in Malibu. This was our 3rd year Anniversary on March 10th, 2004.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Here's Edgar and myself at Parker's Lighthouse in Long Beach. This was our 2nd Anniversary on March 10th, 2003!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This is Liz-Ann. I'm testing my blog account right now :)
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yup, it's amazing, but true. Only for July 4th!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Oh yes, I forgot....Happy July 4th.  As we celebrate our independence day, I would like to remind all American citizens not to fire their freakin guns in the air please.   Also, I hope my credit card payment goes through okay without any late fees.  That is all.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      You would be doing yourself a favor if you download this SWEET internet browser NOW!  Disclaimer: May error out on your once in a while (it's a beta). My computer has yet to error out.  It rocks.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Pepper #30 by Edward Weston
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    This is Dawn (right) my best bud and her sister, Joy!
     

    
</post>


</Blog>