<Blog>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
         radio...       Scripture:   2 Corinthians 4:18 So we fix our eyes not on what is seen, but on what is unseen. For what is seen is temporary, but what is unseen is eternal.    today in my daily devotional, i read about a story of a cool fall day in October 1982 during a Wisconsin and Michigan State football game. There were more than 60.000 Wisconsin Badger fans in the stadium cheering on their beloved Badgers.   However, they were watching wearily as their Badgers were getting pounded by Michigan State (thank goodness not to many Romanians live in Wisconsin so i can be a bit biased .. hehehe.. :)  Well, toward the end of the game something complete strange was happening in the stadium, much of the crowd for no apparent reason would break out and cheer loudly. Other fans and players looked around in confusion, wondering why.  They soon discovered that thousands of fans were tuning via radio to the World Series where their Milwaukee Brewers were beating the St. Loius Cardinals. These fans from Wisconsin were finding something to cheer about.  There is a lesson that i learned from this after reading it and mediating on certain circumstances when we lead worship or certain circumstances are 'losing' in our life. When things are going poorly around us, it is time to tune into a different source. We need to plug into the Word of God and allow the Holy spirit to inspire us through prayer and victory will be ours even when circumstances tell us that we are on the losing end.  We need to keep our focus on the eternal and real reason for our ride here on this earth, and the temporal things around us will change!
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
         unreasonable people...        Quote:  "A reasonable man adapts himself to the world around him. An unreasonable man expects the world to adapt to him. Therefore, all progress is made by unreasonable men." - George Bernard Shaw, 1925 Nobel Prize for literature.    in my morning devotional book that i have used for the past 10 days called:  //ONEIGHTY.DEVOTIONAL - do the evolution, by: Blaine Bartel , It had the following quote taken from Romans 12:1-3.   1. - Therefore, I urge you, brothers, in view of God's mercy, to offer your bodies as living sacrifices, holy and pleasing to God--this is your spiritual act of worship.   2. - Do not conform any longer to the pattern of this world, but be transformed by the renewing of your mind. Then you will be able to test and approve what God's will is--his good, pleasing and perfect will.   3. - For by the grace given me I say to every one of you: Do not think of yourself more highly than you ought, but rather think of yourself with sober judgment, in accordance with the measure of faith God has given you.   i found this passage really interesting from a worship gathering perspective since this past weekend at the West Coast Romanian Youth Convention in Sacramento, Ca. there is talk on royouth.com that many people were jumping about in joy during the finale of the convention, and this wasnt God's work, but a bunch of youth having their worship ideals distorted by todays society. many youth participated in this ecstacy, while others sat on the sidelines and spread the news as soon as the service was over. i learned something from the mentioned quote that could apply to both sides of this controversy.  reason will tell you to go with the flow. reason will tell you that if everyone is doing something, you should as well.  it's time to be unreasonable. (Romans 12:2) Changing your thoughts will change your actions. changing your actions will change the world. so make a change.  i believe this applies to both sides of the 'worship issue'. fundamental vs. charasmatic.  how to remedy this? i believe from both sides of the story that authenticity is what God desires. Strive for it. Live by it. it is something i strive to live to, and it will change your life and those around you if you choose to do the same. dont 'do what others do'. we need to dig our selves in God's word and follow His will for our lives. we all were created to worship Him. it is not about how we worship, but how we worship Him. be real about it.  Jesus was the most authentic human that walked the face of the earth. Follow Him.  
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
         the first entry...   as you can see this is my first entry to the new cosminghiu blog. what can be said about starting this initiative?  well, i created this blogger account over a year ago on march 25th, 2003. as you can see today is may 25th, 2004. so it has been something on my heart to startup for myself to write down thoughts, insights, revelations, meditations, and life tips for all of us.  i am definetly the least 'qualified' of many colleagues in the youth leadership/pastorship within our romanain-american christian youth churches... however, i believe that through a few words each day, we can encourage each other and build each other up as brothers and sisters in Christ.   what is a blog? ::  -------------------------- the term 'blog' has been around for a few years that is rapidly growing. it is basically a play on words for a 'web log' or basically an online journal. --------------------------   purpose of this blog? ::  -------------------------- to share thoughts, ideas, experiences, etc. with anyone willing to follow along this journey of a youth worker within the romanian-american christian youth.  --------------------------  At least this is the purpose to start things off. :)    Currently in the next few days alot will be happening with the ministry i am involved with at our youth group at Bethesda Romanian Penetecostal Church - Troy, MI. (  urlLink http://www.betezda.com  ) and the ministry that i have been honored to be a part of: ROYOUTH Ministries.  Since this coming Memorial Day weekend is the East Coast Romanain Youth Convention in Chicago, Il. it will be a hectic time. However, to keep things in perspective i have managed to add on something else (as usual :) ) a book that i have wanted to read through called;   urlLink  Emerging Worship - by: Dan Kimball    Dan Kimball is the author of the book called: "Emerging Church" as well. This idea of the 'Emerging Church' has intrigued me the past couple of days when i ran across it at the local Bible Bookstore.   Being involved as the Youth Worship Leader at our church, I have been seeking 'alternative forms' of worship for our youth group.   God has blessed our youth at Bethesda RPC and we are beginning to open our hearts toward God through worship. Not just a form of worship where we passively listen tot the 'worship team' and the rest of the group passively looks on (hopefully sings) ... but a worship that involves physical interation. ex. clapping hands, raising arms, and get this... jumping. (at least during our worship team practice times :)  So some of you are saying. Wow. they are JUST beginning to be 'pro-active' in worship, and yet Cosmin is looking for something even more? what is this 'emerging worship' he is talking about?  what 'other way' is there to worship God that we don't already know?  interesting question. i am praying to find out as well. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
         feel good christianity...       Scripture:   Ecclesiastes 11:9-10  9. Be happy, young man, while you are young, and let your heart give you joy in the days of your youth. Follow the ways of your heart and whatever your eyes see, but know that for all these things God will bring you to judgment.   10. So then, banish anxiety from your heart and cast off the troubles of your body, for youth and vigor are meaningless.   this passage spoke volumes to me as i read it for one of my devotional passages today. i just cant stop shaking this idea of 'feel-good christianity' that is plagueing so many of us. myself included.   as youth of the 'worship generation' we tend to seek services and offerings that 'feel-good' and bring us 'joy'. so when we leave a 'worship service' we ask, "How did you feel during the worship?" or "That was an awesome worship time, I really felt Jesus", or we may make certain decisions that arent correct in God's eyes because it is fun, or because the crowd i'm in is doing it (hey, they are Christian too, so it must be right) ...  Then something challenging happens in our life and we don't 'feel' like God is listening or the 'why is this happening to me syndrome' occurs.   I am trying to shed this 'feel-good' Christianity into something real and authentic. Make decisions based on God's word, not feelings. Choose to walk and do what God wants you to do, not what feels right because our vigor and youth are meaningless and we could suffer the consequences both spiritually and physically later on in life.  enjoy life, but enjoy it with God as the center focus. It might not 'feel-good' all the time, but He knows what is best for us as long as we know Him. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
         passionate...       Scripture:   "Be careful not to do your 'acts of righteousness' before men, to be seen by them. If you do, you will have no reward from your Father in heaven."  Matthew 6:1/NIV   Wow, last night we got home a bit early from Chicago since around 1:30pm chicago time it starting pouring... for good :)  ... it was on an off showers til then, but at this point it was one of those good couple of hours rain shower. so, after sitting in the car for almost an hour, we decided to head home. me and claudia were anxious to see our daughter emma before she went to sleep.  well, what can i say about the  urlLink East Coast Romanian Youth Convention - Chicago  except that it was a spirit filled, passionate weekend. The youth crew from  urlLink Philadelphia Romanian Church of God  was awesome in their dedication and acts of service to all of us.   Friday, we got in a bit late cause 1 hour into our trip we had a flat tire and we needed to find a shop to buy a new tire, so after 9 hours of traveling we arrived directly at the convention. The atmosphere as soon as you walked in felt relaxed and organized. The SECURITY volunteers at the door MADE SURE we payed our entrance fee :)  ... we only had room in the balcony, so we saw everyone in the church. after an awesome main sermon by fr. luigi mitoi pastor of Bethany Romanian Independent Pentecostal Church (that's a mouthful) there was a time of worship led by Bethany Praise Band. God's presence was felt throughout the night, however at the end, it was passionate.  Saturday, our  urlLink Bethesda YOUTH Worship team  started the praise and worship and we had an awesome time of praise to our Father! ... the evening ended with Bro. Lane from Church of God with a sermon that led to an altar call for the baptism of the Holy Spirit.... hundreds of youth wept and passionately prayed for an outpouring of the Holy Spirit... almost 2 hours after service should have been done, we all wanted to stay and praise God... it was simply awesome.  Sunday, was a day where everyone relaxed and blew out a sigh of relief as everyone was free to express themselves... the last prayer after a POWERFUL message from Pastor Crinisor from  urlLink Emanuel Romanian Church of God - Anahiem, CA.  about  "Passion in Serving"  ... hundreds of youth came up for the altar call to declare that they were willing to make the change to passionately serve God in any way that they are led to do... once again... it was a night that you wished never ended.  Finally, why the verse chosen for today's blog?  well, throughout the convention i felt something. how was the  heart of the youth . Especially those that served with their talents before God. We have such talented romanian youth. I even mentioned to Claudia that 2-3 of them that performed during the 3 days, would actually go pretty far in an "American Idol" contest :))  Then again, that was the issue. The soloist or band that were on stage you could tell right away who was passionately serving God and making HIM the audience, and who was serving the audience and performing for them.  It is SO EASY to get caught up in the 'emotion' of it all, since music and a large gathering can influence many people behaviour. it is a psychologically proven fact.   It is so easy to fall into the trap of,  "feel-good Christianity" .   This convention had so much talent and passion associated with everything that happened. I dont want to associate my opinion only with this event. because it is not about events, but about our daily walk with Jesus Christ. When we serve him. Do we try to seize the opportunity to serve him while others are watching?  or do we see the 'behind the scenes' service (as many youth from philadelphia did during the convention) as the equal? if not greater?  i pray that my heart is to do His will no matter who is watching or not watching because ultimately HE is watching and that is all that matters. He is my audience of One.  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>