<Blog>

<date>31,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I miss rainbows and I miss movies.  I miss "Mexico" and I miss those great hugs. (the ones I wished would never end) And I miss a whole hell of a lot... like being able to be "me" around someone and knowing that they were being "them" around me. I miss where it was going. (or maybe that was an illusion of where I thought it was going). I miss smiling and seeing a smile in return... knowing that I made it appear.   I miss a certain baboon.   I miss a whole hell of a lot...   but mostly I just miss you.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I think I went into blogger withdrawal while I was gone this weekend... despite the fact that I had so much fun being with such an amazing friend.  I'll apologize for the rambling entries. Sometimes I'm fairly positive that the only thing that keeps me going is my ability to purge onto paper (or computer screen) all the things going through my mind.  Last weekend I discovered my favorite place.  Before then I thought for sure it was curled up in my bed writing.  Or perhaps sitting on a horse soaring over jumps.  I was wrong all that time.  I realized my favorite place was curled up, safe and sound next to someone who cares.  More specifically you.  I suppose that doesn't matter much, that my favorite place is there.  In all likelyhood the "you" I'm referring to isn't even reading.  I guess that's alright.  At least I can admit it to myself.  I'd give just about anything to have my favorite place be riding a horse or writing in my bed right about now, because at least I could go there and feel safe and good and happy.  But my favorite place... well let's just say I need to come up with a new favorite place.  The one I have has some conflicts of interest... and quite frankly has pretty much banished me.  I suppose that's my fault.  For opening my mouth and saying something.    So many things have been my fault lately.  There's no Mexico; that's my fault.  Maybe I'm more upset about that than I'm letting myself admit or believe.  Most likely.  It's really, really hard to sit here missing something and someone this way.  And to know it doesn't matter.  Especially when you started out with the belief that it did and you did.   Part of me thinks I should say I'm sorry.  And then the other part of me says that I should just continue to bite my tongue because I did nothing wrong, other than stand up for myself and demand the respect I know I deserve.  *sigh*  Two different problems.   Perhaps they're not so different. And perhaps I should just fade into oblivion.  I know at least two people who seem to want that very much.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Rather good logic. Stolen from JW.   "Another women's issue, prostitution. I do not understand why prostitution is illegal. Why should prostitution be illegal. Selling is legal. Fucking is legal. Why isn't selling fucking legal? You know, why should it be illegal to sell something that's perfectly legal to give away. I can't follow the logic on that at all. Of all the things you can do to a person, giving someone an orgasm is hardly the worst thing in the world. In the army they give you a medal for spraying napalm on people. Civilian life, you go to jail for giving someone an orgasm. Maybe I'm not supposed to understand it." -George Carlin  I like it.  Sound logic.  Indeed.  
     

    
</post>

<date>30,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm sorry. I'm just hurt. And confused. And angry. And it's so much easier to let myself be angry Than to let myself feel hurt.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I can see how much I meant.   How much all my promises meant. How much all the promises made to me meant.  NOTHING.  Eye-opening really.   I guess I should thank the friend who brought something to my attention that I needed to know about. And I guess I should thank myself for being able to say that that wasn't acceptable.    I'm in the market for a nice guy who doesn't lie or cheat.   I'm a very nice girl.   Perhaps I too should post something on match.com.   Seems like the popular thing to do these days....  
     

    
</post>

<date>30,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      This weekend was what I'd call wonderful.  Three whole days of not sitting around thinking constantly about everything that's upsetting me.  And I got to see someone I haven't seen in a long time... too long.  Actually, I got to see two someone's I hadn't seen in a long time.  I missed them both VERY much.   I need more weekends like this one.   I need more times when I can just be with people that make me smile like this weekend.   I need more times when I can just curl up and feel happy and cozy and safe.   And I definitely need more times when I get hugged so much that I forget about all the crap going on in my head and in my life.   Thank you Steve.  (and Drake, thank you too...)    I would love to wake up in the morning and have everything be "ok".   I just want more good.   I can't take any more bad.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      What a day.  Evil snow. Hooray for me  and the car for making it home without getting killed.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      PS- Oil is checked. Yay me.  Daddy thought I would forget or wouldn't know how...  or something.   It's fine, though.    ...although perhaps I shouldn't be referring to "daddy" anymore. I should figure that out... Old habbits die hard. Especially when they were like air to you. 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm not at all sure what the hell I did wrong.   Everything that was asked of me, I did. One major thing, that was thrown in my face after the fact... as something unwanted. Unwanted. When it's all that's been talked about. I asked about something that I had every right to ask about... And it's been ignored.   Always a clue that my instinct was right. *shrug* What was wanted was had. Someday that realization will hit. All those promises... I made them. They were made to me.   Of course, maybe it was never what was wanted.  I mean, I know what I wanted.  I said what I wanted.  I promised what I wanted. I just have to believe that it wasn't mutual.   Otherwise absolutely none of this makes sense.   OK.   Fine. Good girls can always find someone who wants what they do.   I thought I had.   I thought it was real. Silence is loud though. And tells me that... what I saw was what I thought. And that what I believed (that I was "that" someone) (that I was "the one and only) doesn't even come close to the truth. It'd be a different thing if this had been refuted... if I mattered enough for some kind of rebuttle.   I don't though, or haven't so far.   I know that I wanted what I promised. It didn't matter if it was now or if I had to wait two or three or ten more years. It was worth it.  You were.   And every word out of my mouth  was sincere and honest and true. Every promise.  Every single one.   Do you have any clue what is going to disappear?   Do you even care?
     

    
</post>

<date>27,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      oh, and a quick note...    my senior capstone is done.  *GRIN*  one less thing to worry about i guess.   good thing too.   i have enough.   *and a disclamer... if you don't want to know what i'm thinking/feeling then don't come here and read it, especially if you're just going to get angry or offended.  that's not what i'm writing for.  i'm writing for me.  so my head doesn't explode.  that could be rather messy...   and since i left "my" gun in buffalo (feel free to ask, i'll show you a picture of "my" gun) i need a way to blow off some steam.  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      There are a lot of things I simply do not understand.  I don't understand how you can say one thing to someone, all the while knowing that it's a lie.  I don't understand how you can have exactly what it is you say you want, and still not be satisfied.  I don't know how you can look someone in the eye and say these things and know that you're either saying them to someone else or that you don't mean them.   It's funny to me... in an ironic sort of way.  How I look at what's going on in my life and part of me just wants it to be fixed.  I just want it to go back to a time when I had no reason to doubt anything or question anything.  But I know that's impossible.  I have a reason to question things.  I have a reason to be wary.  Good reasons.  I have a reason to be wary of everything... especially right now.  After this wonderful time full of words that I fully believed meant something.  They didn't.  I come home and I find out they didn't mean anything... and I had to be terrified that I'd be sitting here alone dealing with consequences of everything that happened.  "Luckily" that's not the case... or at least it's 99% sure it's not the case... I guess anything is possible right?   I want what I've been promising.  And I want what I've promised.  I'm left with this awful feeling that I'm not going to get that... for whatever reason.  It all seems so empty.  Hollow words.  I want to be something important.  I'm not.  I want to be "that" someone.  I want to be "the one".  And only.  I don't think I am.  And that hasn't been refuted.   *shrug*  I'm back at square one.  Again.  "This doubt is screaming in my face in this familiar place sheltered and concealed And if this night won't let me rest Don't let me second guess what I know to be real Put away all I know for tonight And maybe I just might learn to let it go Take away my security from me And maybe finally I won't have to know everything I am falling into grace To the unknown  to where you are..." -Lifehouse
     

    
</post>

<date>27,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I think perhaps this will be addicting :)  *I'm on an obsessive lifehouse kick.  Last night I just sat here and listened to this CD and cried.  Because that's what I needed to do... just let myself cry.  I hadn't cried since before my grandmother died.  A lot has happened since then, I've lost a lot... and last night I finally let myself deal with it.    "There goes the world off of my shoulders There goes the world off of my back There it goes." -Lifehouse  *I'm also an obsessive lyric sharer, especially when they touch me so deeply or comfort me so deeply.  "I tried to climb your steps I tried to chase you down I tried to see how low I could get down to the ground I tried to earn my way I tried to change this mind You better believe I tried to beat this When will this end It goes on and on  Over and over and over again Keep spinning around I know it won't stop 'til I step down from this for good." -Lifehouse  "I can't be losin sleep over this no I can't And I cannot stop pacing Give me a few hours and I'll have this all sorted out If my mind would just stop racing I cannot stand still I can't be this unsturdy This cannot be happening This is over my head But underneath my feet Because by tomorrow I'll have this thing beat And everything will be back to the way that it was I wish that it was just that easy I am waiting for tonight Then waiting for tomorrow And I am somewhere in between What is real and just a dream Would you catch me if I fall out of what I fell in? Don't be surprised if I collapse down at your feet again I don't want to run away from this I know that I just don't need this. Because I cannot stand still I can't be this unsturdy This cannot be happening I am waiting for tonight Then waiting for tomorrow And I am somewhere in between What is real and just a dream." - Lifehouse 'Somewhere in Between  *And I don't think words have ever been quite so true.  Those words.  All of them.   There are other words too... very appropriate words.  I just don't know...
     

    
</post>

<date>27,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      My senior capstone is almost finished.  I'm currently working on the conclusion... and it's very relieving.   A lot on my mind currently.  Far too much actually.   Thanks JW.   *kiss*
     

    
</post>

<date>27,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      its youurs  password 1234 user name lolabpstar
     

    
</post>

<date>30,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      "I don't want you to go..."   OK. So why do you want me to stay? 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
       "Go on and take it take another little piece of my heart now baby..."  -Janis Joplin  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      How would you feel if I told you I was going back to him?   How would you feel if I told you there was  anyone  else for that matter?  Would it hurt you?   Don't lie, I know it would. I just want to hear you admit it...  I know it's true.   But I need to hear it. Maybe then this wouldn't hurt so god damn much.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      So help me understand... why I get an email from you when you're visiting a potential job site. why i get an email that tells me how sorry you are for not responding sooner. why i get an email telling me that you'll "talk to me when you're back."  Help me understand... why you  completely ignored me  tonight. why you acted like I didn't exist. why you only looked at me when you thought I wasn't looking.  Help me understand... why you hurt me like that. why you almost made me cry. why you acted oblivious to my pain.  Because I don't understand.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Today has been the kind of day where I ended up sitting here simply wishing for someone to show up at my door and wrap their arms around me and hold me until it all goes away.  I'd beg  if I had to.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      You wanted to talk to me?   That "nice job tonight" and light touch on the back of my neck was suppose to convey that?   I'm sorry... I didn't understand.  I wish you'd be more clear. I would've talked forever...  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
        Compromise by Edie Carey your love is sweet and soft just look how you use those eyes and the way you compromised your love is sweet and strong it pulls me in with the tide and up is down and down is wrong go or stay / stay or go  just be a poet about it  fall down on your knees  be a poet if that's what you claim to be  be a poet outside of your sad poetry  your love is neither hot nor cold  it's that you can't quite name it that makes me feel old  your love comes apart when it hits the light  go or stay / stay or go  just be a poet about it  fall down on your knees  be a poet if that's what you claim to be  be a poet outside of your sad poetry  be a poet about it  yeah - work up a sweat  do everything you have not done yet be a poet outside of your sad poetry your love is sweet and it's soft  i'd kill to believe those eyes  just look how i compromised   
     

    
</post>

<date>23,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      "I need you  just a little just a little Alright? Are you satisfied?" -Edie Carey
     

    
</post>

<date>21,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I use to recognize the girl staring back at me when I looked in the mirror. Now a stranger  looks back at me, taunting me. She looks so familiar so close to this girl I once knew... She looks out at me a glint in her eye a smirk on her face telling me,  unmistakably, "I" don't exist. This familiar stranger has taken over... overthrown me. Soon I'll recognize the stranger, though and "I" will be lost somewhere inside.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Let me just say, I do not appreciate being called a liar. Because I haven't lied about one god damn thing.  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I shall pose a question  (and the person it's posed to know's who they are... because I told them) So on to the question... What the hell am I suppose to do?   Is this some kind of a game to you?  Am I going to be ignored unless I'm avoiding the entire situation completely?  Are you going to continuously ignore the fact that there's  something  and that you're just too damn afraid to do something about it?  Or if there isn't something (which is bull, and you know it as well as I do)... if there isn't something are you just going to ignore the fact that I'm sitting here dying because you keep jerking me around simply because it's easier than simply saying, "Well, I meant it when I said pay back's a bitch."  I mean... seriously.  I have no clue where I stand... because I keep getting all these different messages.  One minute it's one thing, the next minute it's another thing.  I'd rather have "pay back's a bitch" consistently than to have that one minute and "I miss" another minute.   How the hell does that work anyway?   I can't do this anymore.  Every night I sit here and I wish that I'd wake up tomorrow and it'd be different... or that I won't wake up at all.  I can't pretend that I'm OK being "buddy".  I said way back at the beginning, when Rainbows and what was "right" for you (and me) came into all of it that I would  never  be able to go back to being your buddy. I guess my main question is do you even care?  Really.  Do you care one little iota at all?  Am I worth anything.  Because you're making me feel worthless.  Did you know that?  You really are.  I feel like I am because the only time we talk is when no one is around that could "tell" on you.  Do you care at all what that makes me feel like?  I want to know. "I miss..."  You say you do too... but then you ignore me when I ask.  My room is in the same place.  The number is still the same.  Am I not worth a conversation.  I know that I'm not worthy of much else, apparently... but...  Do you care at all? Because I'm dying... and it looks like you're A-OK.   Despite what you tell everyone other than me.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I wonder how many times I would have to say or type the words I'm sorry for this to be fixed?   Probably until my fingers fell off... and I'd be typing with my toes... Until my toes fell off.  And then I'd be typing... pecking the letters with my nose.   I'd do it... all of that, if I thought that it would repent for a stupid friend's stupid actions.  I'll start now... I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry...   I'm sorry    I'd type that forever... I really would... :(
     

    
</post>

<date>19,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Today is Easter... one of my favorite holiday's despite the very blatant religious theme.  I've never been sure why that is... why I like it so much that is.  Maybe because my birthday sometimes falls on Easter, or it's usually really close to it. Today, though, is one of those bittersweet days.  I'm glad it's Easter and that I'm home.   But I'm upset about a lot of other things.  Things that I'm sorry for, despite the fact that I didn't do them.  Things I wish I could fix, but know I can't.   *sigh* Happy Easter I guess.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Too bad a concussion doesn't automatically mean you forget things. There are a few things I'd kill to forget.   Stupid friends who've ruined a friendship or any chance of one. Mexico. Rainbows. *sigh*   So many things associated with Mexico and Rainbows. It's all still there though, right in the front of my memory. Even if my head is bruised, it's still all right there.   I wish it would all just go away....
     

    
</post>

<date>18,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I wish you would just   butt out .
     

    
</post>

<date>18,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      There aren't enough ways to apologize for my friend overstepping every boundry there is.  There simply aren't enough words or ways to say "sorry." I am though.  Sorry that is.  Now I know that he'll never speak to me again... never.  I deserve it for having a friend that would be so stupid.  I understand that she was trying to help... in her own way, but it wasn't helpful.  At all.   I wish with everything in me that she had minded her own business.  I wish that there was a way for him to believe I didn't know about this until it happened... and that I never would have condoned it had I known.  I'm MORTIFIED by this whole thing, and I feel horrible.  I was trying so hard to be a friend... it mattered so much to me to be a good friend.  Because I care so much.  And now that's all ruined.  Because of one stupid act by my "friend".   This can't be fixed.   Because of one friend... I'm losing another.   I'm Sorry .
     

    
</post>

<date>15,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      What am I suppose to make of the two cards I got today? How am I suppose to not be confused... when I get that in my inbox?   How? I'd love to know...  Not that they didn't make me smile in some dark place that I can't admit for fear of losing my sanity. But mostly they just confused... and I want to know how I'm suppose to not be confused.   How? If I knew how, then It'd be better.  Then it wouldn't hurt so much.   *read song below...*
     

    
</post>

<date>14,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      "Take me, touch me, Hold me like you mean it Make me come alive Hurt me, Heal me Come and make me feel it Rescue me tonight Love me back to life..." -Bon Jovi
     

    
</post>

<date>14,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I got the job. I got into the grad school.  I just wish I could be happy...  Perhaps if I was moving to a place where I knew someone... other than someone who doesn't really want to talk to me anymore...  (or perhaps that's just my perception... I don't know).  I know that this is a good opportunity.   I know this is going to be an amazing experience And that my master's degree is going to be completely paid off.   I'm just afraid to be alone out there. It sounds childish.   But it's how I feel.  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      And thank you Jordan, for fixing my links.   It's so much more aesthetically pleasing now.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Tomorrow is my birthday.   And I wish a lot of things were different.   I wish that things were better for someone I care about... probably more than I should at this point.  I wish I was some help to him... Rather than feeling like I'm just bothersome.  Rather than feeling like I'm a source of misery.  I've tried so hard not to be that.  So hard.  I've avoided everything that I'm feeling... all these horrible feelings that stem from things before last Friday and because of Friday.  Instead of talking about that I've tried so hard to be supportive and a good friend.  It's important to me that I am... and I just feel like I'm failing.  I hate that feeling. I wish that I didn't feel so alone in all of this.  I just wish that so many things were different.  I wish I had been a better friend when I got a phone call at 2:30 in the morning... I wish that I fully understood why that call happened in the first place since it seems like talking to me is some form of punishment.  Although at the same time I know that's not true.  Or at least I'd like to believe that it's not true.  I'd like to believe that it's not me... that it's just stuff he has to deal with.   I care so much.  And maybe I shouldn't, but I do.  I care on a lot of different levels, but mostly just the level where he's someone who's meant quite a lot to me for a really long time (almost three years total).  I don't want to lose someone who's had such a dramatic impact on my life.  I don't want to just fade into oblivion because I value him... and not just as someone I dated.  It's not about that.  It's about so much more than that.   Maybe I shouldn't be writing this...  I suppose I should be happy and upbeat and excited that tomorrow's my birthday.   I'm not though. This "I'm OK" mask is slowly slipping away.   I'm upset about things I haven't dealt with yet... so many things.   I'm scared that I'm going to lose this person's friendship... terrified really.  Because he matters so much.  Whether that means anything to him or not is a completely different story.   I just wish everything was different... and if not "everything" than at least some things. Perhaps when I blow out the imaginary candles on the imaginary cake tomorrow, I'll get my wish...
     

    
</post>

<date>13,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I feel as if I'm the butt of some cosmic joke.  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      yay! all fixed!
     

    
</post>

<date>11,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      big links are fixed?
     

    
</post>

<date>11,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Have you ever found yourself somewhere in your life and you really have absolutely no idea how you got there?   I look around and I don't know how I got here.  I don't understand what the hell I did wrong.  I don't understand what I did to deserve this.  I just don't understand.  It's just... blah.  I'm totally overwhelmed and I feel as if I'm totally lost in everything.    I don't know if I want to be found anymore.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Today has been a really good day. Really good. I found out I got hired at the job I recently interviewed for.  Now I just have to get into their Grad school and I'll be all set. And I got to see a certain someone without simply watching them walk past me...  which made me happier than I can possibly describe. *smile*
     

    
</post>

<date>09,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Have you ever... missed someone so much it feels like you can't breathe?  Have you ever... cared so much about someone that it feels like your heart is breaking?  (i have i have i have)  Have you ever... wanted something so bad it hurt?  Have you ever... cried so hard, so much there were no tears anymore?  (i have i have i have)  I miss you like that. I care about you like that. I want this like that. I cry like that.  (i do i do i do)
     

    
</post>

<date>08,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      i want to       fit into a pretty     little package with ribbons....
     

    
</post>

<date>08,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Another thing I realized today? Sitting and reading some of the most amazing poetry I've ever read (my friend is really talented... stunningly so) That it's been FAR too long since I've written Anything  worthwhile.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Today I sat talking to a friend I hadn't spoken to in far too long...  (and the reasons for the not speaking part don't really matter...  most of them were stupid or unintentional)  But today I sat talking to her... And I realized how much I had missed just doing that and having someone other than my journal  and my two other good friends here to talk to about things.  
     

    
</post>

<date>08,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Fly  by Poe  It makes sense that it should happen this way That the sky should break, and the earth should shake as if to say: sure it all matters but in  such an unimportant way as if to say:  fly away sweet bird of prey fly fly away nothing can stand in your way sweet bird if you knew the words I know you would say:         fly away  It makes sense that it should HURT in this way That my heart should break and my  hands should shake- as if to say: sure it don't matter except in the  most important way As if to say:   Fly away sweet bird of prey fly fly away nothing can stand in your way sweet bird if you knew the words I know you'd say:      Fly away  It makes sense that it should feel just this way That you slowly fade and yet still remain- as if to say Everythign matters in such an INVISIBLE way as if to say- Fly Away. It's OK
     

    
</post>

<date>08,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Not sure if this will work... but if you want to see me and my spirited support of the Syracuse Orangemen, go to the link below (hopefully there's a link below!)  It's me in my boss's huge sweatshirt!  urlLink  GO 'CUSE   
     

    
</post>

<date>07,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      'CUSE WON!!!!!!!!!!! Syracuse that is.   And the final four is what they won!   YAYYAYYAYYAYYAY!!!  Definitely a damn good game. And definitely helped me get my mind off of stuff.   GO 'CUSE!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>06,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      So... I'm scared.   And sad. And... a lot of things.  Mostly sad and scared.  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      "I don't want you to hate me."   There's another thing that should've been thought of BEFORE all of this.       *sigh*  my birthday is in 6 days.  And I'm losing everything.  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      This weekend was really great.  Really, really great. I almost bought a stuffed donkey named 'Fiesta'. My birthday present to myself because it reminded me of 'Mexico'...  and other things. I resisted the temptation. And 'Cuse won!!!!  And a lot of really nice things happened.   Very nice things. Feel free to ask me about them.... *smile*  By the way: Did you know I have a "hot cha-cha-cha"?  *feel free to ask about that one too!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I had this dream last night... or maybe it was this morning. An amazing dream.   All about "mexico"  And wishes. And missing no more.    I hate having to wake up from dreams like that.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I have been told I look "cute"  far too many times today.  Huge sweatshirt makin' me look rather little *grin*  All I need now is a set of pigtails!   GO CUSE!  I'm off for the weekend.   If I wanted you to know where I'll I would have told you already.  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Tomorrow is 'Cuse Day'  Since Syracuse is going to the big east final four. *YAY CUSE* I wanted to be spirted, so I asked Ryan to borrow a shirt. He lent me his sweatshirt. LOL I can no longer find my hands. HAHAHAHA I'm *swimming* in this damn thing.  GO CUSE
     

    
</post>

<date>02,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      12 Days until my birthday....    Wonder if I'll get what I want?   I wish, I wish... I think you know what I wish.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      So the words "pathetic" "emotionally stunted" "incapable of commitment" "deeply disappointing" and  "Exactly like Lauren" come to mind.  I'm done wasting my time with someone who's far too old to be this young. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      A note from Cheer Bear:    OK, I've been hanging in the damn closet long enough.      It's about time you both simmer down     And just stop being ridiculous.    Damnit.     *A note from me? I wish I wish... I think you know what I wish.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      "V: so how are things beside you missing an old friend?" "Me: i miss more than an old friend."  "V: Alright.  You miss him completely."  That's the understatement of the decade.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      13 days until my birthday.  I wonder if I'll get what I want?        And if you don't know what it is I want... then obviously I don't want anything from you.  Well... nothing you're going to actually give me in any case.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I guess disappearing is what "you" want. Fine. That's what I'll do.   But not entirely.   You're going to be able to see  everytime I'm out with someone being happy with someone and making them happy. And while you're on this grand search to find what it is you already had, I'll be barely there. And then you'll look for me. You'll realize that you're looking for what you already had. But then I'll be gone.  Suit yourself.  This life is too short to walk away from things that mean something.  And life is definitely too short to screw something up that you claim to want so much.  But since "you" can so easily ignore me (I guess that "maturity" was a facade, because "you" ignored me once again), I'll disappear.  Me and all those things that were so perfect for you will vanish.  My mind, my voice, my everything.   Since that's what you seem to want. And I've always given "you" what you wanted.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I think there are several thoughts that have been running through my head on a fairly regular loop today. They include the words "I miss". They include the words "Hmmm...."   Most of all, though, they include the words, "Don't you dare..." That sentence has ended a lot of ways in my head today. "Don't you dare think that." "Don't you dare confuse me again."  And most importantly, "Don't you dare get your hopes up again because you may very well end up back where you started."   And I don't want to end up there again.    So don't let me get my hopes up.   I miss a lot.   And I want a lot.  Another thought I'll have, as I curl up in my bed  (you know, that bed that calls for me amongst other things)  The thought I'll have is  'I wish, I wish... I think you know what I wish.'  Well, that thought...  And the dream I had last night.  Hopefully I'll have it again.  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Today's thought... Me too.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I had this dream last night.   This amazing dream.   Full of rainbows and "mexico"  And all that.   And lots of other good things.   I didn't want to wake up.  
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Guess what? I'm a muchly smiley girl.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      There are six and a half hours (or so) to wait.   Have I mentioned how much I  hate  waiting... even when it's something/someone worth waiting for. I am impatience personified.  *smile*
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Have I mentioned just how much you make me smile?   Because if I haven't...  you should know that you do.  A lot. *smile*
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
        Remember those who have fallen...  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      OOOOOOOOOOOOOH... Guess what? Only  4  days left.   HOORAY!!  *smiley chiquita*
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Guess what? I'm sooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo proud of you! And guess what else? I'm sooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo happy for you! But guess what  else ? I knew I'd be saying that!  wahahahahahahaha
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I think honesty is something I value more than almost anything on this earth... The fact that you were honest? That puts you at the top of that list.  Thank you ...   6 days... *wink*
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I worry a lot about this... because of everything that's happened... but more because I care so much about this.    about  you 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Graduation Day    Go here to see my favorite graduation present.   (I hope I get to keep it).
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      So my allotted dream time was definitely cut short last night... because I couldn't fall asleep.  I was worried... that you wouldn't want to come still.  That you wouldn't mean what you said.  I much prefer talking to you until 11:30 and then dragging myself to bed with a smile on my face.   I want you here.   And I trust that you meant what you said...  Is it next week yet?  Can we just skip to that? 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm hanging on to the last shred of hope that I've got in me... And I'm telling myself that the way things were couldn't have been an illusion, and that they couldn't have been just there out of convenience.  And I'm telling myself over and over again... reminding myself actually, about the letter I received on graduation and about everything that's been said the past few days.  I'm reminding myself and telling myself that those things meant something. And I'm telling myself you probably didn't get the message... or you needed some time to process some things.   Or something.   You mean more to me than anyone has in a long time, or I wouldn't have stuck around.  You know that.  I think you figured that out the night before graduation... just how much you meant to me.   I thought I meant the same to you... and I'm telling myself over and over that I do.  And that this is something that will be figured out and settled and all that.  I think of bowling and of everything else that happened that night and the next one... and I think of the night before and the very early morning of our graduation.  I know that meant something.  I know you wouldn't have written that letter if you didn't mean it.   I want you to come here next week.  But only if I'm the only one.  At this point I feel entitled to ask for that.... 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
       GOOD LUCK TODAY G!!!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I've been having many smiley dreams lately... Perhaps I should say thank you...  :)
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      There's a place I would much rather be... Sleeping. In PA. *grin*  Make room... *wink*
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I am now a college graduate... Onwards and upwards...
     

    
</post>

<date>16,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      And who says you don't get what you want? :)
     

    
</post>

<date>16,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      ...OK, So the words "wow"  and "What just happened" spin around in my head.    you know how much this means to me, right?  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      You know that feeling you get when you're with someone and you know you want to say something... but you can't because it'll shatter this facade you've worked out, silently, between the two of you? And you know that feeling you get when you're with someone and you get the unmistakable feeling that they would really rather be anywhere else... and that they're just sitting next to you due to a combination of boredom/concern that you may just lose your mind if they weren't sitting there? I hate those feelings.   I hate so much of this.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm really not sure how to do this. And I can't very well ask you, can I? "How do you pretend nothing ever happened?" "How do you pretend you never heard me crying?" "How do you pretend that you never hurt me?" Because you wouldn't like those questions. And I'm sure I wouldn't like the answers.     Here I go... falling back into that familiar role...  I don't want to be that... 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
        "Bright Lights" by Matchbox 20  She got out of town on the railway, new york bound Took all except my name Another alien on broadway Well, some things in this world you just can't change Some things you can't see until it gets too late  [Chorus]  Baby, baby, baby when all your love is gone Who will save me from all I'm up against out in this world And maybe, maybe, maybe You'll find something that's enough to keep you But if the bright lights don't receive you You should turn yourself around and come on home  I got a hole in me now I got a scar I can talk about She keeps a picture of me in her apartment in the city But some things in this world Man, they don't make sense Some things you don't leave until they leave you  And then the things that you miss, you say  [Chorus]  Baby, baby, baby when all your love is gone Who will save me from all I'm up against out in this world And maybe, maybe, maybe You'll find something that's enough to keep you But if the bright lights don't receive you You should turn yourself around and come on home  Let that city take you in (come on home) Let that city spit you out (come on home) Let that city take you down, yeah For god sakes turn around  [Chorus]  Baby, baby, baby when all your love is gone Who will save me from all I'm up against out in this world Yeah well, maybe, maybe, maybe You'll find something that's enough to keep you But if the bright lights dont receive you Well, turn yourself around and come on home  Yeah, come on home Baby, baby, baby, baby Come on home Yeah, come on home Yeah, come on home Yeah, come on home Baby, baby, baby, baby Come on home  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      ...And speaking of bittersweet. Spending time with you.  Bittersweet indeed ...
     

    
</post>

<date>10,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      One more week until I leave  Bittersweet ...
     

    
</post>

<date>05,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      You know how sometimes you're going through a really rough time and you feel like it's never going to get any better because it's been so long since you've had one thing to smile about really?  You know how it feels like that horrible time will never end? And then you have a night where... it's just so damn good.  And all you can do is smile and laugh and feel good about everything.  And you look around, and you look inside yourself... and you know without a shadow of a doubt that everything is fine, or that it's going to be really soon?   That's where I'm at right now. *smile*
     

    
</post>

<date>04,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Let me tell you something...  not one person really knows me. You all know what I let you see (minus a few people... and you know who you are) But to the two or three morons who actually believed I was sitting here twiddling my thumbs I'm laughing at just how pathetic  you  are. It was never like that, nor will it ever be like that. Being upset is one thing... and I have every right to be that.  Because what happened here was far from my fault.  But while I am upset, a lot else great has been happening.   A lot no one cared to ask me about, so I just didn't bother with getting into it.   I'm smiling today.  As I've been smiling inside for quite some time. So don't ever assume you know me or anything about me. Just like someone else, I show you only what I see fit. The rest is all a smoke screen, an illusion. And when it comes down to it, I'm the only one who really knows  what the trick is.   *poof*  And for my next trick... I'll pull my middle finger out of my hat.  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      This has been a losing battle since day one. I'm waving my white flag.  Defeated 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      "Can you take it all away can you take it all away well ya shoved it in my face this pain you gave to me Can you take it all away can you take it all away well ya shoved it my face..." -puddle of mudd  *you could take it away, but you choose not to... instead you choose to continue to lie and hurt. So be it.   I'm better than that, and I'm worth a whole lot more than that. You know that as well as I do... if not better. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      "No, I haven't."  That's a direct quote in response to: "It seems as if you've made up your mind."   Funny (in the ironic sense), that your "No I haven't" looks a whole hell of a lot like "yes you have." Because, guess what?   You're not alone.   And every action you make says that you don't give one flying fuck about me.   Prove me wrong.   It'd be nice to be wrong.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      For G:  Fuck you.  Love, C
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      " 'Cause I can't take any more of this  I wanna' come apart..." -Staind
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      It would appear that I've been a really big fucking moron. Yet again. "I never want to see you hurt." OK.   So what's your fucking explanation? Because I went to work crying this morning.  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      "Don't be neurotic."    Thanks Bri ;-)
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      You know when you want to say something  so badly  that the unsaid words are sitting there, in your head... in your mouth, burning a hole in the tip of your tongue?   It starts to feel like you're sucking on an acid lollypop...  and it's more important to keep on keeping your mouth full of the unsaid, than to say what's on your mind. God I hate that.     ps- don't get worried... i'm ok.   i love you 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hooray for being somewhat computer savy!
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      askldf;alksd;lasdkj;fdlkjas;dlkjald;skja;slkjdf;lasdkj  sorry.  couldn't think of anything better to say to express how I'm feeling right now.  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm fairly certain that I must begin doing something other than just going to work every day...  this "something other" must include running or biking or going to the gym... or "something" because seriously... i feel rather blah about me currently.   Perhaps that's silly and unfounded and all that... but that's how I feel.   Strenuous exercise, here I come... :-/
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I would really like to watch Star Wars.   wahahahahahaha
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I find myself wondering, rather frequently... just what it is that I did to get so lucky.   Also, I find myself hoping that I keep doing whatever it was...  because I'm rather fond of this whole thing. (fond doesn't even come close).   :)
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm rather sick... And I'm also rather smiley. Uncommon combination. Thank you for being wonderful you... and making me smile even though I look and feel as if a mack truck ran me over and then threw itself in reverse and went for another pass. You are fantabulous. :)
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hooray for being a "responsible adult" and going to work even when you're really damn sick. Food poisoning kicks ass.  :(
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I really hope you realize/know just how much I love you.   Because I do...  so much .   More every second.   I must warn you, though... that if you keep making me smile this much I'm afraid my face may get stuck this way ;-)  
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I don't think there's a time during the day when I'm not smiling because of you.   Something you said... or something you did.   Or something. Heehee. love you :)
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      A month ago today I got the best graduation present ever.  You . I win.   Love you *kiss*
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
       The 16th of June  by Me It came to an end  That fate-filled day.  Now I can't chase  The storm away.  I remember the rain  How it fell in a sheet.  I remember how it sounded,  A steady, deadly beat.  I remember the thunder,  How it crashed and boomed.  It rumbled aloud  As the clouds loomed.  I remember the movie,  How I sat and laughed.  Nothing was more important,  Than our friendly craft.  I remember the phone call,  When she asked me to come home.  When I begged to stay,  And left her alone.  I remember I was early,  Arrived at 4:28.  I was going to gloat,  That I wasn't late.  I remember her form,  Slumped on the couch.  How she was half on the floor,  Half in a slouch.  I remember the sirens  Screaming toward the house.  I covered my ears,  Meak as a mouse.  I remember the lights,  Flashing on the wall.  Then I realized,  It was all my fault.  I remember it all,  Hope it all goes away soon.  1993,  The 16th of June.      
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I've made a rule... and although it has been a rule in my mind for quite some time I have decided to put it in writing.   The good stuff is about   urlLink You    The not good stuff is about something else entirely. So that's a rule.    I love you . :)  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm sorry I worried you.  I think sometimes I forget that you read this, and if you don't know what's going through my head when I write something you'll get concerned. I love you for reading. And I love you for worrying. But all is well.   Wearing a denim shirt everyday will make even the sexiest of chiquitas feel insecure.  :)
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm having a rather insecure day.   Not entirely sure why. Just am. Blah to that.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      So many things spinning through my head right now.   *sigh*  And I shouldn't write any of them down here...
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      http://www.niagara.edu/housing/hall.htm  urlLink Check Out Seton Hall      That's where I'll be an RD next year!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I hope I make you smile even half as much as you make me smile...  Because you excell at this whole making me smile thing...  So even if I only make you smile half as often as you make me smile, then I'm doing alright :)  (although I hope that I make you smile as much as you make me smile... because then I too would be excelling... and I'd really love to excell at making you happy).   :)
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      "When you're drowning, you don't say 'I would be incredibly pleased if someone would have the foresight to notice me drowning and come and help me,' you just scream."  -John Lennon
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
        urlLink Ramblin' Is Fun    
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      There's this truly amazing boy that I know... And guess what?  I love him. Guess what else?  I miss him muchly. And guess what  else ? I win... because he's mine.   Wahahahaha   Thank you for being so wonderful.  I love you .
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I guess I should apologize... because I seriously am not being very great right now. Give me a week or two and I'll be back to normal.    My mood has nothing to do with anyone else but me.   (especially not a very special, wonderful boy who I love VERY much) OK?   And I'm really OK... I promise.  :)   You make me smile.  A lot.  
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Sleep did not come easily last night... nor did it last when it finally arrived. Blah.   Hopefully tonight it all works itself out.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Blah.   That's the only word that comes to mind.  Blah.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Yet again... I am a smiley smiley girl.   This time I must say... Phone calls from Montana make me smile. See?  *GRIN*  silly silly... sleepy chiquita.  :)
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Phone calls from Wyoming make me smile. See? *GRIN*   Although I think phone calls from anywhere would make me smile, as long as you were the one calling.  :)
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I don't think anyone has ever called me from so far away before. *smile*  You just keep making me smile.   I miss you . 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
         "cuz you know that i'm just like you i can get shy, hell, i can shut down but we're gathering up everything that scares us we'll divide it by two and you'll see there ain't nothing we can't shut down  cuz i like you, i like you, could you maybe like me, too? i like you, i like you, could it really be that simple?" -Edie Carey  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      This is basically a new feeling... this whole 'can't stop smiling' thing.  And I know why I can't.  I know who is responsible for this phenomenon.   heeheehee I hope they know just how happy they make me, and how much they mean to me.  I hope I've made that clear... because they do.  Make me  so  happy and mean   so   much to me.   I really hope I make that perfectly clear.   You are wonderful.  You are the reason I've been smiling the last two and a half weeks.  You're the reason I didn't stop smiling the last four days.  And you're the reason I'll continue smiling for days and weeks and a long time to come.   You're my smile.  :)
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I don't think I've smiled as much in months... as I did all weekend.  I know that I never really stopped smiling this weekend, even in my sleep.  Even when I wasn't smiling outside, I know I was smiling inside.  Amazing weekends make me a very smiley Chiquita.  Amazing boys (the ones called Guampo anyway) make me very very happy.     Miss you already... 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      So I'm fairly sure I'm more confused than ever. About everything. So many questions spin around in my head, and I shove them back down,  because the last time I asked I got the answer "I don't know." I hate that answer. And now, it seems like you do. Know that is. I rather like that, and prefer it to not knowing. Although... I don't know. Where we stand that is. If I were to go on appearances, I'd say "well, obviously we stand together." I'm just wondering if that's such a smart assumption; it got me into trouble before. I'm also wondering if appearances are right... then does everyone know about them? Selfish and unfair of me to a point.  I suppose. *sigh*   I really just have no fucking clue.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm nervous.  Really nervous.   And I'm scared to move all the way out there.  Really scared. It's only two hours from the nearest friend... well, the nearest real friend anyway. Six hours from my family.   *sigh* I'm scared I'm going to mess this up.  I don't know why.   I just am.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I keep hearing your voice...  you saying "I love you" before we hung up.  And I keep having to talk myself out of calling you three times a day just so I can hear it again and know it wasn't a dream...
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      It was nice...  two weeks ago I knew there was at least one person who read this.   And they cared about what I had to say. I don't have enough words, right now, to describe how  empty  it feels knowing that might not be happening anymore. Ironic, isn't it?   I don't have enough words... more ironic still? I lack words to describe how empty feels. *sigh*
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      "Aren't I lovely  And do you want me cause  I am hungry for something that will make me real Can you see me and   Do you love me cause  I am desperately searching for something  Real..." -Plumb 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Here's a secret for you.   I miss you . 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Check out This Chica's Hair    This is how I'm thinking of getting my hair cut.  Any comments?  (assuming someone out there is reading!
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      So... it appears as if the only person who cared enough about me to come here and read this has stopped. This raises two dilemas:  1) Should I keep writing here when nobody's reading? 2) Does that mean you don't care anymore?   *order is reversed just so the second one doesn't overpower the first on the screen the way it does in my head... and in my heart.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      There's really nothing worse than being confused... or at least I don't think so.   Like this whole seeing something that two weeks ago I was sure was meant for me...  now I don't know if it's for me or if it's not or if it's just a habbit.  I don't know. And it's not like I didn't ask.   I don't know if no answer means that it is or it isn't.   Blah.    All I know for sure is that I wish I could've just been content with being confused for another fifteen mintues... then I would've gotten more kisses.  I love those.           I love you  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      When  urlLink the person who dries your tears    makes you cry, who do you turn to? 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      You know, I don't know what's going to happen.  I hate this feeling of dread that's been sitting in the pit of my stomach for the past week.   All I know for sure is that I love you.   I'm fairly sure that you feel the same way about me. *sigh* I'm hoping with everything in me that I'm not wrong.   We all make mistakes.  And we've both made more than our share over the last year.  I don't want to lose you now based on stupid mistakes that happened a year ago.  
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I feel like everything I say is wrong right now.  I told you about that day so you'd know how much you meant to me... not to make you angry.   And it made you upset...  And I'm  so sorry  because I obviously screwed up when you needed me... and I didn't even realize it.  I never wanted to make you feel like I didn't care about what you were going through.   Ever .  Because I care  all the time .  And I want to be there every second for everything... the happy and the sad and everything in between.   I feel like I'm going to lose you... and I don't want that.  I really really don't want that, because you are wonderful and amazing... and you make me feel so happy.  And I thought I was making you happy... and I want to keep doing that, or trying really hard.   *sigh* I feel like nothing I say is right.  You always say the right things to make everything "ok"... and I just feel like you hate me right now because my words get all jumbled up.    I'm sorry . I'll be quiet... Just don't forget that I love you?   (and don't forget that you love me?)
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I have wonderful coworkers... Even if they were joking around about what they said, it really made me smile for a very long time.    Thank you boys .  :)
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      You know something?   This all started a year ago.  A little more than a year ago.  This little dance... back and forth and back and forth we went, knowing we wanted each other and each alternately too scared or angry or hurt to just do what we wanted... get what we wanted (each other). It's taken us a little more than a year to finally get what we wanted.    I've been thinking about that, and do you know what I've concluded?   When you've fought so long and through so much to get something, you don't walk away from it after a month and a half.  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      so.  the sick feeling is subsiding a little...  i'm not sure it'll go away completely, unless this works itself out.  it's so hard for me to trust people... and i did (and oddly enough still do) trust you. if that's not worth something, then nothing is.  :-/
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I just realized something... I'm contradicting myself. The whole, "Everything was a lie" argument vs. the whole, "No, I don't think so" is kind of getting on my nerves. I think I should clarify for myself... Not  everything  was a lie.  Far from it.  I think everything was true  except  the very  minor  detail about things being "over" with her. I believe everything else was true. I think that just confuses me, which is why I argue with it.   But I believe that that was the only lie... a huge lie, but the only one nonetheless.  Ask yourself if it's smart to walk away from someone who made you feel like that.  Ask your friends if it's smart.  Ask any of my friends.  Life is too short to hang on to something that isn't making you happy.  Life is too short to hang on to something that you know you don't want.  And life is definitely too short to keep hurting someone you claim that you "never want to see hurt."   and p.s.- life is most assuredly too short to walk away from someone who filled an email account with presents.  you don't find that every day.  I know that life is too short.  I learned that a long time ago.  How long do you think that I'll ignore my own advice?  And how long can you pretend not to care?  How long can you hide? I hope you're not too late.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      It's shitty... Anger is my defense mechanism right now.   Because if I don't get angry I'm just going to cry.   Forever.   (if this is true anyway) And I can't cry any more.  I did that for three months.  Three long months.  And you didn't care about it then. So I'm not going to do it now.   I want the last month to not be a lie.  That's all I want.   I want the words, "I never want to see you hurt," to mean something. Because right now I'm hurt.  You're suppose to care about that.  You said you did...
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Maybe I am jumping to a conclusion.  Maybe two of my close friends are wrong.  Maybe things aren't what they seem.  But it hasn't been refuted at all.  There hasn't been one attempt made at trying to get in touch with me to "fix" this.    My thoughts this morning are rather bitter.  But they include: "Do you want the necklace back or should I just send it to her when I mail her the IMs and Emails?" I know... awful isn't it?    If what I heard was true... (and I want with everything in me to believe that it's not), then it's clear to me that he is no better than the last person I was with.  After such animosity toward my last boyfriend... "He really was an asshole wasn't he?"  I cannot believe that you would do the same thing.  It makes me sick.     "I never want to see you hurt."  Was that another lie?   Or do you have a plausible explanation for this?
     

    
</post>

<date>30,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I feel so very alone.   And maybe that's only because all my good friends are scattered everywhere in the state, but none of them are here. And maybe it's because the level of uncertainty in my mind in one aspect of my life is extremely high and I feel as if I'm drowning in confusion. And maybe it's because I'm in a new place and feel as if there's no one here I can really talk to. Maybe it's a combination of things. All I know is I've never felt more alone in my life. 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Blahblahblahblahblahblahblahblahblahblahblahblah.  doyouhearmescreaming?  blahblahblahblahblahblahblahblahblahblahblahblah.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      So many things spinning through my head... I just want them to stop.   I just want to go back to being happy,  like I was two months ago.  I just want things to be simple and to feel like I matter.   That's all I want.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I would  kill  to just have someone wrap their arms around me and hold me for a long time right about now. (i'm picky about who...) I just really need that right now.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      "...There are so many things I need to get out in the open. Things I can speak freely about. And other things I can't. (because...)  I want to play the part of the badass about this, so that I don't have to cry. So that I don't have to show my wounds. I want to wear the tough-girl clothes, and wear the tought-girl face. talk the talk.  you know?  but I can't.   She isn't me. And that's not my face.  I know what she wants to say, though.  There a million things she has tried to chase away.  (The rain is coming.  Steady, steady downpour.)  I'd rather the storms calm soon, than turn into something I can't handle.    I can scarcely handle this."     -Sohpie Marchant  * i respect, admire, and envy the person who wrote this so much.  sophie is an absolutely beautiful, amazing person... and right now her words express how i'm feeling better than any of mine do (and believe me i've tried to do my thoughts justice... i just have nothing left in me that works).  i wish i had words like this in me... words that made it all clear and beautiful despite my pain and confusion. This is just how I feel... even if the words aren't mine.  I'm glad I have these, at least, that I can read and share to help my mind stop spinning...
     

    
</post>

<date>22,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      "I'm standing on a bridge I'm waiting in the dark I thought that you'd be here by now there's nothing but the rain no footsteps on the ground I'm listening but there's no sound  Isn't anyone trying to find me? Won't somebody come take me home?  It's a damn cold night trying to figure out this life won't you take me by the hand take me somewhere new I don't know who you are but I, I'm with you I'm with you.  I'm looking for a place I'm searching for a face is anybody here I know? Cuz' nothing's going right and everything's a mess and no one likes to be alone  Isn't anyone trying to find me Won't somebody come take me home?  It's a damn cold night trying to figure out this life won't you take me by the hand take me somewhere new I don't know who you are but I, I'm with you I'm with you.  Why is everything so confusing? Maybe I'm just out of my mind...  It's a damn cold night trying to figure out this life won't you take me by the hand take me somewhere new I don't know who you are but I, I'm with you I'm with you  Take me by the hand take me somewhere new I don't know who you are but I, I'm with you."     -Avril Lavigne
     

    
</post>

<date>21,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Tears will wet my pillow tonight. And I won't sleep.     I suppose I'm the one to blame here.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm getting very close to throwing up my hands and just saying, "I give up." Do you realize that? Do you even fucking care?
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      "Tell me what it feels to be the one who turns the knife inside of me..."  -Aerosmith  *not that it matters.   obviously. but that's how i feel right now.    ps- they're playing a concert with kiss on Aug 23rd at Darrien Lake and I want to go more than I've ever wanted to do anything in my life.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      i want, simply, to know that there's some sense of security in something... i want to know that there's something i can count on. and right now there's  nothing .   because it's all uncertain. and i fucking hate that.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      "what i want is to not want what isn't mine..."  -another girl's paradise, tori amos
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      "The bad stuff is easier to believe... did you ever notice that?" -Julia Roberts 'Pretty Woman'
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I feel this constant need to apologize... for feeling how I do for acting how I do for being the way I am. And it wasn't that way three months ago.  I don't even know if I can say that three months counts. Should I have even been counting? *here I go again... being how I am*  But it's right there between us.   Like a wall. And the only way to knock it down is to talk about it and get rid of "it".   I've tried to do that, with no luck. I guess it's not important... or a priority to knock down a wall between us. And it's a lot easier to avoid all the work of getting rid of it than it is to do it.    Dejavu
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      So I 'm finally here, settled, with internet in my apartment. I'm still feeling a bit at sea, but I'm hoping that I'm doing alright.  Everyone seems to think so. I miss everyone from home so much.   And I miss a certain boy very much.   Everyone needs to come visit soon.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Ok... odds of anyone reading are slim to none. I just wanted to ammend the previous entry. There are a few people who give a flying fuck.   you know who you are .  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I feel alone. That's how I feel. And sad. And... why the fuck do I bother?  No one gives one flying fuck how I'm feeling right now.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      It's weird... how much she can still hurt me.   Tonight she reminded me, once again, why I distanced myself in the first place. I can't describe how much she hurt me tonight, in the two minutes I saw her. I wish I could close myself off from that...
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Best I'll Ever Be by Sister Hazel Oh I miss you I miss being overwhelmed by you And I need rescue I think I'm fading away  But I keep thinking That you'll wake me up with a whisper in my ear I keep hoping That you'll sneak in my room  So I wait And I wait And I run old scenes through my tired head of the days that we laid by the school and said forever Was that the best I'll ever be?  Oh I miss you I miss talking all night long with you yeah And I need this to find a way to your home  Oh, my love  Can you hear me? Have I been hoping loud enough? Wishing hard enough? Can you see me when I'm asleep all alone alone?  So I wait And I wait And I run myself in the same old circles I sit  and I stare and I run old scenes through my tired head of the days that we laid by the school and said forever Was that the best I'll ever be?  I can't keep my hands from shaking I'm stumbling through the wreakage again But you're gone So I wait And I wait And I run myself in the same old circles I sit  and I stare And I run old scenes through my tired head of the days that we laid on our backs and said forever Oh was that the best I'll ever be? Was that the best I'll ever be? Oh was that the best I'll ever be?   Sister Hazel Rocks My World.  
     

    
</post>

<date>30,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I will never again hear the song 'Rainbow Connection' without thinking of  you  and being sad and angry...  and a lot of emotions that I don't want to talk about Mostly sad. Whenever I hear it, I think of you... and things like Mexico that I want to forget.   "Rainbows are visions but only illusions..." -Kermit T. Frog 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
       I'm Moving On by Rascal Flats  I've dealt with my ghosts and faced all my demons finally content with the past I regret I found you find strength in your moments of weakness for once I'm at peace with myself I've been burdened with blame trapped in the past for too long I'm movin' on  I've lived in this place and I know all the faces Each one is different but they're always the same They mean me no harm but it's time that I face it They'll never allow me to change But I never dreamed home would end up where I don't belong I'm movin' on  I'm moving on At last I can see (last I can see Life has been patiently waiting for me And I know there's no guarentees But I'm not alone There comes a time in everyone's life When all you can see are the years passing by (are the years passing by) And I have made up my mind that those days are gone  I've sold what I could Packed what I couldn't Stopped to fill up on my way out of town I've loved like I should but lived like I shouldn't I had to lose everything to find out Maybe forgiveness will find me somewhere down this road I'm moving on I'm moving on I'm moving on   
     

    
</post>

<date>26,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Sometimes I just don't know what to write.   Like now. No clue whatsoever.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I didn't think it was possible to feel this way. I am absolutely defeated.  I want to just curl up and be held forever and ever... and that just isn't an option.     "Alone would be a pleasant change from here..." -Atreyu 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      When did I become so lonely and alone that I would do anything to not feel that way? When did I turn into this person?   If anyone knows, please fill me in, because right now I disgust myself. 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      What's one more day  week month year of feeling worthless? It's already well established that I mean little to nothing. So what's one more day of having it reinforced?
     

    
</post>

<date>19,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      It was rather unexpected... the conversation last night. I hope that that continues. Because it meant quite a lot to me.  I have no expectations though. I have no hope that it will. I'm done expecting and hoping.   Truly done. They just end you up hurt and alone and wishing you hadn't hoped or expected anything.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Every last word was a lie.    Every last word.   I feel cheap.   I feel betrayed. I feel...   I feel  And damnit I want to stop. I feel worthless. I feel like absolutely nothing. I feel...   I feel  And I would give  anything  to stop.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      "She takes just like a woman, yes she does She makes love just like a woman, yes she does And she aches just like a woman but she breaks just like a little girl."  ~Bob Dylan~
     

    
</post>

<date>16,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
       "Yeah, life throws you curves  But you learned to swerve  Me, I swung and I missed  And the next thing you know, Im reminiscing  Dreaming old dreams  Wishing old wishes  Like you would be back again  I wake up in teardrops that fall down like rain  I put on that old song we danced to and then  I head off to my job, guess not much has changed  Punch the clock, head for home, check the phone just in case  Go to bed, dream of you  Thats what Im doing these days  Yeah, thats what Im doing." -Rascal Flats   (thanks to Monica for these lyrics)
     

    
</post>

<date>15,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      "Write me like a letter  And dot your Is and cross you Ts  Nothing was everything to me  Under the monsters claws and in between his teeth  Was the shadow and a silhouette of what Id thought Id be?  I dont mind falling down and scraping up my knees  Scars and Stitches always fade and only strengthen me..."  -Guster  *they're coming to campus this Sunday!!  Something to look forward to... 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      It's thunder and lightning... and all I want is you here with your arms around me.  I miss you I need you and more than anything I need to know if we're still ok or not... 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
       "Starving Searching this barren wasteland  Trying To grasp being this alone Pleading for a breath of fresh air  Someone's standing on my chest Dying I'm asphyxiating myself Break myself Slave to my weakness Choke on my words Oh I'm drowning and I feel so alone The lights are on and I wish I was home My lips Are screaming pretty nothings  My ears Are bleeding for want of words,  fuck words I need actions Hope has left me fucking shattered  Someone's standing on my chest alone Would be a pleasant change from here How do you gauge loneliness How you ever felt so alone  It feels like the light will never reach me hear I am choking back my longing for shed tears So strangulated by my lonesome fears  Please don't worry too much  It only hurts when I breathe..." -Atreyu  (thanks to Mike, one of my RAs for these lyrics... simply amazing) 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      It's unreal... four days ago I was smiling and looking forward to things and actually feeling as if maybe, just maybe, this would all be ok. Now there's silence once again. And when I did something to express my concern? I heard anger and annoyance in your voice.  Anger and Annoyance  from someone who, four days ago said, "You have no idea how much you mean to me, how much you help me all the time, how much I want us to work, how much I want to come see you." You were right.  I do have no idea.   Especially not now.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I wish I was there to wrap my arms around you and hold you until you felt better. I know that'd be a long time, but I don't ever get tired of having my arms around you. I miss you.  I love you.   I'm here if you need me.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I can't sleep.   This doesn't mean I'm not tired...  it just means that my thoughts are too loud for me to go to sleep. I'm getting sick... sore throat and such. And my eyes are drooping.   But the thought of getting up, going into my bedroom, and climbing into bed isn't very soothing. Everytime I close my eyes I just see everything that's going wrong right now.   Or I see everything I wish was going right... or better. And that's a lot of things, zipping through my brain... Clattering around like the subway.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I have never cried quite this hard. I feel like I've been kicked in the stomach. And I can't stop shaking. Because everything that meant so much to me was just made meaningless  by the person who meant so much. I guess this is what I get for trusting... for believing... for loving.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I feel completely lost.   Completely . Not to mention alone.   I've never felt more alone.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Here they are:  urlLink My Staff!!   This group has made things so much fun so far at NU, and I look forward to spending a lot more time with them, and getting to know them all. BOND THIS!!!!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      And when the person who says they love you has nothing to say to you there's only one thing to say.          goodbye .
     

    
</post>

<date>06,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I sit here and the thoughts in my head just spin and whirl and all I do is wonder what the hell it is I'm doing. What am I fighting for?   When this all started I felt like such a valued part of your life. And now I feel like an inconvenience...  a second thought.   And I'm sick of feeling like I'm fighting a battle that I shouldn't have to fight. I'm sick of feeling sad  and like a failure and like I'm competing for something that was supposedly "mine" four months ago. I'm tired.  I'm sad.   And I'm sick of feeling like that doesn't matter. Like  I  don't matter.    If you care at all ...
     

    
</post>

<date>05,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I think it's about time you come here so I can remind you how amazing you are.   Because you are.   And it's my job to remind you... I'm feeling like I'm not doing such a great job. So, back to my original thought. I think it's about time you come here so I can remind you.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      "This damp air is fighting my defroster. My sighs they ring victorious & fog this tinted glass. It's clouded & so is my head. The hint of these new tears are sharp. I try to hold them back. It's useless. I am useless against them. They are beating me with ease.  On the way home this car hears my confessions. I think tonight I'll take the long way..." -Dashboard Confessional 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I feel like I'm slowly dying. What's really great, is the person who should care  doesn't . Even though they could fix it with something as simple as a conversation or some type of acknowledgement. My heart hurts.   Does that matter at all?
     

    
</post>

<date>02,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm going to stop feeling sad and alone and confused and jumbled up... I know that. I just don't know when.   And that doesn't help me at all.   I would  kill  to have someone just wrap their arms around me and hold me right now.   I need that so badly... to just be absolutely certain that at least one person (the one person holding me) cares enough to do that.  I'm so unsure of everything else that I need to be certain of something. Right now I'm not certain of  anything .       That scares the hell out of me.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Last night I had a lot of dreams... it's the first time in a very long time that I've been able to remember even small parts of what I dreamt anyway.  I can remember a lot of the dreams I had last night... and most of it is stuff I don't want to remember.  Most of the dreams were filled with things that were walking the line between good and bad.  Dreams of all the words said... and all the things left unsaid.  Dreams of all of the fears I have about "it all".  So many fears.   And I dreamt of that beautiful time when there was no doubt or fear or confusion or questioning.  I dreamt of that... and then I woke up.  At first I thought I was just dreaming about all the fears and doubts and questioning and confusion.  Then I realized I'd just woken up to reality...   And I went back to feeling terribly alone...  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      So I finally found a link to allow people who read this to post their comments. I'm rather proud of my computer savy (and my ability to search for a good link and add it to my template).   Heehee.  Right about now this is the type of thing that really makes me happy (gotta' be something right?)
     

    
</post>

<date>29,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'll have to post the link later... but one of my photos got posted on the Yankee Magazine web site.  I'm really excited about it, because I've always loved taking pictures so much.  That's my exciting news...    Everything else is... just ok I suppose.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I don't think I've ever been so proud of something in my life... other than my senior paper.  But this is a lot newer, so right now I'm a bit obsessive:   urlLink My Web Page    
     

    
</post>

<date>20,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I want to stop feeling alone... no.  that's not right. I want to stop  being  alone. Sometimes I really believe that moving here wasn't the best idea. Because I've never felt as alone as I do here.  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Road Trip to PA: October 11th and 12th 2003    
     

    
</post>

<date>17,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
       I quit 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I find myself sitting here, listening to music I stopped listening to because it reminded me of a really dreadful time in my life.  And I find myself missing things before all of the drama that happened that awful year.  I find myself missing someone I shouldn't miss.  I find myself regretting, all over again, things that happened far too long ago to be concerning myself with them now.  It's funny what you miss when you let yourself...  "That's enough Just talking about it i don't mind I don mind no I Laugh enough Just dreaming about it  I need to know if you were real I'd hate to think that I'd been fooled again And as the vision fades I'll say I was blinded by your eyes I felt them burn..." -Vertical Horizon 'Give You Back'
     

    
</post>

<date>14,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
       "I found the pieces in my hand  They were always there It just took some time for me to understand. You gave me words I just can't say So if nothing else I'll just hold on while you drift away 'Cause everything you wanted me to hide Is everything that makes me feel alive. The cities grow The rivers flow Where you are I never know But I'm still here. If you were right and I was wrong Why are you the one who's gone?   And I'm still here I've seen the ashes in my heart I smile the widest  when I cry inside and my insides blow apart. I tried to wear another face Just to make you proud..." -Vertical Horizon 'I'm Still Here'  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      "Nobody's handing out road maps for the road less traveled, you just have to get on the road and start driving."  ~ Dawson's Creek
     

    
</post>

<date>12,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I struggle with two emotions: 1. Being really angry/bitter. 2. Being so worried about you I can hardly stand it.   which one do I go with? 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I can't describe how awesome last night and today were.   And I can't tell you how good it is to be around my friends.  I've missed you guys !!! Jon and Tiani... you guys are wonderful.  You made my weekend, both of you. Monica and Stacy?  YOU KICK ASS.  Friendly's all the way!!!! I need to be with you people more often, because you make me smile.  That's very needed. 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      YAY!  I made it!   Or at least I made it the first part of the trip.  :)
     

    
</post>

<date>09,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Tomorrow I go on my roadtrip... the first part of it is all by myself.  Three hours alone to just...  think .  I'm not sure how fond of that idea I am.  But then I'll be with friends.  I can't wait to see everyone.  I miss them all so much.  And then Saturday even more friends... and a concert that I've been  dying  to see.  Then Sunday it's back to good old Caz... to see friends some more.   I'm thinking of staying gone forever.  I need this vacation so badly... and by the time I'm suppose to come back I have a feeling I'm not going to want to.   Off to pack... off to prepare for my road warrior days. :) Getting away is going to do me a world of good.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink I Want This    I'll accept donations... check, cash, credit. Please?  :)
     

    
</post>

<date>06,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Sometimes I think I write because paper is stronger than I am... Fold it up enough times and nothing can tear it. I keep wondering,  if I curled up tight enough maybe I'd be unbreakable...
     

    
</post>

<date>04,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I wish that I had all the answers, or even one... just so you could feel good about something for two seconds. I feel so very helpless that I can't "fix" the things that are bothering you (although I recognize that's not my job...) I  hate  to see you hurting.   If I could snap my fingers and make you feel good about things, I would do it in an instant. I'm here for you, and I believe in you. Maybe that's not much, but that's all I've got.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Last night I sat here, thinking about all the things that have gone wrong recently... all the stupid, really meaningless crap.  I let myself feel sad and cheated and hurt and upset.... all those things I've been trying so hard to avoid. But then something happened. I got ripped back into the reality of work (via a rather obnoxious fire alarm)... and then I had to go out in the cold with some people, visit the hospital with some people.  And as I sat there talking and laughing with them, I realized that just because life is sometimes really shitty... it's not completely shitty.   When I look at what I have surrounding me (job, friends, family) I know that I win.  I may feel like I've lost, but really  I win .   That makes me smile, all the way down to my heart.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      So, recap of today/tonight:  6 hour train ride Got into town right on time. You'd think that would be good, right?  Considering I was worried I'd be late and my ride would have to wait, I thought it was wonderful.    Moving on to the next part of the night....  Wait for half an hour at dark train station.   Call one of my staff members to see if he will call my ride (i don't have her number, and he's the only number i have memorized).  He says he will. I wait 15 more minutes (7:45pm by then) and then call him back; there's no answer.  Wait five more minutes, to make sure ride wasn't going to show up.   Then proceed to walk 3 miles back to campus... In the wind, freezing cold, and carrying two bags that weigh probably 40lbs all together.   Get back to campus 45 minutes later.   I'm exhausted, I'm  so  sore, and I'm sad.   Tonight I need someone to wrap their arms around me and hold me and just care about me and take care of me.  That's what I need right now, to just feel like I matter.  Because after tonight, I truly feel like I don't.  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
        "Can you help me with this heart inside my chest? It ain't perfect, but you should see me use it But it only works when I make a mess When it looks like I'm about to lose it  If I start to cry I may not stop Love runs dry I run off..."  -Edie Carey  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      One more hour... that's all I have to wait.  One more hour until I get to leave this place and go home.  Last night was a bad night.  A horrible night really.   I'm done having nights like that. I  can't   have nights like that anymore...  I've been slowly losing my mind and losing myself for a long time now.   I want to be found.   And you know something?   I want to find myself, and not leave that to someone else anymore.   It's too important a job to trust anyone else to do it.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
         Yeah, Whatever by Splender  And you're primitive... And you're cynical to me And I chewed down on the bit And almost swallowed it  You sit all alone with your color TV Your hair starts to glisten In spite of the fleas We don't have to stay friends Let's pretend to be enemies  Yeah, whatever makes you happy Yeah, whatever makes it beautiful Yeah, whatever leaves you satisfied 'Cuz I'm out of time For now  And you're paranoid As you look me up and down And I'm soaked in gasoline Mud and ice cream  You sit by the phone  With your tongue hanging out You cradle the flies in the back of your mouth We don't have to stay friends Let's pretend to be enemies  Damned if you do Fucked if you don't Damned if you do What if you won't  You must be aware of what you're Doing to me We sunk like a stone on a rock In the sea    We don't have to stay friends (Not for very long) We don't have to stay friends (Just because you're gone)  Yeah, whatever makes you happy Yeah, whatever makes it beautiful Yeah, whatever leaves you satisfied You get what you want 'cuz you won't let it die  Yeah, whatever makes you happy Yeah, whatever leaves you insecure Yeah, whatever seems to break you down  'Cuz I'm out of time But I'm feeling fine    
     

    
</post>

<date>24,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      OK... I'm not sure I have the words to describe how it felt to get email from you.  (i'm aware that "you" aren't reading... but it still feels good to purge my thoughts this way).   It's my own fault.  I opened  myself up to it.  I sent email first... but I  never  expected to get a response.  Especially not after so long.     Why do you still say all the same things that make me  feel  something and  hope  for things that I cannot hope for and should not hope for.   Sometimes I want to disappear.  Maybe that'd be better for everyone involved.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Back from my trip... still smiling. :) Missing my Steven.   Sometimes it's hard going to see him and then coming back here... it's the same when I visit all my friends.  So happy when I'm there, and then I come back here.   But it was such a good weekend... that's what I'm going to focus on. :)
     

    
</post>

<date>20,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      "On the road again..." Today I'm off on a magical adventure to visit my very wonderful friend, Steve :)  I'm a smiley, smiley girl because of it.   I've needed to get away from campus for awhile... and I've really needed to see him.  He's one of the best friends I have, and I miss him.  A lot.  Hopefully I won't get lost... *grin*
     

    
</post>

<date>16,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I feel like I owe my friends who actually care an apology...  because my current mood has nothing to do with them and everything to do with me.   I know right now I'm crappy company and I'm absolutely no fun to be around. But it's only because I miss everyone so damn much.  Thank you to those of you who've been so wonderful.  I know I don't say it enough, but I love you guys, and I truly appreciate everything you've done.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Even when I'm "perfect" that's still not enough.  What's my motivation in this?
     

    
</post>

<date>10,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       "You do it to yourself, you do And that's what really hurts is You do it to yourself, just you You and no one else You do it to yourself..." -Radiohead  
     

    
</post>

<date>08,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Wisdom teeth  suck .
     

    
</post>

<date>08,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I've been procrastinating all day... have a term paper to write that I really am not motivated to write.  I'm currently watching 'Finding Forrester'.   Before this it was 'When Harry Met Sally'.    I find myself sitting here wishing I could have a 'When Harry Met Sally' moment... you know, one of those moments when everything finally works out and settles into the exact way it's always been meant to be. Like at the end when Harry runs to the party  and Sally is just leaving and they look at each other and he tells her he loves her... and at first she's saying how he can't just do that or say that and have everything be ok. But then... well then he tells her how he loves that she's cold when it's 71 degrees out and how he loves all these ridiculous things about her.  he tells her he loves that she's the last person he wants to talk to when he goes to sleep at night. then Sally says, "You know Harry that's just like you.  You say these things and they make it  impossible  for me to hate you."  And then they kiss and...   live happily ever after .   I guess, to make a long story short I'm sitting here wishing for a happy ending. I'm wishing for that... happily ever after. I wonder when I get that?
     

    
</post>

<date>07,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       I Am Yours  by Tracy Chapman  When all my hopes and dreams Have been betrayed I stand before you My hands are empty  I am yours If you are mine  When I fall and stumble Flat on my face When I'm shamed and humbled In disgrace  I am yours If you are mine  When voices call me To question my faith When misperception Taints my love with hate  I am yours If you are mine  When time decides It won't stop for me When the hawks and vultures Are circling  I am yours If you are mine  
     

    
</post>

<date>07,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      So the past few days I've been putting a lot of time into my sketchbook.   Not that I really sketch things... I can't draw  at all .   But I write lyrics to my favorite songs... I'm such an obsessive lyric collector. I write my poetry there, some of my favorite ones that I've written. I also make collages... I've become really obsessive about that too.   I'm not sure how good they are, but I really love them.  I need more magazines though... I'm low on materials. I make photo collages too.  I started one of my staff.  I can't wait until I have more photos of them so I can finish it.  Today I decided that... I really am a good writer.  Maybe not all my stuff is outstanding, but I've seriously written some good stories and poems.  I was reading through my writing site today, and all the notes I've gotten.  I just realized that no matter what else may be going on in my life, that is something I can do very right.   That's a good feeling.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
        I'm weak when you miss me when you roll me on your tongue.. When you whisper me your best moves I almost believe you but you don't know me at all  I'm covered by lovers, who recite lines convinced their bodies are gonna save mine but you don't know me at all..  Show me where the sun comes through the sky I'll show you where the rain gets in and I'll show you hurricanes and the way that summer fades... underneath the weight of it all  I spent days stupid nailed to your floor and I spent nights pushed against you trying to keep warm but you don't know me at all.  Show me where the sun comes through the sky I'll show you where the rain gets in and I'll show you hurricanes and the way that summer fades underneath the weight of it all   -Matt Nathanson 'Weight of it All'  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Go Here to See My Famous Photo!     It's the one in the middle, the covered bridge.  :)  I'm very proud.  YAY ME!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      OK.  So my website isn't working.  I have  no clue  as to why.  I'm not sure if the webmaster shut it down because I had my quote pages up, and they have some offensive content.  I'd think that they would send me an email telling me they'd shut it down though.  I'd also like to hope that they would allow me the option to take down the offensive material and get my site up and running again.  I worked  so  hard on that web page.  Seriously.  I'm really frustrated that it's suddenly unavailable.  I can't even get to the ftp to make changes.  When I try to go there, it freezes Ie and I have to ctrl+alt+del and start over.  So I'm thinking it's a problem with the server rather than a problem with my page.  I'm hoping so, because I worked too hard on that to have them shut it down without notice or giving me the option to fix it. 
     

    
</post>

<date>31,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Status Report: -Smiling frequently and almost continuously -Can't put the guitar down for more than 20 minutes at a time (go look at the picture, link below!!) -Fingers so sore that they're almost numb... until I play the guitar and then they feel as if they may split open and bleed!  Hooray. -Can play C, D, E, Em, G, G7, A, Am... and I have everything other than G and G7 memorized. -Have a new case and several new picks; like the red pick the best :)   -I could learn a song now... according to Jon.  I just don't know what song he means, nor can I read guitar tabs, so I'm a bit confused!    I LOVE MY GUITAR!!!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>29,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink My Stunning Baby   
     

    
</post>

<date>28,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Agenda Tomorrow:  -Get hood of car fixed  -Take stupid mini guitar to guitar place to see how much it will take to get it fixed  (pray for over $20!!!) -Go get my wrist looked at to see what the doc says about it -Meet Jon and Tiani at 3 -Go guitar shopping (perhaps purchase a nice one!!!!!) *eeep* -See 'The Last Samuri' with Jon and Tiani    **praying for the repair to be over $20 so I can justify spending over $100 on something I've wanted desperately for almost four years.  new years continues...  happier right now than I have been in months.   "goodbye to you..."  (i'd miss you... but who misses misery?)
     

    
</post>

<date>28,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Tonight:  Learned how to play E minor, E major and C-chord (c-chord c-chord c-chord) on the guitar :) Spooned with Greggles and Tiani Promised Brian I'd come bake for him when he bought me a frilly apron to wear (only an apron mind you). Was given the eye by a  scary  man  *eep* Threw myself at Justin to stop scary man Met a  hot  guitarist named Mike Ate too much food at Denny's at 3am Wrote down too many quotes (and missed many others)    Had a fantastic night with my friends        My New Year's Resolution: Start doing things to make myself happy  new year's begins today    
     

    
</post>

<date>26,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I got the new Liz Phair CD for xmas.   This one song reminds me of so many things... It even reminds me of myself...   Red Light Fever  by Liz Phair  Lying wide awake in the dark Trying to figure out where you are Always going nowhere Afraid of going somewhere And somewhere's a place in your heart... Sometimes when I think about you Why you're always running away... Sitting in your car Changing who you are And drowning the thoughts of your life in the music  Scared the lights will turn green You'll have to be seen You'll be like anybody else Scared the lights will turn red You're stuck in your head Too scared to commit to even her How are you gonna get through the year? You can't  Playing on both sides of the net Too many people want too many things And you only want to forget...  Scared all the lights will turn green You'll have to be seen You'll be like anybody else Scared all the lights will turn red You're stuck in your head Too scared to commit to even her How are you gonna make it through?  You're always listening You're always listening to yourself You're always thinking You're always thinking you know  what everybody else should do with their lives  Lying in the dark Trying to figure out where you are... Always going nowhere Afraid of going somewhere And somewhere's a place in your heart Somewhere's a place in your heart  Scared all the lights will turn green You'll have to be seen You'll be like anybody else Scared the lights will turn red You're stuck in your head Too scared to commit to even her How are you gonna get through the year?        
     

    
</post>

<date>23,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Tomorrow is Christmas Eve.   Bah humbug.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      So today? I'm the "lucky" individual who gets to work a 10-hour shift at work. Hoping for early release!   10 hours at that store at one time really doesn't make me happy.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
        The Hollywood Video Mass Xmas Celebration Extraveganza....   Agenda for tomorrow: 11am: meet Greg, Laurie, and Marty at the store 12pm: lunch and stuff at the mall with many coworkers 3pm: Lord of the Rings Return of the King (featuring cookies supplied by yours truly) 7pm: Bowling and dinner  after 7:   the possibilities are endless 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I want  to stop being alone.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I left because there was no room for me. But you could tell me not to go. Say it to me. Tell me not to go. -Stephen Sondheim
     

    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      So this is me being bitter about the damn blizzard that is currently taking place. Tell me again why I live in the Northeast?   Bah humbug.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Today:   -hair cut   -top secret xmas stuff for steve   -more top secret xmas stuff for steve   -BAKING (for  hours )    -Christmas list making (for parents)   -Sleeping   have I mentioned that I'm glad to be home?
     

    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I am home.  :)   I am glad. Very very glad.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hooray... tomorrow I get to leave.   Tomorrow I get to drive to see my friends. YAY.  Needless to say, I'm excited.  Beyond excited.   I have all my Christmas shopping done.   Everything is wrapped. I just have to finish up making some things for a special gift for someone. But that's it. And I'm bringing my friends gifts tomorrow... I can't wait to give them presents.   I love giving presents.    Tomorrow and Thursday will be good days. Then Friday...    HOME   . I can't wait.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Everybody! Everybody! 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       "I've always wanted for you what you've wanted for yourself and yet I wanted to save us high water or hell and I kept on ignoring the ambivalence you felt  and in the meantime I lost myself in the meantime I lost myself I'm sorry I lost myself-.i am..." -Alanis Morissette  
     

    
</post>

<date>07,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      You know, even the good times are cloudy for me.   Even the times when I'm almost completely content with everything going on, there's always that "almost" hanging over my head.   And sometimes I want that to just go away. I want everything that casts a shadow over happiness to just vanish. *poof* 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Just when I thought I couldn't feel any worse...
     

    
</post>

<date>03,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      It's funny... the things you discover about people. Things you never imagined could be true. Things like... you have way more in common than you thought, and that maybe, just maybe there's someone else out there that "gets it." Gets what you're feeling.   That helps.  A lot.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I can't handle any more...
     

    
</post>

<date>30,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      some days it's easier than others. i'm not sure why that is.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Pink Floyd Online - Guitar Tabs - WISH YOU WERE HERE    I can so play this (not the lead part!!)
     

    
</post>

<date>25,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I was thinking tonight and this was my recurring thought:  Some people do really crappy things to the people in their lives who really don't deserve it.   And there's no explanation, other than a cop out.   Well, there's an explanation... but I doubt I should write about it here.  I just hope that the people who do this know just how crappy it is. I'm sure they do.   I'm sure they know exactly how awful it is to hurt someone that's done nothing for four years but do and say and be everything they've asked for and wanted.  "Oh, and that's being a good friend." I hate hypocrisy.  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I can play 'Wish You Were Here' by Pink Floyd on my guitar :)  I made a music video and sent it to my  Mom... played and sang all but the chorus, simply because I can't play it and sing it because I get confused between my strumming rhythm and my singing rhythm :)  The temptation to post the video on my website is almost unbearable... but it's not that great and I still am slow between chords.   So I'll wait until I can rip through it and tear it up :)  My Mom was excited though.   So am I quite honestly.   Now I need to practice my Sister Hazel song so I can get  really  good and impress Jon.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      There's a boy in PA named Jon who has made me smile a very real smile on a day when I didn't think that was possible.   Thank you  for caring enough to IM me for caring enough to say "gosh if I didn't have to work this weekend I'd drive to see you." Because I know you meant it. Just thank you. You're a wonderful friend and I will only love you more when you send my capo or when you make me my compilation of easy guitar songs to learn. (although I love you quite extensively right now)
     

    
</post>

<date>22,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I can't begin to describe how much this hurts. I don't have enough tears for this.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today:  -Dishes done -Laundry Put away -Car started  Currently: -starting a new book   Ahh relaxation
     

    
</post>

<date>17,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Sometimes it's hard to know how to help. Know that I am here if you need me, ok?
     

    
</post>

<date>17,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Update on 6-day weekend: Day 3... -All discipline letters in log completed -Can almost play the F-chord on the guitar (oh happy day) -Succeeding at my plans of napping often and wearing pjs frequently -Valuing the friendship of some people more and more every minute (you know who you are)  Still to do: -Start reading one of the books I got for xmas -Begin the reading due in Counseling Process on Weds. (yay grad school) -Much more sleep -Much more guitar practice -Clean!!! (this  includes  doing dishes!!) -Watch at least one dvd from xmas  I think I can handle that...  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Adding to my list of things to do on my six day weekeend...  -Find peace -Smile through tears -Make more stunning realizations -Wish for life to be different -Accept that it isn't   *check, check, check, check, double check
     

    
</post>

<date>14,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      What does one do with a six day weekend?  Here's my plan so far: -Sleep late -Wear pajamas until after lunchtime -Take many naps -Practice the guitar compulsively -Read some of the books I got for xmas -Clean around the pseudo apartment -Get all my work done for next Weds. classes -Watch many of my new dvds  I like my plan... although I have a feeling I'll need to do  something  a bit more to take up the time between all that.  I'm a big fan of all the relaxing that can be done in six days time.  :)
     

    
</post>

<date>13,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today: -Power outages rock my universe -The 'Tops Man' is sexy, but he wants Colleen :)   "shall we drive by again Col?"   -Fleece pants and oversized sweatshirts belonging to ex-boyfriends make me toasty. And... -Sheryl Crow's greatest hits album knocks my socks off.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Last 3 Days: -1 and a half hour drive= 2 hours due to awful weather and missing exit -Almost killed a beamer with my Buick :) -The Neverending boot quest with Steve (although it was fun) -Finally met Mr. S, Steve's Day (hooray) -Picture developing and book shopping -China Buffet -Moooooovies to see 'Radio'            -no crying at movies!  it's embarrassing!!! -Many hugs -Many laughs -Many snuggles  Missing my friend already... 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Some words mean so much, and as soon as I heard this song I felt as if I'd been hit in the gut... girls, guys, doesn't matter who you are I'm fairly sure we've all felt this way.  I know I have.  A lot lately.  Out There by Sister Hazel  Chorus If she's out there somewhere-somewhere  I would give everything to know. Just to hold and to finally have her, Take me to sunrise from indigo   If it's to be That there's just no one for me I'll try not to cry much So no one will see But if it's to be That there is anyone for me Our hearts will shine So everyone will see I've got some time, So maybe if you're free I could use a friend Just to talk to me   Chorus   Spent most of my life without Anyone near Never cared what happened I never saw clear But I'm getting older now And I'm, thinking of my end And to leave without love Or without a friend  I've got some time So maybe if you are free I could use a friend  Before I die   Chorus   It's not over yet... I'm still standing   If it's to be  That there's just no one for me I will try not to cry much So no one else will see I've got some time So maybe if you're free I could use a friend Just to talk to me   
     

    
</post>

<date>05,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have a crush.... *smile*  It's a silly one, but it's there. heeheehee
     

    
</post>

<date>05,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Last night a very interesting, stunning... and somewhat scary thought came into my head:   What if the past two years was more about hiding from what you really want than actually having it?     I was up for a very long time thinking about that.  And the more I thought about it, the more I became fairly sure that that realization was right on the money. Not that it does me any good.  Hiding from what I really want was just a way of accepting a very harsh truth:    I can never have it. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've never quite had the amazing experience of being such good friends with coworkers before.  I'm  so  thankful for this job, because I've made such amazing friends. Quotes of the night last night:  "You can stick 'em in my frosty." -Tiani "I don't want to be easy!!" -Me "Me: Where did Greg go?  Tiani: I ate him; he's like a little chicken breast." "Thank you for calling Hollywood Video.  I'm Harry(hairy) how can I help you?" -Greg "Me: This coming from the guy with a $145 traffic ticket  Greg: Well you had to unzip my pants."  "Greg: Who are you, McGruff the crime dog  Tiani: Only  you  can prevent forest fires.  Greg: That's Smokey the Bear, dumbass."  Seriously, I love you guys!!!  Thanks for all the laughs.  
     

    
</post>

<date>29,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Thoughts on Dating    
     

    
</post>

<date>28,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Holy exhaustion Batman. This has been the longest day ever.   The temptation to just curl up and go to sleep until tomorrow is almost irresistable.    It's doubly tiring, because I have so much going on right now.   All of it confusing.   So it's all... a jumbled up mess in my head.   It'll get better, I'm sure.  Always does.   Right now it's just overwhelming and tiring.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So I had a very near-death experience tonight;   A mack truck almost hit my car... or pinned it between itself and a big wall. *frown*  May I just say that I'm glad that I had a good driving instructor when I first learned...  someone who made me practice reacting quickly when driving stick otherwise I wouldn't have reacted quickly enough and my friends and I might not be here to talk about how we narrowly escaped being crushed by a mack truck.  So yeah.  "God it's good to be alive..." -Goo Goo Dolls
     

    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I practiced my guitar for an hour and a half today... and I can play 3 new songs.  Not perfectly, but I have the basic idea.  I'm really excited about this.  Maybe I will be able to make Jon proud of me after all... :)
     

    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Can I just say that my intense love for Jon was fed today by the absolutely wonderful guitar presents he sent me?   Jon dear, I  My guitar loves you too.  She thanks you for the capo! :)  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      At some point the bull has to end. If you say you want friendship, then do it. Friendship means you don't turn your back when  you've  done something wrong that hurts your friend to the point of making her act a little crazy.  Friendship means that you try to prove you do care so your friend knows you're sincere. Friendship means you don't jerk your friend around.  I'm about fed up.  I laid myself out.   I  apologized for being the way I've been, even though it is partially warranted.  And I get no response.  That's such crap.  I'm sick to death of getting jerked around by people who start off saying they care.  In the end it becomes clear very rapidly that it's all a lie.  I hate lies.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      You know, I don't know why I ever believe in anything at all anymore. Because I should know by now that it all gets shoved right back down my throat. No matter what.  I give up.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So part of me thinks that I should just say something and ask what the heck is going on.  But at the same time I'm really afraid to ask, because I know the answer I'm going to get.  And then I'm just going to be angry and hurt and I'll just totally alienate.   But if I get the answer I'm expecting then I think I have every right to be angry and hurt.  *sigh* 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So now I'm kind of thinking   What if my father was right?  After last night and how it ended I'm a little unsure of exactly what to think or believe.    If I've made another mistake like all the ones before it I'm not sure I'm going to be OK with it.  But it was so nice... so nice.   I want to believe that there's still a chance for nice. 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This has been a wonderful weekend...  flowers from a very nice boy :) and then a whole weekend with my steven (i use the term "my" loosely!)  Hooray for fabulous Valentine's Days.   Even bigger hooray for my V-Day starting last Wednesday and lasting until Sunday. 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm even smilier today :-D   ps- HAPPY BIRTHDAY JON!!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am a smiley girl...  :)   "And now all I wanna do is spread my wings and fly..." -Chantal Kreviazuk 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's the 3am wake-up calls that make this job awesome.    Highlites of the early wake-up: -hanging out with staff is  always  fun, even at 3am, even when the police are in the building (especially when the police are in the building!) -police requesting "special" brownies to be served upon next visit -Who could pass up being humped in the hallway by the ever-sexy Aaron? *wink* -Jaws: The Revenge is on TNT  (yay cheesy shark movies)  The question arises:  Why, on Jaws, don't they just unfurl the sails on the sailboat?  They sit there trying to get the motor to work, and there's obvious some wind.  I mean, I've sailed before... sails+wind=movement.    hmm... something to ponder as I drift off to sleep...  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      List of Wants/Needs:  1) DVD rack   2) Picture frames  3) SARK's new book  4)  Man's Search for Meaning  by Viktor Frankl  5) Papazan Chair (weggies has them for $90)   6) A new quilt for my bed  7) A better mattress for my futon  8) Canon Digital Rebel (long way off!)   9) Capo for guitar (jon's on that)  10) New printer
     

    
</post>

<date>02,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Alright, I've solved the commenting problem.  You can leave a comment on the left side of the screen in my "chatterbox".  I reserve the right to delete anything there if it's offensive or ridiculous.  Odds are, I'll keep whatever you post though.  Start chattering kiddies....
     

    
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
       A study listed in the Washington Post says that women have better verbal skills than men. I just want to say to the authors of that study: Duh. -- Conan O'Brien  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I miss my comment link. :(  
     

    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
        "...You've been burned more than once You don't think much of trust. Man it takes a silly girl to lie about the dreams she has  Lord it takes a lonely one to wish that she had never dreamt at all  Oh look now, there you go with hope again  Oh, you're so sure I'll be leaving in the end..."  -Dashboard Confessional   
     

    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Mom is in the hospital.   It's nothing too serious... a broken pelvis. I just... hate being so far away at times like this.   She needs me and I'm six hours away.  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Mixed feelings. On ice.    I don't know what I expected.  I should've known myself well enough to know I'd be sitting right here doing exactly this. Wishing for more than I can ever have.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Florida rocked my world.   In ways I never expected.  :)  Link to pictures will be forthcoming... Link to quotes will also be forthcoming...  I  

    
</post>

<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Surprising turn of events...   I got an answer to the question I posed in my last entry though.  The whole "I wonder if the things I miss will ever be back" question.  Apparently the answer is yes... for at least one of those things.  I'm so glad.   I've missed you.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm absolutely exhausted right now... long few days.  I should definitely be in bed at the moment... but I'm thinking about a lot of things.   About how I have so much more to do by Friday afternoon when we leave for Florida. And about how much I miss certain people. And about how much fun I had visiting some friends for even a day. ...About a lot of things that I'm not going to get into right now.   I'm too tired.  *sigh*  I miss so much.  I wonder if that'll ever be a non-issue?  I wonder if the things I miss will ever be back?
     

    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Sunday is going to be a bittersweet day.              I'm not sure yet whether it will be more bitter or sweet...
     

    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My brain is spinning in about seven hundred different directions.  I really have no clue what the heck I think I'm doing right now.    Excuse my neurosis on this.  Life that is.    Honestly there's been  so  much that's happened that has destroyed the very instinct for me to trust.  So much that I can't begin to get in to, because so much of it was my own fault.  I can't do that again... make those mistakes again I mean.  Even though it would be very, very easy to do so.    I think too much.  I realize that.  It's the times that I don't think that I end up with my teeth kicked in and my heart shattered on the ground.    So think I shall...
     

    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "Where should I go? what should I do? I don't understand what you want from me cause I don't know if I can trust you I don't understand what you want from me..." -Nickelback  
     

    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Please don't fall into me simply because I'm here.  The wreckage after such a collision will be irreparable.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i've made so many mistakes in the past and being myself makes nothing last trusting has only  ended in pain and hoping has just ended the same. 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "You go to sleep dreamin' how you would Be a different kind if you thought you could But you come awake the way you are instead..." -Counting Crows
     

    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      When you take off the rose colored glasses And are left faced with the reality of me You will be disappointed.  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This whole situation is my fault.  I knew months ago what would happen if the truth came to the surface.  Ever.  Now it has, and exactly what I thought would happen is happening. I'm sitting here hating myself for not being good enough (again) And instead of just hating myself I'm letting it spill on to you And you don't deserve it.  I know it.   I know that everything you say to me is meant in the most genuine way.  I know that.   I also know that when I hear it (or read it as the case may be) All I do is shake my head in disbelief, because I can no longer believe (truly) that any of it is sincere.     I can't handle this.   Things won't change... no.  I'll just be without a friend, because I don't know how to do this right now.  I'll just curl up into myself and hope that this pain goes away.   I'm not holding my breath. You are better off without me.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I know I owe you more than I'm currently giving... but I don't know how to give more without losing myself completely.  This is mortifying.  This whole damn thing.   I'm sorry I'm being this way...   I just don't know how else to be right now.  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
        "In one of these dreams, you forgive me It makes me think of the bad decisions that keep you at home How could anyone else have changed? All these wrong conclusions that leave you alone How could anyone rearrange? How could everyone else have changed? What I see... I believe For all the things I'm losing I might as well resign myself to try and make a change..."  -Counting Crows  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I cut out my own heart today.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I found myself hating you today for simply being you Becuase the "you" that you are can never be mine.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I honestly don't know what I'm doing.   
     

    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I got an IM last night, from someone not on my buddy list.  I was just on my way to pass out after a night of drunken debauchery and celebration, so I just clicked "accept message" and I went to bed, figuring it was someone I knew that just wanted to wish me a happy birthday.  I kind of expected whoever it was to identify themselves.  They didn't.  I mean, they wished me a happy birthday, said, "I see that you're sleeping.  Goodnight then."   I have no clue who it was...  Well that's not entirely true. I have an  inkling ...   But in order to believe that it was actually that person is to believe that they came out of hiding and silence long enough to wish me a happy birthday.  If that's the case, that means  so  much to me.  More than I can say.    I don't want to believe that, though.  In all odds it will be one of my friends who will reappear on that screenname and say, "Hey, that was me the other night.  Sorry, I should've told you." And I will be extremely disappointed.   
     

    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Someone please stop me from doing this to myself. This whole feeling thing just isn't working out because I'm always doing it for the wrong person.  Just stop me before I mess something up.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink My Easter Present from Steve    
     

    
</post>

<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I think all of my friends are  insane .   You want me to do what?   Tell him?   Absolutely out of the question. I rather value this friendship.   No sense in going and screwing it up by telling him ridiculous things. 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I cannot fully describe what you mean to me J.L.    Thank you .
     

    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I should listen to myself more often. I shouldn't hope. It hurts too damn much to have it all crushed in the end.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Good Stuff:  -I get to move to a new building next year... and my room is  awesome . -I may be able to afford summer classes this year.  Wahoo.  Really Good Stuff: -Going to Pdam tomorrow.   *I can't wait*    Don't want to hope to have a "really really good stuff" section to add to this... I'm having a hard time not hoping.  "With a little makeup I can look brand new, but can I be pretty enough for you?" -matt nathanson 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      (If there is one person you can't stop thinking about, post this same exact sentence in your journal.)
     

    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Good thing I gave up that silly dream of being a writer when I was about 18. Considering I haven't written anything worth the paper it's on (or anything new at all for that matter) in months and months and months and months, (maybe years) I'm probably better off.     Frustrated with myself.  Tempting to burn everything I've ever written, because I hate it all at this point.   Bonfire anyone?
     

    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hmmm... new look. Do I like it?   Leave comments and let me know your opinion. 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "You make me feel lucky as I can be you make me feel lucky as I can be..." -Hoobastank   Tuesday is soon... :) 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I have figured out two good things about my shoebox sized room: 1) Faces the gorge so when there is sun, I get to watch the sunset (which is wonderful). 2) It is SO small, in fact, that I can have my laptop in bed with me while I stay warm and watch a cheesy chick flick.  *grin*   I would post a list of the negatives, but that would take too long and too much typing... and quite frankly I'm enjoying my chick flick.  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today:  -Shower -Grab a bite to eat (although may wait until I'm out and suddenly become famished as I drive by Wendy's). -ATM to take out far too much money -Walmart  (new cell phone and shoes)  and then, if they don't have everything I need at Walmart... -Kmart -Outlet mall  I hate spending money... especially when spending it means that I'm going to be way down on funds.  Bah.  Gotta' love that.      *perhaps more than a little crabby because I was up at 8:30am.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      You know  I can't believe anyone could be so god damn stupid. Espeically not someone I considered to be so god damn insightful about me a month and a half ago.  Your ignorance serves only in hurting me all over again. Thanks for that. But so long as your elective ignorance brings you  some modicum of happiness...  I'm glad.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The concept of curling up and sleeping for three days is very appealing right now.   I feel icky. I'm exhausted.   *cranky bitch fest*  They should have nap time at work.   
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Truly wonderful two days.  That smile you love so much? It's because of you. Thank you. :)
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Last few days: -My brother KICKED ASS on his solo :) -Simply awesome time at Monica's  -Got to see Brian, Richard, and Emmy!!! -Nice (albeit short) visit with Steve on Sunday  -Harrowing drive back to NU on Sunday night (35mph on the thruway due to low/nonexistent visibility).  -Lost my cell phone. No clue where it is or where else to look.  :(   -Started my summer job today.  Definitely not rocket science -No internet in my room after a week.  I'm unimpressed.    Enough time in the computer lab.  Time to harrass the IT people. 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      cannot will not put myself  in the middle of a situation where all i'll get is hurt. i just can't play that game anymore.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's funny...  but I could've stood in the parking lot of McDonalds forever. :) Thank you for another truly wonderful day.  
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Finally, finally,  finally  at home :) Long-ass drive, but it was ok.  Although being stuck in the car for six hours when you're sick sick sick doesn't really help matters. Good things tonight:  -My brother's concert (he has a solo... 90% of the reason I'm home) -Laundry (note sarcasm) -Sleep Good Things to come: -A nice visit from a very nice boy... :)
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's like clockwork...  bah :( 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This whole waking up at like 3am and not being able to go back to sleep thing is getting really fucking old.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A brief thought before I drift off to a very blissful and dream-filled sleep: Truly one of the best days/nights ever today.   *smile*   Thank you .  :)
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Weird phenomenon tonight: It was the last ever episode of 'Frasier' tonight... a show I really like.   And I found myself thinking of my Grandmother as I haven't in quite some time.  'Frasier' was one of her favorite shows of all time and we use to watch it together all the time.    I miss her so very much... 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      To do before Sunday/Monday: -Pack up the stuff going into storage for the summer -Move stuff into storage -Pack up the rest of my stuff -Try to check out a room in the temporary building to see how much of my stuff will fit (from what I hear, it's SMALL... so not much)  -Student Affairs end of the year banquet Thursday at 1 -Conference Aid information meeting Friday 11 -A nice visit from a nice boy (which will be boring due to all the packing/moving I have to do, but hey, if you're game so am I!)    Basically, I have to figure out where I'm putting everything and how I'm going to get everything to fit in my room and all that!  BLAH.  It's going to be awesome times this weekend.  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yeah, I really love my "friends" right now.   Tempting to go visit my  real  frients until it's time to check out of my room and move to my first summer room. Because this whole everyone acting like I don't exist *unless of course they want something* is getting a little damn old.  Grr.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       "Am I pretty enough for you now that my ribs show through? With a little makeup I can look brand new, but can I be pretty enough for you? Fill me with secrets and I'll never tell fatten me up, and I'll feed you well you can polish me perfectly and I'll shine pristine but not even a cherub is this clean Am I all that you d hoped that I would be, hanging on obediently  to the words that I'm finding so hard to believe? Am I all that you d hoped that I would be? Why don't you just stop me if I'm sounding ungrateful Why don't you stop me if I'm coming on a bit too strong." -Matt Nathanson 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Let me tell you how glad I am that I spent three months looking for a code for a comment option here... and then spent the money to maintain it for a year... because only one person consistently leaves comments!  *thanks AYB, definitely appreciate it*  Grrr.  Just feeling frustrated right now... and uninteresting or something.   Bah.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ps- I haven't had much of a chance to say so (other than to brag to my friends that is), but that was the most amazing email I've ever received in my whole life.  Just in case you didn't know.  That meant a lot to me.  A whole lot.  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Wow .
     

    
</post>

<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I say some truly awful things to my friends sometimes.   For example:   "it's always funny to me when someone is in a relationship and has been for an extended period of time and really the majority of the relatiship is just great... it always seems funny and echoes hollow to me when they act like they have one f-ing clue when i say "yeah, I've had three and a half years of lying, cheating, emotionally abusive asshole boyfriends... and before/after that all i've had is rejection." i'm not mad at you.  i'm mad at life.  and i'm really sick of people who have no clue trying to empathize.  because really, they don't have any idea."   Yeah, I'm an  awesome  friend when I'm trying to protect myself and not deal with things.  Really awesome.  
     

    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I think what it comes down to right now is this:  I just can't do this.   Plain and simple.  
     

    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Tonight I was thrown back into memories that I want to forget.  Memories of my best friend calling me drunk off his ass, telling me all the things he thought I'd want to hear... when really all I wanted was for him to never call me like that.   Ever .    This is my dysfunction.  I know that.  I just... Hell. I don't even have the right words anymore.  "And I'll let you know When it comes, when it comes I'll let you know But don't stay up for me Don't wait up for me If I'm not home..." -Tyler Hilton
     

    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      *sigh* What the hell am I doing?
     

    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's very easy to become disenchanted with me. Please don't feel bad if you have. Because I know that you will. Eventually.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Back and forth and back again... My mind does this dance and trips over its own two left feet. If I am consistent in one thing it's this: I always stumble and fall on my face the moment my favorite song starts to play.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I wish I was better at writing codes and designing things... I'd like to change how this site looks a little... hmm.  Perhaps I'll do some reading tonight and try to find out some ideas.     *not the profound, deep post you were expecting, eh?*
     

    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      What truly scares me right now  is how much I already trust you... and I should know better than to let that happen this way.  So quickly and without thought.  Because doing things this way always always  always   lands me with my heart on the ground.  Trampled and bruised and bleeding.  I don't know what I should do now: fight my urge to build up the walls that will protect me or build them higher than ever before.  Believe it or not the higher they go, the better off you'll be.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It would be so easy  to let myself fall into this  without any thought...   I don't trust myself enough to do that.  Every time I've trusted anyone or anything it's ended rather poorly.    It would be nice, though, to be able to...   What a surprising goal to have...
     

    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I wish I could fix myself   for you.  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's at times like these when I feel completely lost. I have no idea what to do sometimes. Like now. No damn clue.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Someone come rescue me from all this work I have to do.   I'm not joking.   Come over, please, and help me... because I simply cannot read all of this crap in two days and absorb it for the final. I may as well have company on my path to failure *wink*
     

    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Fun little activity to kill 30 seconds of the day.  1. Go into your diary's archives. 2. Find your 23rd post (or closest to). 3. Find the fifth sentence (or closest to). 4. Post the text of the sentence in your blog along with these instructions.  "It's about time you both simmer down  And just stop being ridiculous." 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Tomorrow tomorrow tomorrow tomorrow!!!   Tomorrow my Shane comes to see me.  Until Sunday. And then I go to see him.  Until next Wednesday. *smile*   Oh I can't wait until tomorrow.   Off to sleep so tomorrow will be here faster.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "Id like to keep the way you look at me  Right there on your face Id like to keep it making me crazy Id like to move into you  Without taking up your place Can I anticipate? Saying yes, yes Anything you want I say yes I say yes, Im up to the task Anything you ask..."  -Edie Carey  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      May I just say that I have a very lovely boyfriend?   Because I do.  And just so you know babe... it was a very hard decision for me to say "yes just come next weekend," because I really wanted to see you this weekend too.  I really appreciate you recognizing and accepting my need to spend time with my friend.  :)    ps- I love that you're quite adorably jealous.  Makes me feel important.  Don't worry though,  you're  my boy and I like you quite a lot.    
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today marks the day that 1 month ago Shane and I flipped our rings around.  This has been the best month I can remember, if not ever, then in a very long time (but I'm going with ever).    I hope for months and months more of just the same happiness.  Thank you for an amazing month together baby.  *kiss*  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      More "great" news; I have to move this weekend. That means: -Don't get to see Shane :( -I will have very little time to work on my presentation  -I haven't even begun to pack yet   I am absolutely miserable right now.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Shitty two days.   Definite problems with financial "aid" (i use that term very loosely considering they haven't aided me with much of anything). I have no idea what I'm going to do about this situation if I can't get a loan... and according to the FA office, I'm not elligible.  Of course, it's hard to say, because they cancled my damn appointment today.  *angry/frustrated*   A lot else going on in my head... just being stupid and trying to fight it I suppose. Sometimes I think it'd just be easier to curl up and hide or simply run away from everything with potential to hurt me.  Not a great philosophy on life, but sometimes that's what I think.    My journal on line still isn't working.  My presentation is nowhere near done... I really haven't done much of anything actually other than get the books.  Maybe this weekend I'll become motivated... oh wait.  This weekend I'll probably be moving.  So odds are I won't have much time to do it then either.  *sigh*   I'm in a wretched, wretched mood.  I haven't talked to virtually any of my friends in days (weeks in some cases).  It seems as if all of them just have better things to do.  Or like they don't have time to chat.  I started talking with one friend last night and in the end they just faded away.  Didn't say goodbye or anything else.  Just stopped talking.  None of my friends from home ever contacts me at all, which hurts me more than I can describe.  Makes me wonder just how good of a "friend" they are.  Part of me misses them, and part of me is just angry and hurt by them.  It's the same way with my friends from college.  I have 3 that I still keep in touch with (four if you count one that randomly will say they want to be my friend and talk and all that but then disappear as soon as they're back).  The person who was my "best friend" in college hasn't spoken to me in months.  That speaks volumes.    I just feel frustrated with everything.  Quickly falling back into a depression that I don't want to be in... too much thinking, too much stress, too much time sitting here alone.  Yeah, I love summertime.  :(
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Currently trying to deal with the fact that I haven't been able to get to my on line journal and write in it in almost a week.  There have been problems with the site apparently, and a lot of people are without access to their pages.  Grr.  That's the one thing I hate about the site I use; they have far too many issues sometimes.    Other things that make the 'Peeved' list: -my mon/weds class that lasts for 5 and a half hours -the professor of previously mentioned class for keeping us 5 hours and 15 minutes consistently by giving us busy work.  did she not get the memo that we're graduate students and therefore do not need this crap? -the 2 and a half hour presentation for this class that's going to kill me because it's due in a week and we only got the assignment last monday. -the fact that in all likelyhood i'm going to have to move  again  this weekend. -the fact that due to this move i won't be able to see shane this weekend. *pout* -the HUGE bruise on the side of my foot where i rolled my ankle yesterday on the jetboats.   -the fact that i have to go to work and then spend the rest of my afternoon in the library doing research.  things on the "life is pretty great" list: -Shane.   -Shane. -Shane. *heehee* -if I do have to move this weekend, a friend is going to come help me. -one of the people in my group for the project already found a guest speaker for our presentation. -the jetboat trip was one of the most awesome things I've ever done, by far.  it was like swimming... only ten times the intensity and minus all the effort of swimming.   -today I also get to do more top secret stuff.  *wahahaha* -Shane -Shane -Shane  *thought I'd end the list with more of my favorite part of life. :)
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      And life is  urlLink perfect    
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This weekend I am an  urlLink Official Cube Geek .   I can now solve the mini cube... generally in under five minutes.  Sometimes I get turned around, though, and it takes me longer.    Shane left about two hours ago... :( It's been a simply lovely few days though.  I haven't ever been this happy; he makes me feel so good about me and about everything.  Every minute we spend together is one more of sheer bliss for me... and the moments apart just make the ones together even more beautiful and wonderful.     Thank you  for such an amazing few days baby.  I miss you already, and can't wait until you're with me again. 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I go from 0-neurotic in .02 seconds. I'm being passive-aggressive.  Very.   Sometimes I just don't know how to do this.   *sigh*  I'm working on it Believe it or not.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The 16th of June  by Me It came to an end  That fate-filled day.  Now I can't chase  The storm away.  I remember the rain  How it fell in a sheet.  I remember how it sounded,  A steady, deadly beat.  I remember the thunder,  How it crashed and boomed.  It rumbled aloud  As the clouds loomed.  I remember the movie,  How I sat and laughed.  Nothing was more important,  Than our friendly craft.  I remember the phone call,  When she asked me to come home.  When I begged to stay,  And left her alone.  I remember I was early,  Arrived at 4:28.  I was going to gloat,  That I wasn't late.  I remember her form,  Slumped on the couch.  How she was half on the floor,  Half in a slouch.  I remember the sirens  Screaming toward the house.  I covered my ears,  Meak as a mouse.  I remember the lights,  Flashing on the wall.  Then I realized,  It was all my fault.  I remember it all,  Hope it all goes away soon.  1993,  The 16th of June.    
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The past is a fucking powerful thing. Hours left until the past comes racing in to kick in my teeth: 2 and a half.   If I sleep tonight it will be a miracle. The last few nights, actually, the few hours I've gotten have been rather miraculous.   I hate this part of myself.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Really, really, really exhausted.     Also really, really, really, really (times infinity) happy.     Perfect .     Once again, thank you for such an amazing weekend hun.  I can't begin to say how happy you make me.  *kiss*
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Just flashed across the tv screen: The National Weather Service has issued a severe thunderstorm warning for Niagara, NY.    I   hate  thunder.  A lot.  Even more now.    Wishing I was in Oswego with my lovely boyfriend and his ferocious cat,  urlLink Pickel .  Miss you Shane :)
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Kate and Shane on a Hike     urlLink Kate and Shane by the River     urlLink Kate and Shane Close and Happy      
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I still don't have the right words to express how truly wonderful I feel.   Because of you. You're...  nice  *wink* I miss you already.     urlLink Look what my boyfriend bought me!    
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I wish I had better words to express just how wonderful the last two days have been.   I don't though... so I'll just steal some.  Lucky by Hoobastank I knew how it felt to be another one in need of someone to show the way until you saw a part of me that nobody else could see and my life hasn't been the same  You make me feel lucky as I can be you make me feel lucky as I can be  Before I couldn't get a break never had a chance to make the impressions I want to but now it falls right into place when I get to see your face then there's nothing that I can do  You make me feel lucky as I can be you make me feel lucky as I can be  No more dark days, only sun rays no more hard ways with you today  You make me feel you make me feel lucky as I can be lucky as I can be lucky as I can be     Thank you for an amazing two days.  
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Handed in my rough draft today; apparently I'm on the right track with it because I got 10/10 possible points.&nbsp; I have a big sense of relief, because my professor only asked that I add three small parts to the paper, other than the last few things that weren't due for the draft.&nbsp;   Took a test today in this class too.&nbsp; It was  much  more difficult than any of my classmates and I thought it would be.&nbsp; Hopefully I did alright at that too... although I have to have faith in the fact that I'm a really good student, and also really quite smart.&nbsp; So I'm assuming I'll do as well on the test as I did on the paper.  Mom, Dad, and Sean will be here tomorrow and will stay until Sunday.&nbsp; I can't wait to see them.&nbsp; Then I have one more week (4 days) of class.&nbsp; After that I prance of to Rochester and go camping with Steve.&nbsp; :) I'm really excited about that; we've been meaning to go for the last two years (i think), ever since we first went and had such a good time.&nbsp; It will only be for two nights, but it should be fun.&nbsp; Then from the campsite I'll go to Shane's, and then from there to my house and soon after to his parents' house.&nbsp; Busy weekend and week ahead... but I can't wait until next weekend.&nbsp; Especially for the time when I see Shane. 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm having yet another one of those mornings where I wake up and I look around my room and I see the pictures of a certain lovely boy, and I think about a phone call from the night before (or an IM), and I feel luckier and happier than I ever have before.&nbsp; This type of morning is an ever increasing occurrence; in fact I can't remember a morning I haven't felt this way in quite some time :)  And even though I have to go meet with my professor to try to figure out what the heck she wants from me... and I'm stressed and concerned and worried about all that?  I know that I've got him.&nbsp; And that makes everything else just fade away.&nbsp; :)&nbsp;   &nbsp;   Thank you for the talk last night Shane, and for being so understanding about everything.&nbsp; Mainly?&nbsp; Thank you for just being you.&nbsp; You're a truly wonderful and amazing person... and I'm so glad you're in my life.&nbsp; &nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Good Word: -My private graduate loan= approved -Grade in Multicultural Counseling= A+ -Grade in Organizations and Administrations= A -Mom, Dad, and Sean will be here in less than a week -2 weeks from today I'll be at Shane's and we will then go to my house and to see his parents and some of his friends - And  it's a lazy Sunday :)  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Two months ago today was the beginning of my truly wonderful and beautiful relationship with a man who makes me happier than I can ever remember being.&nbsp;  Thank you for an amazing two months Shane.&nbsp;  Here's to the promise of many more just like it... :)&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;    
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      And there won't be a moment that you fade from my mind...   I miss you already. :) 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It was a simply glorious weekend.&nbsp; Friday was a relatively low-key day... Shane and I just went out for lunch and then rented a movie and made dinner that night.&nbsp;  Saturday I went to Caz and spent the afternoon hanging out with Monica and Becky; it was nice seeing both of them.&nbsp; I also got to see Mrs. Egan... that was truly fabulous.&nbsp; I miss her a lot now that I'm not living in Caz anymore.&nbsp; I also miss Max and Ella (her dogs that I walked for two years).&nbsp; Max isn't doing so well with his arthritis and it doesn't appear as if he'll be with us for much longer.&nbsp; I'm really glad I had the opportunity to see them.&nbsp;  Sunday was the big day...  Shane's 26th Birthday!&nbsp;&nbsp;  We woke up fairly early and got ready to go to the Renaissance Faire.&nbsp; Before we left he opened his presents.&nbsp; I got him the baby turtle from 'Finding Nemo' because he seemed to really enjoy that part of the movie (and he likes turtles)... and I thought it was really cute.&nbsp; I also gave him a scrapbook that I've been working on since May.&nbsp; He had suggested that we start one together, and I thought it would be nice for each of us to have one.&nbsp; So I made him one, and myself one.&nbsp; He liked it a lot.&nbsp; He gets one of his presents today because it just got here in the mail... so I won't post what it is until he's here and has it!&nbsp;  The Ren. Faire was such a great time.&nbsp; We were there all day.&nbsp; He bought me a really pretty dress to wear; it was purple with a really pretty Celtic knot embroidered on the front.&nbsp; He also made me a belt to wear.&nbsp; So we walked around in costume all day.&nbsp; :)&nbsp; His boss used me as his audience volunteer during his show, and I got a free Pucking Rat (this requires a lot of explanation!).&nbsp; Another lady that Shane knows was so nice... she gave me a beautiful bead embroidered bag simply because I told her it was beautiful.&nbsp; It has a buttefly in bead work on it.&nbsp; We went to see Brian's mud show, and then we went to watch the jousting horses.&nbsp; That was fabulous.&nbsp; After that we spent much of the afternoon looking around for his friend Jamie and Jamie's girlfriend Carrie.&nbsp; We finally found them just as they were leaving, but they decided to hang around.&nbsp; It was great to see Jamie again, and I'm really glad I finally got to meet Carrie.&nbsp; Fun times all around.&nbsp; That night we got home at around 8pm.&nbsp; Shane decided to take a "quick nap" and told me to wake him at 9pm.&nbsp; The quick nap turned into quite a  long  nap; I tried to wake him up until around 11, and then I finally gave up and went to sleep myself :).  Yesterday was just a really fun day.&nbsp; Brian was having a margurita party and the house of one of the people who works at the Ren Faire with him.&nbsp; We all got there at noon.&nbsp; I'm not sure exactly how much tequilla Brian puts in his marguritas, but I was pretty well intoxicated by 4pm.&nbsp; Needless to say, I couldn't drive home as I'd planned to, so we just drank some more.&nbsp; We were there until about 12:30am, and then went back to the apartment and passed out.&nbsp; It was a really fun night; I got to meet a lot more people from the Faire, and I got to see a lot of people that I'd met the last time I was in Oswego.&nbsp; Plus, I got one extra night there with Shane so that was quite wonderful.&nbsp;  He will be here sometime this afternoon/evening.&nbsp; He's going to spend the week job hunting and handing out resumes around the area.&nbsp; It will be quite nice to have him here.&nbsp; Then he'll go home for the weekend to work at the Ren. Faire.&nbsp;  &nbsp; This weekend was truly fantastic.&nbsp; I can't even fully describe how amazing this man is... how good he treats me, and how good he makes me feel.&nbsp; Simply lovely.&nbsp; Thank you baby, for making your birthday weekend an amazing time for me.&nbsp; I hope you had an even better time than I did.&nbsp;:)  
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Currently at Shane's.&nbsp; He's at work for the day, so I'm taking advantage of his absence and baking his birthday cake.&nbsp; :)&nbsp; After it's done I'm taking a quick jaunt down to Caz to visit with friends for the afternoon.&nbsp; Then I'll come back here in time to meet him when he's done.&nbsp; Then I will banish him to his room while I decorate the cake and hide it over night.&nbsp;  Tomorrow will be a busy and fun day.&nbsp; We'll spend most of the day at the Ren Faire with each other and some of his friends that I've met.&nbsp; I'm looking forward to seeing them again.&nbsp; Oh yes, and he will get his presents.&nbsp; :) I'm off to check the cake and finish doing some cleaning up.&nbsp;  Kelsie- I will post what all the top secret stuff is as soon as he's opened it!  
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Exhausting week that finally ends tomorrow... and then Friday I go to Oswego to be with Shane.  *smile*   Class is going well, although my professor is slightly loopy.  She's got more personality that I can possibly describe... and she goes off on these amazing tangential thought trips.  Heehee.  It makes the 5 hours of class go by pretty quick.  As of tomorrow class is half over; hooray for 2 week long summer courses that give you three graduate credit hours toward your CAS.    Tomorrow the first batch of freshmen come in for CARE.  It's kind of a mini orientation session for the kids and their parents to learn about financial aid, and to take tests, and also have the experience of sleeping over on campus.  We've been preparing for it since May.  CARE session II comes in on Monday while I'm in Oswego, and they leave Tuesday.  Then on Wednesday CARE session III is here.  That should be an interesting few days, because Shane will be here with me starting on Monday (on the hunt for a job!) and I will be frantically making up beds for that last session.  Then Camp College is here the 22nd through the 24th.  More beds to make for that.  It will be good to have him here though... I love coming home to him.  :)    All of the top secret birthday stuff is done... wrapped up and ready to go.  I went on an adventure Sunday to find the cake Shane wanted!  Took me four different stores, but it's found thank goodness.  I can't wait to get there Friday afternoon.  Then Saturday he decided he wanted to work so he could buy  me  a present on Sunday.  Silly boy.  (but oh so lovely).  I'll be going to Caz to visit Monica for the afternoon, so that will be really nice.  Then Saturday night I will probably do some baking for Sunday's birthday celebration.    So it's off to bed.  To dream of lovely things.  :)  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Happiness with you is neverending.   5 more days, maybe 4 if I can escape the freshmen invasion *wink*  I miss you.    "All I really wanna say is you're the reason I wanna stay I loved you before I met you and I met you just in time 'cause there was nothing left... ...you have made me smile again in fact, I might be sore from it it's been a while." -Ben Folds Five  *perhaps the biggest jump in lyrics ever.  those are the ones that remind me of you though.  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      On the agenda this weekend:  -much relaxing  -top secret boyfriend birthday preparation (6 days Shane!) -clean the car -start rebuilding my poetry and prose site -more webpage updating   After this weekend life gets kind of hectic.  I will be working in the office every day from 8:30am-11am.  Then I will go to class at 11 until 4pm.  Then it will be off to the gym until about 5pm.  After that I will come back here and make beds in preparation for the freshmen coming in for the first CARE session on Thursday night.  Then on Friday I get to go to Oswego to spend yet another glorious weekend with Shane; it's his birthday.  :)  This weekend is the first full weekend we haven't seen each other since May.  Thank goodness for phone calls and IMs and the like.  Luckily next weekend will be spent there helping him celebrate his birthday in style.  I have many tricks up my sleeves *wink*   Then after the wonderful weekend, I have another week just like this one full of classes, work, and making beds for freshmen coming in for orientation.  Things kind of settle down after that; I'll only have one more class to finish up in the last week of July/first week in August.   And then?  Shane and I go to my house for almost a whole week to relax in have fun.    A brief note: Thank you Kelsie and MyTwin for everything.    And now it's off to do some more computer work, before moving on to top secret birthday things.  Heehee.  I think I'm more excited about his birthday than Shane is.  :)  Maybe after all that stuff I will play my guitar.  Busy times, relaxing :)   
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      More anonymous notes from more immature and ignorant people.   I'd respond very thoroughly and directly to the most recent one and what it pertains to, but I respect my boyfriend far too much for that.    Again, if you have something to say to me, leave your name. My email address is listed on most of my sites. My AIM name is too.  It's clear, though, that I am dealing with (and in effect we, meaning Shane and I) are dealing with highly immature, vindictive, and spiteful people that have nothing better to do with their time than to hide behind anonymity in order to lash out.  I remember reacting like that in high school.  Thankfully, most people grow up after high school and college and know how to behave like adults.    Obviously that's not always the case, as is evident by this ridiculous childishness.    **thank you, Shane, for the note you left in response to the ridiculousness.    "And I know that I am I am I am  the luckiest." -Ben Folds
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Sometimes I feel invisible.           *note: this is an incomplete thought.  it will remain that way, because the rest isn't very nice.  
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Can't sleep.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I   love   the "mature" people of this world that have nothing better to do with their lives than leave cruel, annonymous notes on someone else's site.  Honestly, that's amazingly witty and intelligent... not to mention quite mature.  A few guesses as to who it could be.  All of them are pathetic excuses for human beings.    My advice?  Get over yourself and grow up.  Or grow a set and leave your name.   And that's all I have to say on that matter.      
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Currently at Shane's house :)  I haven't had internet access in my room at school for several days, so I thought I'd toss up a quick post while I was here.  He is lovely and wonderful.   I smile so frequently when I'm with him.  We went to see Ben Folds, Rufus Wainwright and Guster on Saturday.  Amazing.  Lovely to be there with him, especially during Ben Folds, because he likes him so much.  Happy, happy girl. :)
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The good word: -got an A on my final paper -got an A on my final exam -I am done with this class! -I am leaving for camping as soon as Shane calls me back :) -Two(ish) more days until I'm with him^ (not counting today or Sunday!)   
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's today!!!!!!! Only two and a half hours of work... and then 5 hours of class (bah to class)... and then a 2 and a half hour drive...  Before I go camping!!!! :)  And then it's only Friday and Saturday... Before I go see Shane and we go to my house and to Vt. and then back to my house and do many fun things! I can't  wait  to see you baby! 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Financial Aid crisis: Apparently averted (or so they say).  Cross your fingers, as they don't seem to know what they're doing.  3 more days until I see my Shane :)  And then it's off for the week of road trips.  I can't wait... we have a really fun week planned.  I'm excited to meet his parents, and excited to have him home with me to spend time with my family and meet my closest friends.  They're all psyched to meet him too; anyone who rates this high in my books is a point of interest for my buddies *wink*  Now it's off to pack up some things to move to my new apartment on campus... and for my camping trip.  Woohoo.  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I hate the financial aid office.   I called them today to check in and see if they'd gotten the certification paperwork from my loan people.  They said they hadn't, so I called the lenders.  They told me that the school could access the information on line.  So I called financial aid back and they told me that I was  inelligible  for this loan too!  This is after they told me a month ago that all I'd have to do is apply for a personal education loan that would cover the cost of my classes.  So the lady told me that I needed to come up with more expenses... that a computer would do it.  I'm not sure yet if there's a limit on how much I can spend on the computer or if there's a certain amount I have to spend in order to get the school to certify the loan.  Shane found me a computer on line and got the price up to a place where it should definitely get them to certify the loan.  I'm also going to go on line and find two more options, one significantly less expensive, and one somewhere in the middle.  That way it'll cover all the possibilities she could come up with.  Hopefully one of them will be sufficient for her to certify the loan; if the school wants their money then they need to certify it.  Otherwise I have no way of paying them.   But the bright side?  Shane.  :)  He was right there when I needed him today, and was so helpful in finding a computer that was expensive enough to warrant the loan.  He was also quite wonderful last night with 2 fabulous phone calls... especially the second one :) Thank you Shane, for being there and helping so much.  Knowing you're there helps so much.  I  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "Every time I look at you the world just melts away All my troubles all my fears dissolve in your affections You've seen me at my weakest but you take me as I am And when I fall you offer me a softer place to land  You stay the course you hold the line you keep it all together You're the one true thing I know I can believe in You're all the things that I desire you save me you complete me You're the one true thing I know I can believe." -Sarah McLachlan    
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's been a great weekend so far.  Busy.  But really a lot of fun.  It's been wonderful having my parents here.  Today I think we're going back to Canada for a little while before they all go home.  I'll miss them... but at the same time the peace and quiet will be nice.  My room looks like a bomb hit it!   I talked to Steve the other night; he's still hunting for someplace to camp.  Hopefully he'll find something, otherwise we'll just be hanging out at his house.  I don't really mind doing that, but I've been looking forward to doing some camping.  One more week until I go to Oswego and then Shane and I go home.  :)  I can't wait to see him, or to spend that week together.  I'm really looking forward to going to Vermont and meeting his parents and anyone else that we happen to meet up with.  I'm also looking forward to all the things we have planned while we're at my house.  My parents are excited to see him again; they like him a lot.  So do I :).   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>