<Blog>

<date>31,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Blogs....   A strange phenomenon which has proved to be extremely infectious. Forget about Ebola, Sars or Anthrax. Blogs have become the new threat to life as we know it and is spreading faster than can be imagined, both airborne and by touch and is immensely contagious.  The worst branch of this epidemic seems to be the Xanga-branch. Several people I have observed, who were previously strong and otherwise healthy, have fallen victim to this aggressive virus commonly known as Xanga-blog.  This very destructive mutated form of the blogger virus is claiming several lives every day and the rate seems to be rapidly accelerating.   Other known branches of the virus are Blog-dot and Globe of blogs although these are so rare that only a few cases have been reported so far.  The original form of this virus, known as Blogger, has proved less contagious but in other ways stronger than the mutated branch, Xanga.  Mutual symptoms for all branches are so far known to be an overwhelming urge to rant and tell your most private thoughts and feelings, being in the strong belief that others might actually have an interest in reading them. This is not all, however, as the symptoms will soon escalate into strange behaviour, such as including links in signatures on different forums and discussion groups around the web, in order to spread the virus onto new victims.  Sadly, no cure for this condition has so far been discovered.  A silent enemy that shows no fear and no remorse. The Blog appears to have come to stay!
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       I need a vacation!   So far this day has been terrible. I went to work and went to shut off the alarm as usual..... and found that I simply couldn't remember the code! *slaps forhead* Come on! Something I've done almost every day for nearly 3 years. Talk about early Alzheimer's! So the alarm went howling, I managed to remember the code and shut the thing off and called in to tell the security guys that I did  not  want to see any of them.  After that, everything went fine.  For about 15 minutes.  Then I just happened to slam into a wall because I (for one reason or another) misjudged the distance. *sigh*  I am the only person I know who can actaully manage to do such things (or at least the only one to openly admit it!)  Maybe I should try to get 4 hours of sleep at night instead of only 3... *rolls eyes*  It's not like there's any wild activity going on anyway to keep me from sleeping... (ah, but if only....*snickers*) Ahem!   Actually, the wall-thing happens ocassionally, so maybe it's time to get those contacts after all.... If only the yellow ones I used when playing live "Vampire; the rpg" hadn't been stolen. They looked pretty cool with my black hair. Hehe! Well....if only my hair was still black! *sigh*  This reddish-blond thing is just so damn boring and doesn't go well with anything. I don't really understand the fascination some people have with it. Maybe I should just cut it. It's not like anyone will notice anyway. 4 inches more and I'll be able to sit on it... No one will notice if I get rid of 4 instead.   Hmmm... Maybe I should make a poll. Cut my hair or no? That way I can always say that it wasn't my choice! Ha ha ha!   Movie of the day:  The Tuxedo  (Jackie Chan, Jason Isaacs, Jennifer Love Hewitt)  I started watching this movie with a nagging feeling that this would be another of those poor American comedies which seems to be in massproduction these years, but I'm happy to say that I got myself a surprise. Especially when I discovered that Jason Isaacs is in it. That man is...."nice" to say the least. To tell the truth, he made Harry Potter 2 worth seeing. (Yes, I know... I'm pathetic!) Anyway, The Tuxedo.... It was actually funny. It was actually  very  funny! Certainly recommendable!   Song of the day:  Road to nowhere - Talking Heads Simply a classic. 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Helka claims that I'm depressing to read and asked if I never write anything "happy"...   Well, I tend to write what's on my mind and at the moment that seems to be my own misery, so there you go sweetie!  And yet you pop in here every other day?!?  Just to check on me or to get something to talk about on MSN?  Certain people seems to be.... well, stalking me. Don't know why I've suddenly become so damn interesting, but oh well....   It even appears like my old "friend" the ghostie has returned....  The cat's been acting up several times today and I've encountered the usual cold spots around my apartment. Just hope I don't have to go through the same as I've done twice before now... Right now, I couldn't care less, though. I have too many things to be concerned about right now, so I can't really waste my time focusing on a ghostie that is dying (no pun intended) to get some attention.  If it becomes too annoying I'll perform another cleansing.   Some of my cemetary shots turned out to contain even more than it appeared at first sight. I'll have to run them through a few programmes and maybe even send them to the group so Zub can have a look at them.   Orbs! I  hate  orbs!!! I want full apparitions, thank you very much!  And no Photoshop alterings!!!   Which reminds me....  Pugslee ..... If you send me that Photoshop fake of yours, one... more... time..... I promise you, you'll know what pain is!!   *sigh*  Still losing weight. Back at 62kg which is about 125 lbs.  People have started noticing and it's really annoying. It seems I do nothing but eat and yet... *sigh* No one will mention anything if you're  gaining  weight, but if you're  losing  weight.... damn! You'll find no peace anywhere!    Song of the day:  "The second you sleep" -Saybia (well, actually the entire CD has been playing all day)   I stay to watch you fade away I dream of you tonight, tomorrow you'll be gone   I love that song, although it often makes me remember what I don't want to.  It makes me remember my ex, Michael. One of the only decent guys I've known (I know, there have been far too many and most of them jerks.) Sometimes life simply doesn't turn out the way you think it will.  I never got the chance to say goodbye. He left.... and never came back! I haven't visited his grave since I don't know where he's buried.... Nor do I wish to know....  A soul too beautiful to live!
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      *sigh*  Fell down in a hole again. A very dark one this time.  Maybe that's just how my life is supposed to be. Maybe permanent heart-ache is simply my lot. Not that it really matters anymore. I'm used to it by now, it's a familiar feeling. Guess I would end up feeling strange without it, so it's probably for the best anyway.  Apparently, I always end up being the cause to everybody's problems. No matter what it is, I always seem to play a part in it. Nothing new in that.  Guess it's just so easy to blame "the weird one"...  And I've always been that one, that's no secret.Oh, right... 'They' call it "eccentric".  Even my so-called "friends" usually tease me by saying that everything's my fault anyway. Well, I guess so, when they say it... What is a friend anyway? I only have one.  And people on-line.... well.... they usually think I'm a joker.  At one time, someone mentioned my "feigned evil persona".... Well, who says it's so feigned after all?  When you spend most of your time on the "dark side" you sooner or later will pick up on the darker side of nature. I may be named after a goddess, but I'm only human after all!  But why care...? If there are really people reading this, I can imagine that most, if not all,  will run away screaming.   Should I be so lucky that anyone will even think about me after reading this.... I can only hope that they will try to understand.... and accept.  I'm sorry that I am who I am.... 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      AAAAAAAARRRGH!!!  I'm ready to pack up all my sweet dragons and simply leave!!! Maybe find a small deserted island somewhere or get my own cave in some remote mountain.  Human beings are nothing short of amazing! Someone's being mean to you so of course you do the most logical thing you can think of: Being mean to someone else! Right!  Someone's pissing you off and you simply have to try chasing everyone who're trying to help you away.  Fine, go ahead, why should I care.... *bangs head into wall until neighbour starts complaining*    DVD of the day:  No cure for cancer ( Denis Leary ) I simply love that guy! No one escapes  his  rants!  Woops! Busted by Mithadan. Is my face red. Well.... no, actaully it isn't. And it won't be unless it's very, very hot!  But the guy's close to proving to me that he  is  the impossible being.  Hmmmm... could make for an interesting psychological profile.  (Oh my, I can feel an evil smile appear.) 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Whew!  My CSI marathon is over (for now) and now I feel a bit.... hmmm, "empty" I guess...  My interest for forensics is burning bright these days and I'm taking in everything I can get.  Nothing on the TV but I've seen all their forensics shows anyway, so it doesn't really matter.   I know, a lot of people find me weird because of that interest, but honestly, it's not really my problem! I had a childhood dream (ok, I had several but this is one of them) of becoming a forensic pathologist, but sadly, my inability to understand chemistry when I was in school made an end to that dream and now that I actually  do  understand it, it's too late to do anything about it.  People always claim that "it's never too late" but trust me, it is!  Another question I'm always met with is, "why dead people?"  Well, first of all, dead people don't complain! If they do, something is  very  wrong and you better check a second time.  Second, the living can tell what happened. The dead can't! Unless you help them.  Which is why this is so damn interesting. These people have a story to tell and it's important that it will be told. The worst thing is the smell.... Ever had a raw piece of meat getting overdue? It's nothing in comparison! Trust me, I know! But they say you get used to it.  Actually, the "rule" is that after your first 3 months as a student at the Forensic Institute, you'll be able to eat your lunch again... Uhm, O...k. Only 3 months without lunch... sounds good. Should help you lose a bit of weight. [insert evil cackle here]  
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Not much going on today. Or maybe too much going on, so I don't know where to begin writing and therefore won't start at all.    Album of the day:  "Play" - Moby   The man's a genious, what can I say? "Everloving" gets me every time. Beautiful, haunting and without comparison!     Movie of the day:  Event Horizon My favourite move to date! A killer plot (literally) and oozing with talent. I mean, Sam Neill, Laurence Fishburne, Jason Isaacs and Sean Pertwee... What more is there to wish for?
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I've added a new link to a despairing place where you'll find all things dark and gruesome. Morbid facts and lots of fun!  The home of my sister in despair, the Comtesse. The Asylum Eclectica!
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Woops. Aman the Archer knows I've found her blog. *snickers*  Ah, well... She hasn't said anything bad about me... yet! Teehee!   Wednesday!   The name just says it all, doesn't it?   It's hot, it's humid and it's windy. The summer-weather from Hell. Makes sure you'll stay indoor and watch stupid movies. Heh! I actually saw Daredevil today. The thing I find the most ironic in this movie isn't the fact that we've got a blind superhero, but that we're dealing with a lawyer with a  conscience!    How unrealistic is that???  (I know Mithadan would kill me if he saw this, but what are the odds that he'll even come here?)  Don't really know what to think about that movie. A lot better than Spiderman, but then again, I only saw Spiderman because someone dropped in with it and begged me to put it on. Which I only did because I'm a major fan of Willem Dafoe.  Which brings me to:    Movie of the day:  The Boondock Saints ( Sean Patrick Flanery, Norman Reedus, Willem Dafoe, Billy Connoly )   My, my, what fun they have in Boston...  What can I say? It's brilliant, it's original, it's... it's.....  I love it!!!  And it has the most amazing scene containing a cat, a gun and what those two together can make on a wall. Wonderful humour! Definitely one of my favourite movies! I don't know how many times I've actually seen this movie. And with a sequel in production.... Troy Duffy, you're the man!      ~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~     Song (and album) of the day:   "Bloodflowers" - The Cure   "This dream never ends, you said,   this feeling never goes,   the time will never come to say goodbye..."    
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Ah, the wonders of insanity. I am in total denial or so some people say. And who the hell cares anyway...? It's me after all.   My writer's block seems to have disappeared and my story is flowing freely. Same can be said about my posting in "Brotherhood". The bitch is back!!! Yay! At least for a while.  Ok, some idiotic bitch, who's just become a member of a discussion group I'm a member of, has been irritating me for some time now and today she truly pissed me off. All along she's been giving advice and stuff, telling everyone who would listen about the importance of mutual respect and acceptance in order to make people get along. A pretty interesting subject was being discussed and then another (longtime) member of the group told her that she didn't agree with some of the other person's otherwise interesting viewpoints on that matter. And then pure hell broke loose.... Apparently feeling hurt that someone didn't agree with her, she started a flamewar and lost whatever respect she had build up.  What the hell happened to mutual respect and acceptance? Or does that only work one way?  Rita..... you made a mistake and that's ok, we can all do that. But then you destroyed everything for yourself by flaming someone we all like and highly respect.  A very bad move!! You have your belief, others have theirs! You   preach  (yes you do) about respect and acceptance of each other and yet   you  don't respect or accept others for what they are. People with their own beliefs and opinions!  Step carefully next time you move into the middle of a tight group and start flaming people....  Anyway, I'm feeling a lot better now. Thank you for giving me a reason to rant!  ~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~   Song of the day:   "The Two Trees" - Loreena McKennitt (The Mask and Mirror)
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So a bad day got a whole lot worse!  I had a major fight with the most important person in my life and from there, things took a turn for the worse.  Sounds like a damn episode of "A day in the life of..."  Well, definitely not the invisible man (thank you for that one, Rowan Atkinson) but of the alwaysaroundandbuggingotherpeople Lady DeSpair!    I had a discussion with one of those I-know-it-all-a-lot-better-than-you types earlier today, about this "condition" of mine and of course she claims to know exactly how I feel...  Right! You have no frigging idea how I feel because you haven't tried it!!! So please, stay out of my pathetic life and everything may get a whole lot better. For me at least! Why is it that people always seems to know what's best for you, when they actually don't have a clue? It's pathetic!   Apart from that, certain people have gotten the idea that I need to get myself a tan... Well, not to disappoint anyone, but I've been out in the sun almost everyday in the past week! I got fried and have been peeling my own skin off.... and I'm still deathly pale! And?  So what if you have to wear sun-glasses to look at me? So what if there's no reason to turn on the lights when I enter a room? (and I'm definitely not talking about my bright smile here...)  Just.... go away!  If you have a problem, take it somewhere else. I have enough!
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmm, ok so I have one of those days... *sigh*  Everything's cool, the weather's great, the sun is shining, the cat's curled up next to me catching mice in her sleep.... and I just feel like screaming my lungs out. Maybe I should really try that Primal Scream therapy I've read about. Must certainly be better than this.  I hate it when people are walking on eggshells around me, just waiting for me to explode and yet trying to avoid it. You're.... not ...... helping!!!!!  Just leave me alone!
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, so I'm starting a new blog because the other place (where I've had my angry blog for quite some time) suddenly got the idea that they wanted me to  pay  for it!  Yes, really! Can you believe it?  They  should pay  me  for decorating their site with my wonderful and talented writings.  Well, so you don't agree. That's ok! I forgive you. This time.  Hmmm, it's weird actually. It seems that after spending more than a year on the Barrowdowns, black, green and orange are the only colours I can stand looking at for a longer duration of time.  Oh well, I  know  I'm not the only one with that "problem" so I won't make a fuss about it. There are plenty of other topics that are screaming for my attention.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm so bored I could cry! I have so much to do but I don't feel like doing it. I have a home and people to take care of... But I don't feel like doing it right now.  I keep going back online, but for what? There's no reason whatsoever to be here.  Why is it that the absence of one person can actually affect you that much?  Geez, I think I just realized that I have no life, or at least that it's centered around one person. How pathetic! *runs off to cry in a corner*
     
    
</post>

<date>26,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I now know that my decision about RP'ing was right! Once 'Brotherhood' is done, it's over for me.  *sigh* I haven't been able to write a post for a couple of weeks... I'm trying, I really am and it's not that I don't have any ideas. I have plenty, everyone makes great posts....but when I try to start a post, I simply go blank. My brain shuts down.  I feel like such a failure, having to leave it to others to use my characters. I hate that feeling. I can't tell how many times I've wished that we could just close the damn thing for a month or so. People keep disappearing without a word and we don't even have the players we need. People saying they'll join and then we never hear a word from them again. Even our game-owner is gone at the moment, although I believe that attending your own brother's funeral is a more than valid excuse. We've been cursed from the beginning. So much have happened and now the players have lost focus. What should have become a great story is now a mere shadow of what it could have been. I hate the feeling that I'm letting everyone down. Had I been made the co-owner as was suggested, it would really have been a joke.  Yes, I do a lot of work behind the scenes, making things run as smoothly as possible. In fact, that's how it is in a lot of places. I'm the one you never see, the one pulling the strings. I guess that in a way I'm nothing but a puppeteer. And I don't mind, really. I'm used to working in the shadows.  What I can't accept is the feeling I get when I sit for hours, staring at an empty screen, unable to write more than two lines. I feel like I've burned out.  I think The Cure hit the spot with their song "39".  "The fire is almost out and there's nothing left to burn"  That is how I feel. I've used all I had.  People claim that my writing has never been as good as it is now. Heh! If only they knew the struggle it is to make a decent post. Looking through the posts I've made in 'Brotherhood'  people only see a post. I, on the other hand, see the 7-8 hours of work that often lies within my posts. Far too much time if you're not satisfied with the result anyway! 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmmm, haven't felt like writing anything this weekend.... Still don't feel like writing anything....  Have been reading too much, I guess....   "Had I the heavens’ embroidered cloths,    Enwrought with golden and silver light,    The blue and the dim and the dark cloths    Of night and light and the half light,    I would spread the cloths under your feet:            But I, being poor, have only my dreams;    I have spread my dreams under your feet;    Tread softly because you tread on my dreams. "  -Aedh wishes for the Cloths of Heaven, W.B. Yeats
     
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Damn...I actually left Mordor (Land of Shadow) today. It has simply degraded into something so pathetic that I will have no more of it. Why create a Troll-forum where people can bitch at each other and then start complaining when people actually use it? It should never have been made in the first place! I thought Mordor was a Tolkien discussion board, wisely led by our dear Ringlord, but I guess I was wrong. At least I didn't think it would become a place where we would get an entire section to tell someone how much of an Orc you think (s)he is. It's no longer the place for me. Thank you and goodbye! Which leaves me roaming 3 Tolkien-forums on which I only post on one. And even that is something that doesn't happen very often anymore. I can't count the times I've considered leaving the Downs and yet I'm still there. Although mostly in lurk-mode. And should I decide to leave, I doubt few will miss me if anyone will even notice that I'm gone. No one there has ever been listening to what I had to say anyway.  I should post in 'Brotherhood'. They're all expecting me to do so, but I've never been as empty as now. I can think of absolutely nothing. Definitely time for me to withdraw from RPG's!   Song of the day:   My Immortal  - Evanescence No matter your guise, be it Elf, Dragon, Ranger or simply you, you are my immortal! Always and forever!   Movie of the day:   Equilibrium ( Christian Bale, Emily Watson, Sean Bean, Sean Pertwee ) To stop the inhumanity of humans, any kind of emotion is illegal. Feel and you will be killed.  Brilliant movie! Must be seen! Contains a fabulous soundtrack which, of course, is not available. A very emotional soundtrack so it has probably been considered EC-10 and has been condemned. (Only those who have seen the movie will know what THAT means! So go ahead and see it. You won't regret it.) 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Heh! I've just learned that I should start looking closer into things before accepting to do something. At least with certain persons.  I'm not one who usually reads fan-fiction, especially not Tolkien based, except for a selected few that have been found worthy of my interest (you guys know who you are) and just a couple of days ago I accepted to proofread a story. Oh my.... I am a VERY open-minded person who's practically impossible to embarrass but I must admit that at one time, my eyebrows nearly ended up in my hairline. Uhm..... you COULD have warned me that it was a pretty steamy slash-fiction. Not that I care, but.... Ah well, I got myself a good laugh. Truly an... interesting (to say the least) pairing you've got there. ;p But at least you kept your filthy hands away from my Maglor! You've learned that much during the short time you've known me.  :)  More than once have I been asked why I join RPG's when I don't like fan-fiction. Well, I don't think you can really compare those. I consider an RPG more like a play. In 'Brotherhood' I was given a name and some personality traits for the character I had agreed to play and that's that. To me it's like being on stage. You're presented with a character and a script, now play! At first I had no idea what to do with her, I felt absolutely nothing about her. But then suddenly we established a link and I knew exactly how to work with her. A bit too well, actually, since she managed to settle herself more in my mind than I wanted her to. I even ended up having to convince some people, that it wasn't me, that I'm nothing like her.  That Aman likes her as much as she does and that she's crazy about an older character of mine, Rhana, a turn-coat of the worst kind, can only be found disturbing. But we've already talked about that, right sweetie? ;p  But RPG's are almost history for me. Once 'Brotherhood' has ended, I'm off. Ok, I know I've said that before, but this time I'm serious! No more RPG's for me, at least for a very long time. When writing a post feels more like a burden than something you do to have fun, then it's time to stop. I don't feel that I write very well, so why do it? Maybe someday the RPG I've been looking for for so long will turn up and I'll be able to join. But until then...   I read an interesting theory on the Jack the Ripper case. Was the last victim really Mary Kelly? Those who have seen the photos from that crimescene know that the body was so mutilated that it was beyond recognision. Was it staged?  urlLink Article  by Des McKenna.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm amazed that it appears that quite a few people are now reading this thing. A weird feeling to say the least. But don't expect me to watch my mouth, because that's something I'm practically unable to do.  Someone referred to an earlier entry and asked me who Michael is.  Well, I guess I asked for it by mentioning him, although I didn't mean to open up for that part of my mind again after so many years. *sigh* Michael was.....an incredible person, one of those you simply can't argue with or be mad at. My boyfriend, but still so much more. He just....understood everything. You didn't have to explain anything because he just knew what you meant. All the plans we had.... And then he died in a car-crash in '95, 20 years old. It wasn't his fault. He was just there, in the wrong place at the wrong time.  It's truly amazing how quickly your entire world can change. It only takes a mili-second for everything to fall apart.  That's the story or at least as much of it as I'm going to tell.  I've never fully recovered, that's no secret, but I'm able to live again.   Heh! I'm finally learning how to drive. About time, some would say, but I haven't needed it until now.  Gods, I HATE driving with a stick!!! It should be forbidden by law! Besides, it would prevent a lot of accidents... But that's not going to happen anytime soon and so I'm stuck with the damn thing. *sigh*  But if my sister could make it, then I can definitely do it as well. As long as I remember that I'm surrounded by idiots out there...  I'm still recovering from my vacation. It sounds strange, that you have to recover from a vacation, I know, but that's the way it is. When I left, I was exhausted mentally. When I came back, I was exhausted physically. But I'm feeling better now. And I've finally found some measure of peace. There is a day after this. There's even a day after that.    Album of the day:   Pisces Iscarot  -Smashing Pumpkins  Song of the day:   Obscured  - Smashing Pumpkins (Pisces Iscarot) Truly a masterpiece from Billy Corgan! Even people who despise Smashing Pumpkins have given in to this track. Quiet and soothing, touching the darkness and yet reaching out for the light. Brilliant!
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Honey, I'm ho-ome!!!!!!!   Whoever said vacations are good for the soul and the health had no idea what he (or she, but not likely) was talking about!!!!  After 9 hours of driving and 2½ hours of sailing we (my parents and I, yes I know some may find it pathetic to go on vacatin with my parents, but they invited me and they paid for the thing, so...) were finally able to drag ourselves over the doorstep of one of the most pathetic houses I've ever set foot in.   And then it all started...  My mom and I are, apart from very good friends, very much alike and both terribly dominating (no one guessed that, right?) which is bound to lead to trouble when we're both placed in a small hole together for a week.  Poor, poor dad......  me: Mom......? mom: .... me: Mom! mom: .... me:  MOM!!!  *quickly pulls mom out of the kitchen and turns off the stove which mom has accidentally turned on....with a large, now melting, plastic box on it. * me: *hissing just about every known curse and bad words in the Danish language* mom: Do you have really to say all that? me:  YES!!!  mom: Don't inhale that. Don't want you to get sick or hurt yourself. me: OUT!  Which is why everything smelled and tasted like burned plastic for the rest of that day... Yuck!  Then, when I danced on the cliffs, she nearly got a heart-attack.   mom: Get away from there! me: .... mom: You  are  aware that there's absolutely no support under that rock...? me: Yup! And the surface of the sea is 60 ft below me! mom: Get away from there! me: .... mom: Stop looking at me like that! me: Mommy dearest....I'm an adult! I can look at people any way I want. Besides, I have to take a picture over the edge! mom: ....   Still tired, stressed out, too much sugar, too much food...too little rest.  And too much sun... I'm now showing off the Danish national colours (red and white).  And now, after 2½ hours of sailing and 9 hours of driving, I'm back home... Ok, off to bed!    Album of the day:   Fields of Gold  - Sting This album has one big mistake.  Shape of my heart  isn't on it.... *sniff* Otherwise, it's perfect!
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So..... Today's the day!  I know I should be thrilled that I'm finally going on vacation, but.... I'm simply too tired and have far too much on my mind to even enjoy the thought.  You're awake for more than 30 hours, suffering from stress, guilt and having barely eaten anything for several days, then finally get some sleep..... and is wide awake again 3½ hours later.....  Sleep deprivation? Nah! Totally overrated! I'm not even hallucinating, so what's the fuss?   But I should get going. Everything's packed and I'm ready to be picked up. Or at least I should be.  But DAMN I'll miss my beloved computer!!! *sob*  But I guess most of you can use one week of silence from this corner.  I bid you all a very fond farewell....  Damn, did I really say that? Me, using words said by a HOBBIT of all evil creatures...? Guess that proves that I AM losing it! *faints*  Anyway, I will be back in a week. Behave yourselves in my absence. And yes, that means you too, Helka!  So to all:  Farvel, goodbye, adieu, ave, tot ziens, auf wiedersehen, adiós, au revoir, прощание, arrivederci.....    Song of the day  (or at least this morning so far):  Dante's Prayer  - Loreena McKennitt (The book of Secrets) Peaceful, sooting and simply magnificent!   "Though we share this humble path, alone How fragile is the heart Oh give these clay feet wings to fly To touch the face of the stars  Breathe life into this feeble heart Lift this mortal veil of fear Take these crumbled hopes, etched with tears We'll rise above these earthly cares  Cast your eyes on the ocean Cast your soul to the sea When the dark night seems endless Please remember me...." 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I have lost someone very dear to me. Someone I cared deeply about, for being the friend he was. Someone who actually seemed to care.... Someone who could almost always make me laugh or at least smile... If I had any tears left, I would cry.....but I can't. I've used them all... May the grace of the Goddess ever shine upon your path!  People tell me all the time how cold I am, but if that is the case, would I really care, then?   Damn, I just realised that I've been up for nearly 31 hours now. But how the hell should I be able to sleep?
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      What do you do when someone you've trusted, someone you confided in, suddenly goes behind your back and betrays you? I mean.... once the white-hot fury has settled....and you've managed to keep yourself from screaming out a curse (they work, you know).... you have to do something.... Right?  Are people simply trying to make bad things worse?   Hmmm... Maybe I should just say thanks! I've just been reminded of why I find it nearly impossible to trust anyone!  *bangs head against wall*
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Yay! Only two days to go and I'm off! I can't recall ever needing anything like I do this vacation. One week away from everything, from everyone....alone with my troubled thoughts. Maybe I can solve this...maybe I can't... Only time will tell.   Why is it that things are always dawning on you when it's practically too late to do anything about it?  I'm confused, I'm sad and I'm angry....all at once, making everything a big blur.  Well.... actually, I've grown numb. That's what happens when too many emotions are fighting each other to be the primary devil in the mind and causes the emotional center in the brain to shut down temporarily.  It's a simple chemical reaction in the brain, to prevent the mind from getting lost beyond the dark doors of insanity, nothing more.... but  damn  it feels good when it finally sets in. That's when nothing really matters anymore and you realize that life goes on, with or without you.   I found a friend. Someone who managed to pull me back up when I hit the floor and eased my mind so I, for once, was able to sleep at night and I am grateful for that.  I dared to trust you from the beginning, but I never had the guts to turn to you before now. I thank you for helping me up, though I hope you won't have to again. Thank you for being who you are!   -"I hate and I love. Why do I do this, perhaps you ask. I do not know, but I feel that it is happening and am tormented."                                         -Catullus 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      It is a strange feeling when you finally realize that your relationship is crumpling and breaking between your hands and slowly slipping from your fingers. And that there is absolutely nothing you can do about it.  Did I care too much?  Crave too much? Why all the kind and sweet words, if they are just that? Words.... I wish......  I don't know what I wish... is there anything left to wish for? I no longer know what to think or feel.....or how to... Does it even matter anymore?  How can I make you understand, make you see, when you don't want to see? How can I tell you when you don't want to hear? I'm trying, but I'm losing.......   -"Tell me that one day I'll find the courage to have the life I've dreamed of."                                              -Zazie
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Yay, I actually managed to get 5 hours of sleep for once. Truly amazing!  Someone asked me this weekend, why I'm being such a bitch at times. Standard answer: Because I can!   Well, sugar.... If you deserve it, I show no mercy!   Ah, so Mad Maddox has been "released" from the Cuckoo's Nest once again. You would think that they'd know you by now, right sweetie? ;-p  Good to know that you're back to..... well... since I can't say 'normal' I'll just say 'your old self'. *snickers* Glad I could be of some service by entertaining you with this blog.   For those who doesn't know, Maddox, mostly known as "The Twit", is my former forum-master on the Crypto-zoo forum where I used to be an admin. One of the few guys who pass the "test" although he hasn't turned 35 just yet (one year to go, sweetie). He's a great guy with a mind even more twisted than mine, so beware. He also has the bad habit, from time to time, of asking me to marry him.  No way!!!  Why not, you ask? 1. I know you! 2. You're gay and I don't want to fight with Steve all the time! 3. I've seen you naked and it nearly made me weep because of reason #2!!!  Hmmm, must be why Steve always seems to be in a bliss....  *tries to look innocent but fails utterly*  It has come to my attention that the forum wants their 'Ruthless Reaper' back.  Well guys, I'm sorry but that's impossible. I hacked Master Maddox' account and deleted my own. Well, ok... so I didn't hack it, he gave me the password long ago so I could run things from there when he was....indisposed, but I did delete my account and since I helped close the forum to new members, it's not that easy to come back, even if I wanted to.  I'm aware that the forum has turned into something it shouldn't in our absence, but with all due respect, it's no longer my problem. I ran that forum practically alone and if I want that again, I'll start my own.  Maddox, your e-mail isn't working but I know you'll read this sooner or later.  I seem to have lost the theme article I wrote on Tunguska. Please send it to me, thank you. It's the only one missing, I have all the others.     
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So the celebrating of Lughnassad has come to an end. Hope everyone got through safe and sound! ;-p   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Just finished watching 'Phonebooth'. Pretty sweet! Should teach some people to never answer a phone that doesn't belong to them.   About movies.... Someone asked me about all these movies I mention here and wanted to know if I really am some movie-maniac who do nothing but watch movies all the time.  The answer is, that I have some..... 250-something DVD's and I usually have a movie running in the background when working at the computer. Which I do a lot, so there's your explanation. ;-)   I ran into my old music teacher and vocal-trainer today and it really turned into a fun experience.  We decided to go back to her home and experience "the good old days" once again and we soon found ourselves by her piano.  She said that we could just warm up by starting slowly and being as much of a Loreena McKennitt fan as myself, she immediately started playing "Dante's Prayer" which I knew was my cue.  The song went well (if you ask me) since I know it forwards, backwards and even in my sleep and it's pretty good for warming up. The challenge (or should I say disaster) came 2 seconds after finishing the song, when she forced me onto L.M's "Courtyard Lullaby". That one went pretty well too, or so I thought, until we finished it and looked at me like I had just been singing the lyrics for another song and she looked like she was going to cry. "What the HELL have you been doing? I thought you were singing in those bars, not emptying what they had behind the counter!"  I had to explain that singing Irish folk songs aka Irish drinking songs, need a little "flavour and mood". And then she laughed and said that at least I no longer sound like Janis Joplin. Nope, I don't!  As much as I love Janis, though, I learned from that experience that it's best to shut up when you've lost your voice or you may end up sounding like the Lady for 3 weeks.  She's never forgiven me for not keeping quiet during those 3 weeks, but honestly, if you suddenly sound like Janis Joplin, you damn better use it for something good. So I kept singing. Hehe!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Men!   What do we need them for?  Do  we even need them? For more than testing our own (lack of) patience and stress-level, that is. And yet.....there's just something about them. I had a discussion about men last night, with someone I know, but it didn't take long before others decided to join.  My friend claimed, that whenever you see a relationship with a remarkable age-difference, it simply can't be out of love but is because of money. UsuallyI'm able to compose myself, but that remark caused me to see red.  According to her, you shouldn't have an age-difference of more than 5 years (and it damn better not be the guy who's the younger).  5 years, huh? Well, let me tell you something. Of all the relationships I've had (and I don't intend to count but it's far too many, ok?) with guys my own age, only one didn't end in a complete disaster. Ok, so I may not have made the best choices in my life, but who the hell cares?!? Fact is that you just can't judge people like that!  If you ask me, few guys are attractive until they reach the age of 35. There you have it! Why, you ask? Because that's when they finally grow up!  You can have this guy you've never really noticed and on the morning of his 35th birthday, WHAM! Right in your face. Ooh la la! Gimme!  So, now I'm being called an opportunist. O......k! So just because I prefer men who are acting like adults, it turns out that I'm actually just going for the money! Hmmm, amazing what other people can tell you about yourself and your views.  I must say that if it's money you're after, wouldn't it be a lot better to pull an 'Anna Nicole Smith' on some senile 90-year old millionaire instead of picking a 45-year old with a normal income? Well, I just ask....  The discussion naturally turned to the matter of money and once again I ask  what do we need it for?   Money, the root to all evil! No, men are, I know, but let's stay with the cliches and old beliefs for a while. "Money doesn't make you happy!" We've all heard that before, but damn, it's true! You see the career-riders out there, making lots of money, spending long hours in the office....and when they go home they have nothing. Money may place you in a certain spot in society, but they don't keep you warm at night! Ok, so you can buy that as well, but that doesn't really count, does it? Moeny's not a bad thing to have, but I certainly don't want it at all costs.   To combine these things, can you be happy with an older guy who has lots of money? Good question.... I don't know the answer and I truly doubt I ever will.  And that's fine with me!  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I went for a nice long walk in the forest today, alone, all by myself. Just me, the whispering trees, the warming sun caressing my skin and the soothing touch of the wind as it lazily played with my hair.  Having completely lost track of time, I found myself by a small brook and next I had tied up my long skirt and kicked off my boots. Yes, I am one of those people who have my very own sense of fashion, which means that I almost always wear army boots whether I'm in jeans or wearing one of my long flowing dresses, no matter the season or temperature.  I sat down and relaxed, feeling the cool water surrounding my feet and let go, listening to the voice of Nature and the stories she told.   How long I was sitting there I know not, but a rustling sound got my attention and I caught a glimpse of a screaming red colour out of the corner of my eye.  Keeping perfectly still, I observed the squirrel for quite some time as he slowly came closer to me, having obviously eyed the remains of my discarded apple.  Becoming more bold, apparently deciding that I was no threat, he quickly came closer until he was so near I could have reached out and touched him.  Daring for a moment to turn his back on me, he snatched the apple and moved away but only a few feet and began to eat, still watching me closely as if to see if I had more for him.  Wishing that I did, I watched him as he ate, seeing the fine details of this small creature, the way he held and turned the food in his small "hands", the strong red of his fur and the fine white of his throat and belly, he certainly was a beauty.   Having finished and realised that I didn't have anymore for him, he looked at me once and disappeared up in the tree nest to him.  Finally able to move again, I quickly removed my now icy cold feet from the water and tried to get a little life back into my sleeping legs.  As I was leaving, I turned once and looked up into the tree. There he was, sitting on his throne in the branches, his black eyes watching me.  With a smile I turned and left, knowing that I had just had a wonderful encounter with one of nature's gentle spirits. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      " Huge erection causes blushes on the eve of Royal visit   A giant statue of a naked man with a two-foot erection has caused a row in Salzburg after it was unveiled on the eve of a visit by Prince Charles. Salzburg's mayor Heinz Schaden said he was horrified when he realised what the artwork comprised. He said it would be impossible for Prince Charles to avoid seeing the figure when he arrives in the city and wants it taken down immediately. Mr Schaden said: "No-one asked me or my office for permission to put this up, and if they had, we would have said no. I can't stress strongly enough how totally tasteless this is, and have demanded immediately that those responsible take it down." Called Arc de Triomphe, the statue by artists Ali Janka, Wolfgang Gantner, Tobias Urban and Florian Reither shows a naked man bending over backwards with his hands on the ground and a two-foot erection thrusting into the sky. The statue was described as a tribute to Viagra and was unveiled in front of the Rupertinum Modern Art Gallery, one day before Charles was due to fly in for a visit to the Salzburg Festival."   Culled from: Ananova     urlLink Full story  and  picture of the naughty statue    Ok, now that I've finally stopped laughing hysterically.... My, my..... That is....er... interesting... to say the least. *giggles* I must admit that when I saw the picture of that statue.... gods... I laughed so hard I had to go dry my eyes. I really like that thing with the water! Sure adds some detail. *breaks into hysterical laughter again*  Uhm... Am I the only one who'd like to see who they used as a model for that thing? *broad grin*  I wonder why they don't put up stuff like that  here . We only have less interesting pieces of... "art" Like that ugly fountain with those ugly frogs. And no! I wasn't drunk! No! I didn't trip into the water and no! I didn't kiss that damn frog! That photo is a fake! Period! (denial, denial, denial) 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      How the heck it happened, I don't know.... but I actually passed the driving test..... I now have a driver's licence..... Hmmmmmm..... All I can say is: Be afraid! Be very afraid! [insert evil laughter here]     Album of the day:   urlLink A day without rain  -  Enya   Somehow I managed to forget about this CD for more than a year....but now it's back and it's here to stay! Probably the best album the lady has made so far, although one of my clear favourites of hers, Boadicea, is older than that and so it's missing.  A lot of people actually find that particular "song" rather strange, but I've loved it ever since I heard it the first time, many years ago. In fact that was in the Stephen King movie  Sleepwalkers , a movie that I actually like. Seeing that movie actually kicked me into a crazy search for the answer to one single question. In the very beginning of that movie, there is a quote from a book, an  Encyclopedia of Arcane Knowledge . No one has been able to answer me whether that is actually a real book, or if the dear Mr. King just made it up. Although, I have seen books with descriptions of creatures stranger than these "Sleepwalkers".  And yes, Maddox, I know you're probably rolling your eyes and yawning right now, as it isn't exactly the  Necronomicon , but honestly, I find this a tad more interesting, so no comments on that, thank you very much! ;p
     
    
</post>

<date>28,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Another day, another week.   Only 6 more weeks and my life will once again be worth living. For about a week....then I'll sadly enough have to send the dragon back to its treasure in the US. *sigh* The time from then until New Years, when I'll once again be resting in the dragon's lair, will be horrible. *sniff*  Heh! Someone sent me Nico Claux's e-mail addy. Nico, who's also known as "The vampire of Paris". Uhm.... thanks pal, but what do I need that for? No matter how interesting or fascinating a cannibalistic killer may be, I've had enough correspondence with cons of different kinds to cover a lifetime. I simply don't have the time anymore.   Yay, the kids-discussion came up again. Just fucking great! And now I feel like I've been run over by a truck. What's the point anyway? Might just as well go and ask the Dr.'s to rip it all out, because I don't fucking need it! Could probably be donated to someone who's able to put it to good use.....    Song of the day:  "Clocks" -  Coldplay   urlLink (A Rush of Blood to the Head)  Just so damn relaxing when you're in a bad mood..... And I'm in a VERY bad mood right now.... 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       We won the case!!!!!  Of course we did! It wasn't even a question! *makes funny little dance*  Which led to a discussion with someone about court-room "dramas". We see it time after time on TV and in movies, "Raise your right hand, swear on the Bible".... But what about non-Christians? I mean.... don't get me wrong, but I can swear on the Bible and the next moment lie so you wouldn't know what to look for (not that I would, but you get the point). It really wouldn't have the desired effect.  What would they do? Use my large book of herbal lore? Probably the closest you'll come to something resembling a bible to me.   Guess I was simply born to ask all the weird questions.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Someone has shown a great interest in my RPG-idea but I don't know if I'm ready to "sell" it just yet. Although it may end that way, since I've proved to be a complete and utter failure, when it comes to writing in RPG's. Some say it could become a fabulous fan-fic, but since I simply refuse to write fan-fic, that's really not an option. Guess that if I want to see it happen, I'll have to pass it on. And right now there's already a taker. Only problem is, that after hearing out my thoughts an ideas on the matter, he has one demand. That I play the part of my dear Maglor. "You have an understanding for misery and despair that no one else I know does!" Gee, thanks mate! Just what I've always wanted to hear... Anyway, that may all sound very good. Except for one thing! If I accept this, I'll end up in a new RPG. Then I might just as well run the thing myself. So this idea which has been brewing for 1½ years now is very close to being flushed out the drain. Who would have any interest in writing about the Dagor Dagorath anyway...? I've only come across 3 so far and only one has actually read about it.  But it's truly amazing how a single comment by someone can end up in a twisted idea for a RPG. Guess that although it may never be, I should say thanks to Nazzy10 for planting the seed for this in my head by telling me, that my only purpose in life is to release Melkor from the Void. But who cares?   Movie of the day:   urlLink 28 days later  As a horror movie, it doesn't really hit. I'd recommend   urlLink Resident Evil  over this. What makes this movie brilliant though, is the psychological aspect. When it all comes down to survival, what becomes of our so-called civilised behaviour? We, as humans, are only one very small step above all other animals and when it's a matter of our own survival....it's basic human nature at its best. Or should I say worst?!?! That is what makes this movie worth seeing more than once. As I already have. ;p 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Ah, geez....  Someone managed to start a topic on the Downs which I can't recall ever having seen before. I believe it was something about Balrogs and wings.... *rolls eyes* And Rimbaud threw around the same wonderful humour as always.  Today a person directed me to this oh so funny blog that I simply just HAD to see.... Amazing how people just know exactly what I have to see or do or what not to. Well, it turns out that it was Burrahobbit's, which means that this was my second visit to that place. *sigh*  I don't get it... Honestly, what's so funny about what he's doing?  Hmmm, maybe I should go "au naturelle" like Burra and start a new blog, perhaps one about my non-existent sex-life. Guess a lot of people would find that, if not interesting, then at least horribly pathetic! Should be able to provide people with a good laugh, if anyone should possibly stay awake for that long.   
     
    
</post>

<date>13,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hehe! Hehehehe!  I'm truly sorry that I'm in such a good mood (no, not really but it sounded good!).  I just finished watching  urlLink The Ring  and I haven't stopped laughing yet. I never really intended to watch this movie, but when several people told me that it was pretty good, I decided to give it a shot. And my, I haven't laughed this hard since....hmmmm, when did I laugh like this...? Probably the last time I put on  urlLink The Exorcist .... Or  urlLink Hellraiser . Hehe! Yes, Pinhead and Darth Vader are my childhood heroes. Must be the leather! *siiiiiiiiiigh* ;p  Anyway, I didn't expect much from this movie but I decided to give it a try and I honestly admit that I was surprised. It actually has a story! At one time I started thinking "No! It can't just be this simple!" when I couldn't stop thinking  urlLink Stir of Echoes  (BRILLIANT movie! MUCH better than  urlLink 6th Sense , but sadly kept in its shadow). But then everything took a turn and the movie saved itself. And I'm still laughing.  What a sweet and utterly wicked idea!  The best part is the "forbidden" movie itself. What a masterpiece! Like a wonderful mix of the best (or worst?) of E.A. Poe and H.P. Lovecraft. Makes me want to start digging in the old stuff and read Lovecraft again. The gods know it's too many years ago.   Ah, I'm in the mood for more. Wonder if I should put on my favourite movie,  urlLink Event Horizon .  *gasp* WHAT??? My favourite movie isn't LOTR??? NO FRIGGING WAY!!!! I prefer movies that are able to move me in some way.  urlLink Fellowship...  is ok. It has its moments but  urlLink TTT .... *sigh* What can I say? There are 3 things in that movie that I find worth watching. Gandalf's fight with the Balrog, Gollum (what an adorable creature! I want one!) and then the final seconds before the credits, when the view goes to Mordor. The fiery sky with the lightning, the Nazgul in the air and the tower.... The only scene in the two movies that can make me teary-eyed.  That is the most beautiful picture I have ever seen!!!!  I would give anything to have that particular picture as a wall-painting in my apartment. *sigh* Guess I could call it a "room with a view" then.... ;p  Anyway, I'm off to find another funny movie! Hehe!  
     
    
</post>

<date>12,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       I passed the damn thing!!!!!   Got the theory over with, now it's just a few more lessons and then it's the final driving test. Which I'm not at all nervous about. Why should I be? I'm just going to drive a car.... No big deal!*makes funny little dance*  This is going to be a gooooooood weekend! *makes funny little dance again*   Peeked in at the Barrowdowns chat last night. I knew I shouldn't have and once again I found that it's extremely sad what it has become. I've had wonderful Tolkien discussions (and other topics) on MSN- and Yahoo Messenger.  Aman, we miss you big time on MSN!!!! Sadly, she's not the only one who's disappeared. But all who may be interested, you know the despairing addy. I'm here everyday.  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Maddox, sweetie, I LOVE opening my inbox and finding another of your one-liners! The one today was brilliant!  "Christi, you're insane!"  NO secret! But, uhm... I'M not the one going back to the Cuckoo's Nest every other month. ;p   Had an interesting "conversation" with a nurse today. She was sitting there, twisting what seemed to be the very last drop of blood from my body, smiling ever so sweetly.  Nurse: You look pale... Me: I'm always pale! Nurse: sure you're alright? Me: Positive! Nurse: Let me know if you start feeling bad. Me: I'm not! Nurse: it's just so you don't faint... Me: I'm not going to faint! I've never fainted! I'm too damn stubborn to faint! A dog bit off half my face (well, almost) when I was 9 and I didn't faint! I'm not going to faint so just do your job and don't worry! Nurse: .....  Yes, I know, I could've been nicer to her but I really didn't feel like it. These days I don't feel like being nice to anyone. At least not anyone who has to do with hospitals. (Sorry, love, you know you're an exception!)
     
    
</post>

<date>09,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      My, my...  No one's dared to officially comment on Sunday's entry, but DAMN have they flooded my e-mail, telling me what a sick, twisted and perverted person I am. Well... DUH! That's really old news, sweethearts and I've never claimed to be otherwise.  Claim what you want, the Bodyworld Exhibit is mostly minded on science and studies of the human body and no one's telling you to go there if you don't want. And I DID warn you!   Am feeling a lot better today, but the mere thought that I have more bloodsamples taken (10 or 12) tomorrow really doesn't make me want to jump around from joy. *sigh*  As if I don't have something better to do with my time than letting them suck out all my blood. And I had Anemia already  before  they started that...    I'm just about fed up with Blooger.com. So much that I've started considering the unthinkable.... moving to *gulp* Xanga.... But I won't do it in silence. Everyone will be sure to know if that's going to happen.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      BLLGH! I feel like... I don't know... Just came back from the Dr.   More tests! Tests tests, tests. Bloodsample after bloodsample. I doubt I have much more blood they can take. Soon they'll start ripping off my skin as well.  *sigh* Better throw myself on the couch and feel lousy for a while. *sniff*
     
    
</post>

<date>07,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Damn! This thing's been down and acting strangely most of the weekend. Which means I haven't been able to say anything here. *sob sniffle howl*  Realised yesterday that Günther Van Hagens' "Bodyworld Exhibit" will be in Hamburg, Germany until January. I wanna go! I wanna go! *sigh* Frightening to some, exTREMEly fascinating to others. Heh, like me! A dream to some, a nightmare to others! ;p  Here's a couple of links for those who might be interested.   Warning!!! Probably not for the weak-hearted.    urlLink Official site   urlLink "Eye-account"   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh, no.... oh no.... *laughs hyserically*   urlLink Must read!    Hmmm, don't know if you can call that guy a jackass.... But he's certainly SOME kind of.. uhm... ass.... As much of it he has left, that is.*snickers* Too bad he didn't die. I'm sure there would've been a Darwin Award waiting for him then.  Hmm, other things claim my attention for now but I'm sure I'll be back soon to update this...  Stay tuned! ;p
     
    
</post>

<date>04,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh, my, now we're at it again. Once again someone has created a thread on the Downs to ask us all the brilliant, interesting and thought-provoking question:  Who do YOU think should have played [insert name here] in the movie?   This time it's about Arwen. *sigh* When do people face the truth? They may not be satisfied with the result but there's absolutely nothing they can do about it. And no one cares! It's all a matter of taste. We all have certain actors we prefer but unless you start saving your hard-earned money right NOW so you can make YOUR version of the movie in about..... say a couple of hundred thousand years, it doesn't really matter who you think should've played the part. Because he/she didn't! Simple as that! Accept it or don't watch the movie. It's really not that supergreat anyway.  One thing that can really annoy me, is when people openly admit that they can't tell two movies apart.  "Oh, yeah, I saw Elrond and I yelled 'AGENT SMITH' so everyone could hear what a dork I am!"  Ahem!  Why is it that people for some reason have to make that connection? You don't look at Gandalf (Ian McKellen) and yell " Hey, that's the nazi Richard III dude" . Or look at Bilbo (Ian Holm) and say  "Wow, that insane android from Alien is actually a Hobbit!"   Or do you? I really hope not. A movie is a movie is a movie! Actors are actors! Elrond is NOT Agent Smith! They're both characters, played by Hugo Weaving. Hugo is an actor. Repeat after me  ac-tor!  Good!  And no, he's not too old or anything. He's PERFECT! He's.... oh....right...forgot there are actually people reading this thing. *shoves tongue back behind teeth*  But anyway. How many times can people tell who they think should've been what? Accept that it is the way it is. PLEASE!?! Yup, I know that word isn't one of my regular ones to use but it does work from time to time.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmmm, some very weird things are going on here.  First I had no problems while testing the comments function but apparently everybody else got an error message. Then I played just a bit with the code and had someone testing it for me (thanks Helky) and now it seems to work. Apart from the small detail that now  I  can't see any comments on the site.  Good thing is that I can see all comments elsewhere so don't let that keep you from saying something.  Still don't know what's going on, though. Guess too little sleep and too much caffeine doesn't help much right now.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      YAY!   They finally came up with a way to include comments. So go ahead and comment!  And for you people who'd like to flame me (you do so very nicely in my e-mail) please do so. It's September and Denmark is getting really cold now and since I think that everything below 65 F is cold, then I can really use something to warm this place up! Which can also provide a good laugh!   Hehe! Joe updated his photo gallery for the Downs today and already someone commented on my picture.  Well, what can I say? I didn't get the Beanie Baby Award for nothing! ;p  (woops, looks like mud on the halo!)   Movie of the day:  The two final episodes of  Farscape .  I could weep! There's only on thing I have to say:  I hate FOX Network!!!  Why, oh why did they have to cancel it? They only had one season left. It had been planned that way all along! 5 seasons- the end! Not like all those pathetic never ending shows without a proper story. *Cough*Stargate,Xena, Buffy*cough* Instead, FOX decides to buy it and stop it.  Now we'll just have to deal with the fact that the most brilliant Sci-Fi show ever has left us hanging with a half ending. *sigh*
     
    
</post>

<date>31,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
         An extremely modest man was in the hospital  for a series of tests, the last of which had left his bodily systems extremely  upset.   Upon making several false alarm trips to the bathroom, he decided  the latest episode was another and stayed put. He suddenly filled his bed with diarrhea and was embarrassed beyond his ability to remain rational.   In a  complete loss of composure he jumped out of bed, gathered up the bed sheets, and  threw them out the hospital window.   A drunk was walking by the hospital  when the sheets landed on him. He started yelling, cursing, and swinging his  arms violently trying to get the unknown things off, and ended up with the  soiled sheets in a tangled pile at his feet.   As the drunk stood there,  unsteady on his feet, staring down at the sheets, a hospital security guard  (barely containing his laughter) who had watched the whole incident walked up  and asked, "What the heck is going on here?"   The drunk, still staring  down replied: "I think I just beat the crap out of a ghost".    Happy Samhain, Halloween, Alle Helgen and so on to all! 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      You go to work, do your job....and everytime you turn around to do something, you can feel this guy's eyes being glued to your butt... among other things.  Believe me, I now know the old movie cliche is true. You know, "Oi! Look at me....I'm up here! Those are not my eyes!!!"  Grrrrrrrrrr.... I'm so sick of men right now I could scream! What do we need them for anyway?
     
    
</post>

<date>19,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Sometimes I get the feeling that I've been placed in the middle of a cosmic joke.  
     
    
</post>

<date>15,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I actually slept for about three hours today. Almost too much! ;p  After all it  is  possible to sleep too much.   Hmmmm, sems I made the challenge too hard for the poor people on the Downs. No one's even tried to answer my question in the "BD'ers Trivia" thread. Just because they'd have to actually go look it up.  Well, welcome to the real world, my friends. Here things don't come easily, you'll have to work for it! Ah well...but since no one's even asked for a hint, I guess they just couldn't care less. Not my problem. Gives me more time to...uhm... be awake. *rolls eyes*
     
    
</post>

<date>14,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Need.....sleep.... 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Damn  I'm tired!!! And I won't get much sleep tonight either (no you perverts! That's not why!!! *sigh* If only... *rolls eyes*)  Work, work, work, work, work, work, work.......   Have been studying Rorschach pictures for a couple of hours (I'm still using them for scaring people). Hmm, I honestly think I just saw Mothman, Nessie and Bigfoot... And they all came out of the same UFO.... ZZZZzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz.....  *slaps forehead*  But it'll soon be weekend. What do you mean it's only Monday? I know it's Monday! And what do you mean that 2 hours of sleep a day is unhealthy? I'm busy! I don't have time to sleep! Sleep is overrated anyway.    Maddox, Maddox, Maddox..... What am I to do with you...? Sometimes you're really an idiot!
     
    
</post>

<date>10,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Inbox:   23   Bulk Mail Folder (spam):    238    What...is wrong....with this picture???????   I check that particular e-mail once or twice a week and usually, the bulk mail contains about three times as much as the inbox.... but although math has never been my greatest talent, I  do  know that 3x23 is  not  238!!!!! And since, on Yahoo, you can only block 100 addy's and I did that long ago, I guess I'll just have to live with this. But damn it's annoying. As if I care about all their pathetic porn sites. *rolls eyes*  Although, maybe if I began looking through them *puke* I might someday find that rather.....revealing picture one of my dearly beloved (not) ex'es put up on the web just to piss me off. And it seems that I'm just about the only person who doesn't know the URL...  So girlies... listen to me. A guy and a girl, two bottles of vodka and a camera is  not  and I repeat  not  a good combination!!!!! It may be fun and innocent until the moment you break up and hate each other.  Anyway...  Any bets on Super Bowl? I'd say  Chiefs  vs.  Vikings  may be a good shot.  But I don't know...we'll see. It was a bit of a surprise that the  Bucs  ran off with the victory last year, so I won't make any bets on anything.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Attention!  Someone REALLY needs to update his blog!!!   Argh! Found yet another thread on the Downs about how difficult it is to read the Silmarillion.  Uhm....I really  must  be an idiot, because I've never found anything about the Sil difficult. On the contrary, of Tolkien's books (at least those I've read) I very much prefer this book over LOTR, which has a tendency of making me fall asleep. There, it's said! The first time I read that book, I truly thought I'd never know what happened after Pippin and Gandalf arrived in Gondor, since I simply couldn't get through that part. *yaaaaawn* In all honesty, I think I spent as much time on that particular chapter, as I had used on getting to it.   And another thread: "Do you think the lord of the Rings book is better than the film?" *bangs head against wall* No, of course I don't think the books are better than the movie. PJ's version is  so  much better than those pathetic books. And he really did the right thing, leaving out all those more or less important characters. One thing  I  would've done differently though, is that  I  would've let  Arwen  take the ring to Mordor!!!  Uhm... why do you all look at me like that? You don't think it would work? I mean....if she could steal Glorfindel's horse and a sword and pretend to be Xena (no! I do NOT watch that show!!!) then why couldn't she just kick that darn Hobbit out of the way, grab the ring and go to Mordor?  Surely she could do that. And if we were lucky, she would trip and go with the ring into Mt. Doom....!  What do you mean? Of  course  I don't have anything against Arwen! How did anyone get  that  idea?    Song of the day:  "In my place" -  Coldplay    urlLink (A Rush of Blood to the Head)    I was lost, I was lost, Crossed lines I shouldn't have crossed,  How long must you wait for it? How long must you pay for it?  
     
    
</post>

<date>04,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I've never liked Frodo, but who would've thought I would beat him up and take his place as the one with only 9 fingers...? Or at least that's how many digits I'm able to use at the moment.  It wasn't Gollum but only my own stupidity and so I'm now waiting for my poor finger to heal. If I'll ever get rid of the infection, that is. *sigh* I never thought it could be this difficult to type.  Anyway... my life is the usual dull, boring, lonely misery as always, so no surprises for anyone there. The cold and darkness is getting closer everyday, letting us all know that autumn is really here. I  hate  it!!! I want... no, I  crave  summer!!!  But that's just what you have to deal with when you live in freezing Scandinavia... And Maddox....  please  refrain from telling me that the temperature we've got here during the summer, is what you have in Florida during the friggin' winter. I've heard that enough!    Album of the day:   urlLink Surrealistic Pillow  -  Jefferson Airplane  What can I say? We're talking  White Rabbit  here.... Ah, I miss the good ol' days when I sang that one myself. 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Ooooh, what a game!!!!  Of course Raiders lost, would've been a miracle if they didn't, but damn, did they put up a fight!  *sigh*  I managed to do it again... I got kicked off a board for getting in a fight with the powers. But honestly, when you realise that the board admins are nothing but powerhungry teens and one of the leading moderators goes by the name "Orli's mine", then I simply can't help myself.  But I do believe that I manage to behave on the Downs.  At least I don't fight the admins or the mods. Drive them crazy, yes, but no fights. Unless of course they ask for it! Hehe!
     
    
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Wahahahahahaaaaaaaa!!! *sob*   Chiefs vs. Raiders!!!!!  Tonight!!! And I'll be at work at the time!!!! AAAARRRGH!!!  Sweet, wonderful, nice little DCD-recorder... PLEEEEASE be good and record this. Mmm?  NO ONE bothers me tomorrow! I have a game to watch!
     
    
</post>

<date>17,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      DAMMIT!!!!! Just received the news that my copy of TTT, the extended version has been delayed all over Europe, so I'll be lucky if I have it by Thursday. *sigh* I WANT MY GOLLUM FIGURINE!!! Grrrrr... And I'm curious as to whether the extra scenes will actually manage to make the movie worth seeing or not. "Fellowship" became an entirely different movie and I simply refuse to see any other version of it, but this movie.... *sigh*  I mean.... it will take a LOT to impress me!!! And I'm afraid it won't happen!  Hmmm, for some reason people keep looking at me in a funny way when they ask me about the drive home Saturday and I tell them about my road-rage and speeding. Ok, so you're only supposed to go 110 km/h on the freeway, but really, 140 feels SO much better... And then there are all the idiots out there... *sigh* Men! They just have to show off! What do we need them for anyway??? Ok, so a few suggestions come to mind, but still....?!?! Anyway, there seems to be no way around them, so I guess we'll just have to live with them.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So, I'm back from my vacation. I must say the weather pretty much resembles my mood. It's been raining nearly constantly almost since I left the airport early yesterday and it certainly does not improve anything.  *sigh*  Ah well....In about 40 days I'm the one crossing the ocean, so this time it's easier to endure.  Gods... where do I start...!?!? So much have happened. We actually cut my hair (3-4 inches) so it'll certainly be a while before I'll end up sitting on it again. Damn, it feels strange, it's so short. Although most people probably won't even notice. tsk tsk. My mom taught me not to play with food, but she obviously has no idea what whipped cream is for....*blinks innocently*  It's been a wonderful week, no doubt, only much too short! And so it's back to work, starting out with 12-14 hour workdays. Yay! *rolls eyes*
     
    
</post>

<date>07,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm leaving for a week very early tomorrow morning. Once I've picked up a certain someone at the airport, I'll be able to relax a bit. Something I need more than anything these days.  Take care everyone!  Try not to miss me too much, ok?  Hugs to everyone!
     
    
</post>

<date>06,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      For a time I managed not to live up to my nick as the Lady DeSpair...but in this very moment I see no point in being anything but that.  Just when everything seems to fall into place, when life just couldn't be better.....after far too many tests and samples, you get the message from the Dr. that you have an incurable disease.  The world doesn't stop just because of that, I know. But right now, to me, it certainly feels like it!
     
    
</post>

<date>05,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      The most wonderful thing happened this morning (well, ok, so it was 3.30am, but whatever). I was at work, running around like crazy when suddenly my cell phone rang. I looked and it said "No number" and I was like "HUH? What?" People don't usually call me up at that time, so I was a bit puzzled when I answered. Only to hear the voice I've been missing for far too long.  "Just wanted to check that my phone-card's working and who would be better to call than you?"    Awwwwwww...so sweet!!! *siiiigh*   Only 3 more days...
     
    
</post>

<date>04,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      If only, if only, if only.....  If only there were more than 24 hours in a day.... If only there were more than 7 days in a week.... If only I didn't have so much to do, so much to finish before Friday....  If only I weren't so damn clumsy, lately! I seems that just by walking from here to the kitchen and back, I'm about to kill myself (with some help from my cat). 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      *sigh*  Raiders  lost...again!  Although it seems they're about to replace their quarterback and so there may still be a chance for them.  And Hell may freeze over...when there are two Thursdays in one week.  But there's nothing wrong in hoping for the unthinkable to happen.  Hmm, last time I commented on someone's lack of updates to his blog, it actually worked, so I think I'll try again since it's been nearly a month. Several people really need to update their blogs!!! I've almost started wondering if certain people are even online anymore. Guys, where are you?  Heh, received a link for the coolest quiz/test.  urlLink Try it!  And let me know if you can tell the difference. I got 7 out of 10. *makes funny little dance*
     
    
</post>

<date>22,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Top 10 Indications That Cats Are The Evolutionary Descendants Of Dragons   10. Ability to invoke fear with minor changes of position/facial statement 9. Really wicked breath 8. Enjoy toying with mortals 7. They are constantly offered gifts in order to appease their wrath 6. Ability to gain total control over the humans in its territory 5. Claws that can decimate the toughest armor (and upholstery) 4. Affinity for high perches from which it can survey all that it controls 3. The size of its ego is consistent with that of its evolutionary forebears 2. Habit of playing with food 1. Ability to monitor its territory while seemingly asleep   Hmmmm... Guess we just solved an evolutionary riddle... And on that note... Her Highness is trying to tell me there's something she wants... Ai! I am but a humble slave.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Another year, another birthday...  Why everyone else must celebrate such a thing, I don't know. I'm usually mourning.  When I was little I wished that it could be my birthday every day. Now I see that insanity actually hit me at a very early stage in life. *rolls eyes* And then of course there's the "threat" hanging over my head with the words of my dear betrothed. "You might as well get used to it because the girls and I will be celebrating you every year!" *gulp*  One thing has changed, though. As a teen, I used to say that I had no intention of reaching 30. But I admit, that now where that number is so awfully close... I think I can take on another 10 years. *toothy grin*
     
    
</post>

<date>17,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So, today's the day, or at least people keep telling me. "The movie is out, aren't you going?" Er....no! First of all, I've got pneumonia, I'm not going anywhere. Second.... I really couldn't care less about that movie. I may go see it someday... I may not. Only time will tell. And no, I'm not just saying this because I'm sick and feel like crap. I've felt like this for the last month, I don't really feel like going. Sure, if someone gives me a free ticket, I'll think about it. Until then... well... guess I'll continue not to care.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So, I'm down with pneumonia. Coughing up blood and I know not what. Oh, yay! Last time I had that it "only" took me about one year to get over it. And I've never fully recovered, which is why getting it again is even worse. So I had to call in sick. Weird, since I haven't done that for 1½ years. True, I've been sick but my politic is that as long as I can stand up, I can work. But since I can barely stay on my feet for 10 seconds.... And I feel so bad about it. It takes a lot to make me stay home in bed (which kinda led to a rather heated discussion with a certain someone this morning). Yup, I must be every boss' dream.  But why do I do it? I don't know. Do I ever receive a "thank you" for showing up even though I had to nearly o-d on painkillers just to get out of bed? NO! And yet, I keep showing up, doing my job, taking over for all the others who are sick...  Even this time I tried. I've been sick since Sunday night, and yet I kept going as long as I could. Call me stupid. Call me an idiot. But I know that next time I'll be doing it again. And once again I'll probably end up wondering why. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      *fights through thick layer of dust and cobwebs*  I have been told in no uncertain way,  that I'd better move that butt of mine back to this place and say something. Well...ok.   SOMETHING!  Better? *grins*  No, I've been horribly busy and ever since those 3 days in that bunker, right after my vacation, nothing has been the same and it probably won't be until after I get back from the US. And then I'll be out of my mind for a couple of weeks until I'll (hopefully) be able to function again. I can't keep doing this. I can't keep saying goodbye. Don't want to... *sigh* But yes, I probably work too much. Even on vacation I had to be told all the time to sit down and relax because I kept pacing aimlessly, driving everyone insane.  Just let me shut out the rest of the world. It's a horrible place anyway and right now it's filled with Christmas decorations. And I'm sick of Christmas decorations. Dammit, the stores have been full of them since mid-October. How can they expect anyone to still think "Yay, it's Christmas!" *rolls eyes*  Well, if anyone needs a break from the insanity, come to my place. You won't find the slightest clue that it's even December. What's the fuss? Yule is on the 21st anyway and presents can be given at all times of the year. And frankly, I value a gift more when it's given for no special occasion, than when it's "because it's Christmas"! But that's just me and I'm usually considered a bit "off" so don't go follow my example. It's probably bad for you anyway.   Song of the day:  "Right next to the right one" -  Tim Christensen  
     
    
</post>

<date>30,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WOW!!! Check  urlLink this  out!!!  Is that cool or what? Aren't they cute???  I want one!!!  To begin with.... *evil grin*  It seems that people have finally come to their senses and have stopped reading this thing. About time you guys realised that I have absolutely nothing interesting to say anyway.  Or maybe the comments stopped because Blogspeak was taken down without warning, so no one had the slightest idea that the comment function had been disabled. But then again, my e-mail's right there, on the right *points to link* so there really is no excuse.  Ah well, comments are enabled again, thanks to Haloscan. So go ahead. Use it. It doesn't bite. I may, though! (but only where you want me to) ;p *blinks innocently*
     
    
</post>

<date>20,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've been laughed at, yelled at and called some of the weirdest things lately. Why do you ask? Because of that idiotic movie, that's why!!!  I've now seen Return of the King twice and all I can say is that I'm  not  impressed!!!  Call me a purist, call me a freak. I just don't get why they had to change so much and for the  worse!   Stupid  changes! And that song by Annie Lennox....why does she have to  scream  like that??? It could be pretty but she completely ruins it by sounding like a crow! And no, I don't dislike Annie Lennox, actually I like a lot of what she's made, but this..... *shivers*
     
    
</post>

<date>15,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, being the, according to some, eerie and morbid person that I am, I really thought I had seen it all.  BUT ...apparently the live-webcam craze has reached new heights. Or should I say "depths"!?! 6 feet under, to be precise.  urlLink http://www.seemerot.com  is, apparently, a "new" idea among all the freakish webcam ideas we have so far.  If you're squeamish, don't worry, it's not like rotten.com. The latest "instalment" seems very fresh. TOO fresh if you ask me, which is why I say it's a hoax!  *sigh* What some people do.... *rolls eyes*
     
    
</post>

<date>13,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was cleaning up in my e-mail and had to smile when I found some 1 year+ old PM's from Paul aka littlemanpoet. Dang, he really wanted me to join the Fairy Word Weavers back in the days when there were only 12 members. As usually I simply didn't have the time and had to turn down his offer. And now, to my regret, it seems that the time issue has finally killed the story I was writing. Guess writing just isn't my strength. Only do what you're good at, right? In my case, writing certainly doesnt seem to be it. *sigh*  Anyway, the trip went well and I had a really good time. The girls were wonderful and the boy.... well, he actually said something once in a while. WOW! Actually, when he wanted my opinion on some of his writings and RPG characters, I nearly fell off the chair. Almost seemed a bit empty when he went back to college.  I wonder if I'll ever be allowed to order fries as a side again, since I...erh... kinda.... have a pretty "bad" behaviour when it comes to restaurants...  *blinks innocently*   So? There's absolutely nothing wrong with my way of eating fries, just go ahead and ask C. *snickers*  Ok, so maybe I could've paid less "attention" to them, maybe even used my teeth, but still.... C. certainly didn't mind... *evil grin*   Yes, I know, I know... I'm horrible! And I'm not going to change!!!  Ah well, I'm back here in the cold, it's snowing and I'm bored. And I just want to go back. :-( *sniff*
     
    
</post>

<date>11,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        In February 1821, the Nantucket whaleship Dauphin was sailing up the Chilean coast when it pulled up alongside a derelict whaleboat. Two men crouched on its deck, their beards caked with blood, each sucking marrow from the bones of their dead shipmates. After their rescue, the two survivors recounted the story of the most famous maritime disaster of the 19th century, a horrific tale of murder and cannibalism. The rescued men were from the whaleship Essex, which had sailed from Nantucket in August 1820 with plans to round Cape Horn and hunt sperm whales near the South American coast. On November 20, Captain George Pollard and most of the crew were out hunting in small boats west of the Galapagos Islands when an 85-foot-long sperm whale repeatedly rammed the Essex on the port side, destroying the ship. All aboard swore that the attack was malicious. After retrieving the navigational equipment from the wreck, the men split into the three 25-foot whaleboats, and determined a course. Bad weather blew the men far off course. Their meager food and water supply soon ran out, and men began to weaken and die. Before long, the desperate sailors resorted to consuming their dead crewmates. Later, straws were drawn to see who would be shot to feed the others. In one of the boats, Captain Pollard took part in shooting and eating his own cousin, first promising to deliver a message to the dead boy's mother. By the time they were rescued off the coast of Chile, the eight survivors of the 21-man crew had sailed nearly 4,500 nautical miles across the Pacific. The first mate of the Essex published an account of the journey, which eventually fell into the hands of a young New Bedford sailor named Herman Melville. Chase's harrowing narrative inspired Melville to write Moby Dick, the epic tale of a murderous sperm whale and a vengeful sea captain gone mad.   And it's probably my favourite book of all time! 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well....I'm back!  Got off the plane not 6 hours ago and I feel kinda weird. A little sad and...lonely. I just want to go back.  :-(
     
    
</post>

<date>27,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *sigh*  Got a call some time ago. A friend...no, not really a friend, since I haven't seen her for almost a year now... Anyway, I got a call from a friend, saying that said person has gone into labour and is now at the hospital.  Hooray, yay, congrats...why the hell are you telling ME that??? Fine, rub it in!!!! I'll just go hide somewhere!
     
    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I finally saw the third Matrix film and I must say that unlike how people told me I would react, I actually liked it. And I  loooove  Smith!!! How could I not? It's bad-ass Hugo when he's best (or worst?)! *drools* Ahem, sorry! *composes self* No, really. People had claimed that I wouldn't like it, some even said that I would hate it. So of course I have to find that it's actually an ok movie. But I still hold onto my statement that they should never have made any sequels. The first movie was original and ended just the right way, telling you "THINK!"....so of course Hollywood has to remind us that we are, after all, stupid and unable to think for ourselves. And so they are forced to spell it all out to us, to make sure that we fully understand what's going on. Because we can't figure that out on our own, now can we?   Listening to:   Let your fingers do the walking  - Sort Sol (Glamourpuss)
     
    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Now....why am I reading Poe and Kafka and discussing Faust online...when I should actually be reading the Silmarillion for the Noldolante RPG? ACK!  An on-going joke at the moment is that I now go by the name "The Goddess and The Car" by one of my online friends, referring to my RL first names. I carry the name of a Celtic goddess (try to figure out which one... :p ) but what a lot of people don't know is that I also carry the name of a (very) possessed car, a beautiful red 58 Plymouth Fury (pleeeeeeease, can I have one???) Hmm, thinking about it, it's also the name of Louis XIV's favourite mistress.  Ah well, I prefer the car! :p
     
    
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      And the raven, never flitting, still is sitting, still is sitting  On the pallid bust of Pallas just above my chamber door;  And his eyes have all the seeming of a demon that is dreaming,  And the lamp-light o'er him streaming throws his shadow on the floor;  And my soul from out that shadow that lies floating on the floor   Shall be lifted — nevermore!  
     
    
</post>

<date>15,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmm, bloodsamples: No answer yet. EKG: "normal", but they may want to run it for longer, so who knows.  Why are they checking  this  now, you ask? Because this damned heart of mine skips and jumps as if it were performing "The Nutcracker."  I'm sick of this!!! I want out!!! I'm sick of the people who are trying to make my life a living hell!!!  I'm sick of myself because it seems that I've chased everyone else away!!! People I love... people I care about.... Hell, people even stay away from this place now...In a way that's good... e-mail's not full of flames and junk anymore..  Guess I might end up as the crazy old cat-lady after all....alone... unwanted.... half-eaten by the cats once someone finally comes by.  Or maybe I should just get it over and done with! Wonder how long before anyone would notice.... 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Dammit!!!!!!!!   For I'm not sure how long, I've fought to keep Brotherhood open, begging Bb not to move it to Elvenhome, posting without knowing half of the storyline myself,  while trying to move things in the direction I had discussed and agreed upon with C. very long ago... And now it appears that I'm the only one who's able to remember that. Which means that we've ended up with a line of post now that certainly does NOT match what was planned.... In other words... GAME OVER! At least for me. By following the planned storyline...I just screwed up the storyline! Is that logic or what?  I feel most like deleting my post but damn if I'll ever have peace again if I do. "No, no, I can use it!"  Uh huh... by making a post that gives me the choice to either turn my character into something he's not and having him do something he never would.... or I'm out! Ok, so how the hell do you want to make the ending you intended, since I'm no longer part of your game?  And why the hell do I even care?  I'm sorry I let you down, people. But I guess now there's a spot free on the Downs and everyone can join another RPG. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have been asked to take the part as Sauron in a rpg about Akallabeth. I wonder why they asked ME...? I wouldn't know anything at all about Sauron, oh no. *blinks innocently*  But they promised me it would only be a cameo so I accepted. I kinda have a responsibility towards the glorious Dark Lord, right? It must be done properly! Yes, I know, that's the ego talking again... Guess I only need to add Mr. Bauglir himself and my villain list will be complete. I've been around all I find interesting or at least so I think.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow, it's been quite some time since I've been blogging (but not as long as certain other people *cough* Mith *cough*).   A lot of stuff has happened, other stuff....hasn't. *sigh*  But this isn't the time, nor the place to go into that.   It's funny to see people on the Downs go crazy because of VBulletin3. When it was updated to VBulletin2, it was actually a small setback for me, since I've been used to VB3 for quite some time in another place. One thing that frustrates me, though, is the new rating system. I mean, the ability to actually comment and tell people what you think is something I really like, but that there is no way you can know who commented...is just plain stupid. It would be nice if you actually had the option to include your name (yes, I know, you can write it after your comment, but who the heck thinks about that until they receive a comment themselves and starts thinking about who actually wrote it???) Someone wrote something extremely nice to me and I really wish I was able to see who did it so I knew who to thank. All I can do now is hope that said person may read this when I say,   Thank you, it really means a lot. I appreciate it!    But I'll never know, I guess. Ah well. *sigh*  Brotherhood is up and running again, though not the way it should have been...but I really don't care. I have my project now and so far, I've only got positive feedback. I guess that's good. Being allowed to write the chronicle of your favourite character and knowing that there are actually people waiting for you to finish the next part.... is an interesting experience. 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I'm back....  Yeah, yeah, yeah... "From where?" you ask.  Well, I didn't really tell anyone but I've been on vacation. And now I'm back. And I'm bored. Not that I weren't while on vacation, but still... *rolls eyes* But that's just me.  A lot of things have happened lately. Brotherhood is over (finally), not really the way it was supposed to end, but strange things happened and demands were made (and certain mods apparently got funny ideas) so I never got to make the last post I was supposed to, because honestly, I didn't know if I were even in control of my own character anymore, which in the end caused me to simply boycott the thing. I honestly couldn't care less.   Hmm, what else....? *thinking*  Ah, yes. I've been invited to play the lead in a rpg. A mean bastard! Really looking forward to that one. That makes.... 3 active rpg's and 2 or 3 pending. A life? What the heck do you mean "life"? I have a life! Really, I do! Somewhat.... *rolls eyes*
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This....is absolutely horrible!!!  Everything's changed and with that, I've lost...everything! Comments, links...everything but the posts! It's all gone! WHY, OH WHY??? Ah well, not that there were that many comments anyway, especially not any of importance since the ones using it are generally the same people I talk to almost everyday (and of whom none really has anything interesting to say anyway).
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       "Death borders upon our birth, and our cradle stands in the grave. Our birth is nothing but our death begun."  -Bishop Hall
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      FINALLY weekend!!! Thought it would never come. And then it'll be over before I even get a chance to enjoy it. Ah well.   Too much work, barely any sleep and a post that has just decided it doesn't feel like being written! That's how my week has been so far and it seems the next will fall into the same category. Chaos! What a mess! Otherwise nothing much is going on. Or maybe I just don't have the time to notice it. *rolls eyes*   Listening to:   "In the shadows" - The Rasmus ( urlLink Dead Letters ) Once you've heard this song, it's stuck in your head! 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, was I in for a suprise this morning!?! I was trying to come up with a post for Pack, when I thought I'd take a look around at people's blogs. And what did I find? A new entry from Mith... WOW! Nearly made me fall off the chair and probaly would if I hadn't been so busy reading. And grumbling. Patriots, eh? tsk tsk. *rolls eyes*  ;p Oh, btw, the reason I've never posted any comments on your blog, Mith, is because you have to be a Xanga member to comment on a Xanga site. And since I'm not.... Don't think for one moment that I've never had something to say. According to some, I ALWAYS have something to say, even when I shouldn't. At least here, everyone can post a comment. If you're not a member, you post as anonymous and simply include your name in your comment. How hard can it be? But nooooo, Xanga only allows for members to comment. *grumble grumble*  Gods, I've seen a lot of movies lately. "Troy", "Van Helsing", "The day after tomorrow", "Hellboy", "Kill Bill Vol.2".... hmmm... anymore...? I can't even remember. The only one disappointing is "Day after tomorrow". It's the first time in my life I've actually fallen asleep in the cinema. In the middle of a disaster movie.  "Troy"... what can I say? Fabulous! Amazing! Fantastic! Brilliant! Just like everything else made by Wolfgang Petersen. The man who gave us  urlLink "Das Boot"  and so many other brilliant movies. (Although I do prefer  urlLink "Stalingrad"   by Joseph Vilsmaier over "DB" anytime!) If you haven't seen it, you should! It is truely moving.  Anyway, where was I...? Ah yes,  urlLink "Van Helsing" . Funny, funny, funny! It shoots itself in the foot numerous times, but it is FUNNY! Dracula, the dramaqueen! Most notable performance in it, however, must be David Wenham, who most people know as Faramir in the LOTR. He is absolutely amazing!  urlLink "Hellboy" . Well, I love comics-turned-movie stuff and this is no exception! Glad to see a wonderful portrayal of Kroenen, one of the most mysterious and fascinating characters (bad guy, of course) in the story.   urlLink "Kill Bill vol. 2" . If you like Tarantino, you will LOVE Kill Bill!!! Without doubt the best he's made so far! Daryl Hannah is wonderful as always!  And I could go on...and on...and on....but I won't!    Listening to:   "Once" - Felicia Sorenson (Joseph DoLuca)-  urlLink Brotherhood of the wolf 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>