<Blog>

<date>27,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Change is supposed to be the only thing constant, and with change very human being aspires to grow, grow in terms of career, in terms of social influence, in terms of wealth, respect, power and what not. Growth, like change, has no limits. From time immemorial man has always being growing, be it with the discovery of wheel, metals, industrial revolution, cyber revolution, etc. Horizontal growth and vertical growth have been the major contributors of growth. When man grows with the available means in the space already available, the growth is horizontal. When space is no longer available, man grows vertically to the next stage where he creates space for himself as well as for others. This is typically influenced by discoveries, inventions, etc.   In an organization, the primary motivators for an individual could be either career or money. In both he tends to keep growing. Let me just try to look a bit deeper into growth in career. Growth, like all other adjectives, is relative. We always want to grow towards a goal, a target, something that could be long term or short term. When I speak about goal, it could be an idealistic goal based on position, designation, achievement, etc. However mostly we tend to look at seniors and say to ourselves, “Yes, I need to be like him” – basically you need to have role models. When there is no role model to look forward to, the growth is often achieved by the hard means. Why is this so?    Growth by Reference  I believe that it is easier to grow if you have a reference target, a target that you can keep referring to and check if the actions that you are taking are in line with your career growth plans. For example a technical architect could look forward towards his enterprise/vision architect who could mentor him. When it comes to mentoring, you know what you want to achieve and there is someone who has already reached that target and knows what exactly has to be done in order to reach that level. In this case it is easier to plan your growth and also avoid the pitfalls or diversions that would take place if you were to do it all by yourself. For e.g. doing a MBA may not be of any help if your aim is to continue in the technical line.    Growth by Trial  This usually more time. Even though the person gains more experience, ultimately you would be way behind the person who has grown by reference. It is highly possible that the plans you have laid is not in line with what you need to achieve. This may prove disastrous, as you would have to spend more time in turning around and taking the path you like. Moreover it is highly likely that such growth may not always bear fruit. If the organization does not have space for the goals that you want to achieve, then your growth could be hindered. At this stage, when horizontal growth (here I am considering the org. as the horizontal boundary) is saturated you need to look for vertical growth (probably move over to a new org.).   Organizational Growth  Leaving the personal growth aside, let us look at how and when an organization grows. An organization grows when its employees grow and flourish in their career. Employees taking on more responsibility within the same job profile characterize the horizontal growth. For e.g. software engineer may start off with just maintenance. He could then start coding new modules, reviewing, testing, low-level design, etc. Thus he has space for horizontal growth. Once the horizontal growth is completed he should have an opportunity for vertical growth. Often people would leave when there is less space for vertical growth. Since growth is more like a pyramid, only few people can grow vertically within an organization. Hence attrition may not really be a sign of weakness but it could also be a sign of growth, provided the number of people entering a horizontal space is more than the number of people leaving it.   Growth is a fundamental aspect of life. We need to keep introspecting whether there is growth in our career and life. We also need to keep checking the space around us available for growth and influence our decisions accordingly.  
     
    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
        This poem is a reflection of the last 1317 days with which I have been associated. This is my first attempt at poetry.     derived from dreams  driven by heart  for the morning tomorrow We sweated it so hard   when morning came and time for bread  came the call  it was time for bed  and back to dreams!   little did We see the morning little did We see the tomorrow in today  We did see our dreams We did see our heart  down the lanes of memory  not so far from today  there was a dream, realized  morning had not come but  We did convert dreams to reality  now We dare to dream again in the hope that morning will be none too far !  not just bread but with milk We need to prepare for a journey too far !   ~ Satba 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      March 6, 2004 - DIscussion @ Southern Spice. For some it is supersition, for others it is a branch of science, but all agree it is good business. What is this about astrology ? What is it that give astrology so much following, hatred, and envy ? Let us look more into this ..
     
    
</post>


<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This site contains some good articles and content about cryptography told in a unique way filled with all sorts of games and articles that provides information and at the same time adding the fun aspect to learning. A very good site for people who are interested in knowing more about encryption, etc.   urlLink SimonSingh.net   Dont forget to visit the black chamber where you can learn how encryption was used in the ancient times.   
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Stepped over this site when preparing for a quiz that incidentally contains some questions on Brazil. The article provides information on Rio de Janeiro in a humours way. Looks a bit outdated though esp. on information relating to currency, etc.  Good one if you want to have a laugh !    urlLink Rio De Janeiro, Brazil, Earth   Some favorites ...   Beer is served cold, the beach is served 40 degrees centigrade hot.     During four days the city is turned upside-down and rightside-left. Sometime inside-out also, due to excess of an alcoholic beverage called Batida    Players usually play soccer, while spectators develop boxing, judo, karate, and survival skills.     Weather is hot in spring, very hot in summer, hot in autumn, and quite hot in winter.     You should not take a honeymoon in Rio unless you robbed a bank in the last 3 weeks before your marriage.    Actually, it goes down faster than any other currency known, including Monopoly money.  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      If mythology interests you, then this one needs to be in your favorites ! The site is well organised and well structured. I havent read much, but stumbled on it when I was searching for something related to Greek mythology. Explore it out !     "Timeless Myths is a website containing a collection of myths and legends, from ancient Greece and Rome, and from frozen Norse lands and the magical Celtic realms. Or follow the medieval adventures of Arthur and his unconquerable knights."      urlLink Timeless Myths  
     

    
</post>


<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Spain – Time to Say “Adios”  It is time to say “Adios” to the travelogues that I have been penning down, to the wonderful place on earth called Spain. The last week started out as another busy week. But this was the week when I had to do my shopping, attend some of the farewell treats and also to catch my flight back home.   One thing that I have been doing constantly is basically trying different kinds of food. This week it was time to try out some different kind of breakfast. One of such breakfasts that I had was a French specialty, a couple of break slices with a slice of ham topped with a specially prepared milk cream. The cream provided the needed “kick” to the breakfast that made it one of the best during my stay in Spain.  During my 3 week stay, the “Estacion de Servicion Arje”, a small café opposite to the place I work, had become the most visited place by me for food. This was mainly for lunch and breakfast. The Salmon sandwich had become one of my favorites. Apart from this, “Corral”, which is basically chicken and salads sandwiched between long crispy bread (that resembled more like hot dogs). Another favorite of mine here was the Paehllia Bahilla (I am not sure if this is the correct spelling, but it sounded like this). This resembled more like our tamarind rice mixed with some pieces of squid.  The last dinner that I had during this trip was in “Samar Kanda”, a romantic restaurant beside the artificial tropical forests in the Atocha Railway Station. I had been informed that this was a Kazakhstan or Uzbekistan restaurant. They had an English menu and one of the dishes that attracted my attention was “Ostrich Meat”. My hosts also informed me that this was really good and is infact much softer that chicken and does not cause any stomach related problem. Even though I had to catch the flight back home in another 9 hrs, I decided to take the risk as this was once in a lifetime opportunity to try Ostrich Meat. The Ostrich meat was really good, but I am not sure if it was softer than Chicken as I had to chew a lot. Anyhow it is worth tasting and if enough amount of spice is added it would taste really great.   By the end of the trip I had managed to add Ostrich, Squid, and Ostrich to the growing list of animals that I have eaten in my life. This trip is the one where I managed to taste foods from different regions round the world, from Peru to former Soviet Republics. I would like to keep writing about the different kinds of food that I had during the trip but it is time to say “Adios” to the different kinds of food there and say “hello” to the wonderful Indian food that never fails to satisfy your taste buds.   There was no other major experience during the last week. Towards the end of the week I was more worried about catching the flight early in the morning. However a couple of experiences with the Spanish culture help me shed my worries for some time. For one last time before I left Madrid, my hosts drove me through the center of Madrid at around 1:30 in the morning of Saturday (4th October, 2003) after a very good dinner. I had just 3 hours left to check out and return back.   Journey Back   The journey back was without much of an incident, the only accident being my decision to watch a complete hindi movie “Supari” starring Nandita Das. In this movie the hero keeps repeatedly telling his friends, after half of the movie is complete, that it is wrong to kill someone. That was a great message right !!?? But inspite of this his friend keep bumping people not for money but because one of them wants to sleep and the other wants to forget his dad and his typewriter. [Good Excuses for bumping people off]. Anyhow at the end of the movie, all the friends of the hero are killed, and the hero had already killed around 5 people, 1 person before he delivers the message of the movie to his friends and 4 after he had delivered the message. But even after murdering 5 persons, he is pretty confident that he would definitely come out of jail and hence requests her to wait for him. A “Must” watch movie for those who have just a frustrating day at office. For the rest of the journey I preferred to sleep.    Looking Back …  Looking back this is a trip that I would remember for …  -	The trip that I enjoyed the most -	The trip that helped me in rediscovering myself -	The trip which helped me taste food from different regions of the world -	The trip that helped me in knowing more about the Spanish Identify, the Spanish people, Spanish art and architecture and also about Spanish culture.   The last 3 weeks have definitely gone into as one of the most memorable weeks of my life never to be etched out of my memory forever. As I bring this travelogue to an end, I would consider the following events as the best moments in Madrid.  [3] Lunch at Estacion De Servicion  [2] The Visit to the Salons at Palacio Real [1] The Bull fight  Yes, I cannot also forget the beautiful female in the Metro. But then with the passage of time, her face would keep getting blurred until all that I would remember would be the event rather than the face itself. Anyhow, someone, somewhere will be waiting for me, so why bother about the ripe grapes J  I would finally like to sign off with the following words.  “ All journeys have to end, end in the by lanes of memory that can be visited in the journey of thoughts without the constraints of time.”   Signing off before going to sleep after a memorable journey, “The Journey to España”. Sathish on October 6, 2003 at 22:05 hrs 
      
</post>

<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       The Matadors and the Bulls     One of the main items of interest to me when I embarked on this trip to Spain was the bullfight, something that symbolizes Spain. From day 1, this was one of the events that I was eagerly looking forward to. On the first day at office, my colleagues at the Spanish office showed total disinterest for the bullfight and were surprised that I wanted to see it. Well, I was in fact surprised that they weren’t interested in something that represented Spain.   Today, I decided to go and witness the fight between the Matadors and the bulls. The arena (Plaza de Toros) was located at Ventas, in Madrid and was a magnificent stadium that looked similar to the Colosseum in the Gladiator movie, though not matching it in size. For me bullfighting was a contest between the bulls and the matadors, which the matadors always won. I had expected that the matadors would “cheat” the bulls for few minutes and once the bulls were tired and given up the fight would be complete. But I was in for a surprise.  At 6:00 in the evening, the matadors entered the arena and saluted the box were the king would have sat in the olden days. Once this formality was completed, 4 matadors, one in each corner of the arena, waited with pink clothe (don’t know the exact term) for the bull to make the entry. As the gates opened, the first bull came charging in and the matadors kept inviting it and then “cheating” it. This continued for few minutes, by which time the bull had made around 3 – 4 rounds around the arena. The trumpets blew once again and a couple of men riding on armoured horses with long sticks (I initially assumed it was a stick, but it was more like a spear with a sharp point). The bulls were then made to attack the horses and at that point, the men riding the horses, inserted the spear on to the bulls back. I was initially shocked when I saw blood oozing out of the bulls back. This happened a couple of time and then the matadors, came out with pointed sticks. The bulls were made to charge towards these matadors and in a skilled manner, the matadors inserted these sticks also to the bulls back. At the end of around 10 minutes, the bull had blood oozing from the holes on its back. I began to realize that the bullfighting was not just about winning it was about killing!   After 10 minutes, the chief matador made the entry. After completing the formality of saluting to the imaginary king, this matador was handed a sword and the red clothe. At this stage all the minor matadors moved to the back stage. It was now a one to one contest between the bull and the chief matador. The matador demonstrated his skills to the applause of the crowd gathered there. After about 10 minutes, the matador replaced his sword with another sharper one. It was time for the kill. After another couple of rounds, the matador positioned himself straight in front of the tired bull and pointed the sword at its head. In one quick motion, he had the sword inserted completely into the region between the bulls neck and back. One could only see the handle of the sword. But the bull had not given up. Skillfully, the minor matadors removed the sword from the bulls back, and the chief matador again went for the kill. After the third attempt, the bull moved a few feet and fell on the ground – DEAD! The Spaniards were clapping to the victory of the matador over the bull. Probably around 1000 years back, people used to applaud similarly to the sight of the victorious gladiators who would be standing beside the people they had killed over a sport that meant nothing to mankind!   Another matador came and similarly but less skillfully, killed another bull. The third matador was something of a special. There was a general excitement in the air when this matador made his entry. People were cheering and applauding his every move. His name was Ismael Lopez and he was a star of the crowd and he did demonstrate why he was one. The bull was made to run in circles around him many number of times and this was something that others had not done skillfully. Finally, when it was time for the kill, Lopez had the sword inserted in the right spot at the first attempt. The bull was vomiting bottles of blood and running around. There was blood all around the arena. People were standing and cheering and Lopez was running behind the bull pointing at the bull in a symbol that meant, “He had done it”. The bull tried to force its entry through the gate through which it had entered the arena. But it was in vain. In seconds, the bull dropped dead. The Spaniards gave a standing ovation to Lopez and at the same time they took a white kerchief from their pockets and waved at him. There was applause all around. The display of white kerchief by the crowd meant that they appreciated his fight and he was awarded a medal by the chief organizer. Probably in those days, there would have been a princess who would have liked his act and probably would have considered other options for the night!!    Death in victory becomes a sight of joy!    I couldn’t appreciate it anymore and hence left the stadium and found that many others were also leaving. Now I realize why my Spanish colleagues didn’t want to join me for the bullfight.    Experiencing Life – The Royal Way   Last week, I had mentioned about the Royal Palace that had about 2800 rooms. I decided to visit the palace and experience the Royal Life of Carlos, Alfonso, Fernando, Isabella, etc  The Jardines of Sabatini This has nothing to do with the cricketer “Douglas Jardine” or the tennis player “Gabriella Sabatini”. “Jardine” is the Spanish word for “Garden”, and these were the gardens which were “architected” by Gabriel Sabatini who was one of the chief architect of the Royal Palace. He was responsible for designing most of the rooms in the royal palace and hence the Garden was named after him. There is nothing much to mention about the Gardens, except that it is located in the Palace courtyard, has some fountains (the Spaniards are crazy about fountains!) and has some flora so that it can be called a garden!     The Armory   The palace is a massive structure and on entering inside there is a large square where the soldiers would assemble in those days for a parade. The armory and the pharmacy was located on the sides of this massive square. The armory has a very good collection of (you guessed it right!) armors J and this includes the massive protection gear for both people and horses that you would normally see in Hollywood movies.     The Pharmacy   More than the armory, I liked the pharmacy – one because I felt that the Salar Jung museum in Hyderabad had better armors and secondly because it was for the first time I was seeing a well structured pharmacy, where you could easily retrieve all kinds of herbs. There was also a distillery, weighing scales, leather boxes used to transport medicines across continents and also during the travel of the king. There were so many herbs that I was left wondering that either this pharmacy was also open to the general public or the royal family was a “sick” family J. Probably, just like we have a section in our projects, this might been a necessary part of the risk management for the Royal family.     The Royal Salons   The entry into the main palace was through a staircase that is very similar to the ones we would have seen in old hindi or tamil movies – the only difference is that this is real and much more grand. I was first led into a room that was dedicated to a chief of the Royal Guards, which protected the royal family and the palace in those days. This person was responsible for the formation of the Royal Guards. This room led me into another hall which was a banquet hall used by the king to throw parties. This hall was also used to sign Spain’s accession to the European Community in 1985 and was the place where the Middle East peace conference took place in 1991.   Some of the highlights of all the Salons were – Costly (it has to be costly!!) carpets, paintings hanging everywhere, painting on the ceilings with a theme for each room, etc.   The third room was the best of all, a room that every palace would have. This was where the thrones were present. This was the best ever throne that I had seen in my entire life. I just felt like running towards the throne, sit on it and then proclaim myself the king of Spain. Even if it were for a moment, I would still be one of the few who would have sat on the throne. If luck was on my side, I could also become one of the very few to have farted on the throne J.  The steps leading to the throne were flanked on both sides by roaring lions that had the world at their feet. As far as I have noticed, the lions are the royal symbol of Spain. Any monument linked with the royal family would definitely have a lion somewhere.  The painting on the ceiling of this room was a special one – it represented the Spanish kingdom stretching from America to Philippines (via Spain of course J). There was the kingdom of Valencia, the Indians (Red Indians), the America discovered by Columbus, the Latin America, etc.  I was also led to the dining room, the reading room, the dressing room and the bedroom of the Kings. The dinning room had a massive table that could probably seat about 100 people. This table was made to celebrate the marriage of one of the Kings. Other rooms that I visited include the billiards room, smoking room, etc. There was also a section where Isabella De Catolica and her husband Fernando De Catolica lived. Isabella is one of the most famous queens of the Spanish kingdom. I am not sure if there were many Isabellas, as the Spanish kings generally have either Carlos or Alfonso as their name in alternate hierarchical sequence. However you can find many references to the queen Isabella in Madrid. Infact one of the hurricanes that struck USA recently was also named after her! ;) Anyhow, this section was temporarily closed and hence we could not see the life Isabella had lived.    Temple De Debod   What is the link between Egypt and Spain? This is the question that came to my mind when I reached this temple. The Temple De Debod (Template of Debod) is an Egyptian temple located near the palace, overlooking the ravine bordering Madrid. This temple was build some 2000 years ago, not in Madrid, but in Egypt. In recent history, there was danger to some of the Egyptian Shrines because of certain invading forces and Egypt approached Spain for help. Spain obliged and the shrines of Egypt were protected from the invading forces. As a token of thanks, the Egyptian Government decided to gift this shrine to Spain. In this manner the Temple of Debod was reconstructed in Madrid in the year 1968. There is nothing much in this shrine, except for some rock carvings depicting some King and his life. I was not interested and decided to help out some girls who wanted their picture to be taken in front of the temple. Since it was a temple, probably they wanted the photo to be taken by a person who was coming from the land of Ahimsa, Land that gave birth to religions like Hinduism, Buddhism, Jainism, Sikhism, blah blah … The bullfight is still in my head!!   Search For the Missing Indian  There is a famous story in Kerala. When Neil Armstrong set his foot on the moon and was about to proclaim himself as the first man on moon, he saw a smoke coming from a distant place. He decided to investigate the same and hence moved in the direction of the smoke. To his surprise, he came across a tea shop run by a Malayalee. Forget Malayalees, Indians are supposed to be everywhere. At least that is what I was imagining. But in Madrid I haven’t come across a true Indian. Why true? Read ahead! This weekend after receiving the directions to some of the Indian restaurants in Madrid from one of my colleagues, I decided to search for the missing Indian. On Friday night, I decided to check out an Indian restaurant called Delhi. Unfortunately, after about 1.5 hrs of searching around, I couldn’t locate this restaurant and hence opted for another Indian restaurant called Adrish. This restaurant had proper Indian menu but it was run by Spaniards with a Bangladeshi Cook. The food was also a disappointment. I ordered for Chicken Madras expecting that it would be similar to Chettinadu Chicken. However it was chicken is tomato sauce!   Today, I finally managed to find the Delhi restaurant. Infact this happened accidentally. On Friday I had called up the Delhi restaurant a couple of times and asked for directions but still couldn’t locate it. Probably having missed a customer, they had decided to make corrections. After visiting the palace, when I was walking towards another restaurant, I came across an Indian (looked like an Indian) who was fixing a new board that provided the directions to the Delhi Restaurant. This board was much more clearer and probably helped them improve their business as they had an increased crowd for lunch today (This information is from what they told me). The Delhi restaurant had a better ambience. There was also Songs of Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan, which included the “Afreen, Afreen, …” song. One of the specialties of this restaurant was the option for the customer to customize the food according to his needs. This restaurant also offered fish curry and when I was given the option of customization, I, expecting the host to be Indian, asked for fish curry in Kerala style. But to my disappointment, these guys were Bangladeshis and were not aware of something called “Kerala Style” L I decided to give up on fish and opted for the prawn curry. But these guys were really good. They came and enquired about the Kerala style and I, who always like to live thinking that I am a good cook, described about the Kerala style of preparation. When the prawn curry arrived, I was totally surprised; they had tried to put into action whatever I had told them except for the turmeric part. There was a good amount of coconut and the prawn curry was fabulous. And at the end of the lunch, they gave me free “Indian Masala Chai” as a token of affection. It has been long time (2 weeks has become a very long time for me! ) since I have had such a good tea. Well, even though they were not Indians, they had put their best to give me a proper Indian Lunch. After thanking them for making my day, I decided to go for the bullfight.    The Story of an Icelandic and an Indian  What is common between an Icelandic and an Indian in Spain? Both are foreigners, both have similar problems communicating to the Spanish people, and both find a companion among each other during work, lunch, dinner, and sight seeing. During this week, Inkimar joined me from Iceland team. He was here for a week for the same project on which I was working. He was 37 years old and had similar problems that I have been with the Spaniards. The main topics of our discussion were the culture and habits of Iceland and India. During the last 2 weeks, apart from my normal work, I have also been promoting India a lot as a tourist destination and he is the second person who has taken a strong inclination in visiting India in the near future. These guys (Europeans) generally travel a lot and that is where I feel they gather a lot of knowledge. Since travel is very cheap here, they can afford it. We Indians should also travel a lot. Only then can we learn a lot about the positive aspects of other work culture, technologies, etc and how we can incorporate the same into our lifestyle. Only then can we become a truly developed nation. But as I have been reading, things are also changing in India. There was an article in one of the online sites, on Indian farmers who have started visiting countries like Israel, Australia, Netherlands, etc to learn about their technologies, process, etc and incorporate the same into our agriculture.    Bagets   I don’t want to drag much, but this is a Spanish food item that I liked. It is more like a sandwich. An elliptical bun is cut into 2 and a slice of stuffing of your choice is placed in the middle. This is served along with potato chips. We had cheese ham, spicy ham, Salmon, tuna and chicken bagets. It seems there are 200+ combinations of baggets.  Before closing down … as I was coming in the Metro train after the bullfight, there was this beautiful female who was sitting right in front of me. She had a very good smile and was well dressed and a very special glow on her face. She has been one of the very few females that I have admired in my life. The unfortunate part is that She was not an Indian. Anyhow, my station came and I had to get down, probably never to meet her again.   The coming week is my last week in Madrid before I return to India. I was once mentioning to one of my colleagues here during a particular incident… “In India there is order in chaos and here there is Chaos in Order”. I am not sure if they understood my statement as they gave a confused look or probably they like many of my colleagues in Hyderabad, chose to ignore it.  Looking forward to my trip back, Sathish on September 28, 2003 at 11:39 PM 
      
</post>

<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      A busy and tiring week!!  This is how I would summarize the first week in Spain. Busy and tiring because of the amount of work that I had to do. However I still managed to take time of the busy schedule and managed to visit places and enjoy and discover the different aspects of Spanish (Madrid) life.     The Spanish Identity  A very good start to this process of “Discovering Spain” was given by one of my colleagues “Carlos”. He was a very jovial guy and is from Barcelona. He takes pride in calling himself a Catalonian rather than a Spanish, but then is very proud of Spanish Identity, language, etc. In fact, for me, he represented the face of Spanish Identity.   The Spanish people are very proud about their language. One of the first questions I received from one of the colleagues here was “What do you know about Spain?” and when I mentioned some of the things I know about Spain he also told me that Ricky Martin and Enrique Iglesius also sing in Spanish. His point was that the whole world is listening to Spanish and he hoped that Spanish would become a universal language. At the same time, there is also a realization that English is “slowly” becoming the universal language for communication. Here if you need to survive, you have to know Spanish. For me, since I had company for most of the time, it was not a problem. Moreover one of the first things I learned in Spanish was “Español, No Entiendo” (I don’t understand Spanish), apart from “Hola” and “Gracias”.   One of the best experiences that I had with Español was in the McDonalds. I was in the queue and the nearby queue became empty. A lady who had just come offered me the empty queue and I obliged immediately. The person at the counter knew only Spanish and She kept on telling things in Spanish. Finally I had to release the only mantra that I knew … “Español, No Entiendo”. Well after bit of sign language and help from another person who knew decent English, an order was placed. In the mean time, the person who offered the queue to me, called the manager of the place and was mentioning something and repeatedly pointing at me. At the end of the shouting session, she gave up and left the place without having lunch. The only thing I could do was to keep quiet and when she had left, I asked the person at the counter “Any Problem?” and She said “No Problem”. Anyhow I still don’t know exactly what the problem was, but what I had interpreted from her body language was that She had offered me the queue as she had just entered and I was already in the second queue (Spanish Culture) . However when the second queue became empty, an American who had just entered did not offer her the second queue (American Culture). She was really pissed off!! Hope she had a nice lunch J  The Spanish also are not that very fond of their neighbours, i.e., French. They believe that Español has wider reach than French (which may be right if we include Latin America) and they also believe that Spanish wine is better than French (may be some wine expert can comment on this).   Madrid – City of Fountains, Restaurants and Castles  Madrid is a city famous for Fountains, Restaurants, and Castles. If 4 or more roads meet at a point then you can be assured that you would find a fountain there. And this fountain would definitely have significance. For example, an important road in the city is named after a fountain that is located along that road.    Madrid is also famous for its night life and the enormous number and variety of restaurants that you can find. If you are in Plaza De Cibelles, all you have to do is to go to one of the by-lanes and knock on any door. It would definitely be a restaurant. These are not typical restaurants, but are more famous for “tapas” i.e., along with a glass of beer or wine, etc have some snacks. The Spanish dinner is an extended one. Generally they have tapas around 9:00 – 10:00 pm and then have a late dinner that would extend to 12:00 PM. Most of the Spanish dishes contain either Meat, Sea Foods or Pork. Vegetarians would definitely have a tough time surviving here.  I have been eating mostly sea food and have tried squid, Salmon, tuna, octopus, etc.   Madrid is a very old city. Except for a brief period, it has been the capital of the Iberian Peninsula / Spain for many centuries. As a result any tourist can easily trace the gradual development of the city. This is more visible in Castellana (where most of castles are located) that houses the Spanish Congress and most of the ministries and offices like the Central Post office, Central Bank, etc. All these buildings were constructed a couple of centuries back and are good examples of Spanish (European) Architecture.  There are also many modern day “castles” and these include a Europe Tower designed by the famous Japanese Architect who had also designed the WTC towers in New York.    Typical Spanish Dinner  On Tuesday (September 16, 2003), Carlos and myself decided to go for a typical Spanish dinner. At around 9:30 we entered one of the places where they serve you tapas and he had a glass of beer and I gave him company with a glass of Coca Cola. We also had a slice of salted ham that was well cooked and tasted good. At 10:00 we again took a long walk and then walked into a restaurant at 10:30. We decided to go for 2-course dinner. As part of the first course I tried a platter of seafood, which included octopus, Salmon, tuna, prawns, etc. The second course included a stuffed squid.  In Madrid, I haven’t seen a single Indian yet! However in this restaurant, there was a Spanish girl, Soledar (something like that) meaning lonely.  She worked in the restaurant and served us the food. The first thing She asked to my colleague on seeing me (She knew only Spanish and hence couldn’t communicate with me directly) was whether I am a Hindu. She then showed me a chain that she was wearing and asked if I recognized it. It was a “Rudraksh” chain and she said that she was a devotee of Sai Baba and had got that chain in a temple. Well that was the one of the very few Indian Connections that I have encountered so far here.    Spice Contest – Peru Vs India  One of the major complaints that I have been having about the food here is the amount of spice. It is totally zero! My colleagues here decided to take me to a place where the food would be really spicy. It was a Peruvian restaurant, and Peruvian food is supposed to be very spicy (or at least that is the impression they have created). I decided to take on the challenge and opted for the spiciest food in that restaurant. It was a rice-based food, with lots of sea organisms mixed into it. Well it was not a contest of evens, as the Spiciest Peruvian food could only be compared to our sambhar in the amount of spice. Anyhow it was a different experience and I really liked the Peruvian food.    Annapurna – Indian but not really Indian   On Friday, I had given up. I wanted something spicy and decided to look out for an Indian restaurant. There are very few Indian restaurants and one of the popular one is the Annapurna. The name itself brought joy to my stomach and I took the metro to Alonso Martinez and from there I walked for about 10 minutes before I reached the restaurant. I expected to meet some Indians over there, but then even though the name was purely Indian it was run by Bangladeshis ! There was a Bangladeshi cook, Ali, who reminded me of the Bangladeshi cook in the serial “Tandoori Nights”. The food was anyhow Indian. I decided to go for a Paratha, Murgh Jalfrezi and a plate of Chawal with a glass of lassi. Finally my stomach had got what it wanted. The food was spicy enough and I left the place satisfied enough. It is an expensive place, but I think I will visit this place one more time before I leave Madrid.    Museum De Prado   One of the many highlights of Madrid is the Prado Museum. It is supposed to be one of the 3 largest Museums in the world (in Paintings Category). It has a large collection of Italian, Spanish, German, French and British paintings and sculptures. Though I hate seeing paintings, I decided to visit it just for the sake of not missing it. It is more like tourists wanting to see Charminar. After around 30 – 60 mins in the museum I decided to take the bus trip of Madrid. Madrid Vision – Discovering Madrid  The Madrid Vision is a bus trip, wherein I can take 3 routes to see the complete City. I decided to take 2 routes as you the 3rd route contain the places covered by the first and second route.   The first trip that I took was that of the Modern Madrid. The main aim of this trip was to visit the Real Madrid stadium. Luckily there was also the English commentary and hence I could get to know more about Madrid like the place where the rich lives, the embassy area, the parliament, the post office, stock exchange, etc  The second trip was more historic, and the places they covered included the Discovery Park (this is in dedication to the discovery of America by Christopher Columbus. There is no mention about India at all, although it was a case of mistaken discovery).  Other places included the Royal Palace (containing around 2800 rooms), the Teatro Real (Opera house), the town center (where the 0 km mark of Spain starts), the Plaza Mayor (Mayor in Spanish means big), some historic fountains, etc.   Even though it was a tiring one, the trips were worth taking and this gave me a better insight into the history of Madrid. The city itself was founded by the Arabs in the 700 AD when they conquered the Iberian peninsula and built a fortress here and called it “Madhireedh” (something like that) meaning the land of water / fountains J   Satiago Bernabeau – Inside Real Madrid C.F.  The Real Madrid Football club is situated very close to the place where I stay. The stadium is on the other side and is called “Santiago Bernabeau”. On Tuesday, there was a match going on between Real Madrid and Marseille. Outside we could here the crowds roar when Ronaldo scored a goal for Real Madrid. It was a great experience. If possible I need to go for a match.  The stadium Area had a large collection of trophies right from 1904 to last years Champions Trophy. I also decided to get a small memorabilia from the stadium shopping center.   Retiro   Today, I again took the Metro and reached Retiro. This is a famous park in Madrid and along with another park forms the lungs of the city. The park has some famous fountains and a “large” lake [don’t even compare with Durgam Cheruvu. It is much smaller than that]. This lake is more like a beach for the Spanish, and you can find many people taking a sunbath. There is also a Crystal Palace in the park and is famous. But all I could see was a glass palace with some glass tables and some speakers around it. There was a booklet in Spanish that described its significance, but then I can’t read Spanish!! If you have visited either the Lal Bagh or the Ooty Botanical Gardens , etc then just forget this park. It is not worth visiting. The only highlight was some good Latin music being played by some local people.   City of Plazas  Madrid is also a city of Plazas, Plazas in Spanish means Square. So you have the Plaza de Castilla (Square of Castilla), Plaza de Cibelles, Plaza Mayor,  etc. Most often you will find a fountain in the center of the Plaza.   The Latin Connection   Latin America was once a colony of Spain and that connection is very evident in Madrid. You can find lots of Latin Americans and also places that are named after countries / places in South America. There is a district in Madrid called “Latina” and this has places like Paraguay, Colombia, Republica Argentina, etc.   Other Highlights of Madrid    Puerta De Sol [Gate of Sun]  This is where the town hall of Madrid is located. This place is significant because this is considered to be the center point of Spain. The 0 km mark starts from this place. This was constructed around 300 – 400 years ago. Recent studies by satellite have shown that the people in those days were nearly correct as the exact center of Spain is located just 10 km from this point. This point has around 10 (probably more as I saw only one half) roads leading in a circular fashion. It is believed that all roads in Spain start from this point.     Español – Fast Track    	Sala – Not the hindi “Sala”, but it means “Room”.  	Salida – Exit. Follow the “Salida” signs blindly when you are going out of Metro or other places.  	Chicala – Meaning girl. Probably the work “Chic” had its origin from this word!  	Libre – Means “Free”. If you need to catch a taxi, check if the board near the driver says “LIBRE”.  	Occupado – Occupied. If taxis are not free then it would be “OCCUPADO”  	Perfecto – Meaning Perfect. Have been hearing this and Correcto lot of times, especially in television.  	Correcto – means Correct.   	Naranja – This is pronounced more like Malayalam for lemon and it means the same J Strange! It also is used for Oranges.  Another busy week starts in 7 hrs!   Chao, September 22, 2003 1:05 AM 
      
</post>

<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Spain, the land that is famous for many things, things that I am yet to find out. But as many of my friends have been telling and also based on the very less knowledge about Spain that I have, I was sure to discover new and interesting things. 	 My journey started from Hyderabad on September 13, 2003. I am undertaking this trip for business reasons. Hence the time to “discover” Spain is very limited. Around 500 years back Christopher Columbus set off from Spain to discover India and now I am moving to “discover” Spain.    Hyderabad – Mumbai    I had to travel by the 9:15 flight of Jet Airways. It was a Boeing 737 aircraft and unlike my previous experiences and that of most of my colleagues, the journey was very smooth and not like traveling in an Auto through the lanes of Chennai. To top it all the Airhostesses were too good and caring. There was this hostess, Swati, who caught my attention for most of the journey. She had a different hairstyle that made her forehead look like the “ohm” symbol (if you drew the line along the boundary of her forehead skin and hair). The one factor that I would appreciate in this whole journey to Madrid is the waiting time. The waiting time was just appropriate to refresh yourself and make the move. Earlier there used to be so much waiting time that you would get totally bored waiting for a flight that would take off only after around 6 hrs.    Mumbai – Paris Charles De Gaulle [CDG]   On landing in Mumbai my first job was to get a reliable transit service from Mumbai – Hyderabad. The experience of Jan Westrate at the Mumbai airport during transit was fresh in my mind. But to my joy I found an Air France representative waiting for me and other passengers. Even though I managed to find the Air France representative, She (Yes it is a She and her name was Rupali and She couldn’t be better) couldn’t find my name in the list of passengers. After searching for a while in the list of names, we finally managed to dig out my record using the point of destination (Madrid), as I was the only passenger in that list traveling to Madrid. Air France had arranged for a separate bus (similar to KLM).  As I boarded the Air France bus, a well-known face was staring at me. It was Manikandan, ex-colleague who had worked in my team earlier. He was traveling to London via Paris. He said that he was going for “short-term” which was 3 months long. I basically felt the need for re-defining the terms “short-term” and “long-term”!!   I was probably one of the very few who didn’t have a hard copy of the ticket but still had a ticket that was re-confirmed. I met Clara (J) at the Air France counter and she too was a bit surprised that I didn’t have a hard copy! However because of the help of Rupali I had already managed to get an early check in done and hence all I had to do was collect my boarding pass and return tickets.   The Air France flight (Airbus 340) was decent but not as good as the Austrian Airways flight for several reasons.  -	The push back was very limited. Austrian Airways had a much larger scope for “push back”. -	There was lot of (relatively) dust in the aircraft. -	The blankets had lot of cotton dust. -	There was a movie of Esha Deol and Sanjay Khan’s son!! Most of the other movies were not that great.  Still the flight was a very pleasant one. The landing at the CDG was one of the smoothest landings. During the last 3 hrs of the flight I once again got the sneezing problem because of the cotton dust. I had only 4 hours of proper sleep. My company through out the flight was Gopi, a Malayalee from Palakkad. He was going to a university in France for doing some post Ph.D research.   The CDG is a very big airport. But I felt that Amsterdam was better. Probably I haven’t seen much of CDG. However the airport Architecture looked good. Everything that you need was within 15 min of your reach if you take the proper means and for that you need to properly interpret the signs, which I did not do initially.     Paris – Madrid Bajaras   It was again an Air France flight and this was much better, with very good food, beautiful Airhostess and a sleeping babe for company, who slept throughout the 1.5 hrs of flight! There was one food item that I liked a lot. A Croissant with Apricot Jam stuffed inside. It was “delicious” and I loved it. Need to check out if I can get one here somewhere. Else need to wait for the return flight.  The Aueropuerto De Madrid Bajaras, is not that great compared to Schipol or CDG or even Mumbai. It was a simple airport with the basic needs. Marcelo Cury, my host in Spain, was waiting for me and we took a cab to the hotel.     HUSA Chamartin   This is where I am staying. It is a four star hotel and has a mini bar, a safety box, blah blah. The hotel is pretty decent. The Metro runs right below the hotel. Infact this hotel is a property of the Railways of Spain.     First look at Madrid   The city is a very calm city. It was also a Sunday and nearly every shop was closed. In Spain, most of the shops are closed on Sundays and the Saturday of the first weekend of the month. Some of the other features of Spain are,  1.	Lunch is taken for 2 hours unlike the 0.5 – 1 hr period back home.  2.	Restaurants are open only from 1 – 4 for lunch and 9 – 12 for dinner.  3.	Shops generally close early at around 8:30.  There was one aspect that caught my immediate attention. There were posters stuck on the walls very similar to the film posters that we would find in Chennai or Coimbatore or any other town / city in India (except Hyderabad J ). Madrid looks more like a costly City to live in. The minimum charge for a decent dinner is € 10.00 and everything is costly. Probably it is more to do with the place I have visited today. May be things are cheap in other parts of the city.  The time now here is 9:00 PM and the Sun is just setting down. Have to prepare for a busy week ahead.  Closing down, September 14, 2003 20:55  
      
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Why do we sleep?   Looking back, it was a usual night. During the day I had been part of the team evaluating a couple of design tools for object oriented design. The evaluation was proceeding smoothly and it was one of those days when life seemed to be moving slowly and suddenly there was plenty of time to look into the where my life stood in the road to the future. It was not a road to perdition but it was hazy and the path forward was not clear.   It was a long time since I had seen some unusual dreams, dreams filled with creativity that presented exciting scenarios that rarely happen in our day-to-day life. Sometimes, dreams help you achieve the impossible, though it only happens in dreams. I have often felt that I am at my best whenever I have such dreams. It had been a long time and life was at its lowest ebb and then this dream happened.  Life, as a whole, presents a lot of perplexing questions. There must be some reason, I thought, as to why we humans need to sleep everyday. The very purpose of sleeping daily! It could have been weekly or there could have been some other recharge mechanism. But why sleep? I thought to myself, I sleep for about 8 hours a day. If I could use those 8 hours for some other activity, then would my life have been different? Would the world be a different place? Probably there could be some ways of achieving the impossible. 1000 years ago, no one would have even imagined about the various technological gadgets that we take it for granted as part of our daily life.   As I kept wondering about the need for sleep, I began to realize that my body was not a single piece of human body. It was abnormal or probably it was the way all humans were. My body was made up of various objects and I could see that classes defined these objects and the classes were associated using UML style relationships. It was definitely not a comfortable feeling. I had known myself as being represented by a single framework made up of skeleton and various muscles and organs and covered by a single lining of skin that made the entire body look like a single component. The realization of the new representation of my body gave me a worrying feeling. I wanted to do something about it. I wanted to assemble all the components and deploy it as a single unit. But I just didn’t know how to do it. Was there a tool? Was there a physician who could assemble it? If yes, how do I find the tool or the physician? Do others also experience the same? I was deeply into finding ways to see myself as a single unit of representation. Then this thought came to my mind. Probably this is the correct representation of the human body. And that could be the reason why we sleep. When we sleep, the body was getting un-deployed and necessary corrections and fine-tuning was being done to the components and by the time we are through with the ritual of sleeping, the components get deployed again. That is why we need to sleep daily as the human components are not scalable beyond a day without loosing performance. The human system probably needs to get restarted once a day so that it does not loose its performance.   A strange feeling came to my mind. I wanted to view the objects and their classes and their relationships so that I could study the architecture of the body. Even though I had realized the same, I couldn’t see it. In an attempt to see the classes of my body, I opened my eyes to view what could be the best architecture ever known for mankind. As I opened my eyes, I was getting out of my sleep and the components were getting deployed and the system was restarting. My eyes were wide open and the world was at it was earlier. My body was still a single unit of human body. The components were not visible. I was confused whether what I had seen was just a dream or the realization of the unknown!    
      
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Very few things have given me company for long period of time. My second jeans, the first one that really impressed me is one such item and recently after 4 years of public service, I had to retire active service. A painful decision, but it had to be executed.    The Origin of Jeans    From the days of total ignorance about denim, Jeans has become a part of my everyday life. I have been always thinking that Jeans originated in some Texas ranch or as a necessity for the mineworkers during the American Gold Rush. But I was surprised when I got to know that it originated in Italy and the word "Denim" is actually a French word. Surprised??!! Read the below paragraph taken from the wikipedia.   Jeans were first invented in Genoa, Italy when that city was an independent Republic, and needed all-purpose pants for sailors in the Genoese Navy. The first denim came from (french:de) Nîmes, France ... hence the name denim. Those sailors required a pant that could be worn wet or dry, and whose legs could easily be rolled-up to wear swabbing the deck. These jeans would be laundered by dragging them in large mesh nets behind the ship, and the seawater would bleach them white. The French word for these pants was very similary to their word for Genoa -- this is where we get the term 'jeans' today.     Stepping into the New World   I remember the day when I along with my friends had gone on a "selective cloth hunting" spree to Shopper's stop. The aim was to grab as much as possible within the limited budget of each individual. I had selected the jeans sanctuary in the 3rd floor. It was filled with denims of all the popular international brands - Lee, Levis, Wrangler, Pepe, etc. Jeans definitely was not my area of specialization. The only jean that I had purchased earlier was during my school days and it definitely was not a experience worth remembering. The brand was called "Currency" and I always felt that my weight increased by around 5 kgs whenever I wore that. The shelves were packed with all varieties of jeans, in different colors and fits. I just hoped that I wouldn't get lost in the denim jungle! Suddenly a voice emerged from one of the shelves .   "Pssssst !! Here ... look at me! I am the original one. The rest are fakes. Just check me out"   It was none other than a Levis jean trying to grab my attention. Unfortunately, the other jeans had heard the Levis! From the neighbouring shelf there was a loud laughter. It was Lee trying to divert my attention.  "Levis!!" shouted Lee accompanied by the laughter that sounded more like the ramming of doors during a tropical thunderstorm.    "Levis Strauss what not!! Such a pathetic name that would make the medicines sick!"  The tone was particularly harsh that made Levis look totally lost and depressed.   "Look at me!" exclaimed Lee with a tone that had changed from harsh to one that was more aimed at giving an impression of being a statesman. "I am Lee and you would always be glee with me!! Lee ... Bruce Lee ...Brett Lee !! Don't I sound familiar?" I knew that it was a poor joke and being an expert in that field, I dint want another buddy with similar traits! I knew Lee was not the one. I looked around and found that Pepe was busier trying to break away from the wrangles of wrangler! The decision was simple. I wanted to give a lift to the exponentially decreasing morale of Levis and give it the life it deserved, away from the company of Lee and Pepe. Without any hesitation, I grabbed the Levis one and in minutes I was going on my way back home with Levis breathing the fresh air of Hyderabad, outside that of shopper's stop. Levis had just stepped into active public service.   When life Changed !    I don’t remember when I actually started liking it, but all I remember is that I was not sure as to how and when to use it. Yes, I always wanted some dress that I could wear anytime and anywhere without having the need to keep changing my attire for each and every occasion or every quarter of the day ! Even though I had purchased the Levis jean by chance, it definitely had a great impact in my life. Slowly it was the preferred option to work (casuals are allowed only on Fridays :) ), dinner, home, outing, drive, travel, etc. Apart from the 4 working days of the week, I never felt the need for going for another option. It didn’t matter if it was raining or the temperature was low enough to freeze your bones or whether it was a scorching day with a feeling of being grilled live, it always made me feel comfortable. With all the patience it ever had, it tolerated all the dirt, dust and roughness that it was subjected to! It also gave me company during the chill Christmas nights in Copenhagen, or during the nervous days spent in Netherlands after losing my passport and also when the matadors were taking the bulls by their horns in Madrid.  Life was as comfortable as it could be!    Time and toughness did have its toll! The charm of the youth was being lost gradually as it was losing its shine in a slow process. The frills of old age began to appear and dirt was slowly eating into its life. A stage had reached when I had to take a tough decision!   It wasn’t an easy decision! The hard work had its toll and it was necessary to amputate the lower folding so that it could be saved from further damage. This meant that continuing the active service would be difficult, as it would loose its immunity to the constant wear and tear that it was being subjected to! But the options were limited and amputation had to be performed. With amputation done, it was time to retire it from active life. It is often said that the only constant thing is change. It was true in this case also. It was time to recruit new ones and I decided to get in 2 new ones into service so that the workload could be effectively distributed.   The levis jean would still be in limited service and would definitely be preferred over the young guns in occasions like games, limited outing, etc. It always was an effective companion and would remain to be so but with limited usage.  It definitely is the first jean that I liked and would remain to be so !  
      
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      You never know when boredom strikes you nor can you predict when someone would score a goal in a soccer match!  Fortunately or unfortunately, both of these struck me this week and it has the potential of driving me crazy!     The Goal Part …  It was fun and frustration to watch France snatch victory from the jaws of defeat in the final minutes of the Euro 2004. It was fun because the match was a treat to match with both sides exhibiting quality football. It also made me feel that it wasn’t worthless (also read as senseless) to waste my precious sleeping hours and watch the live feed of the match at around 2:00 AM. I could have been dreaming about some princess in a far off land waiting for me and battling the pressures of life or probably the war of the solar system where my space ship would be engaged in a needless fight to destroy the bloodless aliens from the planet of morons!    It was also frustrating because it took away the opportunity that I would have had had England one. The opportunity to take a good-natured gibe at one of my friend who revels in supporting France! I also had to spend extra minutes in arriving at a counter strategy to mitigate the effects of hearing all the praises that would be showered on France and its players by that friend of mine. All due to Beckham and Victoria!! Probably the effects of personal life affected the performance of Beckham.    BTW… Who cares about the English!! The “Spanish Armada” or the “Azzuri” are going to rule!     The Bore Part …  In software industry boredom happens to be our lifelong friend. Just when we think that life is at its best, boredom knocks on our door and asks us …   “Buddy, isnt it long time since we were together! Would you mind if I joined you in your moments of happiness!!”   Even before we can say a loud “NO”, it jumps in and occupies a corner of our beautiful house and tries to make itself comfortable in whatever space available. Thereafter, it is a battle, a battle to get boredom out of our house. If we don’t get boredom out, we will soon find that boredom has entered our kitchen and is cooking something really fishy for us! Beware … tasting it would be dangerous and could lead to a romance with boredom. Once we begin to like boredom, we will soon find that its friend "Laziness" wouldn't hesitate to join us! (Does that lead to threesome !!)   Anyhow – boredom also provides us with opportunities. Just cleaned my mailbox today. Something that I wanted to do for months. It can also get the best out of us … who knows, boredom might just be cooking a new idea that could get me ignited (Ahem!! I meant it in the positive sense). Its Smoking !!    To conclude, just like Zidane’s free kick that turned the match in favor of France, I just kicked boredom out of my personal life (at least for some time). All my senses are now glued to Euro 2004. But there is much more to follow - Wimbledon, Asia Cup Cricket, Olympics and of course my trip to Coimbatore. It is monsoon time and time for me to take a Monsoon trail and recollect the good old memories that I have about Monsoon. However, boredom still exists in my office life! Probably what I need to do is try for another Goal and get it out!    “Hey, where is the damn football !!”   
      
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      July 26, 1999 – This was the day when I joined my first company after graduation and on Monday, July 26, 2004, I would be completing 5 years in the same organization! 5 years have passed by in a flash!   Till 5 years back, my entire life was confined to a limited area around my house at Coimbatore. My schooling and graduation was done at institutions very close to my house. On July 23rd, 1999 when I was leaving the Coimbatore railway juntion in Sabari Express to join this Organization, my father had remarked to my sister, “ His independent journey in life is finally starting! ”. I am not sure how far I have traveled in this journey and am not going to do an analysis of the same right now!   On the first day at office, one of the first things that impressed me was the reception! There were various clocks that displayed the times of India, Netherlands, etc. On the left side was a small room with a large coffee vending machine. On the right was a conference room where you could see “executives” discussing various strategies! It must have been one of the many boring meetings that I am used to nowadays, but the impression was great. To top it all was the receptionist who seemed to be in total control of the proceedings in that room. This multi national company impressed me!   Trainings were more painful. It started sharp at 0830 hrs and the trainers were busier trying to scare the shit out of us than to make us feel more comfortable. There were only 2 systems outside the training room that had Internet connection and these systems were in great demand during the tea breaks! Finally it was the day when we were allotted our departments or areas of work, and I was among the “elite” gang to be put into the E-Enterprise division. This was a new division and it was in great demand then! From the next day onwards we were in separate training and this was the best part of training. We had total Internet connectivity, were dumped into some “junkyard” kind of room where we made the most of the opportunity and surfed through whatever the Internet could offer us and kept tracking the happenings around the world. It was a hectic period then and the company was not doing well. Our stocks were going down in NASDAQ while those of all other companies were shooting up the sky! From around 20 dollars per share we saw it go down the $1 mark! Many people were also leaving the organization, but I decided to stay put. “ I was in the most sought after department. There must be something in it! ” I don’t want to validate this thinking now, but that was the basic thinking that made me stay put in this organization during the crisis. The organization has since been moving slowly and steadily up the curve after a series of acquisitions and restructuring and this was a great learning experience.   10 years back if I had remarked to someone that I have completed 5 years in the same organization, people would have just shrugged it out and probably would have commented that I have a long way to go! 20 years in the same organization was the criteria when you can start even talking about how long you have been in the same organization. During the dot com boom, the same discussion would have made people look at me with disdain. They would have commented “ 5 years!!!! That is a long time to be in the same organization! ”. People would have also wondered if there were something wrong in me that made me “stick” to the same organization! However in today’s time 5 years is something that would give you some decent respect in the industry! At least in this respect, I have caught up with the times!   Let me go back to the journey 5 years back to Hyderabad. At that time, I don’t think I even imagined that I would stay in this organization for 5 years. My aim was to get 2 years experience and then move to a place closer to my family. Bangalore was the place that I was aiming for. But as I completed 2 years in the organization, I had an excusing of staying here for some more time due to the dot com burst! This was more like a moving target, from 2 years it shifted to 3, then 4 years and finally 5 years! I think now I have given up! No more targets, take it as it comes and make decision based on the current circumstances. That makes it more realistic! :)  When we joined 5 years back there were 40 members in our batch. This figure has come down drastically and now only 11 members are left! Every year we celebrate the completion of 1 more year in this organization. Last year we celebrated the occasion at Mount Opera water theme park. However I have wondered if this was really an occasion for celebration. Anyhow you just need to have an excuse for having fun and I don’t mind that! This year though there are no celebrations. People have become busier to find time for an outing. Probably they have better things in life. However I feel this year was the right time for a bash as it is a significant milestone and also because we are getting our gratuity and a gift voucher worth Rs.10000. That was more than a reason for celebration.   On Monday when we would be moving to our sixth year in office, there is nothing much to expect out of the day except for the customary email from the management thanking and congratulating us for blah blah blah reasons! Else it would be business as usual  ! ;-)  To end this blog, let me pen down the top 10 memorable events that have dotted my life as far as association with this organization is concerned. These are events that I feel would be worth remembering or at least worth enough not to be forgotten! As any countdown would do it, I will list it down starting from the bottom.   10. (a)   One month of Internet “exposure” at the main building junk room.  We were left to ourselves for around 1 month in a “junk” room and during this period we knew how to use the Internet, what are its pitfalls and pluses and what are the main resources, etc. This was a fun filled period and something that we still keep talking about.     10 (b)   Kingfisher Corporate 5-a-side Football Tournament 2002 for us was the year of football! We used to play every weekend at the Gymkhana grounds here in Hyderabad. Finally when the tournament was announced, 2 teams from our organization took part. It was the first time 2 teams were taking part in that tournament from the same organization. In that regard we were trendsetters. I was part of the B team which met the A team in quarterfinals. Finally a team went on to win the finals against Wipro in a thriller! It was pleasing to see all the hard work paying off finally. I enjoyed it!    9.  Playing  around with Yahoo IM to find my first and only 100% Internet buddy!  I was one of the first in my batch to use yahoo messenger and as part of my experiments I happened to find my first and only buddy who has remained a good Internet friend of mine all these years. However even after 5 years I haven’t met her yet! J   8.   Preparation for Bali Trail  This was a quiz event that my friend and I had organized in the organization. I was involved in preparing the presentation. The preparation and effort reminded me of the college days and was similar to the effort that I had put for Nexus ’99.   7.   Trip to Mahabaleshwar  In 2001, we organized a trip to Mahabaleshwar from the organization. The place and the trip was great! I especially loved the stay at Panchgani and the table top, as well as the strawberry ice creams at Mahabaleswar.    6.   Weekend Fever – Movie and Dinner @ Café Bahar For around 1 year or more (2002 – 03) I had a great time with our gang of friends, who were also colleagues. Every weekend you could spot us at either Sangeet or Skyline and this was usually followed or preceded by dinner at Café Bahar or Paradise. Chicken Biriyani and Tandoori Chicken were our favorites! Now however this has stopped as some of them have left the organization and city and others have become busier! Weekends were never boring!    5.   Trip to Denmark This was my first trip outside India. I had to make the trip alone and was totally ignorant of the practices and procedures that one has to follow during such trips. I still remember the way I used to observe other passengers as to how they were using the controls (for lights, push back, food tray, etc). Somehow I managed to go and come back without any issues!    4.   Approval engine   This was my first major activity for a product. I had to redesign and modify most of the portions of this engine and I really enjoyed doing it.    3.   Trip to Spain  Boy…what a trip it was! Read the initial blogs to get a better idea. This was the best trip that I had and enjoyed it to the maximum extent without getting bogged down by constraints.    2.   Losing my passport This one is totally contrary to trip to Spain. During the trip to Netherlands in 2002, I lost my passport and had really tough and anxious moments there and thereafter.    1.   Product 2.1 Architecture  The best moment in the 5-year span is obviously the effort spent in designing and developing the product 2.1. Product 1.0 did not come out all that well and I wanted to address the shortcoming that caused Product 1.0 to fail. When I look back now, I feel great about the way I had approached to 2.1. It may not be the best, but definitely it was lot better and I think I did a good job there!   On this note, it is time for me to sign off and have a good sleep. Tomorrow marks the dawn of another year in this organization. With each year comes new hopes, new dreams and new events that can be blogged ! ;))       
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Belpahar is an industrial township located in Northern Orissa near the industrial belt of Rourkela. I had left from Hyderabad on 12th July and returned back on 15th July 2004. Time to take you on the journey!    The Calcutta Alliance !    This was the first time I was flying Indian Airlines, or so did I think ! Only while boarding did I realize that the flight from Hyderabad to Calcutta stopped over at Bhubaneshwar. Hence the total flying time was approximately 30 mins. The aircraft was an old one and this could be easily made out from the very old overhead control panels which most of the time dint seem to work ! The air hostesses were totally emotionless and were more like zombies out to complete the task assigned ! It is then that I realized that we were flying Alliance Air, a subsidiary of Indian Airlines which owned the old aircrafts.   After 1.5 hours of flying we landed at the Biju Patnaik airport in Bhubaneshwar. Ours was the only aircraft in that airport and the airport was totally void of any activity. From the sky Bhubaneshwar looked more like a town rather than a city. Unlike other citiies, there wasnt any major activity visible from the sky. The only major structure that I saw was of a typical Oriya temple with the architecture that was similar to the Puri temple.  We were initially alloted the last row in the aircraft. However we entered into agreement with some generous Infosys guys because of which we had a relatively better seat. But we were not aware that those guys were getting off at Bhubaneshwar. At Bhubaneshwar, there was one passenger who was looking confused, as we were occupying his seat. The emotionless airhostess was called, and with a totally hopeless expression (which could be read as "What the shit is happening here ! Get off quickly ! Why do u guys give me much work ??!!") she asked us our seat numbers and asked us to move to our seats. Well, we wondered if these people were alloted these flight as part of their punishment !!   Finally we reached Cal, the City of Joy ! The airport pillars were drapped in East Bengal Football Club colors. Clearly the atmosphere was changing. Our immediate task was to catch the Gitanjali Express that would be leaving the Howrah station in another 2 hours. Lot of time ... or so did we think !   One of the highlights of Cal is the bright yellow Amby Taxis. The streets of calcutta are flooded with the yellow taxis that is colorful for first timers like me ! Just like Hyderabad, here also it was the fight for survival ! The taxi drivers did not have the modern mechanisms like power steering, etc. However the ease and tact with which they manouvered the heavy taxis would definitely belittle all the schumachers and alonsos ! The climate was totally humid and for the first time in several months I was sweating, sweating so hard as though the Ganges was flowing from my head. The river Ganga (Hooghly river) did not flow from my head, but it definitely was flowing beneath me when I was over the Howrah bridge. It was a feeling that was totally "meaningless" ! ;)) To be frank, Howrah bridge wasnt as grand as I was expecting. After 90 minutes of battle for survival in the streets of Cal, we were finally at Howrah junction. Wait a second ... the train was at platform 20 and we had just around 20 mins more ! During the search for platform 20, there was an overbridge that never seemed to end ! For a while I thought we would miss the train. With just 10 mins to go, we were finally standing besides the Gitanjali express. With rains pouring down, we had made it just in time on our onward journey to Jharsuguda.   Tanaya – “ Woh Kaun Thi?? ”   It was a day journey from Cal to Jharsuguda. The train passed through the famous places of Kharagpur (has the longest platform in the world !), Tatanagar (Jamshedpur), Rourkela, etc. We had to kill time ! Along with we had a Bengali couple in our bay who were travelling to Bombay. They were young and had the typical bengali looks. Along with them was Tanaya, a cute little girl, who barely managing to stand independently and who was still very much attached to her mother. She must have been around 1 year old and was very active during the entire journey. She was not bothered or worried by the strangers around and easily migled with us as well as others in the train. Tanaya's mother was particularly very expressive whenver she spoke about Tanaya. Very often, Tanaya would let off a cry which was an indication to her mother to get prepared to take care of her basic hunger needs. And each time her mother used to try to pacify her with the words "Oooi Baaaba " in a typical bengali style which would have made even the best of the sweets envious ! Bengali is truly a sweet language and I wouldnt mind trying my hands on Bengali if given a chance !    After around 8 hours of journey we reached Jharsuguda station at 2100 hrs approximately. It was a relatively small station, but being a junction handled a relatively heavy traffic. We were expecting a pick up till Belpahar. However since that did not happen, we had to hire a taxi to Belpahar. The entire distance was about 30 kms and it was a totally dark road. With only hope and the determination to fight it out if cornered, we took the risk and soon we hit the road to Belpahar. En route we crossed the L & T cement plant and also the Ib river, a branch of Mahanadi. After about 45 mins we saw the first signs that we were being taken to the proper destination ! The logo of Tat group were visible and we could see the welcome sign of "Tata Refractory Limited".  We were directly taken to "Tata house" where guests usually stayed. This was our base till we departed !    Tata House – In Competition with Parents!   The Tata house was the first stop and the place where we had the first interaction with the locals inb Belpahar. It had around 20 rooms of various sizes, a canteen that could accomodate around 30 people and around 5 people at any time who knew the art of taking care of the guests. Their smiling faces, the concern shown towards the guests and the care showered on us were unmatched and has no parallels ! During the breakfasts, lunch or dinner they used to keep serving rotis, and rice in a manner where you just cant refuse their offer ! I was reminded of the story of snow white and the dwarfs where the dwarfs took total care of snow white. Of course, we werent any relatives of snow white, nor were they dwarfs, but the attitude was well appreciated by one and all and was one of the highlights of the visit.   Let me talk about the food, a topic that I really like talking about. One of the major difference in the food there was the lack of spice and less amount of salt. Coming from South India where spice is a necessity rather than luxury, this was something that could be easily noticed. In fact one of my colleagues, who had stayed there for 2 weeks earlier, had to have a diet of rice and pickles only so that he could get back his taste buds in proper shape ! One of the food items for breakfast was " urlLink Chakuli ". To be frank, I expected something exotic, but what was served was plain "kal dosa" which was referred to as "Chakuli" in orissa. Another item worht mentioning was "Chanar Pravesh". This was served as dessert and was made from milk and very similar to "Rasmalai".  Apart from the Tata house, there was also the Tata club and the Tata Park. Belpahar is a small locality and has one major street where you get everything from vegetables to electronic items.This is the only place (a 100 metre stretch) where we could also get the mobile signals for Airtel and Idea services. Hence this was a spot that was frequently visited. A raliway gate served as the boundary beyond which the signals were not available ! Though my colleagues were able to get connected occassionally, I was the unfortunate one who always ended up getting the network busy message ! The street also has a Lord Krishna temple, whose architecture is typical Oriya style with cylindrical domes that reach out into the sky !    The Drive Down to Jharsuguda  After 2 days of hectic work, it was time to return back. It was the 14th of July, and it was also my star birthday ! Having totally forgotten about it, I ended up eating mutton and fish which was the first time that I violated the basic birthday code that I had followed right from my childhood days. This was bound to happen one day and it happened this year ! Without any regrets (I like to think it that way;) ) I packed my back and after visiting the Lord Krishna temple there I was on my way back to Jharsuguda raliway station.   Shivanchal Panda was the taxi driver on m journey back. He was a brahmin and was proud of the fact that he had married the lady whom he loved and that too without any hassles from both the families. His father had worked for the Hirakud dam , which was about 80 kms from Belpahar and had later moved to Belpahar. As for himself, he was a taxi driver right from his young days, and had travelled to places like Mumbai, Bangalore, Kerala, Tamil Nadu, etc.He often kept saying that the southern states were far more developed than his state and was aware that education was one of the major reasons. He took much pride in talking about a particular stretch of road on the highway that we were travelling in. This stretch was built by L&T and he claimed that once upon a time this was the best road in whole of India. The project was initiated by Biju Patnaik, whom he respected a lot, and was contracted to L & T. As per his story, Biju Patnaik had tol the constructors that once the road was completed, the amount would be paid only if the milkwalas were able to carry the pots of milk without spilling a drop of milk. Once the construction was completed, it seems this was tested out and there was no drop spilled !! The road from Belpahar to Jharsuguda passed through a jungle which was a haven for dacotis until 4 -5 years back. Now there is a police post for every kilometer which makes travelling during the nights more safe. Around 1 hour we talked about various topics from politics to Kerala to education to his life, etc. Finally with just 10 minutes for the train to arrive, we were at the Jharsuguda station. As soon as I entered the platform, in one of the chairs I found a pretty woman who had this beautiful round eyes, a glowing face and the typical Bengali looks. It was a perfect ending to the stay at Jharsuguda and a perfect beginning to the day ahead in Calcutta the next day !!    Kolkata – The City of Joy   It was the morning of 15th and the time was somewhere around 0520 hrs. Daylight was already shining through the landscape and I wondered if my watch had stopped ! Being in the eastern part of India, this is mainly due to a mismatch formed because of the single time standard being followed in India. Anyhow, I dint feel like sleeping just because the landscape was so green and beautiful and there was a light drizzle that added the shine to the atmosphere ! The paddy fields, the bushes, the coconut trees , etc were all so vibrant as though they were ready for action and were enthusiatic about being part of the new day ! After 2 hours of journey broken by the crossing of the electric trains, I could finally see the Howrah bridge. Soon I found myself searching for the prepaid taxi counter in the railway station. It was an ocean of yellow cars, all packed into one shed. The cars were almost struggling to get out of the shed. often the gaps between each cars would be in cms and it looked like the taxi drivers spent most of the time there shouting at others to get off their way ! Finally I was into one of those taxis. It was a yellow Premier Padmini taxi. Believe me, I never saw a yellow premier padmini taxi ever in Cal, so I think I was among the lucky few to have taken a ride through Cal in a bright yellow premier padmini ! I wanted to sit in the front, but the driver politely told me that the door in the front is not that strong and could fall out any moment !! Well, I dint want to take any chances ! :))   I was dropped at my destination - Hotel Rutt Deen. It is definitely not a place that I would visit again. Though they claimed to be of 5 star category, it was a very shady place and the room stinked badly of old linen ! Toilets werent maintained properly and there was just no AC !! But still the cost was high ! I was a victim of incorrect internet advertising ! "This was definitely not the place to stay for long", I thought to myself. It was better off taking a walk through the lanes of Cal !   Finally I was walking through the Park Street at 0900 hrs. There was another 5 hours for my flight to take off and hence decided to walk for around 2 hours. On enquiring I found that Victoria memorial was just 20 mins walk from the place where I stayed. All I had to do was walk straight down Park Street till it joins Chowringee Stree, take the left there and walk straight till it reaches a junction where you would find the sign board to Victoria Memorial. On the way, the crowd kept increasing and what an amazing crowd it was ! Bong females are really beautiful ! One of the main reasons of their beauty is their beautiful eyes, which are large enough to convey the expressions in total and to keep you glued to the eyes till eternity ! I dont think I ever saw a bong female that was not worth looking at :)) John Keats had mentioned that "A thing of beauty is a joy forever ! ". Calcutta was a city of beautiful people and no wonder it was rightly called "The City of Joy" !   Finally I was walking towards the Victoria Memorial, its reflection on the nearby lake being disturbed by the gentle ripples caused by the monsoon breeze. Against the backdrop of the dark monsoon clouds, the building was a majestic piece whose grandeur would face no competition in the years to come. The lawns were well maintained and it was a place where you could relax and forget all the tensions of the material world. From Victoria Memorial I decided to walk around the golf course / park, and in the process also saw the Hooghly bridge (Vidyasagar Sethu) and the Eden Gardens stadium. The park was located at the center of Calcutta and you could find various football teams discussing and practising the final tactics before taking a break for the oncoming monsoon to sing over Cal.   With 2 hours of good walking, what else could be in your mind ? It was time to search for FOOOOOOD ! I wanted real good bengali stuff and the best hotel in Cal that served Bengali food was Aheli restaurant in the Peerless Inn Hotel. Unfortunately it was closed and would open only at 1230. The time was just 1100 hrs. I did not want to give up. When I reached my hotel, I found that there was another restaurant called "Suruchi" that was being run by All Bengali Womens Union. This was just a km from the place where I stayed and I tool the McLeod road to reach the Elliot road where this hotel was located.   The hotel was open from 1030 for lunch and I was lucky enough to find a restaurant open for lunch so early ! I wanted good Bengali fish based lunch and this was conveyed to the incharge there. Soon, I was served with a bowl of rice and " urlLink Rui Fish Curry ". This went on well with the rice. Though the spices werent as extravagant as in Kerala dishes, it had a different taste mainly promoted by the mustard that is regularly used in bengali dishes. I also had a fish fry (some Jhal) which was cooked really well so as to really excite the taste buds. Having had a sumptuous meal, it was time to catch my flight on my way back to Hyderabad. The flight was without any incidents except for very minor turbulences immediately after take off. The flight was even more exciting because of Hita, the air hostess who accompanied us on our way back to Hyderabad and also because of the good lunch served on the flight. With a truck load of memories, I landed in Hyderabad on July 15th at 1630 hrs to get back into the crowded life of mine !   Signing off ... K.V.Sathish Babu        
      
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      There have been many memorable moments, but three events stand out in my memories as far as organizing the events are concerned. In chronological order, the first event was “Liscar 96” which was an inter school contest conducted in our school. We had just passed out of school and being the immediate we were part of the organizing committee. It was a big hit, had its own bit of controversy, its share of fun, learning, etc. The way we resolved the winners for the tightly contested dance competition after hectic discussions, the manner in which the girls from Alvernia school protested to us that we were partial, the sight of a contestant and her brother protesting that we had no sense of music after we had announced the winners for the solo music competition, etc are all fresh and are memories that would remain as long as the air flows through my lungs. The second event was the sequence of events, preparation and effort leading to Nexus ’99, the National Level Technical Symposium conducted by our department in my college. This one obviously is the best event that I have been part of. The memories related to this event are so vast that I may have to write a book rather than just blog !!   The third event is of course the Bali Trail (held of June 29th and 30th, 2004) in my organization. This was a quiz event were the contestants would be taken to various places of interest around the globe depending on their answers and choices. The teams are supposed to collect certain clues en route to Bali. The first team to reach Bali and submit the key (based on the clues) would be the winner. In the first week of June, we were approached to do a quiz event with a difference for Baanquet. Though I wanted to do a Rapid fire quiz, during the course of the discussions, our thoughts and ideas were leading to organizing a trail. The idea originated from a discussion about the Carmen game that was popular during the DOS days!   There were two main parts of the trail – (1) Tracking each teams trail and displaying the same on the screen, (2) questions for each stop on the trail. The first part had to be done using power point and being a self-proclaimed expert in power point presentations, I agreed to take that responsibility. But somehow I was not comfortable with this. Certain events during Nexus ’99 had made me decide then not to get involved in such activities in future. This time something kept telling me that I was doing exactly what I wanted to avoid. Many times I just dint want to take this forward and wanted to just give it up and lead the silent life focusing more on work than on other activities. But the efforts, enthusiasm, and nervousness of my quiz partner didn’t allow me to go back. As far as this specific quiz is concerned, lots of credit goes to her as she did a great job that was totally contrary to my expectations. In the days leading to the quiz, she was so nervous that at times it seemed that she dint know what she was doing. Most of the time her expressions spoke more than she could ! But in the finals, she did a marvelous job.   When preparing the PPT, the first thing that struck me was the mainframe screen and the typical computer screens of Hollywood movies. Also of special significance were the screens from Matrix movie in which you would find a black screen with green alphabets falling all around. With the real estate on the screen divided and allocated for specific purposes, it was time to put in the content. But suddenly there was a bombshell. My partner wanted one more branching and all of a sudden the number of presentations that I had to make increased from 16 to 81!! “Man! That is some more work!” I thought to myself. I could feel the fumes coming out of my ear. There were two periods when I had to put in lot of extra effort – first was for preparing the 80 presentations and second was for pumping the trivia in for each place.    urlLink      A Screen shot from "The Bali Trail"    During the entire course of the preparation I was sure that the presentation could be prepared in advance. But what worried me later was that during the trials, the presentation wasn’t as smooth as expected. I was doing lots of mistakes in swapping, selection, etc. After the trials on the day before the finals, I was a bit worried. Any goof-up on my part would make the entire effort look worthless. Apart from my effort, it would also take up the shine from the questions that had been prepared by my partner by burning the midnight oil. I also had a history baggage wherein all the events that I have been part of weren’t flawless! I was a bit worried and could feel the hairs turn grey with worry!   The finals had surprises in store for me. When the first slide was projected, the screen layout was looking much more beautiful than I had expected. From the experience of previous trials, we had taken some precautions and had modified and fine-tuned the way we wanted to approach and take the contestants through the finals. All through the way, the progress was smooth. Except for a minor blip the entire show went on flawlessly. I also realized that I could have avoided the trivia part. This was because the audience was more involved in the heat and speed of the finals than on the trivia section. Probably a picture of mine would have been a better replacement. I am not sure which of the two people would have liked to ignore the most!!   It definitely was the first time something (event organizing) went on flawlessly and it definitely found its way to being one of the most memorable events that I was part of (as far as organizing was concerned). However Nexus ’99 would still remain the best event that I was part of especially because of the scale of the event and because of the efforts that we had put and because of the amount of learning that I was subjecting myself to ! The next question that obviously comes to my mind is … “Will I do it again, if opportunity knocks once more?” Probably not! Probably never!   Exceptions should not get generalized!    
      
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Its my Birthday tomorrow ! The collage of Garfield strips brings out my feelings on the eve of my Birthday ! 
      
</post>


<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      “Shruthi” in carnatic music means “melody”, the musical pitch that imparts the melody. Basically the very substance or life of music lies in its shruthi. No folks, this is not a story about Carnatic music but it is basically a travelogue of Ajit's life as he travels through the self imposed obstacles of life is his search for Shruthi - his life ! Finally does he get the Shruthi of his life? This travelogue will take you right there !    Presenting Ajit !    Ajit, the main character of this story, popularly known among his friends as “Atom Shot”. Just like his character the origins of his name is also a mystery. But the most often talked about origin of his name dates back to the good old college days when during the course of gathering materials for an assignment he stumbled upon a story “Atom Shot - The Hero of Endless Space” by Rob Dudwood, in a particular school website. He had hyped the story among his friend and in return they gifted him the name “Atom Shot”. Times flew by and lile most of his fellow Indians,Ajit was also absorbed into the booming field of softwares and projects ! Though belonging to a hitech world he is always boged down by the feeling of being like an adolescent most of the time, being neither orthodox nor modern, neither village bred nor city bred, neither here nor there, always in search of something! Probably that is why he has left behind a trail in search of Shruthi !    But who is Shruthi ?  Shruthi, Shruthi, Shruthi. I have referred to "Shruthi" so many times that you must be wondering " Who the hell is Shruthi ??? ".    "Is she a damsel, a tropican beauty, a babe, the love of Ajit's life, his girl friend, crush, wife, sister, ..."   A beautiful word that provides the much needed positive energy in a stressful and surcharged environment. Shruthi is a word that provides melody to Ajit's soul at times of distress and varying emotions. Shruthi, the word that he would love to die for! Somehow or the other he has had the fascination for this word right from his childhood. Shruthi does not refer to a specific person. During the course of the trail you would find Shruthi taking various forms, shapes, etc. (Did I say shapes ?? :) ) Shruthi is the trail and the trail is for Shruthi!    Oops ! I have been so busy trying to give you guys an sneak preview into the life of Ajit that I almost forgot that Ajit has to catch a train to his native town ! I need to get to him as soon as possible so that I can travel along with him and take you through the journey of his life.   Catch you soon !   
    
</post>


</Blog>