<Blog>

<date>19,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      OMG, I only really clean my apartment when my Mom comes to visit and man am I TIRED!
     

    
</post>

<date>18,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      My membership class at church participated in a good friday service at church today.  It was really neat.  I wasn't that nervous.  Since I've been sober, it's a lot easier to do things that really used to freak me out.  I would be shaking I was so gripped in fear.  I couldn't keep the event in perspective.  It would grow huge in my head and then when it was over, I was like, that wasn't that big a deal.  The service was sort of a pagent reinacting the crucifiction of Christ.  It was a pretty powerful service.  I was a disciple and had a few speaking lines.  I was joking that maybe I would be discovered and that this could be my big break.  It feels so good to be back involved in a church.   And the fact that it is a gay church is really cool.  It is so powerful to be in a place where I am totally loved and accepted exactly the way I am.  George B. came but Ray couldn't make it.   He's helping with a big circuit party this evening.  I think it's an interesting contrast between how we each are spending our Easter Weekends.    Ray and I went to Meteor last night for a bit.  I really can't go hang out there for long and stay sober.  I see people I used to party with and I could easily fall right back into that scene.  It was fun some of the time.  My problem was when everyone else was stoping partying and getting ready to go back to work Monday morning, my party continued.  Stopping was never part of my MO.  I would go until I was exhausted and couldn't get high any more.  But usually I ran out of funds long before that happened.  It really sux to be a poor drug addict.  Sheri and I went to the MFA this afternoon.  It was great.  Amazing exhibit from Paris.  I loved this one Cezanne of male bathers.  Delish!  Now that is art!  Sat out on the patio at Cafe Express and had coffee and bread pudding.  Good Times!  Headed to a meeting tonight with Lamar and then back over to Ray's for dessert with his sister and her partner.    I've got to clean my apartment.  Mom will be here at about 4pm tomorrow night!  Jeeze!
     

    
</post>

<date>16,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      The CMA meeting rocked this evening.  There were only 5 of us but it was cool cuz we could all talk without worrying about saying anything too gay infront of the rehab kids.  It's cool if they come and it was cool to have them not come.   
     

    
</post>

<date>16,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      OMG, what a day.  Work was pretty fun.  We had protesters out in front of the hotel. It was kind of a carnival like atmosphere out there.  Abdalla, one of our bellman was so excited.  I guess they don't protest Coke in Egypt.  He thought it was really cool.  I found out my co-worker Konni isn't working with us anymore and that really has bummed me out.  She is such a groovy person.  I didn't find out what happened, I was just told she was gone.  I left her a voice-mail but I haven't heard from her yet.    I'm headed to a CMA meeting tonight.  This is the first Crystal Meth meeting in Houston.  It's a really small meeting but it's usually a really good meeting.    I'm sitting here with my cat Maximus in between my arms while I type.  It's not making it real easy to type but he's my baby and he gets lonesome during the day so I'm happy to bond for a bit.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Got to drive Ray's new convertible last night.  The weather was stunning.  Sheri and I did some arranging in her house and she gave me a rug for my living room.  It's dirty but it looks pretty good.  I'm praying for Mary.  I think she's really going through some hard times right now.  She has got to get a job and I hope she can become a more loving person.  She's very giving but lives in a really mean place up in her mind.  Went to a good meeting last night at Lambda.  Gave Michael a ride and we had a good talk on the way over.  Was nice to talk to someone about how crazy the Jungle weekend made me.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I worked, came home, chatted with Sheri in the courtyard and then took a nap.  Woke up a little late to pick Mark up at the airport.  Thank God for the tollway.  We went to dinner and then back to his place to watch Madonna on Will & Grace.  OMG, it was pretty good.  Anyway, Ray got a new car today.  This completes the midlife crisis mode.  I'm off to bed.....nite, nite.....
     

    
</post>

<date>21,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well, well, another day.  Today is my last day off before starting my week.  I have my I-Group tonight and I'm still freaked out at the prospect of going.  Not sure why but I just am.  Went to the nooner today and it was pretty good.  Realized that I'm really broke and am not quite sure how I'm going to finance this upcoming trip to California.  I would like to back out but I guess that would be a pretty crappy thing to do to Mark.  Still feeling sad today.  Mary and I went to Half-price books this morning and she turned in some books for cash.  We also hit Randalls and got some groceries.  I'm pretty ready for the week.  My house is clean, laundry is done, I'm rested and ready to go!  Woohoo!  As long as I live through tonights session I guess I'll survive.  I gotta finish up the crazy fourth step and get one with my step work!  I need to pray about that.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Ok well, I'm now a member of Bering Methodist.  I really love that church.  Mom came with me to church this morning to support me.  It's really hard for some reason for me to intigrate my Mother into my life.  I've spent so many years protecting her from the rest of my life that the old alarm bells still ring when the people from different areas in my life begin to mix.  It's so strange.  Mom is pretty hip and can hang with most crowds.  We went to brunch at Sambuca together and that was really fun.  The food was excellent.    Mom and I went over to my neighbor Sheri's place to say hi.  I wanted Mom to see her apt.  It's a pretty cool place.  Now I'm just kind of sad.  I'm not sure why.  I know when the weather is like this that I get down.  I can't think of any reason to really be sad.  I guess I need a meeting and to get out and about.  Helping Ray yesterday get ready for the circuit party was strange.  It really put me in a strange place mentally.  I was listening to club music cleaning my apartment and part of me longed to be able to dress up, go out and cruise hot boys and party all night.  I'm jealous that some people can go out and do all that and still go to work on Monday morning.  Work always interferred with my partying.    I'm so lucky!  I've got a really great life, a cool apartment, great car, good friends and the coolest cat a boy could ask for.  How on earth could I be depressed.  What a goof ball.  Human nature I guess.  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Wow, did I have wild dreams last night.    Mom and I ate dinner at Backstreet Cafe on the patio and the weather was perfect.  We had the best meal!  There was a blond door host who I couldn't help but obsess about.  It's so tacky to cruise boys while at dinner with your mother!  =)  We then came home and watched the movie Four Feathers.  That was really good.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm so crazy today.  Lori gave me my review.  It was a great review but then I told her I wanted to get my realestate liscense and eventually leave FS.  She said she was supportive but I know that it had to bum her out a bit.  It made me kind of crazy too.  My Richey interaction was good!  Thank goodness.  This afternoon, I went to the Galleria and got some things at the Gap and at Oshmans.  I then ran to the 8pm meeting and ended up getting nominated to lead it in May.   That sux.  I should have said that I couldn't do it as I have 3 conflicts next month on Tuesdays.  I'm so freakin nutz tonight.  It's Mark D's Birthday today.  Left him a goofy voice-mail.  I've got to get him some sort of gift for Friday.  I'm going to bed...
     

    
</post>

<date>27,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Wow, what an incredible day.  I got up after Max absolutely would not let me sleep any longer.  I ate some cherios and went Rollerblading.  The weather was perfect!  I bladed by the Musuems and around the neighborhood.  Then I went to church.  I sat with Charles and afterwards was going to go to lunch with Anthony but on the way to lunch, I got a call from Shariq who had 3 free tix to Mama Mia for the 2pm show.  I called Deaton and the three of us blazed over to the Hobby Center. When we got there we ran in Artista and ordered dessert for intermission.  We had 8th row center seats and the show was fluff but was fun.  Many cute boys in the show.  Love those dancer boys!  OMG.   Dessert at intermission was devine!  It's the only "civilized" way to spend intermission....LOL.  Anyway, after the show I had a message from Ray that he wanted to drive down to the beach!  I got home and we left almost immediately for Galveston.  We went to the gay beach and threw my vortex football thing and had a great time.  Then we drove over to this gourmet hamburger joint overlooking the gulf and had dinner.  Wow, it was really good times.  As we left we could see some folks having sex inside their hotel room.  That was quite a show.  Drove home and George arrived early so I called Mary to open up my apartment for the QAF viewing party.  Andrew joined us and it was a great time.  I'm now so pooped that I'm going to sleep like a brick.  I am so blessed!  What an amazing life I have been given.  I'm overwhelmed with all my blessings.  
     

    
</post>

<date>07,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Wow, what a great trip so far in SoCal.  Checked into FS LA today and it's in an incredible location.  We are just blocks from the bars in West Hollywood.  We went to a cool coffee bar called the Abbey and then to an AA meeting at the Gay Community Center.  It was a really good meeting in a beautiful center.  We then went to dinner at Eat Wells and had a really cute waiter. From their we went to see Jimmy James do a show at this place called Vermont.  Bubba McNeilly was his sound guy so we got to talk to them for a while afterwards.  There were lots of cool people there too.  Some chick from Six Feet Under and the Asian guy from Sixteen Candles.  Deaton met the lighting guy and they really hit it off.  Bubba is so sweet.  He wanted us to meet them out at this club but I'm not really up for that much of a scene on a Tuesday night.  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm feeling really crazy lately.  So much is going on in the peoples lives around me that I feel a little overwhelmed.  I just want to hide out for a while!
     

    
</post>

<date>14,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Wow, got back from my trip and went up to Mom's.  Gave her a DVD player.  Probably not really that exciting a gift for her.  Didn't realize I was so cheap on her birtheday so decided to splurge a little on Mother's Day.  She cooked some REALLY good food.  Went to brunch with Jim at the hotel.  Was very nice.  Good thing for me cuz Jim paid.  Whew!  Had a nice night at home and slept like a baby.  I always sleep so good at home.  It is so beautiful out at the lake.  I forget to appreciate the view.  Everyone I talk to lately has been crazy.  George has drama, Ray has drama, Brian Peterson got fired.  Mary's loosing her unemployment, Lori had a car accident....I'm afraid to leave the house or to talk to anyone.  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well, my life is really cooking lately.  It looks like I'll be the next President of the Concierge Association.  I can't believe I'm getting into this.  I pray that it is a good experience.  I've never really done anything like this before and so I'm a litte scared of the responsibility.  I want everything to be perfect and wonderful and my experience with the assoc. is that rarely happens.  Kelly came over and cleaned my apartment.  He wrote me a poem and it was really sweet.  He really seems to be getting the program this time around.  It's about time to begin my realestate classes and I'm wondering how to keep all my balls in the air.  Job, classes, program and HCA.  It's gonna be a busy year!
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      This whole thing with Ray is making me think he's gonna drop me as a friend.  I'm not sure why I feel that way.  I guess I feel that he's gonna get a new set of friends now that he's gonna make lots of money with his sister.  
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well, Larry Sullivan emailed me back today!  That's very cool.  He's such a cool guy.  Anyway, I'm such a goof for giving it this much thought.  James in San Deigo confided in me that he's got a problem with Meth.  I'm so not sure what to tell him.   Max and I stayed in tonight and watched "Far from Heaven"  I think Julianne Moore is my favorite actress of all time!  I just loved this movie.  Max is lying on my desk next to me sleeping.  He's such a sweetie.  Had a good therapy session with Ms. Ledger today.  Talked about my fear that keeps me from connecting with other people.  It felt so good to just stay in tonight!  I'm really pooped.  I'm so freaked out thinking about how Derrick might react to Larry telling him he met me.  I hope Derrick isn't mean about it although he sure has a right to be if he wants I suppose.  It felt so good to cry a little tonight watching the movie.  I really need a good cry now and then!
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I met Larry Sullivan tonight!  He is so charismatic!  He knows Derrick so that kind of freaked me out.  Brought back all sorts of strange feelings.  He talked about his movie "The Trip"  It was really good.  They had a hula boy on the dash of their car just like mine!  Thought that was cool.  Steve K. was there and it was great to see him.  Ray found out that his sister got the contract.  I'm so excited for Ray!  I'm scared that he's gonna change and I'm gonna loose a good friend.  I'm really bummed about that!  It felt different when he told me about the $$ his sister is coming into.  I have such a mental complex about all that stuff.  Larry recognized me from the hotel when I was sitting at the movie so that was very flattering!  He's so hot!  I'm so attracted to actors and people on stage!  It's just so attractive.  Hope he comes to say hi tomorrow at the hotel!
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm headed to the HCA meeting where I'll probably be elected President of the Association.  I think I'll do a great job but I've had so many bad experiences in the past that it's kind of freaking me out.  Guy Y. has been a champ in organizing things.   I really pray that things go smoothly in the transition and that we can take the organization in a new direction.  I had a great day at Mom's yesterday and today.  On Memorial Day Jim grilled ribs and Mom cooked lots of good food.  We ate and slept and watched Moonlight Mile.  Love Jake Gillenhaal.  He's dreamy!  Got up this morning and Ray made french toast for Mom using Potatoe Bread.  It was great!  More sleeping.  Finally he and I drove home this afternoon and now I'm loving on Max some before leaving for the HCA meeting.  I hope this is the right decision!  I will really have to stay in a lot of prayer to deal with some of these folks.  
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, I'm off to realestate school this morning!  It feel good to get this ball rolling!
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Day before yesterday, Walter Amen called me about a house up in the Heights that was listing for 89K and he thought it might be a good place for me.  I called the banker at BofA and was told that my credit score is a 590 and I need to be a 625 to be considered.  That kind of bummed me out so now I've got to decide if I should ask my folks for help or if I should just wait.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      What an amazing day I had yesterday!  The Supreme Court overturned the Texas Sodomy law and it was a wonderful way to start the day!  Deaton and I then went on the Rosenquist tour at MFA and it was wonderful.  Had two amazing pieces of Aids with a doll covered in cellophane and one of a handgun.  Very impressive HUGE works of art.  We ate lunch at Hungry's (cute little Greek waitor too)  and then had an Argitinian meringue dessert at Cafe Europe with Manuel from DeVille.  It was good to see him.  We then went to his place and watched the season finale of QAF and a Simpson's episode where Homer moves in with two gay guys.  It was one of the best episodes I've seen.  We then went to City Hall for a big rally in response to the Supreme Court decision.  It was a wonderful feeling to be there.  I was called be several folks to tell me that I was on Channel 11 on last nights news.   Topped off the evening with the MCC NA meeting and it also was wonderful.  I was really feeling crazy and then was asked to share.  I really needed to share to make me feel a part of that meeting.  I felt like an outsider and sharing brought me into the fold.  My life is amazing right now. 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Tomorrow is my first Business Meeting.  I feel really good about it.  I'm going to say my prayers and get a good night's sleep.  Mayor Brown will be there to kick things off.  Jeeze, what a way to start the year!  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Where have I been?  Busy boy I guess.  Dad and I spent the best day ever yesterday.  He came with me to Bering church.  It was an incredible joy to have him there.  I felt so complete having him there.  I'm so lucky.  We then went to Dharma Cafe for brunch and to see a chinese movie called Together.  It was wonderful story about a boy and his father.  We then came back to my place and hung out with Max for a bit.  I was almost in tears the whole time we were in church together.  I think they were tears of joy.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm kind of freaking out this morning.  I was a little crazy with Walter on the phone talking about mortgage people.  I really need to get a grip but mostly just really need a meeting.  I worked last night on the 4th and that was kind of a bummer but I'm just glad to have a job period.  George bounced a check to me so I spend some time on the phone with Wells Fargo this morning discussing that.  Feeling a little crazy with all this house purchase stuff coming to a head this week.  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Just had a great lunch with Alice and Sheri at Boulevard Bistro.  It was Alice's Birthday.  She's so cool.  I'm off to work for my PM shift.  Gonna grab a sugar free Red Bull on the way.  Last time that really kept me going until midnight.  =)
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Met Walter at his office this morning and we made an offer on the house.  I was hanging out with Steve, Sheri and Toups this afternoon and I sure will miss this place if I get the house.  It would be so fun to work on a place that was mine!  I have to leave this up to God and my Dad.  =)
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Great day.  Worked until about 4:30pm and then headed over to the house to meet the inspector.  Found some things wrong but nothing big.  I'm getting excited.  I think I could make the place really cool.  Not as cool as my apartment but it's gonna be a great investment.  Walter thinkgs that within 2 years i will have been living there for free with the rise in property values.  I hope so.  It's gonna be fun to fix it up.  Went to good meeting at Lambda.  Met a cute boy named Colt but he only has 15 minutes of sobriety so oh well.  Took Kelly to the meeting.  He's having a tough time.  Hope he makes it.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Not really freaking out any more.  I'm pretty excited about the house.  I'm doing some great footwork even if I don't get this house.  Cleaned up with several creditors so my credit is about to get much better.  I figure if I move in and don't have much money at least if I've got good credit I can get a Lowes and Hope Depot card.  Walter is being kind of a goof and I'm getting a little "over" his educational angle with everything.  I know working at FS I get skewed thinking people need to be more customer service oriented.  Anyway.  Went to a good CMA meeting last night.  Met Kelly before hand and took him to coffee and then to the meeting.  I hope he makes it.  He needs to get off his ass and get some community Service done or he's gonna end up in the clink.  I'm excited that I'm going to finance a house on my own and without Dad.  It's cool that he gets full credit for being willing to help and then doesn't have to.  That is good stuff.  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Church this morning reminded me of sitting with Lena and Mason.  I have so many wonderful angels watching over me.  All my Grandparents, Uncle Bruce even Toby.  I have to remember that when times get tough and the doubts get the better of me!
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm so going to miss my apartment.  I'm really scarred and excited to move.  It's so safe and comfortable here surrounded by people I know and love.  Max is totally content and at home.  I've got to take a leap of faith and trust that this is the right thing to do.  I can't rent forever!  Who knows what doors will open when I get up to the heights!  I have to pray for the strength to be brave!  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Got my results back and had a viral load for the first time since I went on the meds.  That's kind of freaking me out.  I guess I'll wait and see if it was a fluke or if I goofed up by switching meds.  My HCV actualy went down on it's own.  I think my regiments of supliments may be paying off.  I try to be really strict with my meds, but maybe I'm not being strict enough.  Headed to dinner with George @ Pei Wei diner and then to see Seabiscuit.   Can't wait to see that movie.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Got my appraisal info today!!  Yeah!  90K What a gift!  Met Walter at the house and decided to put up gutters.  I cut some of the overbrush and it looks much better.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Went to Galveston today and ate a burger at the Spot.  I'm still stuffed.  Went and looked at cars with Deaton.  That was kind of fun.  I'm leading the meeting tonight at CMA and I hope I remember to get a new leader for next month.  The house thing is plugging along.  I've got to keep a grip on my spending.  If my folks don't help me I'm gonna be in bad shape.  Guess I'll have to ask them for help at some point.  They can't read my mind.   Or can they?
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well, the house keep plugging along.  So I go  by the house and they guy took the porch swing.  How cheap is that?  What a dork.  I'm not going to be a sympathetic when it comes to the repairs now.  Anyway, I've been having a blast hitting all the big discount stores.  Spent Saturday night going to Conns outlet, walmart, lowes and home depot and Super Target.  Good Times.  Found some cool stuff.  Not sure what color to get in appliances.  They guy took the swing.  Jeeeze.  Anyway.  Kelly L led a good meeting tonight.  It was really nice and she kept it real.  I always appreciate buck naked honesty in meetings.   That is what really keeps me sober.  I know I've got to start working with a sponsor.  I think I need to interview Lloyd.  He's really got what I want I think.  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Best sober birthday I've ever had.  Woke up this morning and went to breakfast with Ray at Barnaby's.  The waiter was cruising me hard and that's always nice.  Then we went up to the house and he had all sorts of ideas for the yard.  Then I hit the 11:30am Saturday meeting and picked up a chip.  Went with Steve P, Brad, Kelly, Michael and myself to El Tiempo for lunch.  That was fun too!  Then we went home and got ready to head to Texas City to a beach bonfire NA meeting.  Played Volleyball all afternoon.  Meeting was good and the weather was perfect!  I've not had that much fun in a long time.  I'm going to sleep like a baby.  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I had a mild melt down this afternoon.  Work was crazy and then when I left work, Walter and I had a heated conversation and I was in tears when I got off the phone.  Things are going prettywell, but it was just more than I could take in one day.  Max and I are chilling out tonight and are about to watch a movie.  Ray and I are going to breakfast in the morning.  That will be nice.  Tomorrow is 2 years sober.  YEAH!
     

    
</post>

<date>31,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Yesterday I was shot out of a cannon.  Ran around like crazy after work trying to pay off bills and get things in order for the closing.  Walter is sort of a mess.  He calls and says tomorrow is the deadline and is mad at me because he's been slacking.  Jeeze dude.  Bless his heart.  Led a great CMA meeting last night.   This guy Danny asked me to be his sponsor.  I'll have to give some thought in how to proceed with that.  Kelly told his story and it was wonderful.  He has a powerful story.  The group really reacted to it!  Many folks there with very little clean time.  Great meeting.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm stressing out tonight.  Got a call from John Dorrance and I need to clear up another collections account and the settled accounts possibly aren't good enough.  Jeeze.  I'm going to move in completely broke.  I wish my Dad would come through with some cash.  I shared tonight about Casey leaving me a message and how that has been making me crazy.  I really needed to get that off my chest.  Deaton bought a new car today.  It's really pretty.  I'm excited for him.  He still sounds like he's full of shit when he shares but I guess that won't change.  I don't ever hear any buck naked honesty or maybe he really is that healthy.  He's sure proud of himself for sponsoring JP.  What an ego trip that has been for him.  Talks about it nonstop.  I've totally cashed out my mutual funds and that feels sort of scarry.  I'm really in this deal and it's scarry to be so close to the edge with no safety net.  I've got to get a part-time job.  I need to get off my ass and call the Texans.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Finally got the last paperwork for the loan.  John will fax it all off in the morning.  Praise Jesus!  Kelly led a good CMA meeting tonight.  Bobby Glascock was there and asked me to be a temporary sponsor.  I've got to figure out what to do first!  Jeeze.  Gonna go out and get a book tomorrow!  Don't have a day off until I move.  That sux.  Never a dull moment.  Life is really good.  Gonna pray to ask for willingness to move on with my program!  Need to ask Lloyd to be my sponsor.  Need to pray about this.  Mom is coming back from Galveston with Jim tomorrow.  I'm so glad she's having a good time!  She's a neat lady!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Mom is coming today and we're going to pick paint colors and then head to Galveston to spend the night.  I pray that I can be loving and kind to her throughout her stay.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Good day at work.   Got a lot done.  This afternoon, went by and picked up Kelly after work and came by the house for a bit to play with Max.  Tiffany came over and we all ate the chocolates from NO.  Glad to get rid of them.  Kelly and I then drove up to the house and finished the living room.  It looks great.  Went to eat at Someburger and it was good.  Had a nice talk sitting out under the tree at the picnic table.  Came home and am trying to pack a little bit.  Then gonna crash.  Close tomorrow at about 3pm.  Yikes!  Finally, then we have the big social at Gremillion Fine Art.  Can't wait to get this over with.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Just returned from am amazing weekend in NO.  I love that city.  The French Quarter was enchanting.  Love those cajun boys too!  Anyway, stayed at the Fairmont which was beautiful.  The first night we ate at the Rib Room.  Met this crazy old dancer named Chris Owens.  She has her own show on Bourbon Street.  She's like 75 years old.  Crazy.  I ate Prime Rib and it was one of the best pieces of meat I've ever tasted.  Rosie Fitch was the hostess for NO and she was amazing.  What a cool lady.  I then walked around a bit on Bourbon Street and then crashed.  The next morning we went to a hotel and had our meeting.  This professor talked and then we gave short speeches and ended with Jeanne from Vegas giving an update on LCD congress.  Ted Duchan was also there and it was good to see him.  We got Rosie a GC for the Spa at the Ritz and presented it to her at the end of the program.  I think she's going to really enjoy it!  Then went to lunch at the Gumbo Room?  Really good food.  Ate gumbo, red beans and rice and all sort of other stuff.  Had ice cream with prailene sauce and it was incredible.  Then went to the D-Day Museum.  It was very moving.  I want to read about Grandpa's experiences in the war.  Wish I had asked him to tell me stories about the war.  I was really moved by the incredible sacrifices made for me so that I may live such a wonderful life.  Then went back to the hotel and crashed for a bit.  Had a reception at this place called Sbisa.  It was very fun and nice.  After that I left and went to the Side Pocket.  Met a cute dancer named Alex, Sky and Matt.  Matt was a cute blond from Biloxi.  Alex was a latino artist and Sky just had a big cajun dick.  Liked Sky the best.  He told me to meet him at the Bourbon Pub after 2am but I knew that wasn't happening.  Kinda wish I had.  Anyway, went back to hotel and slept until about 5am.  Got up and went to Club NO.  Cool place but kind of a tragic crowd.  Left and went to Cafe du Monde.  Ate Beignets and oj and it was delish.  Wandered to St. Louis Cathederal and accidentally got in on about 45 min of Catholic Mass.  Music was very good and message was also interesting.  Went back to hotel and slept for another hour and then met Steve in the lobby to go to Jazz Brunch.  Ate at the cool place called the Cour of two Sisters.  It's been in biz for over 100 years.  Incredible courtyard in back covered in flowering vines.  Amazing place and huge buffet and live Jazz Band playing.  Really cool.  Then we took some pics and cruised.  Patsy and I had a great ride back.  She's such a neat lady.  It was so nice having someone to talk to.  Nice to be home.  Kind of time to freak out at the fact that in less than a week I've got to be moved into another house!  Yikes!
     

    
</post>

<date>26,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Today, Kelly and I put of the porch fan and worked out in the yard some more.  I dug up all the old Lantana on the side and started to get the ground ready to move Azalea's into those beds.  The old owner had some pretty good plants here so I am grateful for that!  It's realy hot right now so Kelly and I are going to chill out for a bit inside.  Max has been enjoying his newly located window perch.  He can look at the neighbors comings and goings and he even seems to enjoy taunting the two dogs next door.  He seems to be adjusting well.  Last night Kelly and I ordered a Pizza and it tasted great!  I was really tired and slept like a baby.  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Yesterday, Ray, Kelly and I worked like crazy in the yard.  Ray bought all sorts of stuff as a housewarming gift.  Even a great outdoor ceiling fan for the porch.  We dug up the front flowerbeds and rearranged some plants and trimmed out all the overgrown growth.  We got a lot done!  We planted some new bushes and dropped chips in the beds.  It looked great when we finished.  We were all really tired.  I think I should have bought stock in Lowes before this home purchase.  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I've moved!   Holly Cow....what just happened.  In a flash everything I owned was moved to another place.  Tough to navigate all the emotions.  Very sad to leave my old apt and very exciting and a little scarry to move here.  Mary's movers were amazing.  Great guys.  Mary came over with me and help me supervise the unload.  I didn't have anyone else lined up to help as the movers did everything.  Felt a little lonely from time to time.  My main concern is that Max get comfortable here ASAP.  I think he's gonna be ok.   I'm overwhelmed with all the boxes and stuff to unpack.  I wish I had been able to clean this house really good before I moved in.  The kitchen is filthy and I don't want to unpack stuff until the cupboards are at least wiped down.  Max has been sticking close to me last night and tonight.  He knew something was up.  Tons of visitors yesterday.  Mark D. and Brad came over along with Kelly's folks.  That was an interesting combo.  Then Ddavid came over and talked and talked.  Everyone has good info but it get's to be a little much over and over.  George came by last night and so did Jeff P.  I'm so glad to have some nice neighbors.  The elderly woman accross the street is the "neighborhood watch" person.  She knows everything going on.  Well, I'm off to the old apartment to get a few more things.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      You'd think a parent would be source of strength but NOT in my family.  I'm the one Mom leans on and man it feels creepy and lonely.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well, Mom left in the middle of the night allergic to my sofa.  Mark D. brought a gift for her to breakfast.  I really wish he could have met her.  Then she calls later crying about selling the house and not having anyone to talk to about it.  When I call her I don't say the right things and she turns into her normal crazy bitch from hell self.  Not sure what that is all about.  She's nutz.  I just have to love her in spite of it.  I'm really having a tough time.  I've got no one to turn to right now.  Mark is all up his bf's ass and I don't have a sponsor and I got rid of michaely Ledger.  I really need to get up some courage to ask someone to sponsor me.  I'm afraid to ask anyone because I don't feel worthy of their time.  Is that some crazy stuff or what?  It's the way I feel.  I also probably don't want to have to do any work.  I'm really in a pickle right now.  I better get into some action or I'm gonna fall hard.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well, it's been a while.....getting settled in the new house and have been neglecting my program.  It's strange that the reason I have so many blessings is the program and yet I resist dedicating my life to it.  What am I so afraid of?  I need a kick in the ass and I don't want it to be a relapse.  I'm off till Thursday so maybe I'll get off my duff and ask for help.  Mom is almost here and we're going to decorate and plan the rest of the house.  I think she's going to really enjoy what Ray Kelly and I have accomplished.  I pray that I can be loving to her during her visit!  I haven't been to enough meetings and maybe I'll take her to one today!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Had a really nice day off today.  Went to have blood drawn and then went to Lobo to hang with the boys.  Raymond is so cute and Ryan Z was there and it was good to see him.  I had a soy latte and it was delish.   Mathew was working there too.  He's cute but crazy.  Went then to the nooner.  Mark D. was leading it and it was a good meeting.  Then left and went up to 19th street and pooped around.  Ate lunch at Yale Grill & Pharmacy.  It was very good.  Then chilled out at home and left for the Greek Festival.  Met Katherine G there and ate greek Salad and watched all the cute boys.  Ran into an old friend Stephen from the old days.  Supposed to hook up with him for lunch this week.  Should be interesting.  Off to bed.  Work at 7am...fun fun....
     

    
</post>

<date>01,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Just got home from CMA meeting.  Colt is leading it.  I've been having thoughts of getting into a better paying job.  Not sure what that is about as it would mean lots more hours.  I think I need to get going in my program and then worry about more hours.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well, lots has happened since I've taken time off from writing.  Kelly moved in the house is the biggie.  He's been really sweet so far and has been tons of help around the house.   He really fixed up his room neat.  It looks great.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Felt a little better today.  Worked and then went over to Ray's and we installed a new ceiling fan.  It looks great.  Then I went to grocery store and to tan.  Got home and have been chilling out.  Kelly's been working on the bathroom some more and it's going to look great!  I'm really excited about it!  Can't wait to get a floor laid down in there.  Talked with Michael M. yesterday about Michael Golden for a sponsor.  I'm not sure if he's too nice.  I might need a tough one...not sure....Guess I should pray about it.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Good day at work.  Went to the tubs last night and had a nice time.  Had a major emotional hangover today.  Skipped the drag auction at Lambda last night.  I'm so sorry I missed it.  Mary even showed up.  She hasn't been returning my calls lately so I'm sure she's upset about something silly.  She's such a nut case.  I love her but she is so unstable.  I just don't know what to do with her.  Was really sad today.  Kelly and I had a good talk.  We're both after the boys next door.  That should be interesting.  He mowed the boys yard with my mower.  Man was I pissed off.  I'm sure he's gonna be all over Brian and I'll get more jealous.  Got a lot done at work.  Have really been feeling on my game at work.  Getting a lot done with concierge association.  I think we might be on the verge of some major growth finally!  Now I need major growth in my recovery program.  I wish I could put the same motivation and effort I put into work into my program.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Asked Michael Golden to help me with my stepwork.  I never actually said would you be my sponsor.  I'm not positive he's the one I should have asked.  Lloyd might be a stronger sponsor.  I don't do well with people who come on strong.  I tend to shun them.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm feeling really lost in my program right now.  And at the same time I'm excited about my life and the future.  Should I have kept that little kitten?  Would he have been a perfect match for Max?  Who knows.  I just felt like taking him in was the right thing to do today.  I really wish I didn't care so much for the welfare of animals.  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I've had crud in the throat since Friday.  I sound like a frog.  I don't feel bad but when you sound bad I start to think I am sick.  Found a little kitten in the garage today.  Took it to the SPCA which breaks my heart but at the same time I know it's the right thing to do.  Kelly was with me and he drives me nutz sometimes.  He's really sweet but is always suggesting stuff to me that ishould do or buy or whatever.  We don't at all have the same taste and it starts to drive me crazy.  He's been telling me how I should spend my birthday GC's from my folks.  He thinks we need a gas heater in the living room.  He's so crazy.  We could use one but man I wish he'd just shut the fuck up about it.  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Ray came over yesterday after I slept in and we installed lights in the landscaping in the back yard.  It looks really good.  Then I moved the yard and got it looking good.  Today Oscar and Eric from work rand a gas line and attached my gas heater.  It's going to really work good.  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well another one for the books......good weekend behind me!  Went to a cool dinner party at Ray's last week.  This CUTE boys named Marcus was being a huge flirt and it made me pretty crazy.  He was lifting up his shirt across the room when only I could see and grabing his weiner and I was about to explode.  Man that was looking good.  Left Deaton a message afterwards and felt better.  Ray cooked an amazing cajun dinner.  Was delish!  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Just had HCA Christmas Party last night.  Was a nice time.  I'm so glad it's over and that my term is just over half over.  I really can't wait to get over with it!  I'm gonna celebrate when I retire.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      ok, so it's been a while since I've written.   Times have been good but emotional.  During Thanksgiving, I went home and Mom and I had a good heart to heart.  It took some doing but I learned that Mom feels she's being attacked when I try to talk to her about serious things.  I'm not sure what that is about but I think that's why she shuts down and goes into serious defensive mode whenever we've tried in the past.  I also have seen several movies dealing with HIV and death.  "The Event" was about a guy who threw a party with all his friends and then killed himself with them all around him, and then Angels in America has been on HBO for the past couple Sundays.  I didn't totally understand the movies but it was very poignant to watch.  Mary Jane Mann has cancer and that has been hard to take and then we found out that Aunt Mary has cancer too.  It's been a lot to process lately.  Went to Dads and had a talk with Bobbie Anne and she was pretty cool.  I still have anger around that situation and not sure how to get past that!  I've started working with Michael Golden on step work and hopefully today I'll get some more work done on that.  Maybe I need to go set up shop somewhere were I can just focus on my work.  Montrose library might be good.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I'm in such a strange place tonight.  Kelly ate all my food my Mom sent home from Christmas.  I'm like OMG.  What was he thinking?  Hello?  Anyway.  I ate some old soup.  Watched Game Show tonight.  It was pretty good.  I was supposed to do something with Ray but he never called me back.  So I just chilled here and cruised boys online.  Deaton got back into town.  He's not going to Austin so that works out good for me and Michael.  I'm feeling like going to the Club but probably should just go to bed.  I always miss out on the good nights.  The boy from Minnesota will be in on Monday so guess I'll wait for him.  Good Times.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I made it through Christmas.  Did the family thing and felt lots of feelings along the way.  It's been really good in some ways.  I got the old family decorations and have them in my home.  Felt strange at first and sad but now feels really good.  Visiting Nacogdoches was  a little tough.  I always feel like an outsider from the club in that town.  If I'm not  married with a family I feel like I just don't measure up by east tx standards.  Christmas Day at the Hallman's was really nice.  Lots of exchange students from all over the world.  They were fun to get to meet and share experiences with.  Very interesting.  Trying to get settled back into my routine a little.  Feeling a little restless with work.  Very tired of the LCD SA Congress.  Really tired of the whole thing.  HCA is fun from time to time but I really am looking forward to focusing on something else.  Off to work I go.....
     

    
</post>

<date>22,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      OMG, well Dad's family comes in today.  Got just about all my shopping done.  Did Christmas last night with Mark D and Brad.  Ate at Houston's and had a nice dinner discussion.  Brad is cool but very intense.  Makes me feel a little inferior in the brain dept.  Need to get Dad one more goodie but not quite sure what to get.  Headed to see the last Lord of the Rings today.  Should be really good.  Hitting the IMAX screen theater on I-10.  Headed to Mom's on Christmas eve.  Be home for about 24 hours which is perfect.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Tiffany Smith called today and we're going to meet for a beverage at Tila's on Shepherd.  That should be fun to catch up and stuff.  I've really been thinking about my future lately.  Not sure where I'm supposed to go from here.  
     

    
</post>

<date>29,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Kelly is freaking me out.  I'm not sure if I'm crazy or if he's crazy.  He will not stop harping about a gas can that is out in the shed.  He's fixated on it and constantly is puting it outside in the backyard.  It was leaking and stuff and stinking up the storage room.  Not sure why is was doing that but anyway, I think its fine in the shed which is a common place to store gas cans.  Anway, he and I haven't been talking and maybe he should leave.  I wouldn't mind having more space and some privacy might be good for me.  Maybe then I could get a husband and have people over whever I wanted to.  He uses all my toiletries, eats all my food, including my christmas dinner from my Mom.  He won't do the dishes and is generally a moody bitch.  I have my moments too but damn, I let loose on him tonight and man did it feel good to do that!  I of course should be processing this stuff with him in a healthier way but I don't know how to do that.  I just blow up and let the shit fly.  Felt good but he's probably reeling right now.  
     

    
</post>

<date>30,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, it's been a while I know.  Wow, thought I got a raise today when I checked my balance.  I got my tax refund.  Yeah!  Superbowl is in full swing and man is it exciting.  I'm so glad I'm getting to experience it.  PDiddy, Nick Lackey, Mario Lopez, Jessica Simpson, Matthew Lillard, Nelly and others are all in the hotel.  It's so cool.  Walked down Main street last night and it was the coolest scene.  There is no way people cannot be enjoying themselves.  Temp was perfect and downtown looked cool with the trains running and stuff.  Gave 10% of my refund to Bering.  It's really a guilt payment as I am always working on Sunday mornings.  I can't believe that we have four more solid days of craziness at the hotel.  Zehra and Alice are back helping and it sure is good to see them.  They were some of my favorite people I ever got to work with at the hotel.  I am very blessed!
     

    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ed across the street, ed died, Mary Jane Mann dies and Kelly is in Rehab.  Lots has been going on!  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, so I've been playing hookie....sorry about that.  My internet has been screwed since March and it's still not fixed.  Time Warner is off my christmas list.  I'm up at Hollywood cuz I can check my email up here.  Life is wild but the end is in sight.  I've got the LCD congress in a couple weeks, then the GM dinner and then elections for new officers.  I'm going to Dallas over Memorial Day for their round-up.  Got comp rooms at the FS so that should be nice.  Hope I can afford to 'order in" while I'm there.  We'll see.  Got to get a new car in August so better save my pennies instead.  Training two new bozos at work.  One is a drunk and one is a nervous straight boy.  The straight boy is driving me nutz.  I can't wait until he's trained.  Mark D. is on the phone with me and is having house refinance drama.....bless his heart.....
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      What a beautiful day! My last day of vacation.  Had a great talk with Ray last night about jobs, life's work etc.  I realized that Sales and Catering at Four Seasons isn't far off the mark.  It's a great company, great benefits, I've got senority, the positions are individual contributors and there are opportunities to travel and live in exotic locations.  Those are very important things to me.  I can also make great money in sales if I'm good, I can travel and work primarily Monday - Friday.  What a great life that would be.   I really need to pray about where I would like to live and I need to get my thoughts together in that area.  My mind had been telling me I might be totally on the wrong track and after talking with Ray, I realized that I was pretty much on a great track.  Whew....what a relief.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, I'm sitting at home on a Saturday night...thinking of going to the tubs and I have zero libido.&nbsp; This sux so bad.&nbsp; I guess I'll go out first and get the blood flowing.&nbsp; I've been so seditary lately.&nbsp; I bet that has something to do with it too.&nbsp; My insurance has refused to pay for my testosterone injections.&nbsp; That was really helping with fatigue and libido.&nbsp; Guess I'll shower and get a rock star energy drink and hit the town.&nbsp; Max is sitting next to me being really precious!   
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Had a really good day today.&nbsp; Slept in and then goofed around the house doing laundry and stuff.&nbsp; Went over and talked to Merta a bit and Kelly came over too.&nbsp; Saw Kelly's car he plans to buy from her.&nbsp; He's driving her crazy asking questions about the car.&nbsp; She's such a sweet lady.&nbsp; We then took off and I dropped Kelly at the Gap for his group job interview.&nbsp; He's so excited.&nbsp; I went and ran errands.&nbsp; Went to Target and got Max a new electric pooper machine.&nbsp; Then hit the VW dealership and got some parts for the car.&nbsp; Man there was&nbsp;a FINE Jetta there.&nbsp; A GLI.&nbsp; Man I wish I had bought that instead.&nbsp; It was sporty and really cute!&nbsp; I'm thinking I might just buy my car and hang on to it for a bit.&nbsp; Start making bigger payments and pay it off and then just keep it.&nbsp; I dunno.&nbsp; I'm torn between a fun jeep and being frugal and smart with my $$.&nbsp; I then met Lori, Michelle and Jerry for an afternoon exploring downtown.&nbsp;&nbsp; It was fun.&nbsp; Went to a really groovy coffeehouse called Franklin Street Coffee house.&nbsp; It was sooo cool.&nbsp; It was the original Gordon's Jewelers.&nbsp; That sent chills up my spine....LOL....   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Still kind of sad and not really sure where it's coming from.  CMA was good last night.  Jerry kind of ignores the format of the meeting but I guess there are no "big deals."  Kelly and I had a good talk last night a a giggle or two.  He's been a blessing both in preventing me from isolating and help with $$.  He made a new skateboard mouse for Max and Max was having a big time last night playing with it.  Walter has some porn star living with him for a few weeks.  He's a hoot.  He asked me to help find the guy work here in town.  I was pretty curt that we don't do that kind of thing at the hotel.  I really want to get my harms list completed.  Maybe I'll work on that the next couple days I have off.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I was so sad last night. I'm not completely sure why but at Michael Golden's birthday party at Cafe Express I felt I said too much and said things that others didn't like. It may just be in my head, but I really feel like I come on too strong and don't let others shine. I express these big opinions and dominate conversation. I hate that about my mother and I do the same thing. Got michael a gift with Michael M. and he only seemed to thank Michael M. That also may be in my head but who knows.   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, this CMA @ Lambda thing is really kicking into high gear. I want to do the right thing and make sure the crazies don't ramrod us out of Lambda. I really pray for guidance in this matter. I hope I can navigate this situation and end up with a CMA meeting at Lambda. It's Michael Golden's birthday today. I hope to be half the man he is someday. He's an amazing human being.   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Attended BoyGroove last night with Mark D, Michael Golden, JP and Jeff L and his partner Eric. Ate dinner at Paulies and then went to the show. It was cute but a little too long and sort of silly. Way too vulgar. I just really don't see a reason for that much vulgarity. Today is the start of the all Star festivities. Gonna get shot out of a cannon probably. Hope we book a lot of limos! Getting excited about shopping for a new car.   
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      What an amazing day!&nbsp; I worked and then met Deaton for coffee at the Franklin Street Coffeehouse.&nbsp; We then raced off to River Oaks Jeep and I found a kick ass Jeep that I can pimp out with all the bells and whistles.&nbsp; I still have to get my VW turned back in and all the stuff fixed that's wrong with it.&nbsp; I'm stressed about the inspection.&nbsp; Hope they take it easy on me.&nbsp; Tomorrow is the big day with CMA being discussed at Lambda.&nbsp; Can't wait until that's over.&nbsp; I've been talking to Abe everyday.&nbsp; Not sure where that's going but it sure is fun.&nbsp; Met another cute boy who just moved here from Miami.&nbsp; He seems really sweet.&nbsp; Who knows.&nbsp; Not sure if I can date someone who drinks and parties.&nbsp; Might not be a good idea.&nbsp; Kelly has Kyle spending the night tonight.&nbsp; I'm not totally thrilled with it but guess he can live his life.   
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Wow, feel like I'm a little bit "shot out of a cannon" lately.&nbsp; My lease is up on my car, Abe called me back after I told him I was poz, the lambda vote is coming up, I'm sponsoring my first persons in CMA, another sales position opened up at the hotel and Kelly started working at Gap and you'd think he was doing some amazing thing by getting out of the house and doing what the rest of the world does every day.&nbsp; Met Mom last night for dinner with Glenda and Ya Ya sisterhood.&nbsp; Went to Willie G's and it was good.&nbsp; Good to see her.&nbsp; She laid on the guilt about how she doesn't see much of me.&nbsp; For some reason I'm ok with that right now.   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      OK, I'm freaking out today.&nbsp; I've been a bathhouse Betty for the past couple days and have totally fucked off all the stuff I "should"have been doing.&nbsp; My mind is racing about my job, working for a promotions, the SW Regional, trading in or keeping my car, my health, sponsoring people, my step work, whether or not I got ripped off by the bug people today, the rotting wood in the bathroom etc........blah, blah....and it's all high class stuff but it's still real.&nbsp; Not going to meetings for days hasn't helped and not reaching out has also probably not been the right thing to do.&nbsp; So I go to the nooner and CRAZY Diane Nelson wants to meet me this afternoon at 6pm to "talk."&nbsp; Jeeeze lady..what the hell is there to talk about.&nbsp; I'm really not up for that.&nbsp; I'm nervous that I'll be mean to her or say something unkind.&nbsp; I'm pissed that on my day off I have to spend any of it with her.&nbsp; I guess I need to get over it.&nbsp; I'm sober, not in jail and have food and shelter and a car and friends and cloths and a computer and cell phone and TV and blah blah blah.   
     

    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Mark Deaton went with me yesterday to pick up my new Jeep. I really like it but it is rough and tumble vehicle. I think I'll get used to it. Also is hard to shift and manage a cell phone. Not problems I had when I was a drug addict in my last jeep. I think the best moments in the jeep will be heading to the beach. It's a total beach vehicle and especially if I move to California or Hawaii one day it would be perfect. Jerry got thrown in jail and we don't know when he'll get out. Lori and I both were planning trips to Austin so I volunteered to stay and work and I really need the $$. Kelly's working hard at Gap and I haven't seen him in several days. I miss him. Wow can't believe I said that! I guess now with this car, I'd really miss the rent check most! Eek! 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Met with Scott yesterday and we talked about the first step.&nbsp; This was a neat experience.&nbsp; He didn't think he had a problem with alcohol during our meeting and then after CMA he came up to me and said maybe he would rethink that issue.&nbsp; I was really blown away.&nbsp; He also has issues with sex and video game addiction that I'm not totally sure what to do about.&nbsp;&nbsp; Getting so excited about my jeep.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; There is a HOT x-marine in CMA who just moved here from San Diego.&nbsp; I really have a big crush on him.&nbsp; I've got to start working out! 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      What a day yesterday, went to work, had a staff meeting til about 4:30pm, ran to River Oaks and bought my Jeep and then went straight to a concierge association meeting where Konni presented me with a gorgeous crystal bowl.&nbsp; I wasn't expecting it!&nbsp; I got a standing ovation from everyone in attendance.&nbsp; That meant so much to me!&nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Good morning!&nbsp; Well, VW inspected the Jetta and only charged me $275 for the dent in the trunk! Woohooo!!&nbsp; I was so happy!&nbsp; I'm hoping to close negotiations on my new Jeep today.&nbsp; I think it's going to be a pretty sweet deal with I'm done!&nbsp; It's been a blessing to have perfect credit walking into the deal.&nbsp; 2.9% financing rocks!&nbsp; They treated my like a regular person and not like the VW people did.&nbsp; Worked yesterday as Billy was out sick.&nbsp; It really threw me off to go in in the middle of the day.&nbsp; Anyway, if the planets align maybe I'll be a Jeep owner next time I blog.&nbsp; =)   
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It passed!&nbsp; I think 46 to 31.&nbsp;&nbsp; Woohoo!&nbsp; I was less nervous than I thought I might be but I did obsess about it a little the days leading up to it.&nbsp; I got really good feedback from everyone.&nbsp; I'm thrilled to have it behind me.&nbsp; Had a wonderful day.&nbsp; Slept in, Kelly made a great breakfast and he Kyle and I ate at the table.&nbsp; Then we all went to church.&nbsp; Myrta took us all the Black Eye Pea for lunch.&nbsp; That was fun.&nbsp; She's so sweet.&nbsp; She likes Randy Travis and Banana Cream Pie from Flying Saucer.&nbsp; I then headed home and got ready to hit Lambda for the board meeting.&nbsp; When I got home, Kelly made a bowl of Key Lime Blue Bell, I took some calls and then crashed and just woke up.&nbsp; Mom's in Minnesota at her 50th HS reunion and Dad's in Dallas at a big Mary Kay convention.&nbsp; Had a really good talk with Dad.&nbsp; Tomorrow is the day I may buy my new Jeep.&nbsp; I got a really good finance deal and I'm so excited.&nbsp; What a gift the program brings into my life.    
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've had a cold for several days now and it's really bringing me down.  It's so hot and the jeep is really rough and the regional is bearing down on me, Kelly didn't pay his rent in total.  I've got to return to VW on Wednesday and owe $275.  hope they will hold the check until then.  I'll be so glad when this regional is over.  I'm feeling a little shakey in my sobriety.   Need to get to a meeting but also need to rest.  Maybe I'll read my new grapevine.  Sounds like Merta and Kelly are talking.  I think she is such a sweet lady.   I went and got her Saturn today from the Upholstery shop.  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, Konni Godley went nuzt last night and announced to the entire board that people were unsure of who was running the meetings last year. I told her I was very offended and she didn't back down a bit. She's fucking crazy and I'm so sorry she president of the association. She will really fuck it up if she's not careful. Barbara Garvey was the only one who took up for me. I can't thank her enough. Nobody else said a word that I can remember. I was almost in tears when I left the restaurant. I'm fending off some crud today and left work early and hit the sack. Now I'm off to CMA and then right back to bed.  I love my Jeep!!!   OMG, it's the bright spot in my day!       
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today I finished up a 7 day work week. OMG, God was really doing for me what I couldn't do for myself as I spent 26K on my dream Jeep. I realized today that I really LOVE Jeeps. I've got the bug I read about. Anyway... I think I might relax at the tubs this evening. Hope I can do a meeting and then cruise over there. That's usually hard to do but it doesn't get good until late anyway. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>