<Blog>

<date>23,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      was reading other peoples blogs today, when i looked at Kawins, i found that i was in it. wow.  i am rarely ever in anyone elses blog other than keri's. i feel special now. of course i feel special too when im in keri's blog. i actually practiced today! woohoo, good for me. it was fun too. imagine that! proves that new song is very flapping in my opinion. in other news: life still v. flap other than friends lately charlie has been on my nerves he better shape up   cabe
     

    
</post>

<date>22,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      life is not flapping at all. proves to be more flap day by day. the only thing flapping in my life is friends. parents suck. school is alright but still sucks. life outside school other than weekends boring and it sucks. at least i still have my friends.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      yesterday was fun. i went on a road trip(sort of) with my dad to go get my sister from college, and her friend too. the first 5 hours were so boring. we got there and took some pictures got whits stuff and went to go get D and her stuff. on the way home it was boring for the first hour or so till i got in the back with whit and D. we played on my sisters computer for a while till we got to a McDicks. then we ate. after that we started writing this story on her computer. its a game where u pass the story around and someone adds something like half a sentence untill someone ends the story. anyway. we got bored of that after awhile and started saying tounge twisters and i suck at those so i just played on my sisters computer. then we all started singing acopella songs till we got thome.   cabe
     

    
</post>

<date>17,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Flapping time with keri tonight. did lots of stuff. she came over. we went out on my roof for a while. then went down to my Footon swing and looked at the senery and talked for a while. then we went and ate dinner and talked for a while with my parents about lotr and hp. then we watched a movie which was flapping, October Sky(watch it). then sadly she had to go home and i had to do the dishes ALL ALONE. im just jokin keri.   cabe
     

    
</post>

<date>16,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      day was as usual boreing. did i spell that right? oh well. flap day wish i could have seen keri more. went to look for her ALL over school. though should have looked in spot where she usually gets picked up by her mom. Flap.i find myself using the words flapping and flap more often now more than ever. unusual for me. well thats all fer now. miss kiwi.   cabe
     

    
</post>

<date>13,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Best Feeling in the World: Knowing that she loves me back.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      had another boring day. till i got home and got on the internet. jen got a new deadaim and decided to mess with my head. fun fun. for them. -sigh- anyway fun while it lasted. still miss keri terribly. i get to see her today though. im happy. i changed my blog colors. tell me what u think. v. excited that i can change my blog that much. hehe.so anyway i forgive u jen and keri but please use someone else next time. v. flumoxed now.   cabe
     

    
</post>

<date>07,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      today....boring. have nothing to do.miss kiwi.   cabe
     

    
</post>

<date>06,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Had flapping good time with kiwi today....untill charlie came over. ruins everything. i haven't seen my girlfriend in TWO weeks and he comes and ruins it. im sure he wouldn't want me to come and interupt him and his g/f(if he had one). im mad now.but v. v. v. happy i saw my kiwi today. she had to leave early though. v. v. v.flap.   cabe
     

    
</post>

<date>03,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      HAHAHA!! I'm in Caleb's blog! GO ME!!!!! hehehe..yup...ok...must go...read my blog!! :):):)   kiwi
     

    
</post>

<date>03,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      she's comin home tomorrow. can't wait. really can't wait. u know how people say "you've waited this long whats a few more hours?" yea its NOT like that. im a very impatient. I want my Kiwi back!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      just got brand new blogger I miss ker......a lot!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Kiwi the flapping here! hello all! have hacked into cabey's blog.  weeeeee. fun fun.  have just had very nice evening with him. quite flapping.  must go though. will update my own blog soon.    xxoooooo   KIWI'I
     

    
</post>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      y does life suck sooo much?i came in to the kennel that day and she looked at me and i knew something was wrong. she just looked at me with tose eyes. i don't remember exactly what she said but she broke it off again. after a whole $&#*ing year. she calls it off for good. u couldn't imagine what it did to me. hell. pure hell. then it was mitch.oh mitch. u sutpid bastard. thats the real reason she dumped me. well that what i would like to think.no it was actually me. my stupid boyish hormones. its one of those times where u wish u could go back in time and tell urself "don't do that". hell, pure hell. god what i would give to get her back.almost anything. shes a rare thing in this world and i lost her. im a $&#*ing ididot.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      i was goin to try and say this in a cute little poem. but i'm not good at those. Be Happy. don't try to make me happy.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      god. somedays u think every other word out of my mouth is an insult directed twards u.Its NOT. i would never insult u on purpose. sometimes what comes out of my mouth isn't what i'm thinking. if it comes across offensive, im sorry, im not good with words.im sorry. 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      i'm pathetic.this whole thing is pathetic. but y does it stay. y do i have such strong feelings for u. i see u wiht mitch and my whole view bursts into a white hot flame. i can't see anyhting but u too, together, teasing each other like we didn't do. i screwed up i know. u don't think i could have done anything to prevent this? bullshit ur just want me get over u. i could have done something to prevent it and i should have, but i didn't. but y didn't i. it was my first time.i didn't know what the hell i was doin. screw it. i guess its over for u. but its not for me.i'll keep tryin till it kills me.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      You have no idea how i feel.
     

    
</post>

<date>31,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      how can i say to her that i still love her and want her. that she means more than life itself. and not expirience the let down that comes so soon after. i guess i can't.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      y do i still feel this way. it rips me up inside everytime i think of it, of her. y can't i just let her go. can't i move on. its not what i want but its what needs to happen. she has i haven't.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      WOOHOO!!life sucks again.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i need to read that book...
     

    
</post>

<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      why is it that us men can't understand women. they say one thing but want another. we don't knoww what u want if u don't tell us. we're not mind readers!!really tell us whats on your mind cause we sure as hell can't figure it.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I was happy again, but then again I wasn't.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      so today was very boring. orchestra-boring chem-very boring Gov-Extreamly boring English-eh a little boring Geo-easy test, waste of time. not much else though Rachel did punk out...again. is this the 5th time? oh i've lost track. come on rachel...just do it(nike sign). anydangway new sbemail not too good but its worth watching a couple of times. ok im out. later
     

    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Dude, I got a dell!! i know, i know.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      movie day was too fun for words. seriously.no words.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey, stubble, get on the ball. Slackers!! i haven't seen a real post in a while now. im not really yelling at u kalin it more keri's fault. its that osity blog. its distracting. anyway. i want more from the stubble. soon. rather than later. im appalled!
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Nevermind, i got a color scheme now, sort of. Anyway, its been boring. Last few dwindling days of school. Waiting till i can sit on my ass for the summer. Wait for school to start again. I wish i could say my summer will be cool but i can't. Ill just have to see how it goes.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      though if anyone had a color scheme or could help with one, please feel free to tell me. 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      though if anyone had a color scheme or could help with one, please feel free to tell me. 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ok forget the new colors. They sucked. I met Dave G. today during frizbee. Nice guy. Saw Mr. Wades older brother too. Had fun running.....and running.....and running back and forth the whole time. it was fun.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      New color scheme. Tell me if its off because i have no sense of "scheme".
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I don't know jack shit about art. Ker.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      No need to jump down my throat, i was just saying. Anyway. Geo preject finally over, now i have to do a Gov't project. And an English project. Oh well. Hell theres only a couple of days left in this year anyway.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Its "due to" not "do to" keri. Just thought I'd note that.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey guys not much goin on here. I passed math but the bastard imrisek wasn't there today so instead we took a quiz on the same shit as the test. And we didn't get our tests back. That guys pisses me off. Well the days are dwindling down. 12 days left. lets hope those days aren't too long.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Movie Night was fun. Rachel seemed very lonely without spencer. Watched about half the movies half as much as I wanted to. Had a garlic biscuit and milk. I had a little too much of girls swooning over depp for one night, even for one hour. Thats what happens when u say ok to chic flicks. Well I deal with it.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Im such a dork. And my computer is slow as hell.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Wish, as if ur life depended on it.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ow. My forehead hurts. Im gonna have a scar for ever. Something to remind me of you Rachel.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Its raining and lightninging and thundering. I love it. Oh and I also like it when drivers outside get in fights , honk horns and exchange "fuck you buddy"'s. Isn't the human race great.Oooooo thunder. It touches the heart like nothing else.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So, its tuesday and i haven't talked about Hershey yet. What the hell is wrong sith me? Hershey kicked ass. Hershey makes up for the lack of number of coasters with the heart stopping speed and hieght of the coasters. It was awsome. waiting in line with my best friends for an hour and a half for a 45 second ride...is the best thing u could do with a saturday. Other than a movie day with the gang at rachels. Brought 15 bucks and came home with 4.50 and an empty stomach. Nothin like a day at Hershey park. Oh and that was the worse we have ever played devil. What are we doin, gettin suckyer rather than betterer?
     

    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So, haven't blogged in a while. i guess its gettin boring for u readers out there. sorry. life is boring. not complaining. anyway.  Life update:  1)Chem test wasn't as bad as i had previouly thought 2)Geo test was as easy as i had predicted 3)Strolling trip on Saturday!!! im excited if u can't tell. free tickets to the park. kick ass, kick ass. 4)CONGRATULATIONS rachel (a little late, sorry)  Later, Cabe
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      christ, should we care about socks?!  so thought id do a blog since i haven't done one in about a week. not too much exciting here. sealed the deck so if it rains it won't get wet! sitting here playing what little i know on the guitar and fooling around  G E flat C D Flat?  A E D E A  Digga Digga                       Digga digga            Digga digga                                  Doung  sounds good huh? 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      DELETED  this post  cause it was buggin me
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      so...  today i cleaned my windows i scraped the front steps a bit played frizbee for a while with my sister went to the park with my sister, two gloves, a baseball, a tennis ball, and two frizbees drank some lemonade ate some food played my violin for about three minutes watched some tv played my guitar, unsuccessfully (that is one long ass word)  i don't know what ill do tomorrow but it'll be tomorrow  till my next rambling later
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i guess this is suposed to be my vibe my vibe  hmmmm  is that like what i do or what i am or what i like?  well what i do isn't very exciting usually what i am isn't much either and what i like for the most part i can't get  but i try
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Right so here goes  Rooms all painted, hot pink and bright yellow Just kidding but really, the trim is deap space blue the walls are off white or offwhite whichever.And the windows are white.  Don't know about curtains  Those of u that are goin to summer school: I hope u have a wonderful last day before it starts and i hope u have fun during it  Not much else same old stuff  later
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey guess what...   I PASSED!!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I need some lovin too. Sanity level dropping.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey Rachel this ones for you.  Im listening to Pissin In The Wind by Jerry Jeff Walker. You probably don't know what or who that is but i bet u know what Mr. Bojangles is. Good song, if u don't know it come on down to my place ill play it for u.  Went to the art festivale in town with keri today. It was fun. Saw lots o' very good stuff. I almost bought somthin but then realised that its expensive. You know me, cheap as shit man.  Also had a very fun time at the bull with rach, chrissy and dan. Pretty good fun. Expensive and chrissy still owes me ten bucks. Miss waitress was a bitch. We had a fun time hangin out for an hour outside too.  And the last day of school was fun too. You know in that "last day of school this year" kind of way. Spent most of the morning in Imriseks room, fun stuff, with other people there. I think he called me Cabe, no mr. I. Its Caleb to u mister.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well im back. just thought id notify those of u who do not regualarly talk to me.  and ive decided to turn my blog into sort of a Link posting blog. so if u find any good site let me know and ill put them here.  i don't write enough to do anything else with this blog. so send me those links via  urlLink simplycabe@gmail.com  or simplycabe on AIM. 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, im off. off for vacation. with the family.  Ill miss u all terribly.  Adue, adue. till saturday.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      damn, i spelled non-sense wrong...oh well.  today was an ok day. i actually kind of felt good today. i finished my book and ordered the next one. then onto the Devinci Code.  not much else. later
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Fuck, where'd i put my E string?   Fight Club is a good movie. We actually watched a guy movie at movie night. Without any bitchy and moaning on my part. thouhg the girls still swooned over brad pitt. Godd movie though, lots of action. very strange movie. brad pitt as the alter ego of...shit i forget his name. anyway, watch it.  Chrissy, u want a fuckin hug, heres ur fuckin hug. oIoo.  just kidding.  i need a shave. anyway untill the next nonsence comes out of my mouth or fingers, Later.
     

    
</post>


<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Why do I burn and pine for her? Why can't I get over this girl? Why do I love her more than anything else in the world? Can some one tell me this or at least tell me how to get over her. Seriously, I want to know because I can't do it. Its so hard to be  just  her friend. I can't help but want to be alone with her whenever I see her. 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       RAIN. A word as simple as that, can give such an image. Of love, in the rain. I can see a boy and a girl, standing. It begins to rain. The girl looks up from his embrace and smiles. Forhead wet with rain, and those beautiful eyes so full of emotion, they close o' so slowly. And he kisses her in the most intimate expression of love. The feeling just radiating off of the two. The kiss ends the same as it began but eyes open instead of close. Still looking at him she bites her lip in the most enticing way possible. Another embrace. Forever love as I want it for me. 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I want to live in the country again, surounded by woods all around. I want to wake up in the middle of a summers night, lay on my deck and watch the stars. I want to hear the birds all day and fall asleep to the sound of a chorus of insects chirping into the night. I want to be closer to her. I want to be away from it all. School, the city, working, and just enjoy it. I want to feel the warm rain on my face as i lay in the grass. I want to live as if i have not a care in the world. But don't we all? 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It really does feel like ive had a large knive slowly shoved into my heart, but quikly. Its like a jab. A heart stopping moment, when u realize how much life sucks. How much u loved and still love her. But its someone elses hand shes holding. She never did that with u. She never liked that sort of thing when u were with her. I saw it and ignored it best i could. Best i could. Its like having a lead wieght strapped around your heart like a cold , rusty chain; digging in everytime you move. 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I feel like shit. I've been thinking about how keri treats her friends and im really questioning whether she a good one or not. I've takin so much shit from her over the two years i've been well aquainted to her. We claim to be best friends but really how are u supposed to be friends with someone who blows you off all the time. I should call her sometime i know. Everytime she asks me to walk with her upstairs carl or josh comes along and im left in the dust. But on the other side, how exciting am i? not very. Im about the most boring person i know. I son't do anything, i hate the thought of having responsibility, im not very active, i don't ever have anything worth talking about and the list goes on. All i like really is science and math and im not even that fuckin good at either. I claim to be an electronics geek but really i can't do anything with that shit. I admit that i know more than the average joe but not much more. I wait for things to happen to me and blame everyone else when nothing comes to me. One word to describe me: LOSER. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
          Shes so beautiful. Most of the time Ican't take my eyes off of her. I love it when her hair is all a mess. I love her eyes, though dark they light up my world. Her ears look completely differernt and unequal, thats the way she likes things. She doesn't like it when things are "even". Her rosy, cute nose. Her teeth, always clean, unlike mine. Shes just so cute.    I love how she writes though she doesn't give me much to read. I wish I could see some of her most recent works though she'll never let me. I love her art work too. The way she just doodles swirling and swaying lines. It just looks so easy for her. I still have the tiger on my fridge, signed with love. She belittles her talents so much. And so do I. But i don't mean to. Im a horrible critic and Im always looking for something to make better. I criticized one of her works last year and she got really pissed off. No matter how many times I say Im sorry, she'll never forgive me for saying it. It was a stupid comment and I wish for all the world if I could take it back, but i can't. It'll always be there in the back of her mind and mine the way I insulted her art.    I just wish so much to change the many stupid things I've said to her in ignorance.    I love how she loves the rain. I love it when we're outside and its raining and her hair is wet and messy and shes soaked to the bone, but shes still standing there, in front of me and I kiss her, in the rain.    I wish I had been more romantic instead of the raging hormones boy. Man, I never saw her before it was too late. I was trapped, entranced by her...everything. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I love her. Ands its not just the love between friends. I still love her as I did when we were together. But thats not enough. I know so much about her that most people don't. It feels like i know her too well to be just friends, but thats what she wants. I know what was wrong and I caught on too late. She says its no ones fault, but I know, it was mine. I guess we didn't do much. At least we didn't do too many  different  things. I just wish I had another chance, but its too late for that. Way too late. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       You know sometimes i wish i hadn't even been born into this family. Sometimes. I love them all, but when we're all together its chaos. At least between my parents. They divorced when i was five, then got remarried about eight years ago then divorced AGAIN a year ago. And all the while quiet little caleb stands by idly and watches it all in perfect detail. I was so tired of the fights. Always fighting, yelling, crying, screaming. My sister, whitney 18 years old now, and i used to huddle up in her room to comfort each other. There were holes in doors and other broken things along with our spirits. Josh, now 23, was lucky he only had to deal with one divorce at least living through it. Im 16 now and i don't show it, but it hurts. Its always there in the back of my mind. Sometimed i just want to cry, but i realize its uslessness. I love my family very much, but when my parents get together its not fun. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey, i've got a new blog. I can vent, rant and rave now. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I wish i knew how to post sound cause there are only so many ways u can express feeling in the written word.  FUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUU UUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUCCCK!!!!!!!!!!! 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        
    
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Why the fuck does it still bother me. I need a fuckin girlfriend. fuckin. 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Fuck fuck fuck, fuckiddy fuck fuck fuck, fucker funken fuck, fuckidy fuckidy fuck, afuck afuck afuck. 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I need to calm down. My last few posts have been very emotionally unstable. Breath in, Breath out. 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       wear it as jewelry 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        In   My   Face  
    
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Someone just shoot me cause i think thats the only way im gonna get her out of my head. Doesn't have to be messy. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       when you get so many chances to fix a problem and don't. Then when its finally over for good...you realize how you might fix that problem. Isn't life sucky like that? 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       -Sigh- Best frind my ass. She treats me like im and annoying strobe light that won't go off. She usually has that off putting glance when i talk to her in the halls like shes waiting for fucking carl to come save her from her stalker. Mother fucker. 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Am i supposed to do? won't happen it might later in life like after college maybe when we get the house together if we get the house damn i can't wait that long  i haven't had one of those kisses in almost a year damn just one would do i would just like to see what i could do better if i were given a  sec ... thir ..... 7th  chance at it  
    
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Life is a bitch ai don't know why  actually i do  i just don't wanna say it in this blog  damn 
    
    
</post>


<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i love being with you. i love goin to ur house for movie nights. i would rather it be just u and me at movie nights. instead of everyone else. its not that i don't like them, its just that i like u more.  y don't u just dump spencer. i don't get whats so amazing about someone whoblows u off even as ur boyfriend. A-S-S-H-O-L-E. u deserve so much better.  im not saying u deserve me because i don't deserve u. i can't even decribe how wonderful u are.  spencer will probably end up very sucsessfull. if u end up with him u'll be married to a sucsessfull man. i probably won't grow up to be squat. ill probably be a dvd repairman or electronics repairman with a little shop on the corner. i would scoff at myself right now but its kind of hard to put a scoff in writing. lol.  now whos pathetic?
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      spencer  what does he have goin for him? you never see him, when u do hes not the best guy to around. never calls u. never does much with u.  great boyfriend huh?  lol fuck i see u more than u see ur boyfriend  hmmm ::thoughtful glance::  i think u get my point
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well i hope none of my friends find  this  one. oh well fuck it.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      is wrong with me 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Its funny the way feelings go. And how you don't really know what the hell your feeling half the time. At least I don't. I've had these feelings and still have no idea what they mean. Like, Love, and why I feel this way.  And how do we express these feelings, thought inexplicable,&nbsp;to the person your feeling them towards? Especially if that person already has someone that they "feel" about or rather have "feelings" towards. Its a tough question. Though a tough question for me may be a very easy one for some one else, but I won't get into that. I come across this almost every day. And someone finally caught it. But I still can't say it. Its pointless.  I wouldn't want to jeopardize the friendship for something that might not even be there.  I've decided against it. 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i still love her, still can't get her out of my mind, shes still there with those eyes and her cute little nose and her smile and smarts and everything  damn  life is a bitch and now i sorta like rachel, though i should probably keep us as friends if she wants us to be dating ill let her inquire  i think she knows i like her, hopefully keri rachel neither one likes me so what the hell am i after them both for i think i have a condition shit
     

    
</post>


</Blog>