<Blog>

<date>30,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        THE WORST TIME OF THE YEAR   This is the time of the year that I like the least. It's the "everyone else is finished with school, but I still have a take-home exam and a paper to do before monday" time of year. I can see the light at the end of the tunnel, though, and it is bright. After Monday, I have about two days to pack the stuff in my house and then I have to be in DC for work on the 12th for my first day.   I am about to go insane with all the stuff I have to worry about, and you all know how much I love to worry.  Sarah is having a shower at Transy tonight. It's our first big gift-getting event, and I am enjoying watching stuff get picked off our Target list. I know that's tacky, but it's something to do.  
     
    
</post>

<date>24,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I have now completed two days of ceramics. Let me just say, watching Ghost a couple million times does not count as experience because this stuff is HARD. Good thing I"m not doing it for a grade. He he he  I'll be going to Durham this weekend to visit Nicholas. I'm hoping some of my relaxed state of mind will wear off but I"m not holding my breath. If anyone needs me tonight dont' bother.  An hour long Friends, Madonna on Will & Grace, a new ER AND the Dixie Chicks with Diane Sawyer. It's almost more than I can take. Good thing I dont' have any homework. (I really will stop gloating eventually...say around May 24th.)
     
    
</post>

<date>22,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      My long weekend has been so different from Nicholas's I almost feel guilty...I just got back from Fripp Island, SC (near Hilton Head). I laid on the beach, ate lots of seafood, and read Mrs. Dalloway (which arrived just in time for my trip thanks to Amy and Tanya!). It's an amazing book for anyone who enjoys stream of consciousness writing, otherwise stay away.  Tomorrow it's off to a tough day of auditing ceramics.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Had my first exam Saturday. I guess it went okay, but I've stopped trying to forecast how well I did.  I've got one tomorrow (Remedies) and then one on Friday (intellectual property), and then I have a take-home and a paper due by May 5. I realize that these posts are very boring, but that's tough because I'm not having any fun, either.  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I'm emerging from the wedding haze that was Sunday through Tuesday. It was stressful but I got some things accomplished. We arranged (and rearranged and rearranged) the reception site and settled on the flowers. I also started working on the video which I thought would be a 4-6 hour project and is starting to feel like 4-6 days. I'm using iMovie and I thought the idea was Microsoft was bad because it forced you to buy its other programs. However, about five minutes into iMovie I realized I needed Quicktime Pro (which is $30) to use some video Christopher (Nicholas's older brother) had generously converted to digital form for me. Despite Christopher's continued assistance, I think I'm going to just leave it out. So much for the ease of Mac.   I am now back at Transy. I have a comprehensive Political Science exam tomorrow for which I dont' have to study. Then more wedding errands till I leave for Fripp Island with my sorority sisters. Then back to Transy for a busy May Term spent auditing ceramic. Yes, that's right I'm auditing ceramics. As Nicholas said, "I tried to figure out a way to do jackshit for May Term and get to stay on campus. I think you've accomplished it."
     
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Back from KY   Just got back from Kentucky, back to exam studying for me. I've got my first one Saturday, and then I have two more in five days. That may not sound that bad, but I don't look forward to it.  
     
    
</post>

<date>12,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      We're off to Sarah's final Phi Mu Formal tonight. Though I've protested that I shouldn't be required to return for such events, those arguments have fallen on deaf ears. So tonight I get to don a tuxedo and dance the night away. Anyone who's upset that they are missing this should take solace in the fact that I'll be doing the same thing on my wedding day, so any and all criticism of my dance stylings should be saved until then.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      For those of you who haven't been to  urlLink this site , it's pretty funny. ONe of the best parts is the BrideAudit program, where the future bride can figure out how expensive the gifts she gets should be.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      This actually is Sarah and my first blog EVER! For any of you who I haven't talked to in awhile, I just received an internship at the National Organization for Women and I am soooo excited. This summer is going to be wonderful but very very stressful. The wedding plans are going along nicely.  Nicholas and I just added some things to our registry today, really exciting stuff like bath towels and pans.  I tried to add some zest with the Smoothie Pro 60 but Nicholas vetoed it. Oh well...we're not zesty people I guess considering it's friday night at 11:30pm and we're working on our homework (and our new blog) :)
     
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      This is Sarah's first blog. Well, not really, actually it's Nicholas signed in as Sarah, but that's just a technicality.  
     
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Our new blog!!   As you can tell by the excessive exclamation points, I'm excited by my new blog.   
     
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       In Durham   After working all day to get my stuff in order and getting the house clean, I am currently the dirtiest and foulest smelling person ever. I am sweaty, but I also have that "ZEP Heavy Duty Carpet Cleaner" smell on me too, which makes for a nice mix.  I am at the law school right now, and it is eerily calm here. They have apparently decided to make the Blue Lounge an open-air market or something by knocking out the wall that was between the lower level lobby area and the lounge. This has effectively taken a quiet place to study and made it into a loud place to hang out. I am intrigued by this logic, especially since we already have a loud place to hang out called the library.  I think I'm going to go shower now.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I'll be back in Durham this weekend so that Sarah and I can move into our new apartment. Sarah is excited that all of her stuff will be in one place at one time for the first time since she went to college.   I get paid tomorrow for the first time, which should be very nice. I currently have something like $0.64 in my checking account. Hopefully I will at least be able to double that.   Work is actually great. I really enjoy all of the people and the projects that I have had so far are really interesting. I think that Food and Drug work may be something I'm truly interested in.  Lastly, an early congratulations to Elizabeth and Shelly on their marriage tomorrow. Hopefully they will use their combined powers for good or for awesome. (Apologies to  urlLink Strong Bad at homestarrunner.com )  
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Graduation Weekend at Transylvania   I was in Lexington this weekend for Transylvania's Commencement. I flew in Friday night and left this afternoon from Cincinnati. The ceremony itself was really good, about an hour and a half long and nobody spoke for too long. Sarah did get her diploma, which was the important part, and then we did the goodbyes to all the professors and the rest.  After the graduation and the after-party, we went with some friends to "Ten Commandments Mini-Golf," which is a Christian-themed putt-putt venue. It was fantastic. We did the Old Testament course, and there are two others, New Testament and Miracles. Each hole was themed along a day of Creation (all 7 days, with the 7th day being a very easy hole-in-one chance) or another Old Testament story, like Noah, Samson, etc. Though we ended up losing as a team to the Turner/Weatherholt Team and the Hicks/Graham team, we lived to golf another day. Overall a good graduation day, if you don't count Sarah's uncontrollable sobbing for about 15 minutes after we left the graduation reception--she's entitled, though.  I'm now back in DC and I am trying to figure out what to do for Memorial Day. I think maybe I'll go to the National Symphony concert or something, but I may also just stay in if the weather is crappy.  Sarah had another wedding shower today, which is just another event in a very busy week for her, but I'll let her talk about it.  A big thanks goes out to Aimee and Johan (the aforementioned Hicks/Graham team) who drove me to Cincinatti today out of the goodness of their hearts.  
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      While Nicholas has been in D.C., I have been wrapping up the wedding plans.  I met with the minister and started working out the final ceremony details. There were a few bumpsin the road. For instance, it looks like we won't be allowed to have guitars, which could drastically affect our music choice. I also went and tried on my dress with a third petticoat (yes, that's right) but it will still have to be taken up. The favors are almost finished and I only have a few more invitations to send.  In the midst of all this, I totalled my car. Last week, I was leaving Paducah and thought this van was too close to me so I swerved left (I was in the left lane) and overcorrected into to him. He flipped over and I ran off the interstate.  We both escaped unharmed which is no small miracle considering I was going over the speed limit. Well, atleast I don't have to worry about storing it over the summer. I am pretty upset considering I've had a car since I was 16 and I'm used to the independence it affords but oh well.  I graduate in less than two weeks and I cannot believe it. I'm having a yard sale on Thursday to hopefully put a dent in the large amount of stuff I have accumulated over the last four years. It's pretty disgusting.  That's aobut it...  
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       First Day   Today was my first day at the firm. It went well, mostly orientation stuff. I went to lunch with my mentor and did the whole Lexis training, learn about billable hours, etc. I won't talk about work here anymore because I'm aware that this is a public blog and that would be both imprudent and boring, but today was good. No complaints.  My first few days of DC living have been interesting. Yesterday I came to the realization that from the White House to my house is a Very Long Way. I walked it anyway, it was good for me. I then had a  urlLink chipwich , the only kind of ice cream that I will eat in DC owing to the fact that it is among my fondest memories of my first trip to DC when I was but a youth. (All the Holland children nod in remembrance, or not.) I also went by and saw the Supreme Court, which is much closer than the White House, and I've done some of the Smithsonian. Other than that, I've just been figuring out what's around my apartment and seeing how long the Metro-ride is from the apartment (Eastern Market) and work (Farragut West). The answer is 13 minutes once you get on the train. 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       In D.C.   For everyone's clarification, I have moved to DC for the summer. I am living on Capitol Hill, about 6 blocks from our fair  urlLink judiciary  and  urlLink legislature . It's a small apartment, but it's bigger than I thought it would be. I may post pictures on sarahandnicholas.com later this weekend, but those may have to wait until Sarah gets here, as the only digital camera I have is a webcam. Anyone who wants to come see me can sleep on the spacious floor or perhaps on the hide-a-bed in the kitchen. For those who know the area, I live about 2 blocks from Eastern Market, which is apparently a large open-air market on Saturdays and Sundays.   I went to the National Air and Space Museum today (insert your own model rocketry/dork reference here).  In other news,  urlLink you can't take your Segway on the Metro . Also,  urlLink Christopher and Nicholas came in 4th and 5th  in most popular baby names. Congratulations to Christopher for beating me this year, but this was a rebuilding year for Nicholas...  Lastly, congratulations go out to all of the soon-to-be Duke Law Grads. You know who you are.     
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        AND DOWN THE STRETCH THEY COME!!!   It's that time of year folks. Pick your pony and lose your hard-earned cash. My exacta pick this year:  Ten Most Wanted 1st-Empire Maker 2nd . If I was actually betting I'd probably bet this ticket as well as the reverse (box it). I would also pick Peace Rules or Indian Express to Show.   Caveat , I WILL BE WRONG ABOUT ALL OF THESE. Despite having spent 4 years in KY, there was only one time that I ever correctly picked an exacta, and it didn't pay that well. I am the worst handicapper of all time. It's a good thing I never bet more than 2 bucks on anything. Post time for the Derby is 6:04 pm. Don't forget that there are races after the Derby (which has always been weird to me, it's almost like having a minor league game in the same stadium right after Game 7 of the World Series).  
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I have just recently returned from the American Association of University Women's National Women Student Leaders Conference. For all of you confused, the AAUW is a feminist organization composed primarily of older women who have graduated from college (the average member is around 60). The organization is dedicated to equity through education and has just recently tried to start reaching out to younger members. One way they have done this is by hosting the conference. The other is by forming a National Student Advisory Council which I am on. As a member of the council, they paid for me to come to Providence, Rhode Island and not only participate in the NWSLC but also participate in a panel/workshop at the National Convention which was held simultaneously with the Conference. It was really a very rewarding experience in which I got to meet other women my age but also network with women older and wiser than myself.  Of course the highlight of the Conference was meeting the matriarch of the feminist movement Ms. Gloria Steinem.  She was receiving an award from the AAUW Educational Foundation at a dinner on Monday night.  Before the dinner, she did a booksigning which is where I got to meet her. My friend and I almost missed it however because we got the times confused. Luckily we made it right at the beginning and the line wasn't very long. As soon as I saw Gloria, I started to cry. I was just so overwhelmed that this person I had admired and respected for so long was only a few feet away.  Then I promptly started to freak out because I realized I was going to have to say something to her. By the time I actually got up to her I was really crying and really freaking out. I was crying so much that she stood up and hugged me and told me it was okay. I told her I had been worrying about what to say for weeks but all I could think to say at that moment was thank you. I also told her how much I admired her and how I promised my mentor I would ask for her contact information so I could write her for advice. Then Gloria Steinem, one of the most powerful women in the world, gave me her personal email address! I couldn't believe it. Of course now I actually have to think up something to write!
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        The Mall  I'd just like to say for the record that we were not "dehydrated" after Vintage Virginia, we were "tipsy."   We just got back from what's turning into a weekly tradition (aka we've done it two Friday nights in a row). Last week, we walked to the Washington Monument from our house which took about 2 1/2 hours and was great. This week we took the metro to the Washington and walked to the Lincoln Memorial and the FDR Memorial. It was very muggy tonight because it had just rained. (See Nicholas's previous post.) We still had a wonderful time and both admited to getting pretty emotional when reading all of FDR's quotes. I know it's dorky but atleast we're better than the obnoxious high school kids that bounce around their like it's Gadzooks, looking for something to buy.  When I'm not getting teary over marble, I'm completely and utterly freaking out about the quickly approaching nuptials. My new way to deal with planning/stress is assign my parents endlesses little tasks which they seem to be handling very well. As soon as the wedding is, Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix is even sooner. The release of the new book also happens to coincide with my meeting Gloria Steinem. It all might just be more than I can handle.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       The Weather Here   I have to say that I don't understand the weather here in DC. It's pretty hot here now, but for the last two days we've had monsoon rains in the afternoon. And it's not just the classic Atlanta afternoon thunderstorm (the ones I used to pray for as a lifeguard), it's a regular downpour, with dangerous winds and everything.  My week has gone pretty well. I've been busy at work, but yesterday we went to a Maggiano's Restaurant and they fed us family style for two hours. Despite the fact that I went to bed early, I still felt tired from all of the eating. Anyone who complains about being a summer associate has problems.   This weekend Sarah and I are going to go to the Smithsonian Museum of American History to see the reconstructed Julia Child's kitchen they have set up there. I've already been once, but it's really cool and Sarah should definitely see it. It's also Flag Day this weekend, so I think they're doing something big there.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        It's Your Birthday, It's Your Birthday, You Got a Cake, With Your Name on It, and a Candle   I had a pretty good birthday weekend. It started with a welcome party for all the summer associates at a partner's house. It was a pretty amazing house, with all sorts of modern art (Sarah was especially impressed with the Lichtenstein in the study) and sports memoribilia (I was especially impressed by the Michigan Jersey signed by the Fab Five). The food was great and we both enjoyed ourselves.  On Sunday we went to  urlLink Vintage Virginia , which is the Virginia wine festival where the Virginia wineries share their fermented grape-juice. Some of it was pretty foul, but there was enough good to make it worthwhile. Despite the fact that it was really muddy and I walked around all day with my jeans rolled up to me knees like Huck Finn, we had a great time. Needless to say, we were very dehydrated when we got home. Later that night we went to Annie and Kyle's house and shared a birthday cake that Sarah bought at Eastern Market. (Good times, good times.)  Yesterday at work the other summer associates had a surprise birthday celebration for two other summers and me, who have birthdays either on the 8th or the 9th. Last night, Sarah, Annie, Kyle, and I saw  urlLink Finding Nemo , which was absolutely amazing. Pixar always manages to have one really blow-you-out-of-the-theater scene in every movie they do (the door assembly line from Monsters, Inc. comes to mind), but I think this one had three. The inside-the-whale scene in this movie was just amazing, but I thought that the jellyfish scene and the "E-A-C" scene were pretty awesome, too. Best line of the movie goes to the young fish early in the movie who yells, "I'm obnoxious!" If you haven't seen the movie, you can't truly appreciate it, so  urlLink what's stopping you?   We are getting into the first truly hot days of summer here in DC and I believe the firm's business casual policy is a stroke of genius. I can't imagine wearing a suit in this swamp.   In other news, I made  urlLink Sauteed Tilapia  filets tonight which were pretty good. I'd never even heard of Tilapia until the guy at the market sold it to me because I was too flustered to say no, but the magic of the Internet made me a regular Tilapia expert. My next cooking adventure is going to be Pasta Primavera, I'll let you know how that goes.   
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes, the past few days at NOW have been really cool. The first day I called celebrities (or atleast that celebrities "people" ) and tried to get them to donate signed CDs/books/art to the auction NOW is having at their upcoming National Conference. So far I've talked to Norah Jones's management and procured a signed poster from the Guerilla Girls. Currently, I am putting together a master list of all the organizations seen as NOW allies. It is just as fun as it sounds. Today, we took a field trip to a Senate Approbriations subcommittee meeting chaired by none other than the great (or AWFUL) Senior Senator from KY Mr. Mitch McConnell. I should stop doing a random assortment of things and start working on PAC stuff when my supervisor gets back on Monday.   On a side note, walking out the front door and seeing the Capitol on my way to the subway NEVER gets old.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Where We Live, At Least For Right Now    urlLink As promised many days ago, here are some pictures of our apartment.   Sarah has enjoyed her first three days at  urlLink NOW . She works with a girl who was on the first Sorority Life show..exciting stuff.  
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Summer's Almost Over...oh...and the Pictures are In   The last few weeks in DC have been pretty busy, and it doesn't look like things are going to slow down.  Though most of our time has been taken up by work, we have managed to get out on the weekends. This weekend we went to the National Zoo, where we saw the two new(er) pandas, and a frog that for all the world looked dead (I'll see if we can get pictures up). It's a pretty decent zoo overall, though they were doing a lot of remodeling when we were there.  We've also been attending the "Screen on the Green" movies, where they play a movie on a big screen on the Mall. We saw  Cat on a Hot Tin Roof  the first week and  The Postman Always Rings Twice  the second. I'd never seen either, and now I wish I hadn't seen Postman at all. Talk about your melodrama. (Sarah did think it was better than   Spirited Away , which we had rented the night before and definitely had its weird moments.)  Sarah's grandmother was also in town a couple of weekends ago, so we got to spend some time with her and her friends, who especially enjoyed Eastern Market. This weekend we had her friends Elizabeth and Erin visiting for Sarah's birthday (which was yesterday), and this coming weekend Ron and Lisa will be in town. Add to that the fact that we move out in two weekends, and our schedule gets pretty full. Especially since we go on our honeymoon the next weekend.  I've got about a week and a half of work to go, and I'm trying to get my projects finished up. I've really enjoyed my summer here, but being a student won't be so bad, either.  The pictures are available at  urlLink this link . After you get there, go to "Weddings," and then click on "Nicholas and Sara [sic]." The password is Sarah's maiden name. Enjoy!
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      For all of you who have felt it necessary to ask over the last week, married life is great.  Though Sarah and I thought there would be some post-wedding depression, I think the fact that we are in DC (where we only temporarily live and thus are really tourists), has helped keep us from feeling like we've returned to "normal," whatever that means.   Last night we were both at the NOW conference, where they were holding their Democratic Presidential Candidate forum. In attendance were Howard Dean, Al Sharpton, Carol Moseley Braun, and Dennis Kucinich. They were all really interesting, but to be honest the only one who seemed at all Presidential was Dean. Sarah was the time-keeper for the forum, and got to meet them all before and got her time sheet signed by them. We also met John Edward's wife, Elizabeth, who was there as his representative and Sarah got her picture taken with Helen Thomas, who was in attendance as a moderator.   After the forum, we stayed for the NOW PAC auction (Sarah because she had to, me because....well, I had to too). There was some really cool stuff, including a two-hour meeting with Janet Reno in Miami (dance party not included).   Today we have a dinner to attend after Sarah finishes her duties at the NOW conference, but the rest of this weekend is pretty wide open. Finally.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        We've Been Busy, Give Us A Break   Well, our wedding in Paducah was nothing short of spectacular. The rehearsal dinner and fireworks lived up to their billing (with the exception of two bridesmaids falling down the stairs), the ceremony was beautiful , and the reception was a lot of fun (for those who left before the Dippin' Dots, you truly missed out). We both want to thank everyone who was involved in the ceremony, including, in no particular order: the bridesmaids (Lauren (MOH), Elizabeth, Aimee, Heather, and Pamela) and groomsmen (Benjamin (Best Man), Geoffrey, Christopher, Josh, and Tim), the junior groomsmen (Alex and Garrett), the ushers (Ryan, Michael, Michael, Corey, and Kyle), the flower girls (Micah and Madison) and ringbearer (Andrea), Kevin Medlin and Jeff Stewart (our minister tandem), Annie (the reader), Mike Baker and Smith Crafton (the musicians), Lana Suiter (aunt and wedding coordinator extraordinaire), Reagan and Jessica Carfield (our greeters), our program attendants (Paige, Kolby, and Taylor), all of our families, especially our parents, and everyone who attended.  Thank you for helping make this the best wedding EVER!  We got back to DC on Monday morning and ran some errands during the day. Sarah got her hair cut. We may post pictures later, but Sarah doesn't want to spoil the surprise for her friends who are visiting in a couple of weeks. I think it looks great. She likes to say that it's perfect newlywed hair (I'll excuse you while you gag yourself).   We returned to work Tuesday morning, and it was sort of a let down, but not too bad. I had enough to keep me busy and Sarah's office is gearing up for the NOW conference, which is taking place this weekend in Arlington.  Today at work we had the summer golf outing, which was a lot of fun despite the fact that nothing I hit went straight and I lost about 8 balls in ten holes before it started pouring rain and we had to quit. I am bad at golf...there, I said it.  Well, that's the update. We'll try to be a little more regular about this blog thing, but no guarantees. Also, look for updates to  urlLink sarahandnicholas.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Bang! Pow! To the moon!   We leave Saturday for our honeymoon. We're going to St. Thomas for a week, and we are going to do absolutely nothing. It should be a good time, we'll let you know when we get back.    
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Moving In, Again   Sarah and I are no longer in Washington, DC. We left Saturday morning, and drove the four-hour drive in just under seven hours. Apparently, all the people from DC, Northern Virginia, and lower Maryland flock to Virginia beach, clogging up I-95 for 100s of miles on their way. It was amazingly frustrating, but it's over, thank God. Also, thanks to Annie and Kyle for helping us move out of our DC apartment and for countless other unrepaid favors over the summer.  We're now in Durham. We've been moving into our apartment for the last day and a half. We also made a trek out to Target in Raleigh to spend our Target gift certificates on more of our registry stuff. It was a good time. The place is a wreck, but we're getting through it.  In other news, I found out last week that if you need to, you can get 1) a birth certificate delivered to your door in under a week or 2) a passport in a day if you're willing to pay for it. These realizations came soon after I realized that I needed one or the other to travel to St. Thomas. What I don't understand is why if I'm traveling from the US to a US protectorate I have to prove that I'm a US citizen? Didn't we spread our empire to the beautiful Caribbean for a reason? Jeez. By the way, you can only get a passport in a day if you live in DC or NY, and it's by appointment only. However, you can pay a service to do it for you in 3 days, but it'll cost you...a lot. I should be getting a birth certificate delivered tomorrow via FedEx.  I'd better cut this short, I'm not holding up my end of the deal on the unpacking thing (Sarah's just so good at it and seems to enjoy it, so why should I ruin her fun?). 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       What?   Honest to God, someone wants to start a student group called "Students for Genital Integrity," here at Duke Law. They support getting patient consent prior to circumcision. Great.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Excuse Me, Four   Sarah got another call this afternoon. She's on a roll.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Addendum: Make That Three   Sarah just got a call from another job interviewer. After a month of hearing almost nothing; this....When it rains, it pours.  
     
    
</post>

<date>22,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Friday   I promise at some point I will get Sarah to blog again, but I'm not guaranteeing that it will be soon. Until then, you're going to have to put up with me.  Sarah has two (count 'em two) job interviews today. One is with a temp. service and the other for her current dream job, which is as an administrative assistant at a non-profit organization headquartered in Chapel Hill.  It looks like she'll be gainfully employed soon at one of these, but there's no telling. Everyone keep their fingers crossed for her.  Annie and Kyle are visiting us from the DC area this weekend. This has given Sarah a reason to use the china again, which gives her more joy than it should give anyone. I guess it's better than just letting it sit in the cabinet like it does now--though that way it never gets dirty. This looks to be the first of a string of weekends where we have visitors. I think we have people "booked" through October 17.   BTW, does anyone else think that Osten should have been kicked off of Survivor last night? I mean, Ryan S. sucked a lot (okay, a whole lot), but Osten didn't even act like he wanted to be there (which, by the way, would really piss me off if I were the last survivor candidate to get kicked out in favor of Osten).   Sarah and I have wondered aloud out at why these people don't sleep during the day. It's not like they really have that much to do and if they're not sleeping at night  anyway ...I don't get it.   Also, what's with having to see  urlLink Lady Scoutmaster Lillian  in her underwear last night? Feh. (BTW, Lady Scoutmaster reminds me of that Prince song "Lady Cabdriver" from the  1999  album.)
     
    
</post>

<date>22,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, having survived the first hurricane of our marriage, we thought that we had made it without a power outage. Apparently not, though, because the power went out for a couple of hours on Saturday for no apparent reason. I think this usually happens when they start reconnecting everyone's power and they have big power surges when everyone's toaster/oven/TV/vcr/iron/lamps all turn back on at once and they overload some transformer somewhere. Ah well, it could've been worse.  In other news, with the final addition of slip-covers for the couch and love seat and a few pillows, I think we have also weathered our first home-decoration. Although I kicked and screamed the whole way about the necessity of certain items, I'm a cheap bastard and the apartment really does look good, especially for our budget. Of course, we couldn't have done it without the generosity of all of you at our wedding, so we thank you as well. Now we get to do it all over again in 9 months in DC, although I've been promised that much of what we have now, we can use later.  Also, does anyone know a high school student that might want to apply to Transy? Sarah and I received an application with a fee waiver to give to the high school student of our choice. Unfortunately, we don't know any anymore. Do you?
     
    
</post>

<date>19,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Hurricane Isabel   Well, chalk it up to karma from the ice-storm, but we didn't even lose power last night, except for a couple of 5 second outages. The winds were high and the rain was plentiful, but we're fine.  It appears that much of Durham, including most of my classmates, lost power and have not had it restored yet. I haven't seen many crews around my area, but my guess is that most people should have power by tomorrow night--but what do I know?  More later.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       The Day-to-Day   Well, Durham gets more the same all the time. Not much has happened since the last entry, but I guess that's good.  We've got this hurricane coming our way, which should make for even more crappy weather as the week continues, as well as possible power outages and other massive inconveniences. After living through an ice storm with no power for a week, I can honestly say that I think that losing power this time won't be as bad because of the mild weather.  This winter was honestly the crappiest unintended cold-weather campout of all time. Nevertheless, losing power is still not something I welcome anytime.  Sarah had a "group" job interview today, which she described as "new agey." It consisted of some asinine individual questionnaire, followed by a group portion. She's supposed to hear back about that soon. She's also looking into leads at a non-profit in Durham and Lexis-Nexis. Anyone have a job they can offer her??? I have started a research assistant job at the school which requires that I transcribe jury deliberations. It is easily the most demanding thing I have ever done patience wise. It requires almost no skill, yet takes FOREVER.  Well, enough bitching. Almost everything is good here. I saw Freddy vs. Jason last night, which was surprisingly decent even though I was certain it was going to be about a lawsuit for copyright or trade dress infringement and it ended up being a horror movie (actually I guess that would be  Freddy v. Jason ). Moreover, I saw Duke football win a game against Rice University in overtime n Saturday, which was even more horrific. Who could ask for anything more?    
     
    
</post>

<date>07,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Back to School, Back To School   After returning from our honeymoon, which was fantastic, we have settled in Durham quite nicely. I have started school and Sarah has been in the midst of her job search for the last two weeks. We think she may be close to getting a job she'll like at a non-profit, so everyone keep their fingers crossed.  School is school, but it's even harder to get motivated because I recently received and accepted an offer for permanent employment from the firm that I worked at this summer. This was really great news and finally solidifies that we'll be in Washington, D.C. for the foreseeable future- as long as I pass the Bar Exam that is.  Josh Davis lives in Chapel Hill, so we went to lunch with him this weekend and got caught up on the Decatur happenings. We also saw The Magdalene Sisters, which was good, but made me feel really lucky not to have any Catholic-nun baggage...  Anyway, it's good to be in a routine again after such a crazy summer, and maybe that means the blog will become more regular too. I know how happy that would make you guys...
     
    
</post>

<date>31,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Halloween Festivities   After last night's unexciting and generally boring Duke Law Halloween Party (which, sadly, is labeled "The Best Duke Law Party of the Year), we are headed out tonight to Chapel Hill, which is apparently one of the best Halloween experiences this side of New Orleans/Transylvania University.   "They" expect that 75,000 people will descend on Chapel Hill tonight. For those of you who have been there, you know how amazing that is given the size of Franklin St. Sarah has to go for work, she's dressing up as Rosie the Riveter and handing out condoms and info about the EC line. I'm not dressing up, but I think they are going to tape condoms to me. I hope the condoms are still in the wrappers. I'd better go check on that...   Maggie Update   Maggie has gained about 2-3 pounds since we got her three weeks ago. The vet says that she will double in size from 4 to 6 months, so we're guessing that she will be about 15-20 pounds.   She's growing really fast, and we're trying to break her of her puppy habits, though largely unsuccessfully. She still likes to nip at hands and feet, which terrifies children at the park. She also likes to chew the ends of shoelaces until the plastic part is no more. Recently she learned that she could jump off of the couch, which has ruined one of our techniques for keeping tabs on her when we're in the kitchen, etc. Does anybody have a baby-gate they don't need anymore???
     
    
</post>

<date>29,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Best. Homestarrunner. Ever.   I know almost no one appreciates  urlLink homestarrunner.com  as much as I do. But the  urlLink Halloween cartoon  this year is hilarious. I especially like The Cheat as the 1996 Olympics Mascot, Izzy.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Cars Are Funny   You may recall that about 8 months ago, I had to get a wheel-rim replaced on the Corolla because I ran into a curb while driving after an ice-storm. It sucked and it ended up costing about 150 bucks after the new rim and the alignment, etc. All in all, not too bad an experience, though I could have done without it.  Well, in a stroke of genius, I managed to bend another wheel rim, this time while driving in seventy-degree weather. This time, unlike last time, the tire went flat and I thought I had really screwed the rim up bad. It more or less put a damper on our weekend because we had to wait until today to go get it fixed and we had plans to go driving in the mountains to see the leaves change. This morning, really frickin' early, I went to Firestone, where I had it fixed last time. This time, they looked at it, took it back and beat it with a hammer and checked the balance, and then they handed it back to me. Charge: 12 bucks. I don't really know how this time is different from last, but it was, so I'm not complaining.   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       I Didn't Believe in Curses, Until Last Night   Poor Red Sox.  urlLink Poor Sox Fans.   Poor Cubs. Poor Cubs Fans.  Poor rest of the world not in New York or Florida, who once again will not get to watch a good World Series. Think about it, the last Four World Series have been awful.   2000, The Subway Series--Not a single person outside of New York cared, especially since everyone knew that the Yankees were going to kill the Mets.  2001, Yankees-Diamondbacks-- A couple of good games, and it was nice to see the Yankees finally go down, but were  you   watching?  2002, Angels-Giants--Zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz...what's the time difference between here and Caleeforneah?  2003, Marlins-Yankees--Team that no one's ever heard of vs. team that no one wants to hear about again. The two teams that nobody wanted to win end up in the Series. Somebody tell me who wins. (Can MLB get a losers bracket so we can see who wins the more interesting match-up?)  At any rate, I don't plan on this becoming a sports blog, but I've been watching a lot of sports on my week off, including repeats of the World Series of Poker. We also got a DVR from the cable company. It's not quite TiVo, but it works for us.   Maggie is doing well. She had her first vet visit with us. We took her to the clinic where her foster mother works. She was very brave, and barked at dogs at least 12 times her size.  She's currently snoring in my lap.  Sarah is enjoying her job, especially the fact that the staff at PPCNC is mostly female. The office seems happy to have her, as well.  Sarah has uploaded pictures of Maggie and of the Holland parents' visit, which we'll send around to interested parties soon.   
     
    
</post>

<date>08,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Explain This to Me   I know I usually don't complain about this stuff on the blog, but can someone explain to me why Georgia v. Tennessee, the #10 and #14 teams respectively are relegated to ESPN 2 while Notre Dame (unranked) vs. Pittsburgh (#16) gets put on the main network? Anti-SEC bias I tell you.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Maggie   Yes, it's true, we have a dog. Unfortunately what we also have is an unreasonable transfer restriction on our Geocities account, which will probably cause more than half of our faithful readers to not be able to access urlLink these pictures of her first day in our new apartment .  Please bear with us, as well will put together an Ofoto scapbook and send it out as soon as we can access the high-speed connection at Duke.   Meanwhile, you could always  urlLink watch this .
     
    
</post>

<date>05,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        J-O-B=D-O-G    Since this summer, the deal with Nicholas has been I have to get a job before we can get a dog. So two days after becoming the newest employee at Planned Parenthood we are now the proud parents of a small terrier puppy named Maggie.   It was fate. We have been looking at shelters for a while. I was becoming discouraged because we couldn't find a smaller dog like we wanted. Last night, I had started looking into buying one and was going to start calling today. However, we were in Chapel Hill showing a visiting friend when Nicholas suggested going by the shelter. Right inside the door, they have cages for featured pets, usually cats. As we walked in a woman was closing the cage door for a little puppy. Turns out it was Maggie's foster mom who  had just dropped her off so people could look at for a little while. We were the first ones to see and of course adopted her immediately. We get to pick her up tomorrow so we spent the rest of today stocking up on puppy supplies and doing our research on house training.   And yes for all those who are wondering...she is the cutest puppy EVER!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Sarah=Gainfully Employed   Starting next Wednesday, Sarah is employed as an administrative assistant in Chapel Hill. Let the party begin! 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       The Past Couple Weeks   A quick update:  Sarah is absolutely loving her job.   Maggie was spayed, micro-chipped, and received her first rabies shot. I think the experience was more stressful for us than it was for her. She also chipped a canine tooth, which required another trip to the vet. The vet says her tooth is fine (she's going to lose it anyway), and since she was Maggie's foster mother, there was no charge for the visit. She will be traveling with us to Atlanta over the break. The parents have graciously allowed us to give this a try, so we'll see how Maggie deals with the scent of cat in the air.   School is going along quickly. I'm rapidly approaching the "oh-shit-it's-exam time already" stage. Though I don't think I'll be in any way laid back this time around, having a job already for next year certainly takes the pressure off.  In the future:  Sarah is traveling to Lexington this weekend to throw a baby shower for her friend Elizabeth, who is expecting in January. I will be remaining at home to study and spend some quality time with my favorite dog. I hope Maggie has some insights into the Earned Income Tax Credit that she could share with me.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Dog Alarm Clock   If anyone wants to know when it's 7:30 am, just ask Maggie.  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Holy Crap    urlLink Yahoo! News - Eleven Die After Grasshoppers Swarm 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        An addition...    Nicholas forgot to add my explanation to said truckers and receptionist of what I do at Planned Parenthood.  I was able to explain the difference between emergency contraception and the abortion pill to both. While as previously mentioned, the receptionist will not be needing EC anytime soon perhaps she will pass on this valuable information to everyone she knows.  Another positive result of the day was that I discovered the BEST new show on TLC called Clean Sweep. All I can say is it involves organizing, decorating AND a yard sale. Can you sincerely ask for anything more? 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       As Promised, A West Virginia Christmas   Due to the unfortunate passing of Sarah's great-grandmother, we (Sarah, Maggie, and I) started our trek to Paducah on Saturday instead of the next Tuesday so that we could attend the funeral. We had planned to leave Durham at 7:30, reaching Louisville by 4 pm, and then travel the the last 3 hours to Paducah on Sunday so that we could be at the visitation that evening. Unfortunately, someone had other plans for us.  At 11 am, about 20 miles outside of Beckley, West Virginia (for you regular Sarah and Nicholas followers, you know that Beckley holds a special place in our hearts), the engine in the previously trusty and problem-free Corolla began to rev really high. Since there is no tachometer in the car, my first thought was that it was just the mountain incline, the thin air, and the fact that we were in a storm that was dumping 5 inches of snow on the snowy peaks of Central West Virginia. I was wrong.  As we continued, the engine revving got louder and when I slowed and put the car into fourth, the transmission didn't respond properly. We pulled over and (after I freaked out for a few seconds) decided that we needed to see if we could make it to the next exit. To its credit, the Corolla made it the 2 miles to the next exit, where we pulled into the nearest gas station and started demanding answers (Well, actually we just asked where the nearest service station was.) This being Saturday, we were pretty unhopeful of finding someone to fix our car, and had resigned ourselves to live in West Virginia for the rest of our lives.  After determining where the nearest service station was, we got back in the car and made it about a block before the car decided that it had taken enough abuse that day and that it was not going to move any longer, no matter how much we begged it. At this point, the first kindness of strangers moment occurred as the man behind us jumped out of his car and began to help me push the car to the next closest gas station, about 75 feet. He then disappeared without a trace (that is, he got back in his car and went home). At this service station, things really started to look bad as the manager told us that the service station we were going to was closed. Fortunately, another stranger overheard us and informed us that he knew a place that might be able to fix our car, and might be able to do it "today." Needless to say, I was a little bit incredulous at this possibility. I knew that we'd need a new part and that this was at least a 4 hour job, if not more. The mysterious stranger (we'll call him Jim, since that was his name) called the station and ordered us a tow truck and told the manager to "treat us right." He also informed us that we were in Ghent, WV (pronounced "jent" as in gentleman, despite the famous treaty of the same name which is pronounced with a hard G).  After about 20 minutes of waiting in the car, the tow came and (after we pushed the car into three different places to position it for the tow), took us down the back roads of Ghent, Beaver, and Beckley until finally we came to a turn off. Almost immediately I got an eerie feeling, as there was no service station actually within the sightline of the road. Thoughts of Jim telling them to "treat us right" raced through my head, as I bemoaned our decision not to train Maggie to sic. Fortunately, after a few turns, we were at a large service station/junkyard and they unloaded our car. Though we were uncertain about our fate for the day, we thought that the worst of it was over. We were only partly right.  After unloading Maggie and a few of our belongings from the car, we were told that we should go sit in the lounge and wait while they worked on some of the other vehicles that they had in the shop. In the lounge on top of the painted concrete were two faux-leather couches, a TV (with cable), and two 30-40 something truckers. They were watching Fox News and talking when we walked in, dog in tow (because she wouldn't willingly walk across the concrete--primadonna) and plopped down on the couch. Being the second-comers, we didn't get a say in what we watched, so we got to see a fair and balanced look at the war on terror for about an hour and a half, with the two truckers (who were exceedingly nice), discussing their takes on the issues of the day and talking about what it was that was wrong with their trucks. Eventually, one of them got to move on and the other had to go discuss his vehicle with the mechanic, so Sarah used this window to change the station to TLC. When the trucker returned, she decided that instead of changing the station back, she would try to convince him that "What Not to Wear" was entertainment the whole family could enjoy. She explained to him the premise of the show and as they watched, they both commented on the progress of the young high-school teacher that was being made over. At one point, this exchange occurred:   Trucker  (talking about the male fashion consultant on the show): That one's queer ain't he?   Sarah : Yes, I think he's a homosexual.   Me : (Stifled laughter)   And a few minutes later:   Trucker : I need to get my daughter on this show.   Sarah : Really, why is that?   Trucker : All she ever wears is black...I mean, she ain't one of those Goths, but she wears a lot of black.   Sarah : Ohh...  By the time of the reveal on "What Not to Wear," the second driver had left, but not before giving us a case of bite size Quaker Oatmeal Chocolate Chip Cookies, which were (and continue to be) delicious. On a side note, apparently it's not uncommon for drivers to take or give away some of their inventory. The dispatcher at the mechanic's told us that he had a year's supply of detergent from the last time they fixed a Big Lots truck.  By this time it was about 1:00 and out car had just been moved into the mechanic's bay. Much to noone's surprise, at about 1:10, the mechanic came to the conclusion that our clutch was burnt out and would have to be replaced. I was not hopeful that he would be able to fix it by close of business, but he then informed me that they have mechanics on staff 24 hours a day, 7 days a week, 365 days a year (including Christmas). Unfortunately, he also told me that he wouldn't be able to work on the car straight through the day because he would have to go out occasionally to do roadside repairs. He told me that if he could get the part, he could have probably have us on our way by 7 or 8. This was a lie, but at least it was a little lie. He also told me that it would take about 5 hours to fix and gave me an estimate of about 550 dollars. Meanwhile, Sarah sat in the lounge and began to go slowly crazy.   After several hours and a number of circuits around the junkyard (with and without the dog), it didn't look like we were going to get close to leaving by 8, and Sarah began to cross-stitch "All wait and no drive make Sarah go crazy" over and over again. She also began to ask for a time estimate about ever hour from 6 on, each time being told that it would be a "couple more hours." It was a little bit like "Groundhog Day." We also started to talk to the night dispatcher and the night-shift tow drivers. The two drivers were pretty strange. One of them suggested that the other might sodomize our dog, making West Virginians everywhere proud that their reputations as strange and toothless people was not to be thwarted by the kindness of the rest of the people we met that day.  The night dispatcher, after hearing about Sarah's job, also informed us that she "couldn't have no more babies" because, as she put it,"I's spayed." Sarah then left the room and reentered with an axe, screaming "Heeeeeeeere's Johnny!!!" (Okay, so The Shining references are getting a little ridiculous, but we really felt at some point like we might never leave the driver's lounge, and the snow storm made the effect all the more creepy).   We also found out about the newest craze in potpourri. The night dispatcher had a plush teddy bear dipped in scented wax which is used as an air freshener. Apparently they are hot sellers and "if the smell ever goes away, you just hea tit with a hair dryer and the smell will come back." We resisted the temptation to ask where we could purchase one, mostly because, as Sarah put it, "the bear smelled like rancid cough syrup."  Finally, at about 10:30, the mechanic took our car for a test drive to make sure it shifted correctly and (after another thirty minutes of tinkering because it was "making a sound.") we paid for the repair and tow (580 dollars altogether, of which the 80 for the tow is going to be reimbursed by AAA), and headed to Louisville at 11 pm, arriving at 3 am to a surprisingly still awake Elizabeth, Shelly, and Aimee.  For all of the strange events we are truly thankful for all of the people in Ghent and Beckley who actually cared about our predicament and helped us to (miraculously) get a relatively major car repair done for a fair price, on the Saturday before Christmas. Sarah has made a full recovery from her stir-craziness, and Maggie survived, too. I, however, never want to travel again.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       West Virginia Story Coming Soon   On our way to Kentucky our clutch burnt out and we were stuck in a mechanic's lounge in West Virginia for 11 hours. (The mechanic is open 365 days a year, 24 hours a day). Hilarity did not ensue. More later. Merry Christmas.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Funny, in that The Onion-sort-of-not-that-funny-anymore way     urlLink So-Called Obese Pets Held To Unrealistic Body Standards 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Ah, well, there's always next year    urlLink Decatur lost to Buford    in the state semi-final. I think the final score was 42-13. That's a shame, but at least the Bulldogs can be proud of a great season, and build on this next year.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Can this man make Duke football great again?   No sportsfans, I speak not of Ted Roof, newly installed head coach of Duke University Football, but rather of  urlLink Duke's Next President , Richard H. Brodhead, current dean at Yale and and the A. Bartlett Giamatti Professor of English at Yale University. He was chosen recently to replace Nannerl Keohane, and once knew the man that his professorship is named after, the same Bart Giamatti who was Commissioner of Major League Baseball and kicked Pete Rose out. Most importantly, though, he says that he is an "avid college sports fan, which I clearly will have an opportunity to experience at Duke." He's probably talking about basketball (you can't have a discussion about Duke anywhere without someone talking about the basketball Blue Devils), but I hope he doesn't forget the best sport in the land.  Either way, his name is WAY easier to say than President Keohane's.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Aaaaaaacccccccccccccccccckkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkk....(Or, How I Came to Love One of the Largest Financial Institutions in the Country)   So, since Sarah and I have started a budget, I have stopped obsessing about checking our account balances online every fifteen minutes. Unfortunately, today this bit me in the ass to the tune of 120 bucks in overdraft fees. I was none too pleased, and I still haven't figured out what happened accounting wise (though I have taken the precaution of now assuming that we have about 125 bucks less than we do according to the latest B of A statement). Because of the amount and the fact that we don't really have 120 bucks to give the bank, I decided that I should overcome my fear of talking to people and call to see if anything could be done to salvage a generally crappy afternoon. Turns out there was.  I calmly explained myself to the uber-polite Bank of America representative that I thought that I had "overdraft protection" on my account (and, honest to God, I thought I did, I can probably even find the literature about it), and that this should protect me from exactly this eventuality (buying a 3 dollar coffee and getting a 30 dollar fee), by transferring 100 dollars into my account automatically for a five dollar fee. She looked at my accounts, and found that for some odd reason I did not have said protection, but that she would link my accounts from here on out, and would credit me for the 3, 30 dollar fees that were visible on her screen (the last one is still pending, and she said it may not actually show up, but if it did to call.) Thus, as of now I stand only 30 dollars in the hole for my stupid mistake. Though I had thought about changing banks in the near future, I have decided that Bank of America has earned my business for as long as I can find a close-by ATM. I guess it never hurts to ask.   Update:  I called today and got the last charge refunded. Woo-hoo!
     
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       New Comments   Although Squawkbox always told me that it was a "free" commenting service, apparently that's only good for a year. I was informed that I would pretty soon be required to pay for their service. Therefore, being the extreme cheapskate that I am, I have switched to Haloscan, which is not only free, but also has more features than Squawkbox.   Unfortunately, all of the old comments have gone away, never to return. I know this is a blow to all of you who frequent this blog to reminisce about the old days when you commented on our spelling and grammar, but, alas, those days are no more. (At least until you make new comments about our spelling and grammar. (Hey, you leave my grammar out of this!))
     
    
</post>

<date>06,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       That sucks   Though it doesn't damper my excitement much, it's a little disheartening to know that the team that Decatur plays next has won 43 in a row, and that their running back is attempting to break the single-season touchdown record shared by Herschel Walker and Charles Grant. Ah well, maybe he'll go to UGA, where I can one day cheer him on. Kind of like Tim Wansley (also from Buford).  Exams are sucky. I have Federal Income Tax on Friday. I often wonder why I decided to take this class, and I still don't know.  
     
    
</post>

<date>06,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Wow   Could it really be true that Decatur High School is in the semi-finals of the state championship for AA? They play Buford next and they get to play in the  Georgia Dome . Tonihgt in the Georgia Dome, UGA plays LSU for the SEC Championship.   I really don't like the fact that one of the most exciting weeks in college football falls in the middle of exams. I was going to make a cheesy law school joke, but I've decided against it....  
     
    
</post>

<date>29,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       No, No, No, No, No, No,....Please Don't   Someone make  urlLink this stop. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Snowing   We got about 3 inches of snow yesterday and expect more ice and snow tonight. Good thing we stocked up on milk and toilet paper.   Maggie is especially interested in the snow, having only experienced it once before (see West Virginia Christmas story). We went to the apartment tennis courts yesterday and let her off her leash to let her explore it on her own. We have mini-tennisballs that she can get in her mouth, but she wasn't interested in the icy tennis ball yesterday. She would run with it for a few seconds and then drop it.  After a few minutes we were all too cold to continue, so we went inside and watched Back tot he Future and Back to the Future II on the DVD player. The inDemand video isn't working right now, so even though we purchased Harold and Maude, we weren't able to watch it--rats. 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Celebrating Choice   Today is the 31st anniversary of Roe v. Wade. As one can imagine, this is quite a big deal at Planned Parenthood. There was a press conference this morning and tonight  is Rock n Roe, our benefit concert. All proceeds will go to the March for Women's Lives in Washington, DC, April 25. (If  you are prochoice, plan on being there!)  Being raised Southern Baptist, I have a constant voice in my head that argues against my pro-choice beliefs. It places blame, hands out plenty of guilt, and sounds an awful lot like my old youth minister.  When the voice becomes too much, I usually find myself looking around me at the amazing people I work with and the patients we serve everyday. My coworkers are kind, passionate, dedicated people that stand up for the women everyone forgets - minority women, poor women, immigrant women.  The patients are always relieved to find a place free of judgment and full of kindness. These people remind me that choice is not really about politics, religion, or government. It is about women and the life decisions they have right to make. Or as my coworker says Pro choice is pro life when women's lives matter.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Spam Poetry (Written at the end of an advertisement for I don't know what)   Support open-source. She will work it out on her own; let her be. I think the purple was better than the blue. What a good idea? Is it really so different from TV? People like to be spoken to as they speak -- simply and to the point. I am scared of watching the news and reading the newspaper. Rainbows dont' just appear out of nowhere. I love to kiss and tell. There is a great conspiracy brewing. He talks and looks like a puppet but loves to be called george. I love you dearly.Will work for happiness. Here's my point: The rich are benefiting at the expense of everyone else. The proposal is going as planned. Sit back and relax--this will all be over soon. A lot of people are talking about this.I believe in the golden mean. You are my best friend.  
     
    
</post>

<date>15,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Amazon.com marketplace--What did we do before the Internet?   In the past two weeks I have sold three textbooks for about 40 bucks a piece on Amazon.com marketplace. If I tried to sell these books back at the regular bookstore rather than to another poor student, I probably would have gotten about 12 dollars total. I know it doesn't need to be said, but how great is the Internet???  Not much else to say. I have started my last semester of law school. I am excited, but a bit hesitant to end my run as a professional student. Tangentially related to that, I was filling out my Bar application and found myself writing a narrative of the time I got suspended in high school for cursing too much at a soccer game--those were the days. BTW, does anyone remember what date that was? The Virginia Board of Bar Examiners wants to know.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Over the weekend, I noticed that one of Maggie's ears had fallen back down. That's right they were both down, then one was up for about 2 months, now it's back down. Weird...
     
    
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Clean Sweeping   If you don't know by now, Clean Sweep is new (meaning we ripped the idea off from the Brits) home improvement show on TLC. They clean, they purge, the organize, they decorate.  Inspired by the show, I finally threw out the yard sale stuff. Since I don't have a yard in which to sell and probably won't for awhile. I also purged a lot of books and Nicholas and I sold them around  time  town. Nice Price books gave us $15.00 Book Seller gave us $20.00 Books on Ninth gave us $35.00 in store credit to buy more books we don't need.  A grand total of $70.00 (sort of). Way more than we would have made selling them for .25 cents a piece! 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Since my husband uses the blog to rant occasionally about sports and my New Year's Resolution was to write on the bog more, I have decided that I will share my thoughts on a subject that is very close to my heart...the upcoming presidential election. It seems appropriate considering the election is exactly ten months to the day away.  I'm not going to predict a winner or any such nonsense because truthfully I have no idea what will happen. I do however know that in the circles I run (excluding DeWayne and my stepdad) everyone wants Bush to lose. The problem is no one is willing to do anything about it. Everyone wants to offer their opinions but no one wants to get up off their butt and do anything. My fear is if this complacency continues we will soon be looking at another four years of Dubya - another four years of war, greed, and everything bad in the world.  If we are to stop this from happening, then we must start campaigning NOW. I don't care who you support. I personally support Dean and spent last night writing letters to citizens of Iowa hopefully convincing them to do the same. However, if you like Kucinich, that's fine. Tell everyone you know about Kucinich. The important thing is not only to inform people how good your candidate is but how truly bad Bush is and how absolutely essential it is that they vote.  It doesn't take much. Spread the word. Pass out flyers. Write letters. I promise you they'll take your help. Lord knows they/we need it. It's now or never and November is just around the corner.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Me and Cars, Part II   Last weekend, I visited one of my best friends Elizabeth Ferrell and her new little baby, David (better known as Punkin'). Aimee Hicks (another close friend) and I set out on the long seven hour trip to Louisville, KY at about 4:30pm on Thursday afternoon. Aimee was concerned that her engine was running a little hot so we decided to stop in Auto Protocall for quick check-up. Unfortunately, we got there at 4:50 and they close at 5pm. However, the man at the front generously agreed to come look at our car in the parking lot. He established that we had plenty of coolant and that nothing on the service seemed terribly wrong. He also informed us that as long as the temperature gage on the dash didn't pass into the red we were fine. Now, I'm pretty hard on cars (perhaps why I've already been thro two) but Aimee leans more toward safety or paranoia which ever you prefer. She wasn't comfortable just turning on the defrost and therefore cooling the engine so we decided to try Walmart. (I know I know but it's not my car)  Upon pulling up we quickly established that this was only a Tire and Lube Express. However, I decided it wouldn't hurt to ask for some help. I did decide it would hurt to ask the purse-lipped lady inside at the desk so I yelled at one of the mechanics in the garage. He informed me they couldn't do the work at Walmart but he would be glad to take a look. So Duke (our new best friend) came outside and quickly established that Aimee's thermostat is broken. He then informs us that he can call his cousin who could come over and fix it in about 15 minutes if we could get the part. Meanwhile time is ticking away and we decide to ask our respective fiance/husband if we can borrow their cars and both our respective fiance/husbands say no. Well Aimee gives up but I kick and cry till NIcholas relents which is about the same time Duke says his cousin is on the way and Johan (Aimee's fiance) volunteers to rent us a car.  We decide to have Nicholas go get the new thermostat (which the people at Autozone say they have but then change their mind but then find it again).   By now it's about 7:00pm and Duke's cousin has still not shown up. Everyone is getting anxious including Nicholas who has shown up with the new thermostat. Finally, Derrick  the infamous cousin shows up and goes to work on Aimee's car - in the middle of the Walmart parking lot. He works and works and works. Finally about an hour later he's finished and he says wants to take it for a test drive to make sure everything is working. After instructing us to remove our pocketbooks(his word not mine), he takes a couple of laps around the parking lot and established the fans still aren't kicking on. Seeing our desperate faces, he explains he can cut some wires and hook the fans directly to the battery or we can trust that the high speed wind will keep the engine cool. We chose option two. We thank Derrick and ask how much we should pay him. He instructs Aimee to pay him "whatever you think is fair" We give Derrick as much money as we can afford and the promise of our firstborns. Around 9:00 we set out, Derrick's girlfriends phone number in tow "in case we run into any trouble."   We arrive in Lexington at 3:45am and spend the night there. We go to Louisville and spend a lovely weekend with our friends and the baby, who are just glad we're there. Although my friend Erin asked in amazement, "Where do you find these people?!?" 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       As Expected   Maggie now has her own  urlLink Dogster page .   Ed.note:  The last post about what I've been doing lately disappeared for some reason. Rest assured that it wasn't that interesting, and most of the links can be found on the left hand side of the page
     
    
</post>

<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Decisions, Decisions, Decisions...   I have now received acceptance (or rejection) letters from all the law schools I applied to. The final tally goes a little something like this:   urlLink Georgetown : Rejected  urlLink George Washington : Waitlisted  urlLink George Mason : Accepted  urlLink American : Accepted  Overall, I am very happy with my lot and there were no major surprises. Now of course comes the hard part.   I visited George Mason this weekend. While there were certain aspects of the school I liked, overall I don't think I would be very happy there. They are extremely competitive and have a strong focus on economics (not something I'm terribly interested in). The clincher however was when I asked my student guide about gender studies and my interest in this area she pretty much told me to go to American.   American has basically built itself up to be THE feminist law school, obviously something that appeals to me. Also a friend from college visited there and really liked the overall feeling of the school.   Yet, I would still like to see what will happen with GW. Unfortunately, the chances of me hearing from them before my seat deposit at American is due are slim. Ughhh....I'll keep everyone posted.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Only at Centre    urlLink Centre College , sometime rival of our  urlLink alma mater ,  urlLink has a class called "Basketball as Religion." 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Interesting Tidbits   When you run spell check on a blog entry, it pulls up blog as a misspelled word (Replace with bloc, Bloch, blow)...  A woman in France married her dead fiance yesterday. She had to get special permission from the president...  I found out yesterday that in some government language schools they serve diluted wine to lower people's inhibitions so that they feel more comfortable practicing their pronunciation...  My husband sent me tulips yesterday officially making him the sweetest man ever!
     
    
</post>

<date>08,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Were the Grammys held in a high school gym this year?   Though I liked the fact that they pulled Prince out of the closet and dusted him off, the Grammys have pretty much sucked so far. And what's with the early-90's graphics?  
     
    
</post>

<date>06,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Sarah May Just Be Right   According to  urlLink this article in the NY Times , gay marriage may be one of the issues that defines this campaign.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I don't even know where to start...   I read two stories yesterday that helped me reach an important decision. One was "The Note" an election commentary by abc news. The second was the cover story of Newsweek entitled "Why We Were Wrong" which explored the evidence given for the war in Iraq. My conclusion: that there is a serious chance I could go crazy before this election is over.  I say this because I suddenly realized something very important. Instead of talking about why our commander-in-chief led us into a preemptive war on faulty evidence during this election, we're are going to be talking about whether or not the government should be able to tell me who I should marry. (The answer to that question by the way is no.) This is not to say that I do not believe gay marriage is an important issue. I do. I believe it is an issue based fundamentally on your moral beliefs in homosexuality which last time I checked every person gets to decide for themselves. However instead this is going to become another hot button issue to distract from political issues of governmental importance...like the war on faulty evidence previously mentioned. The true irony here is that the party of "personal responsibility" is going to be calling for it on one issue while passing the buck on the other.   So that is the end of my rant and Nicholas is now officially kicking himself for asking me to blog more.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Why God invented Tivo...   Since the four blogs I check regularly haven't mentioned the incident, I will now state how I feel about the Super Bowl/Janet Jackson incident...  It was just a boob (and what I imagine was a very expensive nipple medallion) get the frick over it.   I feel better now.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Congratulations Are Due...   Sarah was accepted to George Mason Law School today. She is waiting to hear from GWU and American, and we have plans to go visit these schools soon to help her make her decision.   Congratulations are also due to Shelly and Elizabeth, who welcomed a baby boy, David Shelly, into the world on Saturday. He was 9 lbs. 5 oz. and 21.5 inches long.  Wow.  
     
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The Sloganator   I'm admittedly the last person to blog about this, but this  urlLink slideshow of posters created with the Bush-Cheney sloganator  is one of the funniest things I've watched in a while.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Calling all Georgians!   Get your senator UNDER CONTROL!   urlLink Georgia Senator Stumps for Bush 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This however does not suck. In fact it is dang near awesome.   urlLink GAS BUDDY 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I want to be really clear about this. It completely and utterly sucks. I don't know what else to say.   urlLink http://www.365gay.com/newscon04/03/031704fedWorkers.htm   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Now that I think about it...   Last night I chased Maggie around for five minutes trying to retrieve a razor blade from her mouth that she had dug out of the bathroom trashcan.  Once I caught her, she ran to the corner and promptly took a shit on the carpet which she hasn't done in months. Did I mention Nicholas had  just  taken her outside?  In other words, maybe one dog is plenty.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Two is better one?   Well people are starting to complain so I suppose it's time for a new post. Although, everyone might want to get used to sparse posting as we are entering a very exciting but stressful period. In the next six months, one of will graduate from law school, one of us will enter law school. One of us will leave our first real job and the other will start their first real job. Nicholas will take the biggest test of his life. We will both be in a wedding a piece. We will be moving from North Carolina to Washington, D.C. where we will buy a house and a car.  It's a darn good thing we just went on vacation. (We had a lovely time by the way)   On top of everything else, we (well mainly me) are considering getting another dog. This is the primarily the result the vacation Maggie had while we were in Wilmington. My wonderful boss, Karen, agreed to keep her. Karen has two dogs, Rudy and Haley, who weigh about 60lbs apiece. You would think our own little 12lb dog would be frightened or anxious but oh no! Maggie can definitely run with the big dogs. Karen said she ran and romped with Rudy for hours on end until  Rudy  finally gave up in exhaustion. And she is the same way at the dog park. She runs and chases other dogs and just has a grand old time. Being the lazy jerks that we are, we  could never give her the physical exercise and fun another dog could. So there it is...now I'll just set back and let the warnings come from my mother and grandmother who didn't even want me to get Maggie.  I wonder if this is the same reasoning people use when having more kids?
     
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Bleahhhhhh....   I don't feel well today, I've got a head cold.  I'm also trying to figure out all this Bar preparation stuff and apply for the bar.  Come to think of it, maybe I can get some help from you people. $0.75 per answer to anyone that can answer any of the following questions. One winner per question.  1) What's the number for the Dekalb County Traffic Court?   2) What was the last year that USA Pools ran the Decatur Pools? (I will take the first year that Alpha Pools ran them.)  3) What was the date of my suspension from DHS?  4) Where in the World is Carmen Sandiego?
     
    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Maggie's Triumphant Return to Dogster    urlLink Dogster  lost a bunch of their pages to a server error about 3 months ago, and Maggie's page was one that was lost.  I recreated her page today.  The link on the left should work, but if you're too lazy,  urlLink I'll put one here, too.    Update:  For those of you who don't read comments,  urlLink Maximus has a Dogster page , too. Maggie and Maximus are Dogster Pup Pals!
     
    
</post>

<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Iron Chef America   Just finished a study break during which I watched Iron Chef America. A couple of observations that struck me while watching it:  1) Japanese actresses in translation (on the original Iron Chef) seem much smarter than American actresses. The actress that they had on from "The OC" was amazed by the taste of the wasabi until she was told that she'd probably never had it fresh because most wasabi paste you get is made from wasabi powder and water. Even J. Peterman knew that. She also did not have a very endearing anime-character giggle.  2) Alton Brown is a legitimate chef. This may seem obvious to any who have watched his show, but one of the joys of watching Good Eats is that AB comes across as just a guy who really knows how to cook instead of a guy who has an encyclopedic knowledge of all things culinary. This show allows him to show just how knowledgeable he is, without having to dumb it down for me. Of course, this sometimes leads him to come across a little like a know-it-all, especially when he constantly corrects the guy who reports from the Kitchen Stadium.  That is all.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Busy Weekend   I had my second to last exam yesterday (Trusts and Estates--perhaps the hardest exam I've ever had, and not because I didn't study). My last one is on Monday (Federal Courts), so I am studying that now.  It is really hard to believe that I will have finished three years of law school after Monday ( I don't want to say "graduate," because that might jinx it, especially since exams aren't over). It's trite but true that it seems like only a few months ago that I moved in with Pete Reaves at The Forest. Of course, when I really think about what's happened over that period, it seems like it's been forever...   Sarah is in DC for the March for Women's Lives/Pro-Choice March tomorrow.  She also went to look at houses in Virginia with our real estate agent up there.   It is also Benjamin's birthday, today--I didn't forget. That also means that Granddaddy's birthday is tomorrow. Happy Birthday to Both!!!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Final Final Exams   I've started studying for my last set of finals in law school. It shouldn't be too terrible, though there is the added pressure of the fact that failing means I don't get to graduate this year, which could really put a kink in my life plans..  I also received my Bar study materials yesterday. They consist of two legal paper sized books of about 1000 pages a piece, one for Virginia, and one for the Multistate portion of the bar. The cost for this course and the multistate course I am taking is about $2500--luckily, the firm pays for it.  I am sufficiently afraid of the bar exam now.  Sarah and I  (mostly Sarah) did a lot of Spring Cleaning today. The apartment looks better than it did when we moved in. I  also bought a basil plant today, because I was sick and tired of paying 2 bucks for a quarter cup of basil every time I needed it, which is too often. I don't have a green thumb, but maybe my "punishment garden" skills will pay off. 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hives Suck!   On Friday night, my arms started to itch. Upon closer inspection, I found a few small red bumps. Reassured by Nicholas that it was just a little heat rash, I took an Aveno bath and tried to watch Pirates of the Caribbean. Halfway through the film, I go to the restroom to discover my left eye is swollen and the bumps have spread to my back. At this point I totally and completely freak out and start to cry. Nicholas takes me to the ER where they are surprisingly quick in getting me in a bed and pumped full of benydrl. A couple of hours of doped up sleep later the hives are gone and we go home at approximately 3am.   The next morning I continue to take benydrl and steroids but the hives come back with a vengeance and I am starting to look like a science experiment. We decide not to go back to the ER b/c they are only going to give me more of the drugs I already have and tell me they don't know what's causing it. By Sunday, the hives are still in place although mainly on my arms and legs. On Monday I get into to see my dermatologist who gives me a prescription for allegra and tells me they won't be able to tell me what caused the hives either. They're pretty sure it wasn't anything topical but beyond that I just have to pray I don't encounter whatever the hell it was ever again. Like I said...hives suck!
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Lookie here...   I'm not saying that we were the first couple to have a wedding website, but this is strange:   urlLink nicholasandsarah.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Ch-Ch-Ch...Ah, never mind...   As you can tell, big changes around here at The Best Blog EVER!!!  A new blogger template means a little easier on the eyes, but I have switched to the Blogger comments, which aren't nearly as intuitive for users as Haloscan, I may end up going back if I really don't like it...(I hate livejournal's comments, and these aren't far off.)  I have begun Bar Preparation "for real" now. Unfortunately, despite being promised by the Bar/Bri people that my home-study CDs would arrive tomorrow, I have been informed that they won't be shipped until Wednesday. That's okay, I have some other materials that can keep me busy in the meantime and I can catch up on the weekends, but I wish they had let us know a little earlier...The task looks more daunting every time I look at the absurd amount of material and number of practice questions that have been provided me. If I live through this, I can live through anything, I'm convinced.  We're back to DC this weekend, with hopes of finding a house/condo that we can make an offer on. We don't want to be back and forth between here and there too many times, so we  are hopeful that this weekend will be fruitful. Keep your fingers crossed for us.  Alright, back to Constitutional Law for now.   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Where has all my initiative gone?   I tried to listen to some bar exam lectures on tape this afternoon and promptly fell asleep on the couch, waking only when Maggie saw another dog out the window and began barking. Even though this is pretty early to be studying, I certainly hope that I can find a little more energy for this stuff soon. Zzzzzzzzzzzzzzz............  We're having Tim and Emily in this weekend and next weekend we return to DC to look at houses, and may even be making an offer if we see something we really like--now wouldn't that be all grown up of us?  I also really want to change the template on our blog, but I am too lazy to reinsert the Haloscan comments code. Also, the new blog templates all have that annoying stuff on the side telling everyone about your interests--I don't want it. Ah, well, I guess we're stuck with this for now.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       March for Women's Lives   Two weeks ago today, I set out for Washington, DC to attend the March for Women's Lives. The March held on April 25 was to protest for " urlLink Choice, Justice, Access, Health, Abortion, Global and Family Planning ." Over  urlLink 1,115,000 people  attended the march and it was one of the most amazing experiences of my life.  I went up early to volunteer at the  urlLink National Organization for Women 's (a co-sponsor of the March along with my current employer  urlLink Planned Parenthood ) headquarters. Immediately I was put to work Friday morning helping recruit people to promote NOW's new voter mobilization called  urlLink 10 for Change . It was really wonderful seeing everyone I worked for this summer especially my boss Linda. This summer one of my main tasks was to secure memorabilia for the PAC auction held every summer at the NOW convention.  In a lightbulb moment, I realized the March would be stockfull of celebrities and if we could get them to sign March posters they could be auctioned off for lots of money. I told my idea to  urlLink Kim Gandy , the president of NOW, who told me she like the way my mind worked but we needed someone to be charge of the poster. Well of course I volunteered and secured myself a backstage pass.  After leaving the NOW office on Friday, I went to visit American University's  urlLink Washington College of Law  where I am now convinced I will be attending in the fall. It is everything I want in a law school. Laid back, feminist oriented, focused on government/non-profit service. It really was exciting.  The next day, after looking at houses in Virginia with our realtor, I made my way downtown to the DC Armory for the March kick-off event. From 3-12pm, my good friend Hannah and I passed out information and sold T-shirts till we about passed out from exhaustion. I've never seen women so excited about T-shirts in my whole life.  The next morning, the day of the March, we woke up bright and early and greeted buses coming from out of town at the Branch Avenue until about noon. I even got to personally greet all my coworkers arriving from North Carolina. Finally, we got to the mall and the excitement was truly palpable. There is nothing like being surrounded by a million people who feel the same way you do. Honestly, there were so many people I didn't think we would be able to logistically march around the capital. Thinking I had more time than I did I made my way backstage but instead ended up following  urlLink Whoopi Goldberg  and Christine Lahti to the front of the line. Suddenly, I looked around and I was right behind  urlLink Ted Turner ,  urlLink Ashley Judd , Calli Khoui (screenwriter of Thelma and Louise and from my hometown), Camryn  urlLink Manheim , Tyne Daly, and a ton of other celebrities. I introduced myself and had them all sign my NOW round and then the next thing I knew we were marching. In the midst of the hubbub I got pushed farther and farther back but I ended up marching the entire way with Tyne Daly's three daughters  urlLink Alisabeth, Kathryne , and Alyxandra  who adopted me and were incredibly kind. The marching itself was incredibly surreal. We were in this group of people as far as the eye could see walking towards the capitol. The truly surreal moment came when I glanced over and saw  urlLink Gloria Steinem ,far from the celebrity held front, marching with us normal people. I reintroduced myself and walked beside for about 15 minutes. It was of course a top ten moment of my life.  After the march, I went backstage to start gathering my celebrity signatures. Cady Lornell, Kim Gandy's daughter and a really sweet child, wanted to meet the celebrities too so she followed me around as we met everyone from  urlLink Susan Sarandon  to  urlLink Moby  to Carole King. I had my picture taken with Sheryl Crow and Julianne Moore - two of my absolute favorites. It was just another surreal moment from the weekend to look around you and realize your next to Candace Bergen, Ed Harris, the  urlLink Indigo Girls . The whole afternoon was fantastic and I stayed until the very end at 6pm and set out for North Carolina.  The whole time I was on such an andreneline high because I knew we were truly making history. While meeting all the famous people I've admired for so long was very cool, I think my favorite thing was how connected you felt to everyone. All weekend long if another marcher identified you as "on their side" it was like you were long lost friends and you could talk about anything. As cheesy as it sounds, we were all truly sisters that weekend. My only prayer for myself and my sisters is that we can transform all the positive energy and experience into incredible change especially on November 2!
     
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The Fix Is In   Well, since I haven't received any correspondence telling me otherwise, I guess Duke Law School is going to graduate me on Saturday.  Right now I'm going to the Durham Bulls game, right after I take Maggie outside. 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Coming up for air   I just wanted to come up from my constant Bar studying to say thank you for all of the birthday wishes and gifts of a week ago. I don't have much free time these days, as moving and studying are occupying me. I did get to see the Pistons embarass the Lakers this evening, but I felt guilty the whole time.  Hope everyone is well, see you on July 29th.
     
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       It's Over   The Bar Exam is finally over and our lives are returning to normal. I will only say that I feel okay about how the exam went, not great, not terrible, but just okay. I'll know on October 15, I'll let you know how it goes.  We're off to Cincinnati next week. It's going to be a long drive through Pennsylvania and Ohio (two swing states, maybe we'll pass by the Kerry or Bush campaign on our way), but we look forward to Tim and Emily's wedding. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       DC Living   Moved into the apartment yesterday. Sarah painted the living room yello today, under my rent-house inspired guidance. We have no furniture, food, etc. (it's all on a truck over the 4th of July Holiday), sleeping on an air mattress and eating PB and J.  Maggie is learning to be a city dog, though she's been imprisoned in the back bedroom because of the painting today.   T-minus 24 days to the bar exam. I may never learn it all.   E-mail us for the new address and phone number.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>