<Blog>


<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      My Dear Excellent Will, I urge you to not stay too much long talking and discussing in the closed loop of the UN. To me it’s like the Chinese society in the Middle Age. No openness, a choice to remain closed and isolated in its own stereotypes: in ultimate analysis no progress. no boldness, no achievement.  The most ardent supporter of the UN among Western people are simply misguided by a philosophical idea, that dates back to a French Enlightenment thinker and pedagogue, Rousseau. According to this sophisticated philosopher in the dim and distant past the mankind lived happily, mostly because we have not discovered yet the ownership of an object: everything was common. Curse be that day when the first man told the others: this is mine! And worse luck the others believed him! This is a sheer utopia. Actually a very dangerous one. Immediately after Rousseau socialistic and communist visions of the World and our lives start to pop up! Lot of people are not having a decent quality of life today for this kind of ideas. I lean more for an understanding of the primitive mankind as envisioned by the English philosopher Hobbes: “homo homini lupus est”. In plain English: we’d better organize soon and defend from ill-intentioned people and animal. We need then a social contract: the upshot is a society with hierarchies and orders. While historically the Rousseau vision could have match some isolated German tribe during the Late Roman Empire, the Hobbes political theory is closer to the reality of man, and nature too. I remind you incidentally that we – humans – are part of the Mother Nature and, except the fact that we think about ourselves, our past and future, we are not so different from the other animals, especially if you look at the big picture.  In final analysis the UN IS LIKE THE ROUSSEAU DREAM, TO WIT A FRIENDLY-PEACELOVING-STATE- OF-NATURE SOCIETY. UNFORTUNATELY THIS IS A SOMETIMES-APPEALING-BUT-ACTUALLY UTOPIA.  The UN has no meaning even if compared to future Space experiences by the mankind.  Here starts a philosophical excursus aimed to demonstrate the flimsy and baseless nature of the so-called United Nations: they are not in our DNA, today, in the past, tomorrow.  Will succeed the mankind to fill the vast emptiness of the Outer Space with love and warm-heartedness, passion and heat? Star Trek can be considered an autonomous culture, able to provide a literature, a political and law philosophy and an ethics. Many myths and fantastic tales are based on realities and old truths.  Star Trek offers a pluralistic and polycentric culture, where differences are welcome. There’s a common belief that, once united, we can be better than before.  In the Star Trek doesn’t exist a predominant or ruling philosophical system. This is why maybe such a predominant system doesn’t exist. The Star Trek Weltanschaung is not characterized by certainties: it is very difficult to hold in a more and more amazing Universe. The ability to keep united, combined and blended opposite views and cultures is the biggest Star Trek Utopia. Star Trek is an example of possible coexistence, even if not always peaceful: if you want peace, get ready to wage war.  According to some philosopher the human being is always searching for something missing, searching for a further explanation. The and aspiration for seeking out is a direct consequence of a pluralistic society: when you have in front of you such a huge variety of interpretations and views, starting your own quest, research and exploration is a natural upshot. And perhaps we are talking about an endless quest, for always new meanings and visions.  The Prime Directive is the main provision in the Star Fleet legal system and states that no Star Fleet Member will interfere with the normal development of a less advanced civilization. Sometimes the implementation of this rule is strict and harsh: an entire Planet could be left to its ill-fate. Why choosing to not act? What right to interfere in other lives and destinies? We must remember though that many times this paramount norm is violated. Is really conceivable an exploration activity based on the non-interference principle? This type of approach should be based on a profound respect toward the other one.  If you want to be a Captain in Star Trek one of the requisite is to be able to communicate with the other, the alien. Ability to cope with any situation deriving from the contact with a different, often radically diverse, culture.  In Star Trek is fundamental to preserve and record the history, the memory of the past: this is one of the main features typical of a human being, ever since.  Once solved the problem of different languages thanks to the universal translator, what actually comes out is the difficulty to communicate due to incompatible and conflicting cultures. Even if we have the more open and gentle attitude possible, historically the encounter of different cultures has ended up in a clash. Some frequent questions by the Federation of the Planet explorer are: our alien interlocutor is able to talk to us? Is he interested in us, in talking with us? Is it right or wrong if he doesn’t understand us? These are all typical ethical questions in the Star Trek Universe.  In Star Trek is difficult to talk about superior or inferior cultures, because simply a contact among different (from a scientific and philosophical point of view) civilizations is going to modify them.  Star Trek addresses in a very artistic way a classical inferiority complex of some parts of the Western World after the conquest and pillage of the New World.  Sometimes in Star Trek a permanent damage to a culture is interpreted as a harm and detriment to the future itself.  In Star Trek is possible to apply these ethical and legal directive, because the immense vastness and great extent of the Space, of the Universe, of our Galaxy allows so many different people and beings to coexist. Nevertheless the more the Galaxy become crowded with new actors and cultures, the more it resembles our own World.  The Prime Directive is not applied anymore when a culture reaches the warp drive, a technological factor that allows cosmic-scale exploration. After the first contact, follows the invitation to join the Federation  The risk of a strict application, implementation, and enforcement of the Prime Directive is to have a museum, not a Universe to discover and to interact with.  When you are in front of different values, how can you decide what’s wrong and what’s right? It is right to be involved or not?  Star Trek shows us its weaknesses and contradictions. This is why it is so humane and tragic. Anyway the Prime Directive starting from its name is not something strict per se. The Prime Directive pretty often comes into conflict with the personal ethics of the main characters. Many violations rain down: the Prime Directive is not felt as an absolute principle or a mandatory rule, but as an attempt to find an answer for a really complicated, complex and elaborate problem: how to relate with the other in an extreme context like that represented by the Space Exploration?  In Star Trek the mankind doesn’t expect or insist to know always the answer, about what’s wrong and what’s right. The Ethics of Star Trek is mostly an elastic, flexible, adaptable moral philosophy, to wit ethics. Infinite are the ambits of application of the ethics.  Frequently the Prime Directive is violated in the name more fundamental principles like preserving life or when for one of the protagonist the situation is a matter of conscience.  In Star Trek, a really utopian society, people don’t deny the existence of conflicts, they are exorcized, neither sublimed, nor repressed. They are instead faced up and confronted. To me sounds really current and past American Society. When you have a non definitive and incomplete decision as the Prime directive, it could be unenforced or ignored. Since is difficult to have clear rules, laws and regulations in the Outer Space, many times the context is more important than the norm.  All Good Things Come To An End: the death is a inevitable and unavoidable part of our life.  The way we face up and cope with the Inevitable is an important personality test: depends on us, on our passion and steadfastness, how to manage and succeed in changing and transforming the unavoidability of the death in a struggle for life, to survive.   In the Star Trek Universe we find ourselves often involved in dealing with the irrationality of seeking out a definitive answer about the mystery of our life and Universe. There’s something we can’t talk about. Sometimes we must recognize that.  The real commandment in the Federation is to preserve life. Try every means to achieve this.  Star Trek teach us that there’s always another way to survive, through trust and mutual help, instead of a ruthless fight.  How is organized the Federation? It is a very soft form of Government, that hold the monopoly of the use of force and the exploration. These tasks are implemented through the Star Fleet. For the remainder the members are Autonomous Planetary System Governments.  In Star Trek Universe we don’t use money anymore, and the mankind has started to building its own society on new bases: profit and personal wealth are no more the main drivers in the individual life. The last goal of each individual and the society itself is to improve himself or herself.  And this could mean in the end a more simple way of life. These amazing possibilities are allowed by extraordinary technological achievements: they seem almost magic. Indeed each new technological advancement appears in the hindsight as a form of magic. Never say never! The human being can free and unleash all his/her best intellectual qualities and skills.  Once we become citizen of the Universe, the immeasurable amount of Space and opportunities is in front of us. And a new equality among humans is established.  What kind of take on Star Trek about the Military? The Star Fleet undertake military actions not for conquest, but for guarantee and ensuring a peaceful coexistence among the members of the Federation. The last resort, however, is always the use of force. The main mission of the Star Fleet is to explore: it is not always an easy and not dangerous task. To explore could be a good insurance for our future, because we don’t know what kind of dangers, perils and hazards are out there. It could be a wise choice.  Who’s going first in Deep Space? The military or the civilian part of a society?  The Star Fleet hierarchy is a very peculiar one, since the personnel is all made of volunteers. Sometimes to disobey orders is considered acceptable or even deserving of the highest praise!  Gandhi: I believe that in case of you have really to choose between cowardice and violence, I think I would choose the last one. For Gandhi non violence means abstinence from doing somebody wrong. Something very similar happens in the Star Fleet.  Star Fleet is ready to fight to preserve life: this is the Second directive. Even in the worst kind of conflict this tenet is always highly regarded.  When a Star Trek Official face an unjustified use of force, he or she usually thinks is non only mandatory, but also morally correct to fight against these forces.   In the movie Star Trek – First Contact, Captain Picard deliberately kills a dying Borg Queen. The Borg represent a mortal enemy for the Federation. Acting this way, the Captain violated current basic rules and conventions like Geneva, being pitiless toward a defeated enemy. One of the teaching we can draw is that when one of the players in the Cosmic arena is not ready to follow a common set of rules and customs, the only way to deal is to get rid of him. On the other hand we could say simply that Picard in this circumstance made a mistake, due to his personal experience with this cruel species.  Even if I respectfully disagree with Patrick Stewart who embodied the mythical Captain Picard, I agree about the sanctity, preciousness, and dignity of the human life. http://www.gruhlke.de/stewart/ps-speaks.html   These are only few, really few of the ideas, cues and hints you can get from the Star Trek Universe, a future only seemingly and apparently distant from us.  In the star trek's world the mankind is finally gone beyond hunger, poverty, wars (at least among humans), and inequalities. We are now able to develop all our potential! Characters like the mythical Captain Kirk or Captain Picard and their adventurous lifes are the embodiment of the Homeric and Dantean Odysseus: "Fatti non foste per viver come bruti, ma per seguir virtute e conoscenza", where no one has gone before! = you aren't born to live like beast, but to seek out virtue and knowledge!  Star Trek represent what human kind could realized, if we could finally keep steady in our mind that we have to be united and cooperate, for building a better world for all of us. So, don’t forget: we can improve ourselves, our life, and the conditions of the other people: we need only, even if it is not a simple thing, to pass some kind of test, to discover after lot of wandering, that united we can be better. I'm sure we have this chance, cuz we got the scientific method and the ability to survive winning the challenges of life in our Planet. Star Trek give us a deep simple message, in addition to be a very well done art work. You can depends on The Next Generation, my fave series ever: sometimes I like to empathize with the Captain Picard character, the thoughtful captain, or the Commander Data, an android who want to become more human! In all fairness I tend to appreciate almost all the episodes, starting from the Original Series with the mythical James T. Kirk to the more recent spin-offs Deep Space 9 and Voyager. I really hope you are curious to hear some of my thoughts about death, religion and destiny. Sooner or later in everybody’s life will pop up a series of interesting and difficult questions. Up to date I can’t consider myself a believer in any classic religion, even if I leaned to distrust too much radical statements. Religion derives from the ancient Latin "re-ligare"= “to be tied by something or somebody”. Often I perceive religion as a kind of restraint to our potentialities. What I mean is that sometimes we’re offered a too simplistic answer to the fundamental and essential question: "What is the Truth about us and about our Universe, about our own role in this World of galaxies and space, time and matter?" A quick answer could be: the Creation explains everything! Personally I regard as more commendable and humble the Modern Science approach to the reality. Since Galileo and many others after him have introduced the fundamental notion of experiment, things are working better, even if w/ some drawbacks. Mainly, but not exclusively thru the glasses of the Science, we can reach a better understanding of many mysteries that surround us. Mainly, but not exclusively, because our World, our life, ourselves are kind of evasive, enigmatic, and obscure sometimes: perhaps this is the beautiful aspect of all. By the way I agree with Charles Darwin and his thoughts in "The Origin of the Species": his scientific theory, until proved otherwise, explains a lot of the life’s dynamics. I like the idea of religion suggested by Albert Einstein too, when he goes back to the Spanish philosopher Spinoza: in his opinion God is the order that we see permeating our Universe, at any level of complexity. How can we answer to the fear of die? We have already a way to seek immortality, a gift courtesy provided by "Mother Nature": we can breed, and transmit to our descendants our genetic and cultural message. Maybe we don’t need to care about our existence after death, cuz we have already an answer. This is the simple and simultaneously complicated way created by an Evolutionary process on Planet Earth. But what is really peculiar of any human being is that we can transmit to the future generations our thoughts, memories, inner ideas and beliefs. We have "free will", but the matter is dominated by not accidental Physics Laws, even if you wouldn’t think this once you are familiar w/ the subatomic world of quanta: This is the real challenge to the human comprehension and knowledge: how is possible that from seemingly chaotic subatomic particles we can arrive to the human consciousness? How in conclusion the Universe succeeds to be aware and conscious of his/its existence? What is the mystery of the Life? It's up to us try to find an answer. Undoubtedly science could help, but keeping always in mind that at the bottom of our choice, we act so irrationally and arbitrarily. I like to end my thoughts citing from the C. Sagan novel-based movie “Contact”. An alien creature referring to the mankind told the protagonist, Ellie : You are capable of such wonderful dreams, but also terrible nightmares. And you feel so alone, searching for answers to pressing questions. But you are not alone! This remind me the value of Space exploration: Space is the last Frontier of Science. For a better understanding of our Universe and of ourselves, we need to go outside and take new comparisons and perspective. Star Trek inculcate and insinuate such attitude and motivation: amazing stuff is waiting for us just out there. Please, don't hesitate to contact me to discuss issues like these above, ok? Wish you all the best, Dear William! ^_^  End of the long excursus aimed at demonstrate the intrinsic fallacy of the UN building.  Why I told you all this stuff, Dear William? My purpose was just to give an idea on how the UN cannot be - neither remotely and distantly - able to be a valuable, functioning and effective model in a near or distant future, where the Mankind really has evolved and improved toward a higher level of civilization and understanding of the Universe and ourselves.  To make a long story short, US now is simply trying to keep up appereances. UN have never been effective in any meaning or sense at all. Do you really believe the US want to dominate this strange organization? The only practical reason it is still in place is because of the tourism for New York City, even if for a person like me the UN would be the last place to visit. Indeed I know about many people asking for getting rid of the UN and packing it up and make it leave for Paris or some place in Africa or Asia.  The UN is simply a place to see where the wind is blowing. THE WORLD HAS WORKED WELL FOR LONG TIME WITH BILATERALS AGREEMNTS. WHEN THERE ARE REALLY MULTILATERAL NEED, YOU CAN RELY ON MORE AGILE AND EFFECTIVE ORGANIZATIONS.  Dear William, you talk to me about Globalization, but you are misguided once again. Globalization is another big big hoax. GLOBALIZATION IS NOT SO CERTAIN, DEFINITE, AND SETTLED. ARE YOU SO SURE WE ARE GOING A MORE AND MORE STANDARDIZE WORLD? I am not so sure. And please, give me the or a scientific or even plausible explanation of why we should be all equal in our diversity? I really don’t understand: we are all equal? Are you all diverse? Another paramount problem is one of your first assumption: we are not equal. Well, this is blatantly NOT TRUE! Only if we start recognizing that we are actually not equal, we can really start to work in finding tangible solutions to concrete problems. It is important to discover the historical and historic reasons for these big and small differences, but they are there, displaying all their meaning, value, influence, and power. All the Countries in the World are not equal, first of all because many of them are not real Countries at all: they fake or failed States. It would’ve been much better for them to remain Western colonies: trust me. In too many cases they demonstrate to don’t be able to keep up and cope with the challenges a modern State and Government sooner or later need to face up and confront.  How can you talk about the US needing to pay its dues to an organization such as the UN? How can the most advanced Democracy in the Planet pay taxes to an organization where you can’t find any sign of accountability, transparency and effectiveness?  DO YOU LOVE BUREAUCRACIES? BUREAUCRACIES ARE NOT GOOD FOR YOUR HEALTH. Bureaucracies are like many form of cancer: once they took root, it is very difficult, if not often impossible to eradicate and extirpate them.  How, please, tell me how can you even consider the UN as a neutral arbiter in international disputes??? Where’s the neutrality in a body where most of the Countries Members are moved by hate and envy??? Why do you trust people who basically hate you? Why the most advanced democracy on Earth must be or should be restrain and curbed, if it feels threatened by anti-democratic tyrannical, despotic and dictatorial forces? It’s a sheer complete non sense. We are by a far extent much better than this bunch of barbaric thugs! How can be the UN a legitimate body?  Given all these clarifying conditions, Why the Bush Administration sought a UN mandate? This is a good question. We could investigate more this need of the current U.S. administration to go searching support overseas, but mainly we would end up talking about the immense and powerful pressure exercised by the public opinion all over the Planet.  Pomerantz: “The way to democracy is not unilateralism, military force, or might-is-right-ism. “ ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS STATEMENT? I REMIND with urgency YOU THAT IN EUROPE WAR  ULTIMATELY BROUGHT DEMOCRATIC INSTITUTIONS.  You talked about a more active role by the US in the UN. I really don’t know how to convince you, whereas I know I’m repeating myself, but  DEAR WILLIAM, HISTORICALLY THE U.N. WORKED ONLY AND EXCLUSIVELY AFTER A UNITED STATES INTERVENTION AND IMPLEMENTATION OF OTHERWISE COMPLETELY INEFFECTIVE STATEMENTS.  The Third World Countries don’t want a free global market. They are turning over in their mind very strange ideas and firm beliefs, like those regarding the fact that everything is due to them, because they are poor. There is a real serious danger in all of this.  All the best, Dear William. And to quote Takeshi Maruki: “Respect! Always.” 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Yes, the UN, like the League of Nations before it, owes its existence largely to the United States.  However, even though that is the case, and even though the headquarters in UN may be in a Rockefeller-donated building, I fail to see how this means that the UN “exists courtesy of the hosting country.”  Surely there is some debt of gratitude owed, but there is a logical fallacy inherent in assuming perpetual subservience or allegiance.  The US (with aid from the Allied powers) was in position to create the UN, and it did; however, it would be an act of utmost hypocrisy now to demand dominion over the agency and its other member states.  That is not a “negotiating table.”   If that is to be the case, then the UN may as well be dissolved, and the US and other superpowers can work out whatever small amount of treaties they may need without the bulky legislative framework of the UN.  If we do not wish to be hypocrites, if we accept the continuing globalization of the world, if we understand the values of diversity (even in spite of the associated difficulties), then we must not talk about the UN existing courtesy of any one power, regardless of the circumstances of its creation.  We also must not talk about the exclusion of three quarters of the world’s population.  We can talk about the need for UN delegations to represent the people, and we can discuss how many delegations are not doing that at this point.  The answer for this, though, is not to remove these countries from the UN.    The US needs to do a better job of supporting the agency it created.  It needs to pay its dues.  It needs to begin considering the UN as a first option for international disputes.  It needs to use the veto more responsibly.  It needs to recognize instances when the UN has done well—unlike when the US criticized UN troops for the infamous “Black Hawk Down” incident in Somalia rather than thanking them for saving our troops.  The US can and should play a strong role—the strongest role—in the UN.  The US should learn to use the UN for its own needs.  To quote  urlLink Ian William :   Most member states agree with the American neoconservatives that one of the functions of the UN is to give the Lilliputians strings to restrain the global Gulliver. They think it is essential to keep the United States involved and entangled in the organization, even if it does occasionally lurch up and break the strings. This goes to the heart of the organization's normative role, which is often overlooked in the face of its enforcement failures. The State Department, and others in the Bush administration, certainly feel the need for external validation, as proven by their extraordinary efforts to mount a "coalition" for the Iraq War: the effect was intended to counter the lack of a UN mandate. But ad hoc lists of bullyable micro-states do not cut the mustard. The UN is the only body that can make a conquest legitimate.  We agree on the need for transparency and frankness. I disagree, though, that the way to transparency is to excommunicate three quarters of the members.  That is not openness; that is not frankness or transparency; that is not even a negotiating table.  That is, simply put, and “Old Boys’ Club.”  For the US to consent to the world being run by and Old Boys’ Club is to run counter to everything democracy stands for, and is one of the main reasons why so many people in this world dislike the US.  The way to democracy is not unilateralism, military force, or might-is-right-ism.  In the UN, we have a perfect forum to show the world how democracy, despite its ugly flaws, is the best system of governance invented to date.  While we act unilaterally, we invoke anger and self-righteousness in addition to the unavoidable jealously.  When the UN—with help from the Americans—is able to prove itself a viable and long-lasting organization, and when the American government proves willing to play by the rules it helped define, then we finally will have a system that may allow for sensible global politics.  Then, we will no longer be the police for of the world, and we will no longer seem so alone.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      My Dear William,  I kindly but firmly remind you that the so-called United Nations have been created by the United States of America.  The Manhattan’s ground where now are the UN buildings were donated by the multi-millionaire-Democrat-Oil-Magnate Rockefeller. My point is that this fake, hypocrite, and ineffective organization must be realistic and recognize that they exist courtesy of the hosting Country. The main purpose of UN in 1945 was to establishing a negotiating table with the other Allies after the atrocities of WW2.  Now I ask myself: are you waiting for a United Nations? I remind you that more than ¾ of the Members States are basically a bunch of dictators and anti-democratic, repressive and arrogant, ruthless rulers. It’s really hilarious that these bunch of thugs periodically lecture the U.S. the most ancient and advanced Democracy in this Planet how a democratic Government should work and behave! How can a bunch of criminals create laws to punish themselves???  You mention the solution to all the U.N.’s problems and contradictions: consider members only the Western democracies and few other commendable exceptions. And what you get almost immediately is more transparency and frankness, some of the ingredients of a healthy democratic environment.  You talk about coming to a table in good faith: forget about it! It’s against human and Governments’ nature. Remember: our inner nature - not to mention Countries’ attitude - is against sliced pies!  Another sheer wrong point of you is that U.S. is like the other Countries! It’s not. The United States had been created because they have a Mission: to be the land of the free. Unfortunately many people don’t like this ever since. I strongly recommend you to read again the Washington Political Will, very telling about real American concerns. America is a Country of believers: in a sense is a religious Country, much more than Israel or the Muslim failed-States. U.S. deserves the place they gained in the World Arena: they are the first Democratic Planetary Empire in the History and my wish is that it will last still for a long long time.  Americans and the values they carry with them all over the World are typically passionate, irresistible and sweeping: so be proud to be American! Don’t be tired to repeat to yourself that you are “confident of your own core values, enough so that you have the arrogance to wish other people could have the same set of values”. You seems to me like the Athenian at the peak of their amazing civilization and leadership: read the Pericle’s funeral oration http://www.cyber.vt.edu/psci/summer98/privpsci/readings/thuc/thuc.ch2.b1.html   You say you do not want my country to be the police force for the world. Why not? Sometimes you have to take annoying, but at the same time necessary actions! Like it or not, this is an inevitable burden for a leader.  Don’t be shy about your core own American values: you live in a World profoundly and deeply un-democratic and – worse – anti-democratic! Wake up!  Unfortunately now U.S. appear alone: sometimes it’s tough to maintain your own convictions and firm beliefs.  I promise to articulate in a more exhaustive, comprehensive, and coherent manner these my random thoughts and statements.  All the Best. ^_^ Watch and Study Star Trek! 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Perhaps not surprisingly, I have to disagree with you.  Again.  There is no doubt in my mind that the UN is good for mankind.  The trouble comes from mixing together several different issues, I think.  When discussing the UN, one must consider what the UN practically  is , what it ideally  should be , and what it practically  can be .  I won't argue that the UN as it exists now can be laughably ineffective.  I think that some of the basic setup of the organization is flawed.  This isn't news to anyone, not even the members of the United Nations.  The system of permanent veto power is flawed, although I would be hard pressed to come up with a system that isn't.  The funding of the UN is deplorable.  The authority of the agency itself is questionable.  But much of this can be changed.  Kofi Annan, the secretary general,  urlLink has called for a reanalysis of the UN .  I think that in the wake of the Iraq war, this is absolutely necessary.  Whether or not one agrees with the decision of the Coalition of the Willing to invade Iraq, all evidence seems to indicate that the UN and the security council shot itself in the foot in the events leading up to war.  How can they possibly pass a strongly-worded (at least, for the UN) resolution like  urlLink this one  condemning Iraq for numerous violations and then back it up with nothing?  Although I personally believe that the inspectors should have been given more time in Iraq--and I think that the fact that the US teams are now asking for more time to find the same WMDs confirms that--I still think that the UN had painted itself into a corner in this matter.  So the UN is flawed, no doubt about it.    But  why ?  And, more importantly,  how can it be fixed ?  By excluding people?  By eliminating the representatives of despots?  You raise an interesting question about whether or not that should happen, and one to which I have not formulated a complete or satisfactory answer even within my own mind.  However, one thing is clear to me: that is  not  the solution to making the UN something useful.  What is much more likely to do that is for countries that currently have the power--both politically, militarily, and economically--to finally come to the table in good faith.  The organization can not function when its most dominant players do not pay their dues, when they practice short-sighted partisan politics, and when they are dishonest about their goals and objectives.  I'm sure that you will respond that this is giving yet another free slice of the pie to undeserving countries--I can hear it now.  I have several different problems with this: first of all, I think that perhaps we have fundamentally different definitions of "deserving".  Secondly, I think that the US is just as guilty of wanting hypocrisy as any other country.  Finally, I think that all of the world may be better off if the pie is divided.  I am proud to be American.  I am happy that, currently, our country is on top of the world, that we are the standard by which every other judges themselves.  I do not think that this position is unearned, or that being on top is an undesirable or even immoral position, as some people seem to.  I have never and will never intentionally critique the US because it is on top.  Still, at the same time, I do not want my country to be the police force for the world.  I am confident of my own core values, enough so that I have the arrogance to wish other people could have the same set of values.  Still, I am humble enough to realize that even if everyone accepted my core values, there would still be a lot of disagreement in the world.  I enjoy diversity enough to welcome these disagreements.  And even when there are violations of these core values so atrocious as to merit police action, I would rather that that action not be unilateral.  Imagine if the UN or some similar body could actually rise to the point of being an effective body in this sense!  Imagine if the US did not have to focus a huge portion of it attention and budget on minding what we view to be the problems of the rest of the world?  Imagine if we did not have to deal with the anger and hatred that will always be associated with such interventions?  Wouldn't that be better for everyone?  The US and the other superpowers--especially the veto powers--are key to making that vision a reality.  We can have philosophical discussion about the demands of the smaller countries, but fundamentally it the actions of a small handful of nations that will determine the longterm efficiency of the UN.  If we choose our actions wisely, perhaps we have a chance to differentiate our time from the 2600 years of human history that precede it.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, I could agree that you need a negotiating table with your enemy, but, please, stop calling the UN, the good for all mankind!!! The more I think about it, the less I can stand that bunch of dictators and expensive and convoluted bureaucrats. The Communist members of UN want their big cake and eat it too! My dear misguided Communists, I remind that no pain, no gain! And please, rehash the last 2600 years of history, Ok? The human events are less unique than many people believe: what really change are the masks! ^_^  FABIO
     

    
</post>

<date>02,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I won't argue that Communism is rather Utopian in nature, and possibly even doomed to fail.  But should those nations who are currently undertaking the experiment of Communism be excluded from the realm of international politics?  Should a country like China--with a huge percentage of the world's population, land mass, et cetera--be forbidden entrance into the international forum?  The fact that the UN is itself an exercize in Democracy gives some small credibility to your bold claim--made so frequently on your website--that only Democracies should be allowed in the UN.  However, can the UN seek to have  any  credibility whatsoever if it excludes the huge portion of the world still ruled by Communists?  And even the despots: is it feasable for the UN to condemn a despot who has no representative, and thus no voice?
     

    
</post>

<date>02,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Unfotunately there is still a lot of Communism out there. Communism basically is an utopistic evolution and interpretation of one of the first tenet of Christianity: we are all equal! Are you really sure? From what I know, life, in any form I can see, is always different and similar at the same time, but mostly and always surprisingly diversified. The phenomenon of life is competition, starting from the cells, and even before, from the many tiny parts components like mitochondria and ribosomes. Life is competition, is first-come first-served, is cruelty and realism, is skill to survive in a hostile environment. Life seems crazy and chaotic, it is incredibly ordered and resiliant instead. Communism is against our Nature, because it wants to impose attitudes and behaviors, that can not last and are detrimental for our welfare and progress.  Where can you find today Communism? Simple. In the European radical-chic salons, in the UN and in many under-developed so-called Countries.  We need to working on it! And urgently!
     

    
</post>

<date>28,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Something worth reading:   Is Space Exploration Worth the Cost?     Virgiliu Pop , Timisoara, January 13, 2004   The new space policy of the Bush administration, aimed at taking the humankind back to the Moon and on to Mars, came under fire before even being released. In their bid at the Democratic nomination for the White House, several politicians criticized George W. Bush's grand space plans, arguing that the money would find a better use here, on Earth. 'I also want to explore planet Earth and planet D.C.' Dennis Kucinich said. Al Sharpton too suggested that Bush instead try to discover the lower-income parts of Washington. 'I mean, it won't cost as much ... and it would be just as enlightening for him'. Joseph Lieberman stated that the money would be needed 'right here on Earth to give health care that's affordable to every body, to improve our education system, and do better on veterans' benefits and homeland security'. And Howard Dean agreed that 'space exploration is terrific', but went on to ask 'Where is the tax increase to pay for it? It is not worth bankrupting the country.'  Since the beginning of the space era, it has been argued that the money spent on space exploration should rather be used on meeting the needs of the underprivileged. 'If our nation can spend twenty billion dollars to put a man on the moon, it can spend billions of dollars to put God's children on their own two feet right here on earth' were stating respected figures like Martin Luther King Jr. People like him were not necessarily opposing space exploration; they were instead disputing the priorities - is space exploration worth pursuing when money is so badly needed elsewhere? Unfortunately, the benefits of the space exploration are not self-evident, no matter how real they are. And people are genuine in their worry that money is being wasted in space. Their concern with spending priorities needs to be addressed.  The high profile of space exploration makes it appear more expensive than it actually is. The uninformed, yet caring citizen, is under the earnest impression that the money would make a genuine difference in the fight against poverty. The real dimensions of the social needs are, in reality, out of proportion with the money spent in space - be it in the past, now or in the immediate future. Otherwise, there won't be any social needs left after the Congress stopped funding the Apollo missions to the Moon.   In the same time, many of the critics of the space programme on social grounds are 'limousine liberals'. They point the finger at the US government for wasting their tax money in space instead of helping the poor, but they are not feeling guilty for their own consumerist life style and for their own scale of priorities.  For instance, this year, total pet-related sales in the United States are projected to be $31 billion - the double, almost to the cent, of the $15.47 billion NASA budget. An estimated $5 billion worth of holiday season gifts were offered - not to the poor - but to the roving family pets - six times more than NASA spent on its own roving Martian explorers, Spirit and Opportunity, who cost the American taxpayer $820 million both. Instead of providing a launch pad for the immorally expensive shuttles, Florida can do better and clothe the underprivileged - a genuine alligator pet collar cost only $400 a piece.   Are space rockets expensive toys for the big boys? In any case, they cost less than the $20.3 billion a year spent in the US on the human popular toy industry. One doesn't need toys to play with when the most popular game is playing deaf and blind to the needs of the poor - provided one criticizes the waste in space.  Instead of betting on the future, Americans spend $586.5 billion a year on gambling. It is perhaps immoral to criticize one's personal choice, so instead of kicking the habit and feeding the poor with this money, one should stop instead the enormous waste in space who stands at a scandalous amount of 40 times less than gaming tokens.  Speaking about personal choice, $31 billion go annually in the US on tobacco products - twice the NASA budget - and $58 billion is spent on alcohol consumption - almost four times the NASA budget. Forget space spin-offs - here are genuine tangible benefits: $250 billion are spent annually in the US on the medical treatment of tobacco - and alcohol-related diseases - only sixteen times more than on space exploration.   In the eve of the launch of Apollo 11, a moving event occurred at NASA's moonport. Reverend Ralph Abernathy, president of the Southern Christian Leadership Conference and heir to Martin Luther King Jr., came to Cape Canaveral together with several hundred members of the Poor People's Campaign, to protest the money being spent on space exploration, while so many people remained poor. He was met by Thomas Paine, the administrator of NASA, who was informed that in the face of such suffering, space flight represented an inhuman priority and funds should be spent instead to feed the hungry, clothe the naked, tend the sick, and house the homeless.  Paine enlightened the good reverend that the advances in space exploration were child's play compared to the tremendously difficult human problems of the society, and told him that 'if we could solve the problems of poverty by not pushing the button to launch men to the moon tomorrow, then we would not push that button.'  Here are $976.3 billion dollars - almost a trillion - spent every year in the US on pets, toys, gambling, alcohol and tobacco. It is 63 times the amount spent on space exploration - with the difference that NASA has not destroyed lives as the alcohol, tobacco and gambling did. It is not the exploration spirit that Americans need to give up in order to alleviate poverty. It is the consumerist spirit.  Instead of not pushing the button, why not kick the habit?  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Welcome to our new members, Mark, Chris, and Nick.  Hope you enjoy it.  Plenty to discuss here, and no formal rules.  As you've probably seen, there was another big primary in the US yesterday.  Predicatably, Kerry won.  What wasn't so predicatable, though, was how close Edwards came.  Dean finished way beyond the pack (approximately 20 points behind the leaders).  Raises a couple of questions:  Is Dean definitely finished?  Will he endorse Edwards or Kerry, or neither?  Will his endorsement matter?  Does Edwards have a chance?  More news relevant to our host country: France is currently  urlLink considering sending troops into Haiti.   Possibly even without UN approval or involvement.  It is also interesting to compare the article written by the  urlLink Associated Press  with the one written by  urlLink the BBC .  Worth noting that the President of Haiti, who locals are trying to supplant and France is trying to support, was put into power in 1994 by US aid...then accused of rigging the elections in 2000.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well.  I don't really have anything cool or new to post... but I'll see if I can't be more helpful in the future.  For now, I just want to thank you for inviting me to your site.  ...ok, going to sleep now.  Class comes WAY TOO EARLY.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      One of the most important things to come out of Iraq didn't get all that much press...  urlLink See the letter .
     

    
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Some more interesting reading out there.  The sometimes wacky, sometimes dead-on  urlLink Andrew Sullivan  has come out with a  urlLink great article  in  Time  explaining why he would support Dean over Kerry, were he a Democrat.  I think it is a good analysis.  I especially like how he has highlighted the Dean quote: " "I think the problem with the Democratic Party in general is that they've been so afraid to lose they're willing to say whatever it takes to win."  True stuff, there.  Also, Lee Harris has  urlLink an interesting article  up about Independents, team players, and voting the party line. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So, I've been trying to compile a handy list of where the candidates stand to try and become a better informed voter, especially in time for the primaries (I am now officially registered to vote in the Florida primaries).  This has been surprisingly hard work, basically involving going to  urlLink websites   urlLink like   urlLink these  and printing out loads of position papers, et cetera.  A lot to sift through, true, but it's a worth while post.  But today, I found another interesting one: the  urlLink AOL Presidential Match Guide .  The site gives you an interactive quiz, giving a sample opinion and asking whether you agree/disagree et cetera.  At the end, it matches you up to the closest candidate based on your views and some prioritization that you fill out at end.  It gives you a handy ranking of the major (top 7) democratic candidates plus President Bush.  Personally, I was terrified at how high Al Sharpton was on my list.  Another interesting site, if you don't mind strong anti-Bush leanings:   urlLink Bush in 30 seconds.org .  They held a competition for 30-second spots, with the winner to be shown during the Super Bowl.  Unfortunately, CBS has refused to run the ads, claiming that they don't run "topical" ads--excepting of course the government funded anti-drug ads and the Phillip Morris anti-smoking ads.  A little sad.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, the horrible attacks in Madrid have been dominating the news for the past few days, as they well should.  It was a tragic act of senseless violence, and absolutely deplorable whatever the cause.  Indeed, it is almost offensive to even speak of this event  having  a cause.  The effects, though, are beginning to come clear. I wasn't the only one to wonder how the Europe reaction to March 11 would compare to the American reaction to September 11th.  And, to my eyes at least, some of the reactions coming out of Spain have been incredible tragic and lead down a terrible road.  Apparently, according to  urlLink this article , among others, Spanish Prime Minister-elect Jose Luis Rodriguez Zapatero is planning on pulling Spanish troops out of Iraq.  Indeed, this was one of the huge reasons that Zapatero and the Socialists were able to upset the Popular Party and win the elections.  Now, regardless of your views on the war in Iraq (and I'll get to that later), isn't this a  terrible  thing to happen?  It is bad enough to cave in to the demands of a terrorist or criminal mind to prevent violence, but this almost seems like acceding to their demands after the tragedy.  The bombing in Madrid was a horrible, horrible tragedy, and every sane person in the world surely laments it.  But that doesn't mean that to proper response is encourage the terrorists--the only individuals sick enough to celebrate this tragedy--by fleeing from Iraq.  I must admit to being rather out of touch with all of the justifications used by the Popular Party to support the Spanish involvement with the Iraq war.  It could be very well true that these reasons merit a second look, and maybe the reasons were sufficiently flawed to provoke a withdrawal.  But it shouldn't be a gut reaction.  Now is the time to reconsider, perhaps.  A time for protests and editorials, a time to parade  urlLink  Guernica   around the world.  But it's not the time for an immediate withdrawal.  Could one even conceive of a better way to please the monsters behind this attack?  The reaction in our home-away-from-home, France, has been notably different.   urlLink An editorial in  Le Monde   shows that some French intellectuals are starting to realize that they were unaware of the threat of terrorism, even after September 11th.  It is easy and logical to see why the French among others were upset about US actions against potential threats when they did even see the  real  threats!  Now, perhaps we'll see more news about  urlLink French assistance in the war on terrorism .  A word on the causes for the war in Iraq: I've waffled back and forth on my opinion about whether or not this was a just war for quite some time now, as new evidence appears (or rather, fails to appear) regarding Iraq and the WMD threat.  One thing I was always skeptical about, even well before the war, though, was the connection between the war and Iraq and the war against Al Queda.  However, Blogger  urlLink Andrew Sullivan  makes an interesting argument that this terror attack in fact confirms that link: ...if the appeasement brigade really do believe that the war to depose Saddam is and was utterly unconnected with the war against al Qaeda, then why on earth would al Qaeda respond by targeting Spain? If the two issues are completely unrelated, why has al Qaeda made the connection? The answer is obvious: the removal of the Taliban and the Saddam dictatorship were two major blows to the cause of Islamist terror. They removed an al Qaeda client state and a potential harbor for terrorists and weapons of mass destruction. So it's vital that the Islamist mass murderers target those who backed both wars.  I'm not entirely convinced, but it's a good point.  These are sad, sad times.  My heart goes out to my Spanish colleagues.  I remember the events of September 11th all too well, so I have some idea of how you must feel.  Hopefully, though, all of us can use this tragedy as a way to reflect upon our own actions.  Maybe, if we act in the right way now, we can stop the kind of monsters--I can't even bear to call them people--who would be capable of doing something so awful.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Will- finally got around to reading your post and, not surprisingly, agree with much of your sentiment.  One aspect I find particularly debatable is the supposed "obvious" connections between al Qaeda and Iraq.  The blogger cited implies that the only reason for al Qaeda to target Spain would be in retaliation for their role in the removal of Saddam which must have crippled al Qaeda activity.  As Quoted:  If the two issues are completely unrelated, why has al Qaeda made the connection? The answer is obvious: the removal of the Taliban and the Saddam dictatorship were two major blows to the cause of Islamist terror.  They removed an al Qaeda client state and a potential harbor for terrorists and weapons of mass destruction.  I agree that Iraq did not actively condemn al Qaeda activity, but at the same time that does not make them a current client.  From articles that I have read I have serious reservation concerning the extent the Bush administration and others would like to solidify this connection.  Based on my knowledge of the situation it remains entirely feasible that the agenda's of both parties were completely independent.  It is all too easy to assume corroboration just because they shared what I guess could be called "anti-American" beliefs.  I guess I think there are far simpler rationalizations for al Qaeda to target Spain.  Basically any county allied to the U.S. in any cause or propagating what it perceived as western ideals could be targeted.  The fall of Saddam could have had no immediate impact on al Qaeda activity, but provides them with perfect chance to set their sights on countries and hopefully provide maximum impact on the resolve of U.S. allies (as is underway in Spain).  I am interested to hear your opinion as well as any others.   On a different note, I found  urlLink an article on the U.S. space initiative  that summarizes mush of the incorrect reporting on budgetary aspects as well as some of the political jockeying that is taking place.  Thought you all might enjoy it and find it useful in discussing some of the gross inaccuracies about the initiative that have been reported in the media.  A good look at how critical analysis is lacking in even quality news sources. 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      There's an interesting  urlLink article  out now in  The New Republic  by former NATO Supreme Allied Commander and US Presidential candidate Wes Clark.  Some of the key grafs: While our troops should help secure the borders and handle internal threats that are too large for the still-nascent Iraqi forces, they should, as soon as possible, stop policing the country for one simple reason:  They're not very good at it.  Instead, we need to involve Middle Eastern countries and the larger international community in building a unified Iraq with a representative government that doesn't threaten its neighbors or serve as a magnet for Al Qaeda recruiting and that exerts enough control to ensure domestic stability and promote economic development.  (Emphasis mine)  Reading this reminds me of a recent  urlLink interview  I saw on BBC World's  HardTalk  with Ali Allawi, the Iraqi Defense Minister, regarding the June 30th handover of sovereignty.  Asked whether he felt that the newly-born Iraqi government could succeed at stabilizing the country when the most powerful military in the world had failed over the past year and half, he replied in the affirmative.  He was convinced of this, he said, because the US army "is not too familiar with local conditions and circumstances and tends to use methods and methodology that are designed for different theatres."  Now, I'm no military expert, but those are two serious critiques from two people we probably shouldn't ignore.  That we should avoid at all costs having our army unfamiliar with "local conditions and circumstances," was, of course, one of the major lessons of the Viet Nam war, and this lesson surely has not been forgotten.  And it's not as if the US Department of Defense couldn't have foreseen a need for understanding this region; after all, they've had over a decade of experience there, including a major previous operation, Desert Storm.  So, why aren't they getting it right?  To cite Clark again: In essence, the Bush administration has scared Iran and Syria into believing that, if the United States is successful in its occupation of Iraq, they will be the next targets. To the Iranians and Syrians, the implication is that their survival depends on dragging the U.S. mission in Iraq into failure. Furthermore, America's perceived pro-Israel bias, and its failure to engage seriously in resolving the Israeli-Palestinian conflict, has fed the poisonous atmosphere fueling Arab anger toward the United States and its efforts in Iraq. Clark proceeds to layout some specific guidelines for how to begin solving these problems, standing in stark contrast to Bush's stay-the-course-ism and Kerry's silence (grooming himself as a VP nominee, perhaps?). To clear the air, the United States must first involve regional governments in Iraq's reconstruction, giving them a seat at the table in that country's development so they understand that they are not the next targets of regime change. The United States must also actively push the Middle East road map, with its goal of a two-state solution. The Bush administration cannot simply articulate a plan and expect the Israelis and Palestinians to follow--that clearly has not worked. Instead, it must hold serious and sustained dialogue between the two sides and among the so-called front-line states to hammer out details of a peace process. The road to Baghdad runs through Jerusalem, not, as the neoconservatives unquestioningly believe, the other way around. Clark goes on to call for an "Iraqi Development Committee," endorsed by the UN, and having representatives from each of the nations that border Iraq.  Clarke believes that this international body will help Iraq from selecting a theocratic or ethno-centric government, which would leading almost inevitably to repression and the splintering of Iraq into various sub-states.  Some food for thought as we prepare for Tuesday's discussion...
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      In  urlLink my last post , I wrote about how I support the need for new troops, but that I don't support taking them from other hotspots like Korea.  This, of course, raises the logical question of where else we can get them, as I hinted at the title of the previous post.    First, let's talk about numbers.  Currently, there are about 135,000 US troops on the ground in Iraq (Source:  urlLink DoD ).  Coalition forces, heavily dominated by US troops, number more than 200,000 in Afghanistan and 26,000 in Kuwait (Source:  urlLink Global Security ).  Add that to troops in Africa, Korea, et cetera, and a figure of around 250,000 actively committed US forces around the world seems reasonable.  Recent moves by the DoD and the National Guard have increased the total National Guard and Reservists on active duty to 169,000, supplementing this total (Source:  urlLink DoD ).  Getting estimates of the total size of the US Armed forces has proven very difficult.  In the end, the best results I was able to get were from the  urlLink Justifications of Estimates provided by each branch of the military  to accompany their budget requests.    Army: 480,000 Active; 14,000 Reserve  Navy: 371,500 Active; 85,000 Reserve  Marines: 17,500 Active; 30,000 Reserve  National Guard: 350,000  Adding these gives a total of about 870,000 active troops and 480,000 reservists, counting the national guard. From these numbers must come all of our active troops dispersed across the world, counting all of their rotations, all of those troops in training, and all troops permanently stationed in the US (for example, military lawyers, support staff,  et cetera .  I must admit to being fairly naive about those matters, but it seems to me that an active body of troops more than three times the size of the number of troops currently assigned to combat or policing duties is about reasonable.  This leaves the remaining half a million reservists--many of whom are already serving rotations in places like Iraq and Afghanistan--to cover any additional temporary increases in demand.  Now, while I fully admit my lack of practical experience to back up the figures, I would contend that this is enough soldiers that we don't need to pull men and women out of Korea in order to recharge Iraq.   Still, where might new troops come from, given the need?  Well, you might not be aware of this, but legislation is currently undergoing debate that would reinstate the draft.  Matching bills in both parties of congress-- urlLink HR163  and  urlLink S89 , both of 2003--have seen serious debate in committee, and both houses have queried the DoD for more information.  An interesting side-note about these bills is that they also make the draft manditory for women.  Anyone know how many other countries have manditory service or draft registration for women?
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Some rambling thoughts for William about my inability to have a coherent well-defined stance on any substantive issue of global political import this evening.  I think we are working with different news/information sources.    The amazing sobering power of our nazi-american (sic) print and visual media sources leads me endlessly to a sofa where I sit, leads me endlessly to a corner of my room where I sit or to the kitchen where I sit or to my bed where I sit, too lazy to procreate, foregoing all books not about something quasi-legal, quasi-scientific, semi-philosophical, or not about a man with long hair having sex with lonely italian-looking women on horse farms or in deserted chateaus.     urlLink  Simulacra and Simulation   might as well be called  Book About Something Besides Chateau Sex, Which I Will Never Read.   Feeling the piss-warm glow of "freedom" off the studio light glow from some newswoman's breasts and tired of hating words like hating propaganda, I have replaced reason and learning with this season’s mindscrew of images and processed flagrant media of various sorts.  My outrageous print sources include a circular with prices that are too high, pizza fliers that only give me "a dollar off a 14 inch pizza!" and a strange depressing “Have you seen me?” moment where I realize that I haven’t even seen the printed cards the last million times they’ve come – and, like the porn stars say, what’s the point of coming if no one sees you?  I’m sure by now I’ve probably seen a million runaways in a millions gutters and supermarkets, but the moment I start looking, I stop living and stop believing that safety is a wet blanket and happiness really is a warm gun, tucked in my pants like a prosthetic god or a Dionysian vision or a bank teller in Ohio.    I don’t have to burn books anymore – the kind folks in the advertising department have simply started printing pretty pictures on the pages, dismantling the moments of lucidity and coherent social import and stuffing them in my mailbox, sliding them under my door, filling my underwear drawer with them and building special plastic sacks in which to place my daily/weekly/hourly load of print medium values.  The women-in-bras section is certainly my favorite.  It stares at me, reminding me of a kinder time when men had to take pictures of women in bras with them to the bathroom and… you know…soften pages out of the sears catalog to wipe their ass in an outhouse.  Perhaps their asses were harder than mine – or perhaps our ads are simply more abrasive.  I have this dream where every flier in my mailbox has a swastika, a picture of Hitler, a giant eagle (which we share with our fatherland), and our national motto printed by the free postage parallel lines.  It reads like my dream:   “Buy this crap, troglodyte, or we’ll call you longhaired or french or a hippie or a  dopesmoking socially retarded mercantile-illiterate dumb-shit, all of which are apparently bad things to be called according to a semi-normative standard established by some old fat christian man named Bob, who’s never accomplished anything of social, cultural or artistic merit besides that time he drank a whole fifth of whiskey and then made love to his ugly middle-aged wife twice.”    Bob paints his beautiful vision in my mind as I think of all the other bobs that didn’t make it to the second time.  God loves you, Bob, and God loves the political malaise festival that is America.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The United States has just announced that it will be sending 4,000 additional troops to join the coalition forces in Iraq.  In the interests of doing the job right, as discussed in  urlLink this previous post , I support that decision.  But then I considered  urlLink where the troops were coming from: South Korea .  Now, I'm not yet an expert on Southeast Asian politics--I've only been here three weeks--but that doesn't seem like the best idea to me.  A lot of people believed before the war the Kim Jong-il was at least as great a threat as Saddam Hussein.  There was a damn good reason why we had 37,000 troops and a 4-star general stationed there.  Has that reason changed in the past year?  Has N. Korea gotten a lot more stable, and somehow managed not to get any press on this issue?  A quick check of  urlLink the news  makes me think not.  True, other nations--particularly China--are starting to focus on the situation of North Korea a bit more.  However, this is still a burdgeoning nuclear power.  The Vice-Minister for Foreign Affairs has claimed "that the DPRK now has a nuclear deterrent and that U.S. actions have caused them to strengthen their deterrent – both in quality and in quantity."   urlLink Recent visits by American officials from Los Alamos  have raised some concerns over the nuclear program:   I view a “deterrent” to have at least three components: 1) The ability to make plutonium metal, 2) the ability to design and build a nuclear device, and 3) the ability to integrate the nuclear device into a delivery system. What we saw at Yongbyon was that they apparently have the capability to do the first. However, I saw nothing and talked to no one that allowed me to assess whether or not they have the ability to design a nuclear device. And, of course, we were not able to assess the integration into a delivery vehicle.  So, perhaps their nuclear program isn't ready yet.  But when you consider the Vice-Minister's non-chalant way of saying "the bomb dropped by the US at Nagasaki was made after four months of preparation. It's now a half century later, and we have more up-to-date technologies, so you can come to your own conclusions on this matter," I start to think that maybe we're adding troops to one crisis at the expense of ignoring another.  South Korea's in a bit of a state of turmoil--afterall, it was only a few days ago that the President was reinstated by the Supreme Court after an impeachment bid, and only a few months ago that that president was shot and wounded while on the campaign trail.  Meanwhile, the North Korean tiger lurks just above the DMZ, posing just as much a threat as ever.  And the Americans have just announced plans to extract 4,000 of the 37,000 troops from the country, with additional plans to remove more troops, withdraw the 4-star general, and abandon posts in the capital city of Seoul.  Does this really seem like a good idea?
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Nick's post brought up a very interesting number representing the total cost to date of the War on Iraq ( urlLink see below ).  However, like in any purchase, you have to consider not just the cost, but the value of whatever you are getting.  So, what is the value of what we are getting thus far?  Obviously, with the mess that is Abu Ghraib, many Americans find themselves enormously depressed when considering the war.  Interviews shown in the wake of the Nick Berg video showed a lot people calling for withdrawal from Iraq--something backed up by  urlLink the latest poll numbers .  The Brits are having similar doubts after the fraudlent pictures from the Mirror, and pundits are once again calling for Blair's head.  But what would it be like if the Coalition forces left?  Today,  urlLink a suicide car bomber assassinated Izz al-Din Salim,  the head of the Iraqi Governing Council, along with several others, both American and Iraqi.  It seems that even with the coalition forces present, the fundamental security of the country has not been assured.  Salim's death means 2 out of twenty five members of the IGC have been assassinated--8% of the highest local authority.  Salim currently held the rotating presidency.  Salim was also a leading Shiite Muslim.  If important officials like him cannot be protected, the coalition forces pulling out of Iraq would seem like abandoning a dying man to the vultures.  If the IGC is still to play a vital role in the transition of power and the eventual election of a democratic government for Iraq, clearly more security is needed.   urlLink The Spanish troops , called home in the wake of the 3/11 Madrid attacks and the ensuing elections,  urlLink certainly think so.   The are additional reasons to stay in Iraq beyond simply helping the Iraqi people out of a tough situation we are partly responsible for putting them in: the war on terror.  Whatever your opinions on the connection between Sadaam's regime and al Queda, one thing is clear: Iraq is currently acting as a magnet for the types of people who plan these attacks.  Yes, it makes life hell for the coalition troops, but at the same time, I have to think that capturing these men will be easier in Iraq than in Afghanistan.  Perhaps staying in Iraq means we capture or kill men like Abu Musab al-Zarqawi just a little bit sooner.  Every fanatical leader who gets on TV to tell insurgents that captured female soldiers should be kept as slaves further convinces me that leaving Iraq might mean running away from the people we are trying to hunt down.  And there is clearly a lot more to be done in the war of terror.  I was watching the news the other day, and they were discussing how locals lining up to see the marriage procession of the prince of Denmark were forbidden to throw flowers due to worries over suspected terrorism.  And now al Queda has even said that  urlLink  Canada  is a target .  Clearly, the world isn't a terribly safe place right now.  We need to be doing a better job on the terrorism front.  This may require radical changes in our strategy--perhaps a new Secretary of Defense, although  urlLink Joe Lieberman doesn't think so --but right now, I can't see how pulling out Iraq helps us more than it hurts.  (Thanks to  urlLink Big Tent  for some of these links.)
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's been an extraordinary week in world news.  We've had the election of a new government in the world's largest democracy, which proved a shock to all experts predicting a BJP landslide.  We've had assassination in Chechnya, throwing that troubled place back a few steps.  We've had the Korean President reinstated after an impeachment bid was overthrown by the Supreme Court.  The ever-volatile situation in Gaza and the West Bank has once more flared up, with the worst violence there in years.  For a change, news in the other hemisphere was dominated by the events in this one, with the scandal resulting from the horrible abuses at Abu Ghraib and the decapitation of Nick Berg dominating the news.  Still, the Americas have provided plenty of newsworthy material themselves, ranging from the elections in the Dominican Republic to massive demonstrations by Castro loyalists in Cuba, and from gay marriage in Massachusetts to private spaceflight to the threshold of Outer Space.  If we can't find anything to write on now, than clearly this site should be shut down!  So, hopefully, we'll start seeing some more activity on this site; and hopefully, as we begin to create our own identity, a new name should suggest itself.  Please put your suggestions in as comments to the Name post below.  Additionally, please send me any links you want posted in your section on the sidebar
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I apologize for not updating in awhile, I'm too busy living and watching rocket launches at Top Secret locations.  I'll try to be better.    Here are my thoughts for the day: The cost of the war in Iraq at this point is estimated to be about $113.600,000,000. We could have given a $20 check to every man, woman and child in the world instead. That probably would have gone a long way toward stopping terrorism. 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Florilegium is seeking a new name, to replace the "spcorner" in our URL, and possible also the title itself.  New names should be catchy, appropriate, easy to remember, and easy to spell.  Would you believe that earlier suggestions, including Dialectic(s), Small Step(s), TalkSpot, and Florilegium itself were all taken?  Some candidates, along with their definitions / explantions:     One Method  -  Reference to a T.S. Eliot quote: "There is no method but to be very intelligent."   Brethren  -  Reference to Thomas Paine quote: "The world is my country, all mankind are my brethren, and to do good is my religion."   Sustained Thought  -  Reference to Voltaire quote: "No problem can withstand the assault of sustained thinking."   Biased Opinions  -  Refers to the fact that we are several people with several different points of view, but all biased in our own way.  Tagline could be the Oscar Wilde quote: "It is only about things that do not interest one that one can give a really unbiased opinion, which is no doubt the reason why an unbiased opinion is always valueless."   Suggest others or give your opinions in the comments section.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A collection of articles that might interest all of you, from an internal UN staff email.  On 8 May 2004, the Franklin and Eleanor  Roosevelt Institute honoured Secretary-General Kofi Annan by awarding him the Roosevelt Institute's Four Freedoms Medal. The "Four Freedoms" was an expression coined by President Franklin Delano Roosevelt in a speech to the United States Congress in 1941. Roosevelt Institute Co-Chairman Ambassador William J. vanden Heuvel presented the award to Mrs. Nane Annan on the Secretary-General's behalf following a ceremony at the Abbey of Middelburg, The Netherlands — the ancestral home of the Roosevelt family.  Below are links to past issues of the UN Chronicle and its online edition that are particularly relevant to the Four Freedoms.  FREEDOM OF SPEECH AND EXPRESSION  urlLink 3 May 2004 Remarks on World Press Freedom Day in New York  By Secretary-General Kofi Annan   urlLink Journalists: Must They Remain Neutral in Conflict?  By Ann Grier Cutter, Public Relations Coordinator, Carnegie Commission on Preventing Deadly Conflict, 1999   urlLink Interview with Guy-Olivier Segond, Special Ambassador for the World Summit on the Information Society (WSIS), Geneva 2003     FREEDOM OF WORSHIP  urlLink 29 August 2000 Addressing Millennium Summit of Religious and Spiritual Leaders  By Secretary-General Kofi Annan   urlLink Chronicle Essay: Measuring Civilization  By Mark Lattimer, Director, Minority Rights Group International, 2002   urlLink Reinforcing a Humanitarian Mandate  By Agon Demjaha, Kosovar Civil Society Foundation of the Federal Republic of Yugoslavia, 2000    FREEDOM FROM WANT  urlLink 16 January 2004 We must refocus our energies on poverty and other threats  By Secretary-General Kofi Annan   urlLink Eradicating Extreme Poverty and Hunger: How We Define Poverty  By Ramon O. Blanco, Ambassador, Permanent Mission of the Dominican Republic to the UN, 2002   urlLink Not by Bread Alone   . . . but not without bread either  By Thomas Hammarberg, Secretary-General's Special Representative for Human Rights, Cambodia, 1998    FREEDOM FROM FEAR  urlLink 6 February 2003 ‘Disturbing’ Erosion in WMD Norms  By Secretary-General Kofi Annan   urlLink Defending... The Universal Declaration of Human Rights  By Dumitru Mazilu, Chairman of the 31st session of the United Nations Commission on International Trade Law, 1998   urlLink The Geneva Conventions: Protecting People in Times of War  By Yves Sandoz, Director, International Law and Communication, International Committee of the Red Cross, 1999
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Not too long ago, US President George W. Bush labeled cleric Moqtada al-Sadr as a "thug," among other things.  For his part, al-Sadr has lead his supports in continual warfare against coalition troops, punctuating the days with ceasefires and attacks with alarming frequency.  A credible test to become a news anchor over the past few weeks could have been one's ability to say "the radical cleric Moqtada al-Sadr" ten times fast.  Al-Sadr's actions have lead 80% of Iraqis to hold a  better  opinion of al-Sadr over the past three months, encouraged by the continual harassment and grief he has brought to the Americans and their allies, and outraged at the Coalition's willingness to return fire at troops holed up in holy shrines.  But now, that situation has changed completely, practically overnight.    urlLink New reports  have shown that President Bush has adopted a new lenient stance towards al-Sadr: if not going so far as welcoming al-Sadr with open arms, the President has said that he will not oppose giving al-Sadr a role in the new Iraqi government.  In turn, al-Sadr has told his armed followers: "Each of the individuals of the Mehdi Army, the loyalists who made sacrifices...should return to their governorates to do their duty."  Despite the quick fate of previous ceasefires between al-Sadr supporters and coalition forces, this statement gives hope for a period of calm in what has been a major hotspot in Iraq, both militarily and psychologically.  And that is undeniably a good thing for everyone (expect, perhaps, the most fanatical of Bush/Blair-haters).  But at what cost did this come?  Is Bush simply being as  laissez-faire  as the transfer of "full sovereignty" demands, and declaring that it is not his business to oppose the appointment of  any  individual to the Iraqi government?  Or is this administration, so intent--and rightly so--on harshly quashing terrorist both at home and abroad suddenly starting to adopt a strategy of appeasement in the light of continued violence and scandal? 
     
 
    urlLink Read more! 

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yes, this prison scandal just gets worse and worse.  The steady stream of images and videos seems to have slowed, only to be replaced by a similar stream of leaked memos and communiques.  The only question left is: which are more damning?  About the conditions: The [inmates] work seven days a week, are fed only twice a day, get no coffee, no cigarettes, no salt, pepper or ketchup and no organized recreation. ... They have to pay $10 every time they need to see a nurse. If they want to write to their families, they have to use special postcards with the sheriff's picture on them. If their loved ones visit, they see them through thick plate glass or over a video link.  Most inmates are serving sentences of a year or less for relatively minor convictions or are awaiting trial ... They wear pink underwear and black and white striped uniforms. Around 2,000 inmates live in tents under the blazing ... sun in temperatures which last summer often exceeded 120 degrees Fahrenheit ... "I got meal costs down to 40 cents a day per inmate. It costs $1.15 a day to feed the department's dogs. Now, I'm cutting prisoners' calories from 3,000 to 2,500 a day," the sheriff said during a recent tour.  Next morning at 6 a.m., 15 [prisoners] assembled for chain gang duty. They were padlocked together by the ankle, five to each chain, and marched military style out to a van that transported them to their work site -- a county cemetery half an hour out of the city in the desert.  Yes, that is fundamentally disturbing.  Of course, what makes it even more disturbing is that fact that  urlLink the article  is from October, 2003.  And that it is talking about a prison not in Iraq, but in Arizona. That's right, this was all happening  in the United States .  So much damage has already been done.  A significant number of Iraqis--54%, according to  urlLink a recent poll --believe that all Americans are fundamentally similar to the soldiers who committed the abuses at Abu Ghraib.  Now, it is up to Americans to prove to Iraqis and to the world that those who could commit abuses such as those in Arizona or Iraq, and those who could order such abuses committed, are not the majority of the population, but rather a freakish one percent who will be dealt with harshly--and humanely. 
     
 
    urlLink Read more! 

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Baudrillard talks of the "procession of simulacra," and our daily home page or a cursory glance at online sources reveals just such a procession.  The difference between cnn.com, yahoo.com, and I-made-this-up-and-you-believe-it.com seems to be merely a function of repetition and belief in credibility.  Like frames in a Warhol silkscreen, we look with similar aesthetic contentment on endless takes of the same constructed reality, created entirely with the amusement of the audience in mind rather than the accuracy of a given situation.  Like Israel Goldkiss' father in  The Million Dollar Hotel , we must acknowledge that each day, news media in 60 countries decide what "the Truth" is, and in each one it's different, as it is narrowly tailored to suit the entertainment, consumerism, and ideological needs of its intended audience.  Where, oh where, is Chechnya in my nightly digest?  Our fickle consumer media are selling us sadness in the worst sense: localized regional media promote the isolation of individual cultures from the broad perspective of "humanity."  A quick glance in a book store can show where the proliferation of online and print media will take us.  The endless repetition of ideas that are miscontextualized or without original reference.  Like the self-righteous author who writes to see words on a page, we watch to have referential fodder with which we make bland political references in specialized social contexts.  We are a globe obsessed with "being told" but wholly disinterested in "finding out."  Ours is an archetypal society suffering from graphomania (and blogging, by the way, is a perfect point of reference for such limitless proliferation of knowledge).  Each country reads its region-specific news as each individual writes to a small group of disarticulated viewers, each suffering from a desire to write and be read.  An extensive quote from Kundera reveals the perfect position of Americans to talk endlessly to ourselves about little or nothing:   Graphomania [an obsession with writing] takes on the proportions of a mass epidemic whenever a society develops to the point where it can provide three basic conditions:  a high enough degree of general well-being to enable people to devote their energies to useless activities;  an advanced state of social atomization and the resultant general feeling of the isolation of the individual;  a radical absence of significant social change in the internal development of the nation.    (In this connection I find it symptomatic that in France, a country where nothing really happens, the percentage of writers is twenty-one times higher than in Israel...)  ...the effect transmits a kind of flashback to the cause.  If general isolation causes graphomania, mass graphomania itself reinforces and aggravates the feeling of general isolation.  The invention of printing originally promoted mutual understanding.  In the era of graphomania the writing of books has the opposite effect: everyone surrounds himself with his own writings as with a wall of mirrors cutting off all voices from without.  Worse still than print are electronic media.  We are faced with the endless procession of simulacra: copies of impressions of representations of ideas.  Tonight's top headline is a perfect example: "Nation's capital mourns Ronald Reagan."  Does this mean I cannot mourn one for the Gipper?  If the nation were actually grieving, we would know it by our grief.  Rather, a nation distanced from political discourse, like Reagan was distanced from memory and reality, is comforted by the passive knowledge that somewhere, somehow, someone is mourning a president that died.  If we have so little concern for a two-term vestige of American history, how more passive and indifferent still is our acceptance of news reports telling us everything from the turmoil visited on Iraq (or social change for the better?) by our presence to the global distain of U.S. foreign policy in general.  A headline reading "World Hates U.S." might as well read "People Somewhere Hate Something Intangible and Disjointed with No Cohesive Basis from which to Self-Identify."  Try to get riled up about that.
     
 
    urlLink Read more! 

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      As anyone who drives can tell you by the thinning of their wallet, the high oil prices of late are still hitting hard.  True, the price at the pump has been slowly dropping for the past several days, but compared to a year ago, they’re up about $0.54 a gallon (US Department of Energy).  Since the start of this sharp increase almost two months ago, analysts everywhere have been saying that this rise isn’t just a spike, it’s going to last a while.  The reason for this?  Despite the obvious conclusion that prices are up because of war in Iraq and the recent terrorist attack in Saudi Arabia, a simpler explanation is that prices are up because worldwide demand is up.  Sure, the troubles in the Middle East are causing an increase in cost, but many economies, notably China’s, are growing at greater rates now than they were a year ago.  China’s oil consumption is up 20%, and that has profound affects on the world’s oil supply.    So what’s going to happen?  Well, the first place everyone seems to turn is OPEC.  On a side note, if you are ever looking for a laugh, go to OPEC’s website, where they have a nice little document that tries to explain why the increase in oil prices are really just the result of G8 nations charging too much gas tax ( urlLink Look here ).  Now I don’t want to get into a discussion about taxes, yes you can argue that they’re too high, but for right now, they’re not what’s causing the rise in prices.  Back to OPEC…so, a rise in demand combined with a steady supply…let’s see if I remember my economics courses…an increase in price!  So an increase in supply should be the ticket to lower fuel costs.  Well, at OPEC’s meeting in Beirut this past weekend, they agreed to increase their production quotas by 8% or about 2 million barrels per day (bpd) as of July 1.  This announcement seems to have calmed some nerves as prices have been dropping the last few days.  The question then becomes, is this sustainable?  OPEC nations are known for over producing, so it is unknown whether the quota increase will actually increase oil supplies, or just legitimize what is being produced.  On a bit of a tangent here, it should be noted that of the 11 OPEC member states, it was Saudi Arabia who was pushing the most for the quota increase.  Now while they control about 25% of the world’s oil reserves and have the ability to increase production, some other OPEC nations are at, or close to their limits.  Indeed, Indonesia has recently become a net importer of oil.  Ah well, at least in America oil will be cheaper thanks to the Saudis, and in an election year too, how nice of them! Okay, so I was talking about supply.  So setting aside OPEC, we’re still faced with an ever more oil-hungry world consuming an ever decreasing supply pretty grim, eh?  A bit.  New technologies are being developed all the time that find new sources of oil and allow better extraction of know reserves.  A great example of this is in Alberta, Canada.  About 25% of the world’s oil reserves are locked up there.  The problem is that it’s too expensive to extract oil from the sand it’s mixed with, but given a few more dollars per barrel increase, and a lot more oil will be flowing down from Fort McMurray.  There are situations like this all over the world.  Combine that with a decrease in SUV sales and an increase in hybrid car sales (not that those last two will have that big of a market influence, but they’re good indicators) and the future is about as clear as, well the oil.  The good news is that it doesn’t look like there’s going to be an actual fuel shortage anytime soon, but the bad news is that the days of $30 per barrel seem to have passed us by.   The bottom line though, however, you may think Is that the recent drop is just a temporary sink In the long run, you see, the costs will have to rise, Despite a calmed Iraq and more presidential lies So when you’re filling up, have extra cash at hand ‘Cause we’ll still all be stuck with supply and demand.  
     
 
    urlLink Read more! 

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The United States spends an enormous amount on its military.  In fiscal year 2004 (covering the period from October 1, 2003 to September 30, 2004), the U.S. government spent $454 billion on national defense, an amount equivalent to 19.6% of total U.S. government outlays or 4.0% of U.S. gross domestic product.  Maybe I'm pinching pennies, but I don’t believe that this level of spending can be justified, even in the context of the U.S. war against terrorism.  The U.S. military serves two main functions:  as a defense against foreign attack on the United States and its possessions, and as a foreign policy tool can be invoked, if necessary, to further U.S. interests.  The military do other things—for example, responding to natural disasters, and conducting research and development applicable to civilian purposes—but these functions comprise a small portion of all military activity and could just as well be served by non-military personnel.  Thus, the two benefits of the U.S. military are guaranteeing public safety and furthering U.S. interests abroad.  I discuss these two issues separately.  What are the public safety benefits provided by the military, and are they worth the costs?  It is difficult to compare intangibles such as public safety with monetary costs.  Nonetheless, recent events do provide some context.  For example,  urlLink according to the Center for Contemporary Conflict , the direct costs of the September 11th attacks were estimated to be $27.2 billion, and the medium-term effect on the U.S. economy was much larger (somewhat less than $500 billion).  Thus, the benefits of improved public safety can be very large indeed.  The real question is whether a strong military can provide those benefits.  Certain portions of the military, such as the CIA, certainly do play an important role in defense against terrorist attacks.  However, intelligence gathering, which makes up about 10% of all military expenditures ( urlLink Source ), is only one of many functions of the U.S. military.  The other 90% of the military is much better suited to defend and attack foreign armies.  However, the threats faced by the United States today are not the same kind of threats the U.S. faced fifty years ago.  Today, long after the end of the Cold War, I find it hard to imagine a situation in which the U.S. would be directly attacked by another nation’s army.  Thus, the majority of military expenditures provide little in the way of public safety benefits.  The other main role of the military is to promote U.S. foreign policy.  Unfortunately, the military’s foreign policy benefits are even harder to quantify than its public safety benefits.  Obviously, the military has been crucial to recent American policy in Iraq, Afghanistan, and Haiti.  It is also an important negotiating tool with countries such as China and North Korea.  The U.S. certainly has a strong moral and economic interest in promoting free, democratic government across the world, and in toppling regimes that are hostile to the U.S.  However, it is not clear that military force is the best way of promoting these interests.  Certainly it is not the only way.  I posit (without trying to justify the statement—that would take a separate essay) that because of the U.S.’s massive investment in the military, other political, monetary, and technological options that would be much more effective often go overlooked.  Ultimately, I am not advocating that the U.S. should eliminate its military.  A strong, well-trained military is an essential component of both U.S. national defense and foreign policy.  However, I argue that it is simply inappropriate for 4.0% of the U.S. gross domestic product to be spent on military defense.  I find it hard to believe that U.S. citizens would be any less safe if the military’s budget were reduced by fifty percent and half of the 1.4 million active duty personnel were sent home.  The other $220 billion dollars could be used for other purposes, or even refunded to taxpayers.  The 700,000 men and women released from the military could be retrained as scientists, engineers—or even as teachers.  Note:  My  urlLink source  of budget information is the  Budget of the United States Government:  Fiscal Year 2005 , published by the Government Printing Office.  The sheer magnitude of the numbers presented in that document are just staggering.  In fiscal year 2004, the U.S. government spent $2.319 trillion.  Approximately 65% of the total, or $1.497 trillion, went to social programs such as social security, federal employee retirement insurance and unemployment insurance, and Medicare.  Twenty percent ($454 billion) went to national defense.  Six percent, or $127 billion, went to environmental, transportation, and community development programs; another six percent ($144 billion) went to other programs such as agriculture, international affairs, and justice; and seven percent ($156 billion) went to payments on the national debt.  In the same year, total federal receipts were $1.798 trillion.  Of this, $765 billion came from individual income taxes, $169 billion came from corporate income taxes, and $732 billion came from social security taxes and other retirement receipts.  Hard to imagine.
     
 
    urlLink Read more! 

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      In an attempt to wrench the collective curiosity--or perhaps the inner workings of ones digestive tract--I chose to title this post “Donald Rumsfeld: The Best Defense Secretary America Has Ever Had”.  Hopefully, the seduction of such a preposterous statement will be successful in luring you all into extended discourse as to if and how this could possibly be the case.  Judging strictly from my own observations, I feel pretty safe in assuming that there would be quite a few self-proclaimed Republicans out there that would struggle to adhere to such a claim; not to mention the democratic constituency.  Nonetheless, this is the manner in which President Bush elected to classify Mr. Rumsfeld while at the Pentagon recently, presumably concerning the Abu-Ghraib mistreatment of prisoners (Source:  “What did he know?”, the May 22nd Economist)  All that said, and attempting to put my political bias aside, I thought it would be interesting to try and sift through his former political history to really see what he had done for our country.  The life of Rummy:  attended Princeton University; served as a Naval Aviator from 1954-57; took a job as a congressional administrative assistant during the Eisenhower administration; spent some time as an investment banker before being elected to the House of Representatives at the age of 30 in 1962 and re-elected in '64, '66, and '68; resigned from the House in '69 to take a position in the Nixon administration (held several positions); served as U.S. ambassador to NATO; member of the Ford administration, serving various duties and becoming the youngest Secretary of Defense in U.S. history.  He again held many responsibilities during the Reagan years: most notable were his duties as Regan’s special envoy to the Middle East, where he met and shook hands with Saddam (back when we liked Iraq for their harsh stance and mass execution of Iranians) and seemingly forgot to mention U.S. concern for the alleged Iraqi use of biological weapons during the Iran-Iraq war, and all the while maintained powerful roles on many executive boards in private industry ( Source ).  Not too shabby of a political trail, but seems to me there may be a few activities to be suspicious of.  As the CFO of  Searle & Co , a global pharmaceutical company, he was successful in finally receiving FDA approval for a chemical sweetener called  aspartame , despite the fact that since its discovery in 1965 it was the source of serious health controversy.  Aspartame has since triggered more complaints to the FDA than any other food additive.  Upwards 10,000 complaints have been registered over 92 indentified symptoms, including death.  Other scientific reports report symptoms of headache, memory loss, seizures, vision loss, coma, cancer, and brain tumors ( urlLink NWVexclusive/exclusive15.html">Source ).  I leave the conclusion up to your own device.   In the current administration not much else new appears on his resume other than his dealings with the so-called “War on Terror”.  One such contribution, reported by Seymour Hersh of the  New Yorker , is Mr. Rumsfeld’s authorization of a secret interrogation program instituted post September 11th.  Designed to target “high value targets,” the program, as reported by  Newsweek  (a Justice Department memo being the original source), apparently gave the CIA the go-ahead to employ sleep deprivation and other “stress factors,” with an additional memo categorizing the Geneva Conventions as “quaint”.  First put in to practice in Afghanistan, the tactics appear to have ultimately proven successful, and therefore were integrated into the Iraq war and somehow indirectly enabled the gruesome metamorphosis that has since transpired.  Having taken the moral high ground as a pillar of support beneath U.S.-led aggression, I sincerely hope the approval given by any and all relevant government agencies for this program, including the president, be rapidly withdrawn.    It would take quite an extended effort to really analyze the contribution of all former Defense Secretaries (see  urlLink this  for a list) to produce some sort of quasi-determination of who was most effectual.  For those of you who may know the former participants in greater detail, please enlighten me on your perspective.  As for my biased opinion, I would hope that there is at least one former participant that displays a bit less political shadiness and doesn’t carry ties to almost every presidential administration that has done something really stupid- i.e. Nixon and Watergate, Reagan and the Iran Contra.  A bit more sympathy for the immense power and fall-out of war would seem to me to be another desirable quality currently lacking in our appointed secretary.  This last point partially substantiated by the fact that Henry Kissinger, not the gentlest person himself, described him as the most ruthless man he ever met ( Source ).
     
 
    urlLink Read more! 

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Judges do not have the right to "legislate from the bench," nor does the President have the right to select judges without the consent of congress through a cowardly loophole, as has Bush on numerous occasions.  Recent important decisions including today's strike-down of the partial-birth abortion ban and the Supreme Court's ruling last year in Lawrence v. Texas, and the pending decision in Padilla v. Rumsfeld show the tenuous survival of many personal liberties in America.    Sandra Day O'Connor has been and continues to be the middle-ground of reason on the Court, tempering the mindless hermeneutics and conservative ideology of Scalia and Rehnquist.  I cringe to think of what similarly conservative King George II might do, and worse still what his judicial nominees might do, both untempered by any need for reelection.    But, with several justices about to retire, the next election will likely decide the fate of personal liberties as americans know them.  Voting "Bush" is essentially the same as voting "invasion of personal liberty" "anti-choice" "anti-gay" and "bring back the draft, which I constructively dodged"  Voting "Kerry" is essentially the same as voting "continuation of personal liberty status quo" "pro-choice" "gay-ambivalent" and "draft? what draft?" This is not a polarization - this is a sad default to the lesser of two irrelevant philosophically desiccated career jackasses.  One of these two "I couldn't care less about their existence" politicians will effectively decide the fate of personal liberties in America, and that scares the hell out of me.    Sadly, I know a great number (hopefully not a "majority") of americans will vote FOR Bush based on his substantive (sic) views on abortion, gay rights and the quid pro quo of "give me your personal liberties and I'll give you a pretense of security and the illusory quest to track down 'evil doers.'"  This is a sick, sick, schizophrenic country, and I wonder if some executive tyranny might not actually do some good to wake the sedated liberal pulse of this country from the endless after dinner drink that is political indifference.  I question only the ability of that pulse to resurface given the judicial precedents and strong weight of stare decisis that would certainly result from Bush judicial appointments.
     
 
    urlLink Read more! 

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Iraq is a young nation, created by the British from the whole cloth left behind by plate tectonics and World War I only 84 years ago.  In fact, the United States is a young country; one of the first to arise out of the misguided colonialism of the 17th, 18th, and 19th centuries, it will soon turn 230 years old.  (Half of this country was "settled" only two generations ago – barely enough time to establish a cuisine.)  Other countries like Japan, Russia, England, France, and India can trace their national history back more than 800 years.  They have had several governments, of course, but their national borders are recognizable on maps that don’t even include the continent on which the United States sits.  Comparing that to an average American life span of about 76 years, this makes the United States about 22 years old.  (That would, of course, be 3 in dog years.)  So the next time you watch the news, think of the US as a recent college graduate whose new job is helping an 8-year-old kid form an independent democracy.   The hegemonic military power of the United States is currently in Iraq trying to remedy some of the problems left over from that misguided colonialism that spawned our own Declaration of Independence.  Those problems will not be fixed by June 30th.  I don’t think the second Bush administration ever meant them to fixed by June 30th.  It is just a date set on paper for a political ceremony, almost a public relations ceremony, to show the world that the United States is not trying to be a colonial power.  Though my disgust with the current United States foreign policy has forced me to quit reading most political news or opinion, the idea that Iraq should have an independent government as soon as possible seems fairly acceptable to people of several political leanings.  The sticking point is that a young nation like Iraq needs a strong leader - a dictator, king, tyrant, or a tsar - to maintain its integrity, and the United States is not going to accept that responsibility.  There was some fault in thinking that led the war hawks of the second Bush administration to precipitate a war against Saddam Hussein.  I don’t know whether it was optimism, greed, ignorance, or belligerence.  It doesn’t really matter.  Instead of being a leader of world governments against the tyranny of Saddam Hussein, the United States has now replaced him as Tyrant of Iraq.   Taking a look back at a few famous tyrants, kings and tsars, we find that Peter built the modern state of Russia, Tito held Yugoslavia together, and Saddam Hussein’s power held Iraq together as a nation.  In my understanding, it is for this reason that the first Bush administration left Saddam in power after the first Gulf War.  There is no love lost between Iraq’s Sunni, Shia, or Kurds and only Saddam’s ruthless dictatorship kept them together as a country. There are probably even different factions within the Sunni, Shiite and Kurdish groups.  Coalitions of weaker groups or individuals are not stable until a leader such as a chief, a king, or a dictator emerges and unites them.  (I’m sure this is in a textbook somewhere, please cite it for me when you get the chance.)  For Iraq to have a good chance at remaining a country, which would be better for the stability of the region, it needs a new dictator.   The US invasion of Iraq has now put my country in the position of being that dictator, and, by necessity, we are forced to embody what we have pledged to destroy.  Control, and the necessary repression that goes with it, is now the job of the United States military.  It is not possible to be friendly or to negotiate with some holding a rocket-propelled grenade.  It would simply lead to a quick death.  Repression of the guerilla factions within Iraq by force is required in order to protect the population and maintain the integrity of the country.  This was formerly the job of a total nut case named Saddam Hussein, and he was very good at the control and repression.  Now the position belongs to the United States – not the first job I would want my first year out of college.   Many people I would call liberals (and/or hippies) deny the benefits of dictatorships.  I’ve seen some good intentioned non-profit organizations suffer from severe inefficiencies due to the lack of powerful leadership.  (The United Nations might be put into this category.)  I would guess that many...uh, "liberal institutions" have foundered quickly after their founding because they had no dictator in control to maintain focus.  In some ways, a dictator is just a very strong leader.  A dictator can efficiently solve disputes among members of their group.  That can’t always be a bad thing - sometimes it’s okay to crush the opposition because sometimes the opposition is wrong.     Of course, critical differences exist between leadership and dictatorship.  This is probably summed up by Plato’s "benevolent dictatorship", which, it would seem, is still an ideal.  (See heading: "Absolute power corrupts absolutely".) A dictator is a leader, but a vicious and cruel one. Stalin lead the Union of Soviet Socialist Republics through World War II, but he is the probably the poster-child for People-Who-Should-Have-Been-Assassinated. It is the responsibility of leaders to be forceful, to exact control on organizations and countries, but it is also their responsibility to allow others their freedoms.  The balance between freedom and control that a leader adopts is the difference between a "president" and a "dictator".  The new leaders of the Commonwealth of Independent states have all found their own balance.  Some, like  Aleksandr Lukashenko of Belarus  and  Islam Karimov of Uzbekistan  are called dictators while  Vladimir Putin , still a very powerful leader, is usually called a president.  For me, freedom of speech and press are the keys to being a leader and not a dictator, although those who have actually carried the responsibility of leadership would probably have more valuable opinions.   In any case, the United States certainly read Plato in college and should have known better (I think even a drunk cowboy on cocaine would have at least flipped the Cliff’s Notes during his four years in Connecticut). The second Bush administration took the country from being viewed as a world leader trying to rebuild Afghanistan several years ago to the antipode, the position of being a greedy tyrant invading Iraq.  The good will and coalition support that the US received after the September 11th attacks seems to have disappeared.  I offer no solutions.  We have entered a phase of "lose-lose" decision making.  Somebody screwed up about two-and-a-half years ago , but I’m not interested in taking the time to figure out exactly who to blame.  It would be just a little too late.  Once the United States invaded Iraq, and its residents were simply not happy with an occupying army, or became unhappy with the occupying army, somebody was going to get the short end of the stick.  Either the US beats the guerilla rabble into plowshares, becoming itself a dictator and probably losing several American lives in the process, or it risks the balkanization of Iraq to the detriment of nearly all Iraqis.  For Iraq’s sake, I hope it doesn’t turn out that it things would have turned out better under the dictatorship of Saddam Hussein.    Note:  Actual  average American life span  is 77 years.    Note:  All historical ideas are just off the top of my head.   Note:  The fact that  President G.W. Bush makes his home on a ranch in Texas and has put Saddam Hussein’s pistol on a plaque in the White House as a war trophy  supports the idea that he is a cowboy.  The fact that he drank excessively and used cocaine during college I guess I saw on the news once or something.   Note:  The idea that Saddam Hussein should be put back in power to maintain the stability of Iraq is hyperbole used to illustrate the difficult political/diplomatic/military position in which the United States found itself.  Saddam was a total tool.   
     
 
    urlLink Read more! 

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I know that everyone has heard at one point or another about the fiascos underlining the Indian parliamentary elections given the amount of media attention that was given. Firstly, the Indian National Congress obtained an unexpected triumph in India’s elections against the Bharat Janta Party (BJP) a Hindu nationalist led coalition. Secondly, the chair of the party Sonia Gandhi refused to accept the post of prime minister, undoubtedly due to criticism that she was Italian born. Finally, she decided to place former finance minister Manmohan Singh as the prime minister due to large concerns over the financial future of the Indian economy.   One of the questions that arises is: who is really in power? At first glance, it may seem quite simple to thinking that the people voted for the Congress party, and therefore it’s the people’s choice that will be in control. However, if that were the case, then there should have been no opposition by Sonia Gandhi to accept the seat of prime minister since the people were not concerned by her being born Italian. Given the circumstances--and her children's fear for their mother’s life amid fears of an assassination attempt--it is not surprising. But is the placement of Mr. Singh in office a mere distraction, while Sonia Gandhi will continue to pull the strings?  Also, given that the current collation was backed by the Communist Party of India, and given the fact that that party's concerns over not having received negotiated seats in the government lead Manmohan Singh to give away those seats as agreed, leads me to believe that the government may be run primarily by the communist party, while the people have the general impression that it’s the Congress party that are in control. There is also another theory of mine that points to important figures in the financial world being in charge, due to the appointment of Manmohan Singh as a minister when the financial future of India was questioned.         Primarily, the new government brings greater opportunities to the poor with the attempt to increase expenditure on public welfare while maintaining the economic growth rate at seven percent per year. Given that the BJP did bring about prosperity in India, there has been the notion that the economic benefit was not felt all the way at the bottom.  In any case, will the Congress party be able to bring about any substantial difference given that the poverty gap has increased tremendously over the years?  This one of the things which remains to be seen. These are issues which are common to the developing world, where public welfare has taken a back seat to those in power concerned about their own economic well-being.  But this is also common to the developed world, although not as apparent. In any case, many of the strains arising on the public--such as health care and unemployment--are due to the large population exceeding one billion in figure and increasing exponentially. If Congress is to remain in power, then this is one of the issues which have to be dealt with in insuring the future success of India as a whole.    
     
 
    urlLink Read more! 

    
</post>



</Blog>