<Blog>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Bald is Beautiful   Today's WSJ features stories on two true business icons.   urlLink There is absolutely no question - Mike Armstrong is right.   His plans for AT&T were the company's only choice - and the lack of execution was caused by a combination of crooked competition and possibly the world's least-motivated workforce.  Meanwhile,  urlLink there should be no more entertaining spectacle this summer then watching Dick Grasso's legal team take down sanctimonious windbag Eliot Spitzer .  What Grasso was paid is clearly, from a PR perspective, obscene.  But illegal?  No way.  This will be a bridge too far for Spitzer.  It's about time.  
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink O.J., 10 years later   If this doesn't make you sick, I don't know what will.  I remember  exactly  where I was.  Trapped in the Four Seasons hotel in Philadelphia, while a block party raged outside.  Disgusting...
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink WSJ.com - Too Much, Too Late   Got Abu Ghraib on the mind? Or just read too many Tom Brokaw books?  Read this to put things in perspective.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Amazing   This story speaks for itself - there have been so many stories written about the pervasiveness of camera phones, but even TV cameras are getting into the act.  Privacy advocates may cry foul, but here's one man who no doubt welcomes as many cameras as possible into our society.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        urlLink WSJ.com - Vermont on Ice   Absolutely on target - I recall a ski visit not long ago when we needed supplies for the kids and asked someone in the ski shop where the nearest department store was.  I was told 'we don't  have  department stores in Vermont - and  certainly  not Wal-Mart'.  We went to New Hampshire...
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Google's IPO  and the Valley's arrogance.   Jim Cramer couldn't be more right.&nbsp; My personal experience with Google (other than using it for search, which I still love) was with Reservoir Partners where we tried paid search for a few campaigns.   High prices, low response and we kept getting suspended (and having to pay to reinitiate) for low clickthrough.&nbsp; I'd be inclined to write it off to bad marketing but we were concurrently using Overture and getting  much  better results.   Search Engine Marketing is a 2003 trend that's already over the hill. Not useless, but past its prime. The world is full of SEM consultants who will soon be looking for the next hype wave to ride, and if that describes you, then you should start thinking about it right now.   This is all part of a broader theme I've been watching, also illustrated by the fight over  urlLink expensing options.  Google is not the only company in Silicon Valley that's over the hill - much of the rest of the valley is as well. The smart VCs know this and are pushing their overvalued charges through Wall Street as fast as they can while they can still get out.   I know that I, for one, wouldn't go near the Google IPO with my money.&nbsp; My god, I actually agree with  urlLink Dan Gillmor  - albeit for completely different reasons.  Maybe&nbsp;it won't be so bad if&nbsp;Google screws it up after all... 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>