<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I'm having a blast shopping for all the new toys and furnishings for My Asian Themed Facility and Chambers. Plans include building out various chambers, including an Elegant Goddess Bedroom, Suspension Bondage Temple, Medical Room, School Room, and Torture Room with articulating St. Anne's Cross, spanking bench, bondage table, stocks, suspension net, sling swing, and bondage chairs. We will also have a total sensory deprivation chamber! WOO HOO!!! This is going to be HOT!!! To help, folks need to be sure and visit  urlLink http://www.dominademanda.com/news.htm  to contribute to your Goddess building this for all of us!  

						
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Plans are all seet for the House of Shaman Hot August Delights weekend gathering in late August. It will be wonderful to see all our extended lifestyle family again and PLAY! I also look forward to meeting those that are looking to be considered for personal service to Myself and/or the Household.In the meantime, we secure the lease later today for the new facilities. I've been packing up all the goodies to build out a lavish Asian-Themed Fantasy Chamber in the main room and something more Polynesian-Themed in the front reception area. The articulating cross and suspension temple will definitely be moved there, as well as several bondage tables, spanking benches, and cages. I've found a carpenter to build out a large costume/fashion wardrobe/costume armoir for the area next to the lavatory and a full-on makeup station will be easy to add. So much  potential and so much more can fit into this facility. What's a Goddess to do but SHOP!  

						
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Six weeks with family and children visiting for the summer is drawing to a close. Although I will dearly miss everyone after they leave, I will look forward to catching up on all the phone and email messages, as well as messages here :)So many things to review and consider, and, hopefully, some wonderful interviews to schedule soon.House of Shaman's 2-day lifestyle gathering is coming up in late August... sooner than I'm ready I fear! Now, how many submissives service trainees, slaves, and pets will it take to clean, prep, cook, and serve for 30, as well as get the gardens trimmed back and presentable? Hmmmm... I'm thinking 5-6, which will work for 2 days prior to the event weekend and then provide ample coverage for Our guests during the gathering. PLUS... 5-6 in service,  will be even more eye candy and playtoys (boy/girl/trans) for Me!  

						
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I'm so excited today, I could boink a slave silly! I've just found EXACTLY what I have been searching for... A place to house our lavish and classy Asian Themed Facilities. It is a wonderful, safe, secure 1200 square foot location in South Florida, all under AC and where I will do My Live Appointsments. We will also do our fetish photography and videos, in addition to web content production, web design/hosting, and classes for lifestyle counseling, lifestyle grooming, and lifestyle fashions. WOOT! I can have a place to offer My airbrush sun tanning, as well as colour, aura, light, and tarot readings and healings, too! I'm soooooo excited... now all I need to do is get the funds together for the first 3 - 6 months rent. Hopefully, everyone will pool together to help!  

						
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I have now officially separated My Lifestyle FemDomme personal lifestyle, family, and household with Master Shaman from My ProDomme activities and commercial ventures. I am also hosting Mistress Intrigue's website now and hope to offer this service to other quality FemDommes, ProDommes, and Lifestyle Mistresses. Finally, we are also going to start more marketing efforts for Fetish Fires Fotography.   We are hoping all our friends and lifestyle family will review these websites and give us their input and suggestions, as well as referrals!    urlLink www.DominaDeManda.com  - Sadistic Goddess and Exotically Elegant FemDomme (ProDomme website)  urlLink www.FetishFires.com  - Fetish Photo and Video Services   urlLink www.DoMyBidding.com  - Domina's personal website and a portal to  urlLink Domina DeManda's  and  urlLink Mistress Intrigue's  ProDomme websites  urlLink www.HouseOfShaman.com  - Master Shaman's Personal Lifestyle Household website   Now, if I can get My blogs to work as well as CollerMe's journal!  

						
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Yes... that's right... blogging My thoughts... ideas... experiences... Such a challenge. Wondering if I can be as disciplined with Myself as with My pets?   

						
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   What an unbelievable whirlwind week! So much going on and so many wonderful happenings... Two new submissive service trainees, who both have tremendous potential, will be under a consideration term with Me for 30 days... New furnishings, toys, decor, and equipment all selected and/or ordered for new facilities... AND, I get to go hot, sexy, exotic, erotic, clothes shopping tomorrow! Oh... Life can be very good and oh-so-delicious!  The only drawback is that we are on "hold" and waiting for the landlord to make a final decision on leasing us the facility. Come to find out they may have to use it to expand their family business... This would normally be a HUGE disappointment for Me... However, I'm confident that if not this place, there will be another perfect place just around the corner ;)  I most certainly am looking forward to the weekend lifestyle gathering at House of Shaman at the end of the month... Good food, great people, wonderful discussions, and sinfully hot playthings! WOOT!  I am a blessed Goddess, no question!  

						
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Ouch! I detest Mondays... Again, still up at 3:15am Eastern catching up on email. Doesn't anyone use the phone anymore? LOL!  Ahhh... well I did. I got 7 calls out to prospective submissives who want to train. Did the intitial screening interviews and I'm please that 5 out of 7 passed and will move to the next step in the process :)  I am a bit disappointed with the current stats and numbers of actual (versus lip service) donations toward the move in costs on the new facilities. The good news is, those in training have been wonderful and not only have pinched pennies to help out, but are also volunteering their time and "muscle" when we are ready to clean, move, and decorate.  Still, My disappointment in the cash contributions does not outweigh My determination nor enthusiasm for this project. The potential for all that visit the facility or "call it home" is so tremendous and positive. How could I give up on that dream becoming reality?  In a nutshell, I can't. It has been 3 years in the planning and almost 20 years prior to that in the dreaming of...  Ok, My pretties... if you haven't donated, get whatever you can My way to help! If you have, MAHALO Nui Loa... truly.  Now, off to collapse and visit the decadence of dreamland... 

						
</post>


</Blog>