<Blog>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't enjoy entries like these because they never bring good news. They are sad and pessimistic and they cast a pall on the long weekend. My current job won't be hiring me full time, because they'd rather hire a paralegal who can take over some of my bosses legal stuff as well as do all the admin things. I think that's just terrible. That means that she likes me, but not enough to keep me around, and she appreciates me, but not enough to keep me around. So, none of the effort I have put into this will pay of at all in the end for any reason. God, that's just depressing. I don't understand it. It makes me wonder why I even bother to try. The answer to that question just dumbfounds me because I can't find a good enough answer. Not one that holds up. Maybe I should just try to stop caring. There's no reason for me to put so much effort into something that will pay off very little in the end. On the brighter side, i'll get to move on to something else.   
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I like this new posting via e-mail feature. Isn't it cool?I can't figure out how to remove the annoying MSN link though. It's the drawback.     The Big Boss is so funny. He's this really nice old man in his 70's who walks around in really bright colored sweaters and makes these hilarious announcements over the PA about the upcoming Lakers games. 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got my resume redone, and it looks fabulous. Thanks to the lady at the firm, it looks more beautiful than ever, and I think it might be a hit. If only I could get over my fear of interviews- but I guess the only way to do that is to keep going on them and to keep getting used to being in that kind of situation.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got a lead about a job from my neighbor via my mom. We shall see what happens.    
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm working on updating my template before I do anything else. I'm going to post mostly job-related links, and I think i'll eventually have a volunteer links section as well, since volunteering is what keeps most unemployed people sane (that and a handy bottle of wine). I won't link to many personal blogs like I do over on  urlLink FreshLife  because this is a different sort of blog. I'll only link to blogs that are specifically work related, like Call Centre Confidential, for example. If you know of others, let me know, phantom readers!
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Adventures in Temping 
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Maybe  urlLink this  article could serve as inspiration to not give up my until-now fruitless job search. Just maybe. I'm always cautiously optimistic about these things because articles are just articles until you have any sort of personal experience. If the UK media reports it, it must be true? Seriously doubtful. But, there's always the faint hope that they know what they are talking about. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've decided to ditch my pretty, title boxes. Sigh. I wish they didn't mess up the template so much.   
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, no, more like three actually. Three&nbsp; being the number of days per week to which they might (or will definitely) cut my hours. I'm not happy about this. I have rent! I have to be able to live! I just don't know what to do. Well, find a new job is one of the options, obviously, but I had been hoping to stay here as long as possible. There might be something in the works right now, but I don't want to jinx it so I won't talk about it here until I'm sure something will happen.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The thing about articles like  urlLink these  is that they give and take hope at will. Job cuts are up! But they're down from last year! Really! We swear! So how bad was it last year, when I graduated? Pretty bad, apparently. Has it gotten better? Sort of. Well, that depends on how much you believe these articles and analyses of our economic future. Apparently, things aren't as bad as they were at this time last year. In fact, last year probably seemed like job armaggeddon compared to this year, but I haven't seen it. I've seen people try to cut corners wherever they could, to quit hiring indefinitely, to basically shaft every single new grad they could by telling them they just couldn't afford it, when in fact they could afford it, they just wanted to post bigger profits.  So do I take much stock in articles like these? I wouldn't bet my last temporary job on it.    
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, it's official. It  urlLink sucks  to be ugly for just one or two more reasons now. Go figure.   
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My stay here at Corp HQ is going to be extended by about 2 weeks. They figured out how to give me more hours, ever since I threatened to find other work- so now i'm helping out one of the exec's assistants get out from her pile of work that's been building up for many weeks.  We'll see how this is going to work. It gives me more hours! Good news! 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      They gave me more work to do for tomorrow and Friday, so now I get to work from 8-5 both days. It's a good solution for now, so for now I am not going anywhere, but I won't know for sure until Friday what I am going to do.   
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here's an interesting  urlLink article  from the BBC News site about one man's adventures in learning French at a language school. Since i'm studying to get my  urlLink TESL Certificate , I found it to be hilarious. 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well,  boss and I had the official "I think you should just come in 3 days per week" chat, and I've decided that I can't live off of that. So, because I like working here so much, I'll stay a bit longer, but i'll tell the ladies downstairs that I gotta start looking again soon.  It's a pity, but it was a good experience for me to have.   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Thoughts from  urlLink Allsion  that i'm sure every job seeker has had before, and I'm one of them:    "The bastards never called me. Not even to say "no." Not even to laugh the evil laugh you so often hear bastards employ when they are doing something in that particularly evil-bastard style. No. Mine was the silent rejection of a dream-jobless loser."   Yeah. I know.    
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have had the worst work week ever, I think. I keep missing things, messing things up, overlooking small details that end up biting me in the ass. I hate myself sometimes, really I do. I know my employers deserve better than I have been doing. I need to chill out for a little while. My assignment might be ending soon, and then we'll see where I go from here. I just feel so tired right now it isn't even funny. Tired and rundown.  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The permanent agency called with a couple of leads, but they came to nothing since I don't have the experience they need. Oh well. At least they remember I still exist. That's a good thing! Keep up the good work.   
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm currently trolling various job-related websites for new career prospects and ideas. A self-help guru I was listening to said that if you think about something positively, it will attract that thing into your life. Maybe it will work with the jobs. What do I have to lose? 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I hate my new job.   Hate hate hate. Nothing but hate.   But, i'm trying to make the most of it. I get paid! Money is good! I have full time hours! More money for me!   But I still don't like it.   I told the ladies that I want something else. I'll give my notice and make sure that something else comes my way.   If I believe it, it will be true.   I'll tell myself that.  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have a new temp job, which is a good thing for my short-term money making prospects, at any rate. I'm a "benefits coordinator" for HealthCareCorp. Steady hours, more pay (overall), this will be nice for a time.   In other job news, I got an old interviewer to get me some editing contacts, so i'll work on handling those.   
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      More from  urlLink Allison's job hunt :   "I'm not going to die, or anything, but I realized, as the crushing blow of reality was delivered, that this was a job I really, really wanted, separating it from all the ones I have ever had, which were just jobs I needed. I feel like someone I love just walked out on me, which I know is really dramatic, but it's that same helpless feeling."    I've been there. I'm still there to a certain degree, though i'm moving on from past slights as a jobseeker. I wish I could offer her a teacake, or something that might make her cheer up a little. I know people who tried to do the same.   At work, Peruvia, my immediate supervisor, and I were speaking in Spanish (her native language), and I thought it was fun! She tells me I need to practice, just like she needs to practice her Mad English Skillz. Yeah. So, we practice together, because that's what we do at Team Money.    
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      They took my threats of leaving seriously, and found me a new position in the same department, this time actually interacting with people instead of putting things into a computer like a Monkey with too much free time to waste. We get to process things, but we work as a team, we get it done, and it is fabulous like that. It isn't the most creative job, but it's a job, and it's steady, and for now it isn't bad. I'm still looking for the Dream Job, and when I get it, i'll let you know.  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Team Money's week went rather slowly. Tuesday was a madhouse, as expected, because all of the mail piled up and so we were backlogged. I didn't get a break until 1:00 that day. Not one break. Well, the same could go for today as well. We were extremely busy. Wednesday and yesterday, not so much.  We got a new printer installed in Mama Ruska's office- so no more large, crappy-ass printer. Fast superprinter! Woo! Now I won't have to argue with Buddah over the size of the things that get printed. Fun times, fun times. So, work has been tolerable, and I like my team. We are good together.  I have an interview for two temp-to-hire positions on Monday! I'm excited. As much as I love Team Money, i'm not sure that i'd really want to dedicate a long time to them. Frankly, i'm still at that commitmentphobia stage where work is concerned, which is why temping has been so good for me. I still want to travel like a crazy, travelling woman! I still want the security of a full-time job! I'm a bundle of contradictions. Basically, I'm afraid of what I want, either way.  Help me, please, I don't know what to do.    
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This week at work:  &nbsp; Mama Ruska got into a car accident and will be OK, though she's in pain. I miss her&nbsp; whenever I have to go in her office to use the printer (which is a lot of the time).  &nbsp; I  urlLink pretended to be sick  all of Wednesday and most of Thursday so I could go home and curl&nbsp; up and watch VH1 and E! in the afternoons in my cozy room on my cozy bed with DVD player and cable&nbsp;TV&nbsp;at the ready. I feel slightly guilty about this, but not enough to actually regret doing it. Call it a guilty pleasure. I need those every once in awhile.  &nbsp; Buddah painted a&nbsp;garish clown/Tammy Faye&nbsp;face on a white squash and it is currently above her desk, mocking everyone with&nbsp; it's squashy smile and long, drawn-on eyelashes. I'm scared of it, and vaguely fascinated. I suggested she bring in fake yarn hair for the top of the squash. Or, maybe I could knit it a little squash-hat. Hmm.  &nbsp; We had an organizational meeting&nbsp;today, during which the management explained that they were going to be more "team oriented" or something like that. Oddly, this is an idea that they implemented about two years ago, according to some people,&nbsp; so it is hardly new. At any rate, I'm still a temp, Caveman gets out of his "cave" as we like to call it, and I now report to Mama Ruska (when she manages to get her crashy self back to work). They are trying to make everything more centralized and efficient, so we shall see.  &nbsp;  &nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Someone called me with a job lead, and never bothered to call me back when they said they would. Wow, there's forgetting for you. Maybe she'll call me tomorrow. Maybe i'll call her tomorrow. I want my job lead!    
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Let's see... It is nearly midnight, i'm still not in bed, and I have to be at work in roughly 8 hours to help get the deposit in for month end by noon. I have to clean three different areas in this house,&nbsp; and get my crap all packed up so I can go home and get packing for this weekend. Yeah. I'm nuts.   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This day would never end....... Slow-mo.  I woke up a half an hour late. I didn't get much sleep.  I think they will let me go on vacation, though.  I know it's my decision ultimately. This was such a boring day at work that I don't even know what to say.   
     

    
</post>




</Blog>