<Blog>


<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [via  urlLink Singularity Now journal ]  "Cyberkinetics Inc. of Foxboro, Mass., has received Food and Drug Administration approval to begin a clinical trial in which four-square-millimeter chips will be placed beneath the skulls of paralyzed patients.  If successful, the chips could allow patients to command a computer to act — merely by thinking about the instructions they wish to send.  It's a small, early step in a mission to improve the quality of life for victims of strokes and debilitating diseases like cerebral palsy or Lou Gehrig's. Many victims of such ailments can now survive for long periods thanks to life support, but their quality of life is poor."   At last!  Now all we need is decent speech-recognition software...
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [via  urlLink Nanobot  via  urlLink boingboing ]   "The genius of nanotechnology is the reduction of space. Smaller is infinitely more powerful. Consider the first transatlantic telephone cable. This bulky line carried approximately 32 phone calls. You might assume that to add more callers, one must simply enlarge the cable. That was the old way of thinking. Today, scientists recognize that less matter and less space, not more, equals more raw power. A micro-thin fiber optic cable can now carry 320,000 phone calls on a simple thread of light.  It seems that scientists on the cutting edge of nanotechnology are reaching the same conclusions about space as did the kabbalists thousands of years ago." &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;- Rabbi Berg   While Yehuda Berg is perhaps not the most sanctified individual to discuss these issues, having turned the Jewish mystic tradition toward  urlLink profit  and  urlLink Hollywood , his analysis of the situation is astute.  The Kabbalistic doctrine of  urlLink  tzimtzum  , advanced by Rabbi Isaac Luria in the 1600s, holds that the creation of the universe by God was not an eminent creative act but instead resulted from contraction.  That is, instead of a positive creation of the universe from nothing out of God's form, there was a self-gathering or pulling-in of God (who  is  the entire univers) to leave room for existence as we know it to take place in the void left-over from that contraction.  In the same way, Berg's comments recall that principle in modern communication networks: signal processing is used to pack an increasing number of messages into a static-sized physical channel.  In the internet this is done by what is called a Multiple Access protocol;  whether through partitioning a channel by time-, frequency- or code-division, random-access, or taking turns.  Berg takes this further by implying that through nanotechnology we are doing the same thing with the physical world itself.   Now, not only are we packing more information into static physical channels, we are also packing more physical complexity in to static-sized containers by decreasing the contents' spatial requirements.
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Cosmos 'a billion years older'   Measurements made in an underground laboratory suggest an atomic reaction that produces energy inside stars is slower than was believed.  It means that estimates of stellar lifetimes are too short. A readjustment gives the Universe an age of 14.7 instead of 13.7 billion years.   urlLink Chandra opens new line of investigation on dark energy   Astronomers have detected and probed dark energy by applying a powerful, new method that uses images of galaxy clusters made by NASA's Chandra X-ray Observatory. The results trace the transition of the expansion of the Universe from a decelerating to an accelerating phase several billion years ago, and give intriguing clues about the nature of dark energy and the fate of the Universe.  Don't you hate it when all your cosmological theories turn out to be just that?  Here's to another billion years of not knowing what the universe really is!
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Claire Whelan, a computer science grad at Dublin CIty University in Ireland,  urlLink has managed to decrypt blacked out words  in declassified documents, using " little more than an electronic dictionary and text-analysis software ."  She should be talking to  urlLink The Memory Hole  soon I hope.   [ via  urlLink Metafilter  ]
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I rededicate you, forgotten blog, by the themes of miscommunication, novelty, alternative interpretations, and a healthy mistrust and lust of technology.  Wake up.  I am another inferior imitator in this game.  This will be a slow awakening, like being interrupted from a dream but still locked in sleep paralysis.
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      by  urlLink Dr Vladimir Dimitrov , cybernetician of engineering and mathematics.    "In human systems, emergence implies serendipity and creativity both at individual (intrapersonal) and group (interpersonal) levels of interaction. For creativity to take hold and flourish, emergence needs space and freedom. Emergence cannot be designed. Emergence cannot be imposed. It simply happens - as a spontaneous burst of energy accumulated through the complex interplay of interactions. At an individual level this is the enigmatic and often paradoxical interplay between physical, emotional, intellectual and spiritual fractals of human personality. At a group level, this is the autopoiesis of communications - people in dialogue with people, people in communication with their environment, people in communion with the spiritual essence of the universe...  Emergence can breathe order out of chaos, simplicity out of complexity, serenity out of confusion, inspiration out of every day monotony, insight out of mere intellectual speculations. While we cannot design a specific emergence, we are not merely helpless witnesses. We can create conditions for it to happen, we can read its presages and empower its heralds. We can seed it and make it blossom for the Good of Life on our planet."  Dimitrov recently published a book, titled  urlLink A New Kind of Social Science: Study of Self-organization of Human Dynamics .  If this book is anything like this older article of his, it could be quite interesting.
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [via  urlLink Chapel Perilous ]  "The Mayan calendar is NOT an instrument for tracking the procession of time as previously thought, but as a meter and measure of the evolution of human consciousness."   "There is a repeating pattern to all of Creation. Quantum physics has proven this over and over in the organization of matter. There is a pattern of intentions and events, as well. We - or rather Consciousness - have been down this same road seven times before over the last 16 billion years. Each of these cycles of Creation runs 20 times faster than the last one. The same amount of Creation is paced 20 times tighter. This is why time seems to be going so fast. It is not "time" but Creation itself that is accelerating."   "There is a formula that goes like this: "Peace of Mind" comes when persons or a society are "centered." Centered-ness comes from certainty. Certainty comes from only one place: the recognition of patterns. So when a person or society has recognized a pattern as great as all of Creation, there is great certainty and centered-ness - and there is great Peace of Mind.   This is our challenge: to educate humanity that the changes scheduled as per the Mayan calendar are for the uplifting of all. They are the sure steps of the continued evolution of Consciousness and the increase in personal choice of experience." 
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Timeline of World Religions   via  urlLink Internet Sacred Text Archive     urlLink Military History Timeline   via  urlLink The War Scholar     urlLink Timeline of Invention  and  urlLink Timeline of Transportation Technology  and  urlLink all these other timelines   via  urlLink Wikipedia    I want to collect all this info, metadata tag it, and  write software that visualizes threads of interactions between these facets of human existence.  To know where we are going, our first recourse is to look back from where we have come.  Timelines are a collection of data points.  Histories are like stories, weaving meaning from those points as collective memory.  But often histories are myopic, centered on the point of view of an individual or culture and unable (or unwilling) to see their histories are subjective and not objective.  There must be some way to weave together this course in a manner that does not take sides, or that takes all sides.
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [via  urlLink Omega Point Institute ]     The radial fractal properties of the 13:20 universal frequency of synchronization have equally universal applications. The Tzolkin, the self-repeating 260 day (kin) sacred count, is the basis of the Mayan long count of the great cycle of history. The long count, of course, appears to be a purely chronological phenomenon, marking the count of days between August 13, 3113 BC and December 21, AD 2012. The count of days, is also represented by a master fourth-dimensional 13:20 matrix. The 1,872,000 kin (day) duration of the long count consists of thirteen major sub-cycles called baktuns, each sub-cycle consisting of 144,000 days or kin. Each of these sub-cycles is again divided into 20 smaller sub-cycles called katuns, each of which consists of 7200 days or kin. This also means that there are 7200 260-day cycles to the entire set of thirteen baktuns. The thirteen baktuns and 20 katuns represent a perfect fractal of the 260-unit fourth-dimensional timing matrix spread out as a chronotopology called history, where each katun represents one of 260 kin. The baktuns represent a set of waves (morphogenetic fields), each with 20 lesser waves rising in a pitch of climax during the thirteenth and final baktun, AD 1618-2012.   from  urlLink Planet Art Network    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [via  urlLink Download Aborted! ]    What happens when a bio-cracker unleashes a plant virus on all the wheat in North America, and the genetic code to "Wheat 2.0" is closed-source, patented code owned by a corporation? Should life be Open Source?    Lately there's been a lot of debate about the virtues and perils of genetically modified life. A few weeks ago, Canadian farmer Percy Schmeiser lost an epic David vs. Goliath- legal battle against Monsanto, the maker of seeds with a patented gene. The court narrowly sided with Monsanto, which sued Schmeiser in 1997 after company agents found a patented gene in canola plants Schmeiser's farm. The farmer argued that the seed had blown into his field from a neighboring farm.  
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Inspired by  urlLink this post  at  urlLink LVX23  about Jesus being a Discordian (through evidence by way of  urlLink the Gospel of Thomas ), I wonder what chance our current reality-models hold for future generations.  Past Illuminatists/Occultists used the Kabbalah/Tarot synchrony as a technology that mapped a reality-model onto a physical device for accessing that model (the Sepher Sephiroth onto a pack of playing cards), that has wormed its way into our current space-time locality (even if the signal is partially diluted by the noise of huckster-fortune tellers).  Our current reality-models of quantum psychology and self-organization emerging at the edge of chaos are intractable to the 2-dimensional medium of ink on paper.  They require computer visualization to realize their import and intricacy and transport it to future generations, just as now there are simulations of the mandelbrot fractal playing across LCD screens in classrooms around (selected portions of) the world.  My greatest fear is that there will be an age of darkness when the glow of computer screens, access to computers is removed from the world and our ability to transmit and understand these models  urlLink  on an intuitive level   is lost because they simply are too complex to draw on a piece of paper.  Surely they might be reconstructed from the 2-dimensional knowledge-store that will ( urlLink hopefully ) remain, but this is work that has caused the greatest cognitive dissonance in our present society and it would be ill to be repeated.
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink World's first brain prosthesis revealed &nbsp;&nbsp; |&nbsp;&nbsp;[via  urlLink New Scientist ]   The world's first brain prosthesis - an artificial hippocampus - is about to be tested in California. Unlike devices like cochlear implants, which merely stimulate brain activity, this silicon chip implant will perform the same processes as the damaged part of the brain it is replacing.  The prosthesis will first be tested on tissue from rats' brains, and then on live animals. If all goes well, it will then be tested as a way to help people who have suffered brain damage due to stroke, epilepsy or Alzheimer's disease.  
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Cory Doctorow, of the  urlLink Electronic Frontier Foundation  (and  urlLink boingboing ) recently gave a  urlLink talk criticizing Digital Rights Management technology , on which just about every corporation these days is spending increasing amounts of money in order to protect their copyright/IP-based business models against the consumers' (rights/desire) to make digital reproductions of purchased content.  The recipients of the talk were the Microsoft's Research Group; Microsoft is one company that is particularly throwing a lot of money into DRM systems.  In Cory's words, the talk boils down to:   Here's what I'm here to convince you of:  1. That DRM systems don't work 2. That DRM systems are bad for society 3. That DRM systems are bad for business 4. That DRM systems are bad for artists 5. That DRM is a bad business-move for MSFT  It's a big brief, this talk. Microsoft has sunk a lot of capital into DRM systems, and spent a lot of time sending folks like Martha and Brian and Peter around to various smoke-filled rooms to make sure that Microsoft DRM finds a hospitable home in the future world. Companies like Microsoft steer like old Buicks, and this issue has a lot of forward momentum that will be hard to soak up without driving the engine block back into the driver's compartment. At best I think that Microsoft might convert some of that momentum on DRM into angular momentum, and in so doing, save all our asses.  I found this to be a lucid and concise explanation of this important issue (concise relative the complexity of the issue) that is proving itself a nuisance for the nascent Information Age.  And Doctorow says "Arrrrr!" a whole lot!
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [via  urlLink Future Hi ]    Brain machines differ from traditional biofeedback, in that they act directly on our physiology either through sending subtle electrical currents into the brain, or through light and sound machines.  Not much came out of this field, and it seemed to disappear, but the basic science behind it is sound.  The key to these devices is the process called  entrainment .  The idea is that with regular application of certain frequencies of sound and/or light you can train your brain to go voluntarily into different states. Here is a quick summary:     State Frequency range &nbsp;&nbsp; State of mind  Delta&nbsp;&nbsp; 0.5Hz - 4Hz Deep sleep  Theta&nbsp;&nbsp; 4Hz - 8Hz Drowsiness (also first stage of sleep)  Alpha&nbsp;&nbsp; 8Hz - 14Hz Relaxed but alert  Beta&nbsp;&nbsp; 14Hz - 30Hz Highly alert and focused   Well, it turns out this stuff has gone a bit open source.  There are several programs available for download that generate these binarual beats to help you get into these different states.  The one I just discovered and downloaded last night is  urlLink Brainwave Generator  
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Paradigm Shift  - by LVX23   [via  urlLink Future Hi ]   "I had a vision last weekend concerning cultural/technological evolution and the concept of the Singularity (what follows is a rough outline of a larger paper I'm working on). The Singularity is alternatively imagined to be some apocalyptic transformation through fire which will purge the planet of the Old Ways and sweep the pure of heart into the next phase of existence, or it is a sudden shift in perception as technology is accelerating so quickly that life is indistinguishable from imagination. I tend to lean towards the latter, though I question how much of the Old Ways will disappear in the new paradigm.  But the vision I had was somewhat more mundane, acknowledging some of the current threads which will irrevocably necessitate a fundamental shift in the way we humans relate to each other and our world. Such a shift will undoubtedly call into question the entire edifice of western culture."   This is a prescient article much aligned with my own vision of the times to come, and what we can do as individuals in the interim to smooth the transition.   My personal research for the past two years started as an independent study project in Subsymbolic techniques of Artificial Intelligence.  These include artificial neural networks, evolutionary computation (aLife, genetic algorithms), and swarm intelligence.  The term "subsymbolic" is derived from the paradigm shift to viewing intelligence as emergent from lower-level interactions in connectionist systems in nature, as opposed to the traditional view of "symbolic" AI which relies on explicit logic/rule-based abstractions derived from the assumption that human intelligence is inherently symbolic manipulation (and deals with techniques such as path-finding, heuristic searches and knowledge representation).  "The first current is the shift from classical Newtonian Mechanics and Cartesian dualism which has laid the foundation of human logic for at least the past 400 years, producing the economic, industrial, and political theories which now rule the planet, to the emerging logic set informed by Relativity and Quantum Mechanics...  Binary classification of nature is failing. Yes or No, right or wrong, black or white - these are increasingly becoming more and more fuzzy as the western mind grasps the gradients between such polarities."  Symbolic AI and Subsymbolic AI fall along the fault-lines produced by the classical/Cartesian POV and the relativistic/quantum POV.  But the revolution that marks these paradigm shifts is not a clean break.  It is more of an evolution that takes what has worked from the theories and models which came before and incorporates them into those new models which shore up the rotting foundations.  For example, the idea from heuristics of winnowing a search space to a smaller field of inquiry is incorporated into genetic algorithms by having multiple agents explore a large sample of the entire search space in parallel, through variations and permutations on their digital DNA that serves as the "solution" to their problem of survival.  The use of binary logic for information representation in computer systems was inspired by the  I Ching  system of centuries ago in ancient China.  From combinations Yang and Yin, 0 and 1, the entire universe can be represented (to some precision...).  This very formula is now in the throes of growth like a cicada nymph shedding its husk.  Fuzzy logic does not require the complete abandon of a binary system, merely its revise.  In artificial neural networks, the activation function for a neuron can be of two types: binary or bipolar.  With binary there are only two values: 0 or 1, off or on.  WIth a bipolar activation function, there is a continuous spectrum of values between 0 and 1, a Real number line with a virtually infinite number of values (given the finest degree of precision).  But the binary system still exists in the bipolar, as vectors for changing values to become greater or lesser within the spectrum.  At the same time, this is a return to the I Ching as a foundation for computational logic.  For Yin and Yang may represent the entire universe, but it is their interplay, the spectrum of hexagrams (or beyond) which falls out between them which gives the real representation of nature.  Modern digital signal processing would be nowhere without this concept; if every sample could be a 0 or a 1 with no intermediate values, the mp3s I am listening to right now would not sound so great.   This is all well and abstract, it is easy to lose myself thinking about these things, but applying them to my life often escapes me.  I have started doing yoga and meditating regularly, it is the first time in years I have intentionally spent some part of the day not thinking about something or other.  And I've been spreading out.  Two years ago I roomed with a psychology and government student, now doing environmental law, who was not well versed in the physical sciences.  I had him read books about quantum mechanics and chaos theory, and his world view was changed.  He borrowed those books and has read them several time since.  I visited my twin brother in Pittsburgh a week ago.  We talked about these abstract theories, we share the same interests along these lines.  But he is more practical, hands-on, where I am prone to abstractions.  He taught me to play the game Go, and in just two or three games my own views were changed drastically by watching those black and white pieces form patterns of space and tension on the board.  The evolution of classical ideas to these relativistic and quantum ones will take more than abstract science.  It requires the hands-on moments, the emotional moments that bridge the gaps between individuals, just as fuzzy logic bridges the gaps between binary opposites with a full spectrum of possibilities.  Just as subsymbolic intelligence relies on the bottom-up interactions of so many individuals' interaction with each other through their local environment as opposed to formalized top-down rules prohibiting information into narrowly specified channels.  This paradigm shift that restructures the fabric of society will be paid in blood, and that is why we have to come together as people, as bipolar creatures of flesh and guts instead of hiding behind our abstract ideas and words.  A singularity that embraces such things as nanotechnology and cybernetics will not occur without embracing its own opposite in the momentary experience of each individual, beyond the technology.
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Any technology indistinguishable from magic is insufficiently advanced  "Think for a moment on how our culture characterizes "magic". Generally, it is envisioned as "occult" -- the obscure and arcane. It requires intensive specialized training, and even then, it is so dangerous and sensitive to tiny errors -- get one word wrong in a spell, and... -- that ordinary people can't possibly use it. It is capricious and erratic. And when magic is preformed by an adept on behalf of the uninitiated, often there is a terrible, punitive cost. The "magic" we imagine is rare and strange and uncanny and scary and very, very marginal to every day life.  Is that our dream for our technology, then? To make occult, arcane systems that give power to wizards in their isolated holdfasts and to sorcerors with their dusty tomes, but have no impact on the poor peasants who give their towers a wide berth, save perhaps to make them superstitious petitioners unto a power they loathe? I think it is manefestly obvious that is not what technologists dream."  [via  urlLink Chapel.Perilous ]    Based on Arthur C. Clark's saying, "Any sufficiently advanced technology is indistinguishable from magic," this article sets up the dichotomy of the general characterization of magick as inaccessible and perilous in contrast to the idea of ubiquitous and connective technologies that should appear as "just part of life."  However this is only an apparent dichotomy, and perhaps the difference between the two is being taken out of proportion to aggrandize one at the expense of the other.  In Aleister Crowley's   urlLink Magick: Liber ABA ,  urlLink Part III: Magick in Theory and Practice  , he  urlLink defines   magick  as: "the Science and Art of causing Change to occur in conformity with Will," with the further postulate that "ANY required change may be effected by the application of the proper kind and degree of Force in the proper manner, through the proper medium to the proper object."  I interpret this, along with A.C. Clark's saying, to mean that any sufficiently advanced technology is indistinguishable from magick not because it becomes obscure in how it functions, but because it becomes  a part of every-day life  as every intentional action in life is an act of magick (especially including science and technology).  The most basic pieces of technology, like a hammer, or language, are the most magickal because they have ceased to stand apart from our existence as biological entities, but become a transparent interface between our intentional will and the medium of our environment.
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [via  urlLink KurzweilAI ]    "Joy says he thinks the probability of a ''civilization-changing event'' is most likely in the double digits, perhaps as high as 50 percent. He doesn't merely ascribe these odds to terrorism; he suggests a pandemic disease might arise from a sudden accident or as a consequence of cutting-edge research."  Interesting tidbit:   "He's not exactly optimistic, predicting that public awareness will most likely come only after an actual accident at a company or a university. Until then, he says, speed -- the mad rush for patents and market share and money -- will trump caution."   Insightful point of view of current patent system and economic trends as releasing the throttle on accelerating technological change by increasing the value of haste in practice over hesitant policies.   More importantly:    "Good science, he says, is the discovery of truth -- for example, an experiment that yields an accurate result and that is repeatable. But science may not be good for us anymore if it yields a bad outcome."   This comment falls into a critical divide between two prevailing  urlLink epistemologies   [Principia Cybernetica] , that is two different ways of distinguishing adequate knowledge from inadequate knowledge (and scientific theories).  On the one hand, the empiricism of experimental science relies on the assumption of an absolute relationship between a model and what is being modeled.  That is, the degree of "truth" of some knowledge derives from how accurately it corresponds to an  actual  relationship in reality outside of the observer.  This is the notion of good science being discovery of truth through accurate results.  On the other hand, in constructivist approaches all models are relative, so what determines the adequacy of some knowledge is the quality of the relationship that having such a model places the observer into with respect to the environment.  In other words, "truth" is not some reflection on external circumstances, but derives from the efficacy or utility that the model brings to the observer's life.  This is the possibility that "good science" is not good when it results in a bad outcome.
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Is the World's Oil Running Out Fast?   "How long will the oil keep flowing? If you think oil prices are high at $40 a barrel then wait till they are four times that much.   How will you pay to run your car? How will you get the children to school? How will you heat your house? How much will transported food go up in price?   How will we pay for plastics, metals, rubber, cheap flights, Simpson's DVDs, 3G phones and everlasting economic growth?   The basic answer is, we won't.   This is the message from the Association for the Study of Peak Oil (ASPO)."  and   urlLink Life After the Oil Crash  "Interest in the Titanic has been revived because it's the perfect metaphor for our nation.  Intuitively, we know this is true.  We just don't want to admit we've already hit the iceberg."  "George Bush and Hummers are not the problem.  John Kerry and Hybrids are not the solution."  "Deal with reality, or reality will deal with you."  "A post oil world is going to be just like the Bible, well at least the bad parts of the Bible."  -Matt Savinar, The Oil Age is Over: What to Expect as  the World Runs Out of Cheap Oil, 2005-2050 
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [via  urlLink KurzweilAI ]  Researchers from the Weizmann Institute in Israel have constructed a molecular-size computer that is programmed to find signs of cancer cells, and when they are present, dispense DNA molecules designed to eradicate those cells.  The researchers' computer is a proof-of-concept that works only in a test tube, but the device is meant to eventually work in the human body.  The computer is small enough that one trillion of them fit in a drop of water and consists of three modules made from strands of DNA: input, computation and output. 
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [at  urlLink The Panda's Thumb ]   RNA networks, protein networks all seem to exhibit a   urlLink scale-free   structure. I intend to show that this  scale free  structure and other aspects of these networks not only can be expected from simple evolutionary principles but also how this scale free structure helps explain such issues as  modularity ,  robustness , and  evolvability .   Characteristics of  scale-free  networks  As is well known DNA sequences map to RNA or protein structures.      There are far more sequences than structures    Contains few highly-connected motifs and many less connected nodes    Motifs have a neutral network which extends throughout sequence space     For these frequent structures, their networks expand through sequence space, this means that gor any given fold, one can traverse through sequence space (that is change every nucleotide position) without changing the structure of the fold. In addition these structures are close in the sense that any such structure is within a small distance from any random sequence.  These findings have significant implications for our understanding of evolution.   
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [via  urlLink Invisible College ]  This Theory of Ego Transcendence is designed as a simple cybernetic device to trigger the experience of ego death, with emphasis on self-control breakdown, using the breakdown of self-control logic as the pivotal point. It is as simple and to-the-point as possible, while vividly portraying and conveying the main insights provided by the mystic altered state of cognition. This combination of ideas is the most concise and selective expression possible, of the essential insights involved in ego transcendence. 
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [via  urlLink WorldChanging  via  urlLink Metafilter ]   India's  urlLink Barefoot College  teaches poor and illiterate women to build and maintain rural solar systems in areas with little or no electric supply.
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [via  urlLink KurzweilAI ]  What we think of as life on this planet is only the surface layer of a vast undiscovered world. The great majority of Earth's species are bacteria and other microorganisms. They form the bottom of the food chain and orchestrate the cycling of carbon, nitrogen, and other nutrients through the ecosystem. They are the dark matter of life. They may also hold the key to generating a near-infinite amount of energy, developing powerful pharmaceuticals, and cleaning up the ecological messes our species has made. But we don't really know what they can do, because we don't even know what they are.  Venter wants to change that. He's circling the globe in his luxury yacht the Sorcerer II on an expedition that updates the great scientific voyages of the 18th and 19th centuries, notably Charles Darwin's journey aboard HMS Beagle. But instead of bagging his finds in bottles and gunnysacks, Venter is capturing their DNA on filter paper and shipping it to be sequenced and analyzed at his headquarters in Rockville, Maryland. The hope is to uncover tens or even hundreds of millions of new genes, an immense bolus of information on Earth's biodiversity. In the process, he's having a hell of a good time and getting a very good tan. "We're talking about an unknown world of enormous importance," says Harvard biologist and writer E. O. Wilson, who serves on the scientific advisory board of the Sorcerer II expedition. "Venter is one of the first to get serious about exploring that world in its totality. This is a guy who thinks big and acts accordingly." 
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I want to mention a few blogs I recently found or had sitting in my bookmarks before adding to this site:   urlLink Cydonian Imperative   urlLink Dehisience   urlLink Hive Mind   urlLink Hyperstition   urlLink Key 23   urlLink Mad Ghoul   urlLink The Play Ethic   urlLink Posthuman Blues    Also, I will be posting to this site minimally this week as my time is being consumed by two things:  (1) I have to finish an independent coding project in  urlLink swarm   urlLink intelligence  ( urlLink .   urlLink . ),  ad hoc  network routing, and P2P applications by the weekend.  (2) I am participating in the  urlLink Maybe Logic Academy  Robert Anton Wilson course, 8-Dimensions of "Mind", which started this week.  So far it looks amazing.
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [via  urlLink Etemenanki ]    urlLink Ammonia on Mars could mean life   Ammonia may have been found in Mars' atmosphere which some scientists say could indicate life on the Red Planet.  Researchers say its spectral signature has been tentatively detected by sensors on board the European Space Agency's orbiting Mars Express craft.  Ammonia survives for only a short time in the Martian atmosphere so if it really does exist it must be getting constantly replenished.  There are two possible sources: either active volcanoes, none of which have been found yet on Mars, or microbes.    urlLink Is Physicist Vittorio Formisano's  Mars Data Being Suppressed by ESA?    "Speculation is that already  methane is a rather strong indicator life is probably present  today on Mars. ...Formaldehyde (also detected?) is destroyed  in the Martian atmosphere within 7.5 hours. There is no way that  formaldehyde can exist and remain for a long time in the Martian  atmosphere. If (formaldehyde) confirmed (in addition to the confirmed methane), possibly life on Mars today, yes."   - Vittorio Formisano, Ph.D., Physicist , May 6, 2004 
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Esoteric Subjects on the Web  5000+ Links for General Reference and Esoteric Study  Qabala and Related Material    urlLink Weblogs/Blogs  section  
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [via  urlLink Consciousness Evolution Network ]  Let us begin this overview by first noting what appears to be a rather dismal fact: today we hear a lot about Cultural Creatives and the new and exciting rise of an Integral Culture--a holistic, balanced, inclusive, caring culture that moves beyond the traditional and the modern and into a postmodern transformation. But, in fact, significant psychological evidence indicates that in today's world, less than 2% of the population is at anything that could be called an "integral" wave of awareness (where "integral" means something like Gebser's integral-aperspectival, Loevinger's autonomous and integrated stages, Spiral Dynamics' yellow and turquoise memes, Wade's authentic, Arlin's postformal, the centauric self and mature vision-logic, etc.).  The same evidence suggests, however, that a very large percentage of the population--close to 25%--is at the immediately preceding wave of development (which is Loevinger's individualistic stage, Spiral Dynamics' green meme, Paul Ray's cultural creatives, Wade's affiliative, Sinnott's relativistic, etc.). Moreover, because most of this population has been at the green-meme wave for several decades, it appears that a large portion--perhaps up to one-third--are ready to move forward to the next wave of expanding consciousness--which means, move forward to a truly integral wave of awareness.   
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [via  urlLink Consciousness Evolution Network ]   "All human beings, all persons who reach adulthood in the world today are programmed biocomputers. None of us can escape our own nature as programmable entities. Literally each of us may be our programs, nothing more, nothing less."   -- John C. Lilly, M.D.  "You can't teach an old dog new tricks," "a leopard doesn't change its spots" -- language is full of sayings implying that people never change. Our entire society seems to be organized to prevent anyone from doing so. But throughout history groups of people have been looking for the means by which we can reliably change. The aim of this article is to give you an overview of our current position and pointers to sources for your own experiments.   John Lilly, more commonly known for his work on communication with dolphins, was one of the first researchers in what Tim Leary called 'neuropsychology': using the operation of the brain rather than human behaviour to determine the limits within which humans can act. Lilly's experiments showed that the brain could be treated as a programmable entity similar to a digital computer, but a computer which could program itself.   
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I designed a logo for this blog today, that is a glyph for some forces I see in this universe which influence many posts here.  After reading about fluid dynamics and chaos theory a few years ago I became interested in self-organization in complex systems.  In particular, I wondered what forces might be sufficient for the emergence of life and consciousness in the universe, and how we can interact with those forces as conscious entities living within such systems.  Putting aside the mathematics of nonlinear differential equations and second-order cybernetics, I have tried to abstract an intuitive model inspired by the appearance of vortices in fractal representations and in time-worn mysticisms of world cultures.  I call this  Vortex Magic .   "...vortices relate to the most essential property of complex dynamic interactions - their ability to self-organise. Both the maelstrom in the stormy waters and the tornado in the stormy airs are examples of natural vortices; they seem to have hidden engines which produce inwardly directed  centripetal  (‘sucking’) forces along the vertical axis of the whirling streams of water or air, and outwardly directed  centrifugal  forces. Both types of forces can be of significant magnitude, as in the case of tornado or hurricane. Of course, there are no hidden engines; it is the dynamic interaction of the ‘out-of-equilibrium’ streams of fluid entrained in a whirling motion that ‘fires’ emergent forces." -Vladimir Dimitrov,  urlLink Law of Requisite Vorticity in Human Dynamics    There are two different forces involved in a vortex: the inward-spiral (centripetal) and the outward-spiral (centrifugal).  It is the interplay and balance between these forces that creates a space in which organization, life, might occur.  This has been called self-organization on the edge of chaos, that is the region between complete chaos and complete randomness in which organization occurs.  In mysticism, these can be recognized as the two faces of the swastika:  The clockwise swastika from Hindu mysticism can be seen as representative of the "coming together of the forces of the universe."  The counter-clockwise form popularized by the Nazis in turn is the "coming apart of the forces of the universe."  The clockwise is the centripetal force and complete chaos, that is the fractal interconnection of all parts of the universe ( albeit  non-linearly).  The counter-clockwise is centrifugal force and complete randomness, that is the disconnection of any significant event in the universe from others (i.e. non-causality).  In Hinduism, consciousness exists as an absolute unity, Brahma the infinite spirit, that pervades all life in space-time.  In stark contrast, modern evolutionary theory sees consciousness as a side-effect of random mutations, disconnected gambles or accidents on the part of directionless nature.  Incidentally, this polarity of forces is itself recognized within Hinduism.  First, Brahma is actually part of a tripartite deity that includes Vishnu the protector and Shiva the destroyer.  So it is more fitting to see Vishnu as inward-spiral force, Shiva as outward-spiral force and Brahma as the balance between them in which creation wells.  Furthermore, there is the concept of the three gunas, which are the three forces behind nature.  These are Tamas (inertia), Rajas (activity) and Sattva (essence or balance).  Conceptually then, life exists as a shifting balance between inertia (or protection/conservation/aggregation) and change (destruction of old forms/dynamics/separation).   Evolutionary theory has also grasped on this interplay in describing the mechanisms of DNA replication and mutation. (I apologize for errors of simplification, as I am not a molecular biologist).  Strands of DNA encode for the possible form of an organism- DNA acts as an information medium on which our two forces act.  mRNA (messenger RNA) copies portions of the DNA to be translated into the proteins (i.e. the material expression of DNA).  "Transcription errors" can occur when segments of mRNA are mistranslated by things called transcriptase and copied in an incorrect manner giving rise to mutations in the resulting organism.  However it is possible for certain sections of the mRNA to fold in on themselves and avoid being miscopied by transcriptase, in other words protecting important features of the genetic memory.  So the mechanisms by which life perpetuates includes this same dynamic between change and inertia.  As these forces act  on a medium, it is reasonable to ask "what medium" and "what result?"  These vorticial forces are a transformation function that goes between matter and information.  This is not a one-way process, but a cycle that has two possible directions denoted by each of the polar forces.  In order to clarify this glyph demonstrates:     The inward/centripetal/inertial (clockwise) force acts as a battery or store.  It goes from information into matter via a message (such as an energy resource), and thus matter becomes a medium storing information (potential energy).  The outward/centrifugal/active (counterclockwise) force acts as a release or computation.  It turns matter into information via an expenditure of energy, and in turn uses information as a medium to act some transformation on the material world.  In other words, this is like a dynamo that slowly builds up potential energy through conserving information in a material matrix, then releases it in a flash by converting the material back into information in order to enact some further change on the material layer.    Hinduism is of course not the sole source of vorticity in time-worn mysticism.  " The myth of the God of the Egyptians, Khem or Khemnu, who created the universe on a potters wheel thinly veiling a keen and ancient understanding of the realtionship between spiralling forces and the formative powers of the very universe, at least ten thousand years before inventor Nikola Tesla talked about planets forming and creating planets from "the ether" via "aether whirls"" - urlLink Vortex Science and Magic  (the only source I could find about this stuff online).     The author of this site goes on to quote Nikola Tesla from The New York Times, April 21, 1908, pg. 5, column 6; "How The Electrician's Lamp Of Aladdin May Contruct New Worlds":   "Every ponderable atom is differentiated from a tenuous fluid, filling all space merely by spinning motion, as a whirl of water in a calm lake. By being set in movement this fluid, the ether, becomes gross matter. It's movement arrested, the primary substance reverts to it's normal state.    It appears, then, possible for man through harnessed energy of the medium and suitable agencies for  starting and stopping aether whirls  to cause matter to form and disappear. At his command, almost without effort on his part, old worlds would vanish and new ones would spring into being. He could alter the size of this planet, control its seasons, adjust its distance from the sun, guide it on its eternal journey along any path he might choose, though the depths of the universe. He could make planets collide and produce his suns and stars, his heat and light, he could originate life in all its infinite forms. To cause at will the birth and death of matter would be man's grandest deed, which would make him the master of physical creation, make him fufill his ultimate destiny."  It appears Tesla is proposing that we might gain control of the very forces which shape our life and consciousness.  I feel we do have some free-will in these matters, but perhaps more of an active co-creation and not a total "harnessing of energy": we cannot step outside the forces that shape us and attempt to control them like the machines we make.  But we can join with them in their creative power and thus partake of it as it flows through us as a medium.  Dimitrov says:  " The law of requisite vorticity states that  only vorticity can create vorticity . Vorticity is like energy and energy, according to the law of conservation, can only be transformed from one type of energy to another. In other words, only energy can create energy: from a state of potentiality, energy becomes motion, explosion, growth, transformation, and then again ‘implodes’ into potentiality. Vorticity behaves in the same way; once ‘imploded’ in the fluid dynamics, it may turn into whirlpools and tornadoes (when appropriate conditions arise), and then again to calm down into a dormant state. Vorticity is energy, and the proof of the law of the energy conservation is proof of the law of requisite vorticity.      Vorticity at the macro scale of the existential dynamics projects onto the scale of the human dynamics. The way we ‘fire’ (educe, create) vorticity in our inner dynamics is by ‘connecting’ ourselves consciously to the existential vortex, to the powerhouse of the universe. There is no other way. One alone is responsible to make this connection as a result of his (her) own efforts." 
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This Sunday, July 24 [Gregorian calendar] is the Day out of Time in the Thirteen Moon/28-day calendar.   "The Day Out of Time is the 365th day of the Thirteen Moon calendar year. As the extra day outside of the 52 weeks of the thirteen moons, the Day Out of Time is no day of the week or month at all. It is, therefore, the day to experience true freedom in fourth dimensional time."     On this Day Out of Time, White Spectral Mirror, the 365th day of the Thirteen Moon/28-day calendar year, we, the people, are gathered in numerous celebrations and festivals at sites around the world -why? Because we are celebrating the Great Calendar Change of 2004. As of the next day, Blue Crystal Storm, the first day of the Thirteen Moon/28-day calendar year, there will be a New Time on Earth. What does this mean?  It means that for the first time in human history, the people of the Earth - not from one country, but from many countries and diverse cultural traditions - will be in support of and already following the new calendar. The times in which we are living are dangerous and complex. The Earth’s future is in the balance. The people know that things will not get better until we are living in a New Time. There are but a few years until the cycle of history closes in 2012. The people know this. The signs are everywhere that the great standards are changing. A new way must be found for the next evolutionary leap. We can no longer wait for a Caesar or a Pope, a president or a prime minister to issue the mandate for this kind of change. That is why we, the people of the Earth, have undertaken this change by ourselves and of our own volition. It is reason and common sense, intelligence and compassion for all of life that move us to make this change. We know that the future is ours to create.   urlLink ...    urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Fractal patterns of early life revealed   [via  urlLink KurzweilAI ]  Newly uncovered fossils reveal in extraordinary clarity the strangeness of the Earth's earliest complex life.  The finds show that the organisms were assembled in fractal patterns from frond-like building blocks. They were unable to move and had no reproductive organs, perhaps reproducing by dropping off new fronds.      urlLink Fractal Organization of Nature   [via  urlLink General Systems, Gravity, and Unified Field Theory @ Cornell University ]  (excerpt of full table)     . Conservation, Entropy, Symmetry x 4 Forces of Physics = Cosmos .   . Gather (Unit) Repeat (Pair) Share (Group) Transform (Emergent Unit)  .   (level) MICROPHYSICAL REALM (3 families of 4 particles; 4 quantum nos. x hadrons, leptons, bosons)  G A T H E R      (level) BIOPHYSICAL REALM (DNA: 4 nucleotides each of 3 chemical groups; 4 nucleotides code in triplets; )  R E P E A T E     Cell RNA; Chemical Systems DNA: Replication; Double Helix Genetic Code; 4 Nucleotides Code in  Triplets; Nucleus, Organelles  Cell: Collective System Identity Cell Membrane   Organism Cell Cell Division Mitosis-Meiosis Specialized Organs Chromosomes, Gonads Organism: Collective Cellular Identity; Skin   Species Organism Sexual Reproduction Male-Female Population Genetics; Social Organization Specialized Professions  Species: Social Identity Closed Genome   Gaia (Planet Earth) Species Speciation Tetraploids Hybrids Ecosystem Mutualisms;  Bio-geochemical Cycles Niche Specializations Gaia: Earth-Life; Atmosphere; Common Descent, DNA   (level) ASTROPHYSICAL REALM (gravitation: 4 third-order equations; 4x3 Nucleosynthetic Pathway)  S H A R E     Star Planet Earth-Moon Planetary System 4x3 Nucleosynthetic Pathway Nuclear Fusion: Helium, Carbon Star: Energy and  Element Production   Galaxy Star Binary Stars Sun-Jupiter Galactic Structure; Disc, Nucleus, Spiral Arms; Globular Clusters; Giant Molecular Clouds Quasars, Ellipticals, Spirals Galaxy: Star Nurseries Supernova Generations Element Accumulation   Universe Galaxy Galactic Pairs; Andromeda- Milky Way Galactic Clusters, Voids, Walls Cellular Megastructure Tetragrammaton Trinity; "The Word" Universe:  Electromagnetic Energy;  Conservation Laws   First Cause Universe Universe Pairs; Antiuniverse Antimatter Multiverse; Anthropic Principle First Cause   (level) METAPHYSICAL REALM - Expanded Form - Rational Mind (3 Conservation Laws x 4 Physical Forces)  T R A N S F O R M     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [via  urlLink CTHEORY ] an international journal of theory, technology, and culture.    urlLink Part 1   Mutations in the Body Politic  A question: are we connected because we are collective, or are we collective because we are connected? Another, related question: in the "network society," is it possible to reformat the body politic without resorting to the paradigm of modern sovereignty?  The overarching argument made in this essay is that networks, swarms, and multitudes are examples of mutations in the contemporary body politic. These mutations are structurally innovative, but politically ambivalent. In some contexts -- such as that of the various anti-globalization movements -- they contain the potential to become politically radical. In other contexts -- such as that of the diversification of international economic organizations -- they become conservative or reactionary.   urlLink Part 2   Are networks, swarms, and multitudes indications of mutations in the body politic? If so, how do they articulate the concepts of connectivity and collectivity, which have been at the heart of political theory for some time? This essay attempts to sort out the conceptual underpinnings of network thinking, and in doing so it brings together technology, biology, and politics into a set of relationships.  While networks may seem ubiquitous these days, we are still far from a thorough understanding of them as political ontologies. Much of this has to do with the way in which time and dynamic change is configured in fields such as graph theory and network science. In these fields, as in much network thinking generally, a network is taken as a static, meta-temporal pattern -- a Eulerian and Kantian view. Bergson's view of duration critiques this notion of dynamic change in networks, but this leaves us with the strange sense that networks do not exist (at least not in their traditional, static forms). 
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [via  urlLink Discordian Research Technology News ]  Imagine, for a moment, that you wanted to create a memetic virus - a belief or system of beliefs of your choosing that would spread from person to person, instill its targets with specific thoughts or opinions of your choosing, and be almost impossible to eradicate once it had taken root in a mind. Why anyone would want to do such a thing is not really important for the purposes of this exercise, but there could be many reasons. Perhaps you were after personal gain and wanted to foster a belief system that would convince people to give their money and possessions to you. Perhaps you were an aspiring tyrant striving for the unquestioning obedience of the populace. Perhaps you were a political or military leader seeking to create the perfect army of fanatically dedicated and loyal soldiers. None of that truly matters. The question is, how could you create such a virus? How could you craft a system of beliefs that would inspire this reaction? 
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink PDF Chaos Library    [via  urlLink Gaianxaos: X-talks ]    urlLink Journal of Sociocybernetics    [via  urlLink RC5-1 ]    urlLink Stigmergic Systems 
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [via  urlLink The Low Beyond ]    If computing power doubles every two years, what happens when computers are doing the research?  If I created a mind with no built-in desires, what would it do?  How can I do something that will still matter in two hundred million years?    1.1 What is humanity's place in the cosmos?   The same place held by all the other technology-using species now briefly living on or around the ten billion trillion (1) stars in this Universe:  Our role in the cosmos is to become or create our successors.  I don't think anyone would dispute that something smarter (or otherwise higher) than human might evolve, or be created, in a few million years.  So, once you've accepted that possibility, you may as well accept that neurohacking, BCI (Brain-Computer Interfaces), Artificial Intelligence, or some other intelligence-enhancement technology will transcend the human condition, almost certainly within your lifetime (unless we blow ourselves to dust first)... 
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [via  urlLink Principia Cybernetica ]  This chapter does not deal with specific tools and techniques for managing complex systems, but proposes some basic concepts that help us to think and speak about complexity. We review classical thinking and its intrinsic drawbacks when dealing with complexity. We then show how complexity forces us to build models with indeterminacy and unpredictability. However, we can still deal with the problems created in this way by being adaptive, and profiting from a complex system’s capability for selforganization, and the distributed intelligence this may produce. 
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [via  urlLink The Complexity & Artificial Life Research Concept for Self-Organizing Systems ]  Abstract: The role of the "process of death" in evolution of the universe and the creation of complexity is discussed.  Where the concept of "death" includes the meaning of a thermodynamic-like death of an organized entity.  This process of death is viewed in terms of major levels of complexity with the context of massive dissipative structures.  We hypothesize that within a level of major complexity there are three regimes: chaotic, ordered, and the edge-of-chaos.  The role of "death" is a form of information feedback from order to chaos via the edge-of-chaos between levels of major complexity. Death can release stored information that is key to the further evolution of complexity of a surrounding dissipative structure.  It is further hypothesized that in the increasing complexity of our existence, there are successive levels of selection processes. By understanding these processes we can predict the structure of our future.       
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Bill targets firms that 'induce' copyright violations    New legislation recently introduced by a group of powerful U.S. senators would allow artists and entertainment companies to sue creators of products, such as peer-to-peer (P-to-P) software, that "induce" copyright violations.  Senate Judiciary Committee (news - web sites) chairman Orrin Hatch, clearly targeting P-to-P vendors, claimed his bill focuses on companies that profit by encouraging children and teenagers to infringe copyrights. "It is illegal and immoral to induce or encourage children to commit crimes," Hatch, a Utah Republican, said in a statement. "Tragically, some corporations now seem to think that they can legally profit by inducing children to steal. Some think they can legally lure children into breaking the law with false promises of 'freemusic.'"  and   urlLink Software piracy losses double    About 36 percent of software installations worldwide are pirated copies, the study by trade group Business Software Alliance and market researcher IDC showed.  In dollar terms, the losses were greatest in Western Europe, where piracy cut revenue by $9.6 billion in 2003, followed by Asia and North America.  The Business Software Alliance blamed the rapid spread of piracy on so-called peer-to-peer networks, where Internet users illegally swap software and other files such as music for free or at discounted prices.  "Peer-to-peer file-sharing services are becoming a huge problem for us," said Jeffrey Hardee, the Business Software Alliance's Asia-Pacific director.   The P2P software issue is reminiscent of the invention of the printing press by Gutenberg.  Before the printing press, the Bible was hand-written in Latin by Roman-Catholic priests.  They were the only people who read Latin and thus controlled the interpretation of the Bible.  Some were trained as scribes and spent their lives copying the Bible by hand, adding commentary in the margins that was later copied into the main text itself (giving rise to different versions).  After the printing press came along, Gutenberg translated the Bible into German, which was understood by many more people.  The printing process was fast and relatively error-free during replication.  The result of this was a wide spread of Christianity due to the greater accessibility of the Bible.  In the same way, P2P software allows for a wider spread of content, removing control from the previous gatekeepers in the various media corporations.
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [at  urlLink Future Hi ]  Yes, the Self is our uniqueness, our individuality, and the point of reflection, but what of the deeper, less tangible levels? It seems that as we drill further into the Self, it becomes less and less defined. The nearer we get to its root, the less we actually are as individuals. This is exhibited in the eastern meditative states of nirvana & satori where individual identity is sloughed off as the Self merges into the plenum of unity. At it's core, the Self seems contradictory to identity. Or rather, it becomes identified with something far greater and much smoother than the individual. It's like a raindrop falling into a pool of water. As it falls the drop is singular among many, distinguished from the other drops nearby. Striking the surface it is absorbed into the pool and its individuality as a drop is dissolved while simultaneously expanded to encompass the whole pool. Instead of reflecting the world from the outside of a small sphere, it reflects from the entire surface of the pool. As one delves deeper and deeper into the Self, more and more of creation is reflected on its surface. 
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      EDIT:  Thank you to  urlLink John Fenderson  for pointing out  urlLink The Mitochondria Conspiracy  to me.  This one sentence sums up my point as succinctly as a sack of breaks falling on your head:  " Their real purpose?  Conquest!!  Eons ago these nasty wee beasties invaded the happy eukariotes off Pangaea'a shores, convincing them with slick tongues and fancy mini-chromosomes to enter into a bargain, and it was a Bargain With The Devil! "    Mitochondria organelles are found in cells of multicellular organisms.  They have been called the "powerhouse of the human body."  They are responsible for getting the energy out of glucose in respiration by breaking it down into ATP.  They exist in each cell of the human body and are responsible for the synthesis of proteins from amino-acids and the replicaiton of DNA. [ urlLink Mitochondria ]  In short, these cells are necessary for the most basic physical aspects of life and reproduction of organisms on a cellular level.  But mitochondria are not part of our bodies.  They have their own DNA.  They are another species living in our bodies that needs us for shelter while we need them for energy.  Mitochondria have their own replication cycle independent of the host-organism's, yet they regulate that host's own DNA replication cycle. [ urlLink Mitochondria: Architecture dictates function ]  The video game  Parasite Eve  for PS1 suggests that mitochondria have significantly evolved and have even begun to take control of their host organisms.  While this is only a video game, the idea is compelling: We have a foreign organism living in every cell of our bodies that we depend on for our own cellular reproduction.  A significant number of forces in human society are externalized communication from the DNA-RNA feedback system (i.e. awareness of the necessity of reproduction for continuing the species, whether as conscious analysis or intuitive urges).  How many of these forces are tied to the necessity of mitochondria reproduction, for which we are merely vehicles or vessels?  What memes have we developed solely for the benefit of these organisms but not necessarily our own?  As is said on the homepage of the  urlLink Mitochondria Research Society : "Mitochondria Means the Most to Us".   urlLink In study , it appears that mitochondria are also drivers of information processing in neurons, that is there is some link between neural activity and the mitochondria energy production cycle.  I can only surmise there is some link between our thought patterns, our bio-survival urges, and the reproductive necessities of the mitochondria we house.   Whose DNA are we competing for the successful evolution of anyway? 
    
</post>


</Blog>