<Blog>


<date>31,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Just woke up. So what do  I  get to do tonight at midnight?! ..probably sleep. :(  ... vince is sick. again. so much for party of the year. 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I am inV1NCEible (4:56:22 AM): anyway. im gonna hop in bed and watch the morning news at 5.. lol. wunchun77 (4:56:34 AM): how weird wunchun77 (4:56:36 AM): haha wunchun77 (4:56:37 AM): okay wunchun77 (4:56:39 AM): goodnight! 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       i'm going to sleep now. but gosh.   urlLink somebody   kept me up until the wee hours of the morning. -_- 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       ive found--with the help of a friend--that i wouldnt be making the best of christmas break if i went to bed at a regular hour (like say 10pm).. so in order to make my break as good as it can be, i will try not to go to bed before 1am everyday. 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       MARYrowsABOAT (7:20:48 PM):don`t ever use the word good MARYrowsABOAT (7:20:51 PM):its.. not a good sat word MARYrowsABOAT (7:20:52 PM):hehehe I am inV1NCEible (7:20:56 PM):lol I am inV1NCEible (7:21:12 PM): i dont have an ample vocabulary to beable to form a coherent thought while using good words. MARYrowsABOAT (7:21:22 PM): .......... MARYrowsABOAT (7:21:29 PM): beable? MARYrowsABOAT (7:21:31 PM): Oh hahhhhhah MARYrowsABOAT (7:21:32 PM): hAHAHA MARYrowsABOAT (7:21:34 PM): LOL. I am inV1NCEible (7:21:35 PM): be able* MARYrowsABOAT (7:21:37 PM): im so stupid I am inV1NCEible (7:21:37 PM): =P MARYrowsABOAT (7:21:48 PM): LOL MARYrowsABOAT (7:21:49 PM): i was like. MARYrowsABOAT (7:21:53 PM): dang. whats beable MARYrowsABOAT (7:21:56 PM): i never heard that one. MARYrowsABOAT (7:22:03 PM): no wonder it sounded weird. I am inV1NCEible (7:22:04 PM): lol MARYrowsABOAT (7:22:05 PM): Anyway. 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       weeeeee.. it feels good to not have school!  looking for a last minute gift for vincent? (* urlLink hint hint * free overnight shipping with coupon code " SHIP1DAY " ;) ) 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I am inV1NCEible: happy hannukah I am inV1NCEible: ..from a christian guy :) giveSTRIPES: haha. thanks giveSTRIPES: merry christmas giveSTRIPES: kind of I am inV1NCEible: lol... thanks.  hehe. all the political correctness at school. always "holidays" and "winter break" really, who's getting offended?   MERRY   CHRISTMAS   EVERYONE  !!  
    
    
</post>

<date>17,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       American Red Cross -  urlLink Blood Donor Eligibility   " Marijuana, 'Weed', 'Pot', 'Ganga'  Acceptable as long as you are not under the influence of marijuana at the time of donation."  ...always promoting the healthy lifestyle. haha. 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       somethings seriously wrong with the world if i can take psats, not take a it seriously, guess for any question that i dont know the answer off the top of my head, and yet,  still  manage to get 80th percentile.  woot. 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       9 more days until Jesus' birthday. :) 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink vincent's friend test  - I made this because tina wanted me to make a quiz to show that she can do as well on mine as I  urlLink did  on hers... but feel free to take it if you're bored. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Lee Harris on Saddam's Capture:  Thank God He's Alive    But there is another reason to be thankful that Saddam Hussein is alive. The man who called upon his countrymen and fellow Muslims to sacrifice their own lives in suicide attacks, to blow themselves to bits in order to glorify his name, failed to follow his own instructions. He refused the grand opportunity of a martyr's death, or even that of the hardened Hollywood gangster, determined that the cops would never take him alive. Instead, Saddam Hussein surrendered meekly and was, according to the reports, even cooperative.  We took Saddam Hussein alive, and, in doing this, we have done a great deal more than simply knock down a statue of a dictator -- we have vanquished a collective nightmare. We have turned the light on a bogey-man, and revealed him to be a broken old man, hiding fearfully in a six by eight hole.   Read the whole thing. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
         "Ladies and gentlemen, we got him," U.S. administrator L. Paul Bremer told a news conference. "The tyrant is a prisoner."  Unless you've been living in a hole in the ground, you probably know by now that Saddam Hussein has been captured alive in.. well, a hole in the ground. It's about [insert four letter word + ing] time.  It makes me wonder though if this will stop or even decrease the guerrilla attacks. The US thought they would get better after Qusai and Odai were killed, but they had the reverse effect. Perhaps this just gives the guerilla campaign more reason to fight?  But regardless of that, this is obviously a victory for the US, England (or perhaps just Blair), and the Iraqi masses.  "I'm very happy for the Iraqi people. Life is going to be safer now," said 35-year-old Yehya Hassan, a resident of Baghdad. "Now we can start a new beginning." 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       themadrhymer1: it was great, i was at the mall a lil bit today looking at shoes themadrhymer1: i was like "hey, these look pretty nice" I am inV1NCEible: what shoes were they? themadrhymer1: and then i found out i was in the women's athletic section I am inV1NCEible: i did that today too -_- themadrhymer1: hahaha 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink   holdthebutton.com   Yup. Try to beat me, Tina, I  DARE  you. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I spent most of the day today in bed trying to get some rest.. it didn't work though.  People that have the flu should stay home at home and not go to school! That way they don't get people like me sick too. Gosh. I hope that this goes away completely before xmas break.  Anyway, I'm gonna go get some more sleep. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       vincent has the flu. :( 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Coversation I heard today...  "What would you like today, Miss?" "Umm.. can I get one pound of fried shrimp, a steak--medium rare, a slice of cherry cheese cake, and a diet pepsi?" "Sure."  Seriously? A diet pepsi?! You just ordered like one hundred and five pounds of fat! What good is a diet pepsi going to do you? Silly people.  ...you wonder why you get fat. 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Would it be weird that I'm up at 4AM? Or that I haven't gone to bed?  ..how about both? 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       "How are you doing today?"  *muffled voice* "Umm... al-wight"  "That's good. School going well?"  "uh huh"  "Still running cross country?"  "nu uh.. our sesonn ennded."  "Oh, I see. Nice break before track."  *nods*  So I went to the dentist today. How do they expect you to answer these questions? Or do they expect you to at all? I always think its awkward for me..but how is it for the person that talks to people all day but doesn't really get responses? 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       In an attempt to wear clean clothes, I did laundry today.  ...I think I'm missing another sock. Damn dryer. :\ 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
        I know. A couple people have told me how sickeningly disgusting these things look. It looks like Nabisco has come up with a new cookie. Mint'nCreme!  A few people have said that they would never  ever  eat these... even after I said how good they are. But I swear, they taste good.  It's like double stuffed. But half of it tastes like thin mints. THIN MINTS! How can you pass this up?! The cookies which taste like heaven but you can only get once a year (except off of  urlLink eBay  of course).  Try it before you swear them off completely. :) 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       It was a late start this morning, and yet I woke up at 7am to the sound of the ground rumbling. I was laying in bed, and the ground was shaking. I wish I was kidding.  They were working on  urlLink Ball Road --I guess. Some wise guy came up with this lovely contraption which breaks up concrete by using a heavy weight which is repeatedly lifted and then dropped back onto the ground every 10 seconds. Slamming it. Hard.  What a way to wake up... to what sounds like the end of the world. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Somehow, I got sucked back into the blogging addiction. And while I know that I'll probably regret putting this page up later, it's time for a change of pace.  A brand new blog.  Stick around, and maybe you'll find something interesting. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       blah blah? 
    
    
</post>

<date>31,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i went with my brother to UCI early this morning to help out in the homeless outreach thing. it was awesome. the group made bagged lunches w/ sandwiches, chips, bananas, and water. five cars were filled with food and college students (haha, i think i was the youngest one there).  we drove to LA and there was this street there that was filled with homeless people. :( and we started giving out the food. i should have known that it wasn't gonna be kicked back and chill when they went over the safety instructions. (driver has to stay in the driver's seat the whole time; if anything happens.. like a riot... you should get back into the car right away and drive off)  soon after we started giving out food, we were crowded by A LOT of people.  you don't realize how lucky you are until you do something like this. and while it was an awkward situation (and probably not the most safe one), I'm really glad that i did it. it's so different from volunteering at a place like a soup kitchen.  we had to save half the food for a different part of the street. our car didn't have too hard of a time with this, because we could just close the trunk and get back into the car. but the car in front of us was an SUV, so you could like see all the food, even when they closed the back, so some people really got mad knowing that there was more food and we couldn't give them any. i'm really glad that didn't get violent. some of the people stuffed the bags into their jackets that they got from a different car and tried to get another bag from a different car.  at the 2nd part of the street, we ran out of food. at first it was slow, but then there ended up being A LONG line of people just as the food was running low. we ended up giving out the muffins that we were going to eat for lunch too. there was this little girl that was in the line. she was 5th in line when we ran out of food. :(  it was so awesome seeing the smiles on some of these people's faces. when we drove off, people all over the street had our bags. a lot of them smiled and waved as we drove away.  one lady was like,"thank you. jesus loves you," as we handed her a bag of food. 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Xameliaxbedeliax: im telling you that you are staying an oxnerd. i will not take no for an answer. I am inV1NCEible: youre funny amelia... haha. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I went to the Cypress bball game tonight vs kennedy. woohoo! go centurions! (lol, i'm working on it). chs won by like 20 points. thanks for dragging me along lauren. :) 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I didn't think I'd blog again.. or at least not for a couple months. But I guess now is a better time than any. Yesterday was the end of the semester, and I wasn't happy with my grades.  This semester was different because I really worked my ass off to do the best I could. I stopped copying massive amounts of homework assignments. I did my work, or at least as much as I could in the time that I had. I learned this semester, that I couldn't make the cut. And I won't survive much longer.  The way Oxford works is whack, and it took me years to figure out exactly how things are. In 7th grade, you start out with what are suppose to be 200 of the smartest people in the district. As every year, every semester, goes by, people get kicked out of the school. These are the people who are "not as smart," and couldn't meet the 3.0 requirement. By junior year, you end up with only the people who in jr high had straight a's and awesome grades. Everyone else, by now, is long gone. You're left with a group that is supposedly the best of the best because the worst of the best were forced to leave, and while I used to be near the top of the bell curve, I'm now left near the bottom.  Sure I could graduate at Oxford, but with what? The pride of knowing that I survived six years of hardships? With a mediocre GPA which will get me into a college that I don't want to be at--A college where my SAT score is 300 points higher than the school's average. But I'm there because I couldn't get a GPA to match it.  Oxford has a problem that as soon as students fall into hard time, the school turns their backs on them. Instead of truly helping them to catch up, the school recommends that you go to another school. The school recommends that you lessen your workload and take some "regular" classes at another school. The school which is suppose to prepare you for college forces you to go some else and it closes a door behind you after you leave.  I don't know how much more of this I would be able to take. Every semester, I have to constantly worry about if I'll be at the school in a couple months. I have to worry about keeping my grades up.  I'm sick of it.  I'm sick of being a guinea pig so that the school can find out how to create the "perfect" school.  Face it, Oxford looks good on paper, but how well does the school actually work?  Sure we have high test scores: we kick out anyone that can't keep up.  It used to be a matter of finishing what I started.  I'd gone this far, why give up now?  But have I really succeeded if I finish with a GPA that I'm not proud of?  How much is Oxford really a college prep school if its seniors can't get into the colleges they want to?  Thank you to everyone else who is leaving this semester or is planning to leave at the end of the year.  And there are tons of you.  Someone else called it The Great Walkout.  Thank you for making me realize that I can leave, and I don't have to put up with this.  Oxford is not the best; we're a poor excuse for a high school, and we don't have to have our college admissions, our careers fucked because our high school's system doesn't work.  I'm done.  I've realized that I can do better, I can go elsewhere.  I don't have to put up with the stuff that Oxford students always complain about.  I don't have to struggle through everything I do because Oxford is still trying to figure out how it wants to run its school.  I don't have to put up with the empty promises of a gym and new classrooms.  Good bye Oxford.  Cuz dude, I'm a Centurion now. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       cR zYgr Ly9 8 7: haha yea cypress has the best homecomings I am inV1NCEible: lol yea I am inV1NCEible: unless you go to cypress I am inV1NCEible: haha cR zYgr Ly9 8 7: haha exactly cR zYgr Ly9 8 7: one year it rains, the next year we have no queen I am inV1NCEible: and you lose.. badly I am inV1NCEible: dont forget about that cR zYgr Ly9 8 7: haha i didnt want to mention that one 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       did anyone else hear that there was a reported bomb threat during 6th period today? mr. cullinane said something happened, but he can't say anything about it. he was acting really weird when taylor kept on questioning him about what happened that he cant tell anyone about. weird.  yea. i think the rumors are true. 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i went to the girls'  urlLink soccer game  after school today vs cypress. varsity score: 0-5, jv score: 1-11. ouch. big ouch. but it was fun. :)  ran into some cypress ppl: tina, jenn, lindsay (soon to be oxford person again). and lots of props to crystal who still managed to stay positive.. even while down by 10 points. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I took a shower today. 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
         i went to go see  urlLink The Passion of the Christ  this afternoon. it's definitely a movie that everyone should go see--though i can't say i would want to see it again. it's an extremely powerful movie. i don't think that theres any other movie where there were parts that made me cringe to just watch. if you haven't seen this, go see it.  
    
    
</post>

<date>27,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       back in the day..   
    
    
</post>

<date>27,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       again with the TPing? this is getting old...   
    
    
</post>

<date>27,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Islamic Extremist  :  Islam  ::  KKK  :  Christianity  Think about that next time before you form prejudices against Muslims. 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       yes. it's the perfect escape from homework. online pool.     
    
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       today marks the beginning...   ...what are  you  giving up? 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
         pic of me from jcamp in san deigo from the past summer. 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
         it's raining. it's pouring. and no one's happy but tina. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       erika and i headed over to roundtable tonight to grab some yummy pizza.. then we went to the oxford talent show, which had its good and bad moments. overall, it was pretty cool though. the lord of the rings impression.. daaamnn. that was good.  also saw the last few minutes of the cypress homegame versus torrance. first cif game. won by three cuz they missed their at-the-buzzer three pointer. :) woot. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Zeiganfreid:    yuck orange font    xrunvincerunx:      i like orange fonts =)      Zeiganfreid:    I DO NOT!    xrunvincerunx:   not my problem.. haha     Zeiganfreid:    :?    Zeiganfreid:    touche   i love orange. :) 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
         this is a pic of a small tree in front of my house.. it just stopped raining. practice was funn today. 4 miles in the pouring rain! (sadly, i'm not kidding when i said it was fun.. haha) 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       *sigh* it's just one of those days. it sucks when you're having a great day until someone says something that just ruins your mood. thanks tina. :/  i'm off to bed. 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       First-year students at Medical School were receiving their first anatomy class with a real dead human body. They all gathered around the surgery table with the body covered with a white sheet.  The professor started the class by telling them in medicine, it is necessary to have 2 important qualities as a doctor: The first is that you not be disgusted by anything involving the human body."  As an example, the Professor pulled back the sheet, stuck his finger in the butt of the corpse, withdrew it and stuck it in his mouth.  Go ahead and do the same thing," he told his students. The students freaked out, hesitated for several minutes, but eventually (because they wanted to pass the course)took turns sticking a finger in the butt of the dead body and sucking on it.  When everyone finished, the Professor looked at them and told them the second most important quality is observation. "I stuck in my middle finger and sucked on my index finger. Now learn to pay attention."  urlLink (Courtesy of John)  
    
    
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       MARYrowsABOAT: hey vincent MARYrowsABOAT: guess what xrunvincerunx: hi MARYrowsABOAT: i have a new friend xrunvincerunx: what MARYrowsABOAT: his name is vincent MARYrowsABOAT: inVINCEible 3108 MARYrowsABOAT: and thats his sn   I am inV1NCEible (8:48:38 PM): so umm. how long have you had that sn? inVINCEible 3108 (8:48:57 PM): a while now inVINCEible 3108 (8:49:01 PM): since like 8 inVINCEible 3108 (8:49:12 PM): let me have your sn I am inV1NCEible (8:49:22 PM): lol... no.. I am inV1NCEible (8:51:09 PM): anyway, bye. inVINCEible 3108 (8:51:42 PM): who is this? I am inV1NCEible (8:51:58 PM): i'm vincent. haha. inVINCEible 3108 (8:52:05 PM): from/ inVINCEible 3108 (8:52:09 PM): *? I am inV1NCEible (8:52:15 PM): im mary's friend... maryrowsaboat inVINCEible 3108 (8:52:29 PM): oh i see I am inV1NCEible (8:52:50 PM): she... uhh... found your xanga while looking for mine inVINCEible 3108 (8:53:11 PM): what school do you go to I am inV1NCEible (8:53:14 PM): cypress hs I am inV1NCEible (8:54:35 PM): man this is weird. inVINCEible 3108 (8:55:37 PM): yeah inVINCEible 3108 (8:55:41 PM): what grade school did you come from? I am inV1NCEible (8:55:59 PM): st. irenaeus.. then oxford inVINCEible 3108 (8:56:10 PM): oh foreal? inVINCEible 3108 (8:56:12 PM): what grade you in now? I am inV1NCEible (8:56:15 PM): 11th I am inV1NCEible (8:56:25 PM):  Member Since: 11/23/2003 i_am_invinceible Member Since: 12/5/2002 inVINCEible I am inV1NCEible (8:56:28 PM): haha.. i win :-P inVINCEible 3108 (8:56:39 PM): so you know carl dehesa? inVINCEible 3108 (8:56:49 PM): haha I am inV1NCEible (8:56:53 PM): woah.. yea. i do. though i havent talked to him in years inVINCEible 3108 (8:57:15 PM): and kathy and martin right? I am inV1NCEible (8:57:28 PM): yea I am inV1NCEible (9:02:57 PM): uh.. anyway. bye.  omg.. i cant believe it. identical sns. he goes to bosco.. we both have mutual friends and no one ever told me. PS. my new sn is  xrunvincerunx . add it to your buddy list. 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       thank you to whoever TPed my house last night.. i really appreciate it. 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
        thewordsofanoxnerd:  the other day i had a meeting w/ mrs hoffman about college and she told me that because i took these hard classes and got my 3.2 if i had taken the easy classes i would have been better off GPA wise  thewordsofanoxnerd:  and now i cant get into a UC  the thing that bugs me is.. if the counselors  know  that the hard classes are screwing people over. Why  continue  to FUCK up people's chances of college admissions? 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       john and i have a new toy... :)         
    
    
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i've quickly learned at while running with cypress, many things are different on the road.  you don't get yelled at by passing cars (as often). little--but deadly--objects such as pennies and nickels aren't thrown at you. and little lexington kids don't yell at you, throw rocks at you and such. haha.  the funny thing about running past lexington with the oxford team is that every 8th grade boy you run past automatically assumes that since you're at oxford, you're also a 8th grade boy. little do they realize that many of us are like 3+ years older. one of these days, one of them is gonna get hurt.  well, off to bed. practice tomorrow at 9am. woohoo. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       its funny how many people i dont really even talk to read this blog. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       scary moment: when the person that's cutting your hair says "opps." =( 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       drama drama at this school. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       haha. i love this schedule. 40something minute classes..by the time you get started, there's only like half an hour left of class. much better than looking at the clock and realizing that you have over and hour and 20some minutes left. yay for non-block schedule. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       okay. so cypress' distance team. every year since forever and a half ago, oa coaches have gone by distance. so it'll be like, go out and do 6 miles.  cypress... they're different. not bad, not good. but different. and it's screwing with my head. they go by time. so instead, you'd be going out and doing like 40 minutes. run faster, run slower--doesn't matter. the time isn't going to be going any faster.  so since i'm not part of running club (ahaha, running club... it's so damn shaddy, but it's brilliant), i just did 25 minutes on my own today (25 minutes on your own seems like a hell of a lot longer), plus about 1/2 mile warmup and 1/2 mile cooldown (lol, i'm reforming, but not that fast).  this is changing the whole concept of running. but i guess it makes sense. it's not suppose to be the distance from point a to point b that matters: it's the journey you take to get there.  it explains a lot though. over the summer, oa had practice the same time cypress did in the morning. once we ran into one of the cypress cc runners, and we asked how much they were running... only to calmly recieve the answer "twenty." hehe. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
         this is what they do to your ID card when you leave... 
    
    
</post>

<date>31,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       As practice was finishing up today, Coach was telling everyone what events they are going to be running at the meet tomorrow against Loara.  As he said my name, he noted that he "needed to talk to me about my racing."  So I walked up to him a little bit later.  I thought for sure that he was going to tell me I was going out too damn fast... because the last few races, I've been going out pretty fast.  Nope.  "Vince, tomorrow in the 800, if you're leading the race again... do something three feet from the line." "You want me to fall?" "Yea." "Umm.. okay.  I can fall."  So since I just transferred to Cypress, I'm not allowed to run Varsity.  Since I'm a junior, I'm not allowed to run Frosh/Soph. But I run Frosh/Soph anyway... and I fall. 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       someperson: interested in anyone? xrunvincerunx: i used to have a crush on you. xrunvincerunx: :)  --five minute later--  someperson: i liked you at one point. someperson: that i know. someperson: that i'll tell. xrunvincerunx: when? xrunvincerunx: haha. thatd be funny if it was at the same time i liked you someperson: um. this year. xrunvincerunx: oh. not so funny anymore. :\ 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
         tragedys theory :   hey    xrunvincerunx :    i almost fainted three times today     tragedys theory :   dude i know serious heat exhaustion + dehydration + only breakfast + running + a bajillion degress = DEATH    xrunvincerunx :    word..   
    
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       okay so my brother, simon, and i are starting a photography company that takes pics at dances and such. so we did a photoshoot today to get some pics for our portfolio. it was an interesting day...    i always seem to be in the air somewhere.   highlight pics from the day...             
    
    
</post>

<date>27,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
        we went to chino relays today. looong day. was up since 6am, and my first race--5PM. nice little wait. ran the 400 leg of the distance med.. 56 point something seconds. alright i guess since it was my first 400 of the season. guys and girls both took 1st in division two and cypress won sweepstakes. :)  it was a really really nice track. all weather, of course. but dang. bleachers on both sides to seat 10,000.. and their built into the side of a hill... a hill which surrounds three sides of the track. 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       details mag. recently published an article basically telling readers how to tell the difference between a gay man and an asian man...  urlLink     click the pic above for a larger view... this is freakin' disgusting. i don't understand how any magazine editor could let this be published. please sign this  urlLink petition  (click click). we can't let something so blatantly racist and homophobic slide past us like it means nothing. i'm not just angry.. i'm shocked. 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       current estimated world population: 6,355,683,423  number of human deaths possible from one pound of plutonium if finely ground up and inhaled: 42,000,000,000  1984 U.S. plutonium inventory, in pounds: 380,000  these numbers multiplied together: 16,000,000,000,000,000  that's a sixteen with fifteen zeros behind it.  16,000,000,000,000,000 / 6,355,683,423 = 2,517,431.869   we have enough plutonium to kill the world 2,517,431 times.  Source: Science Digest, July 1984 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       pic from the Woodbridge Dual Meet last thursday.    urlLink Cypress High School Track & Field: Photos  
    
    
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
          &quot;I firmly believe marriage should be a contract between two cute people.&quot; -Jack from    Will &amp; Grace     
    
    
</post>

<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       how high can you jump?   
    
    
</post>

<date>19,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i was just watching the 5pm news and "breaking news" happened with some guy getting arrested in cypress, which is normally a pretty un-newsworthy place. he just got tackled by the police and stuff..but i noticed that it was happening at a motel on lincoln so i just ran outside my house and i can see the abc helicopter hovering. :) 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       first home meet against woodbridge today. i got first in my race! (800m) it was pretty cool. i was scared though because i couldnt hear/see anyone during the race, so i had no idea how i was doing or if anyone was near me. but hey, it worked out. 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       omg i dont have anything green to wear! 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       journalistjulia: you know about that sicko that killed his daughters/grandkids in fresno? journalistjulia: well the cops arent releasing any info about how they were killed...and some are in counseling journalistjulia: it must be pretty bad   urlLink Yahoo! News - Fresno Suspect Was Polygamist, Police Say : "Officers were called to the home Friday afternoon for a child custody dispute. What they found inside was ghastly: bodies so entangled that it took hours for investigators to reach a final count and 10 wooden caskets lining a wall of a front room."   crap.. fucking sicko. this isn't happy sunday morning news which usually comes on sundays. :\  
    
    
</post>

<date>13,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       went to eagle rock relays today.. i just got home. dang i'm tired. 7am  until 10pm.  15 hours!!  i ran two events--4xmile and 4x800. I thought i did really really bad in mile, but turns out i only did bad. in 800 i did really well considering i haven't been training as long as everyone else. i have still yet to catch up to my PRs from last season (i'm about 20 seconds off)..but i'll get there soon.  ohh, on the way to the meet, the two buses from chs got lost and like this bus from another school started following us! so we like faked them out by pretending we were going to make a turn and then going straight instead.. coach eyman was like "quick! ditch them at the light!" haha. it was funny... like racing buses.  i'm gonna go eat some food and hop in bed/pass out. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       went to the pasta party tonight w/ some of the team where we played dare or dare.  it was an ass-smacking, bench-peeing good time. then lizzie came and i left to go to cheesecake factory and ya. now im home and getting ready for bed (yes, yes, it's 9pm). but i have a race tomorrow and i have to be up at 6amish. so g'night!  did anyone go to mr. patriot tonight? how was it? 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ran first race of the season today. did really crappy. over 30 seconds off my pr for 1600. :(  i was afraid of going out too fast, so i paced myself instead, and i ended up going slower than i should have.. and i couldnt catch up to who i wanted to. i realized this afterwards when i was barely even tired. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
         so true.. so true. 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
         urlLink Yahoo! News - McDonald's Salad Has More Fat Than Cheeseburger  Global hamburger giant McDonald's latest line in healthy looking salads may contain more fat than its hamburgers, according to the company's website.   hahahahaha.. this is great. go mcdonalds for fixing america's fat problems with fatty salads!  
    
    
</post>

<date>07,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       whoever TPed my house last night... you're a fucking asshole. my parents got pissed this time. three weekends in a row. i got yelled at and they called the cops this time. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink CBS | Late Show Top Ten Archive: January 23, 2004 : "Top Ten Good Things About Having A Stripper As A News Anchor  10. 'Finally, a way to get teens interested in current events.'  9. 'Easy way of fulfilling the station's FCC nudity requirement.'  8. 'Top story tonight -- I got a new tattoo.'  7. 'Impressive to watch her do the news while the sports guy's throwing dollars at her.'  6. 'Oh geez, I dunno -- Maybe the fact that she's naked!'  5. 'Carrying on the proud tradition started by Edward R. Murrow.'  4. 'Fun to hear anchor say, 'To hear more on the Iowa Caucus, meet me in the Champagne Room in 5 minutes.'  3. 'She covers the five W's of journalism; who, what, when, where and WOW!'  2. 'Studies have found that clothing detracts from viewers' ability to process news.'  1. Viewers intrigued every time she says, 'This just in.''" 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink CBS | Late Show Top Ten Archive: February 02, 2004 : "Top Ten Things You Don't Want To Hear From A Guy At Starbucks  10. 'We ran out of coffee filters, so I'm using one of my old undershirts.'  9. 'Try our triple cappuccino -- It's a legal alternative to crack.'  8. 'Let me make sure that's not too hot.'  7. 'You know, I licked every one of these stirrers.'  6. 'One Decaf Venti Skim Latte -- 39 dollars.'  5. 'Sugar with that?'  4. 'Grande Caramel Macchaito? Talk English!'  3. 'If I catch any of you people going into a Dunkin' Donuts for coffee, I'll break your legs!'  2. 'Some whipped cream for you... and some whipped cream for me.'  1. 'After work, I'm gonna pick up a hooker-uccino.'" 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
         i hate these math problems that like are fairly easy..but they take  forever  and 1/3 of a page to do. 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       FUCK. I, now, have had a total of 5  urlLink Gmail  invites (one which i used for my own account). And I thought about eBaying them off earlier, but I didn't because I was afraid of losing my own Gmail account because auctioning off other accounts had to be against the usage policy. But now that Google is letting Gmail users invite other users, they are  urlLink selling  like crazy on eBay. I just saw an auction go for $150!!! Noelle,  urlLink Thomas ,  urlLink Lianne ,  urlLink Andy ,  urlLink Brandon ... be happy that you got the invites, because I should have sold them. :P 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i went back to life night at st. i tonight.. first time in like a year since i dont have to go anymore. i went to hang out with  urlLink amanda , but ran into jeff there (didn't expect to see him there...). daniel, katie, danielle (the kennedy people) were there as well. they're getting confirmed (when i say everyone, i mean everyone but jeff) on saturday though so it's the last time they have to go.  yea... last year's lifenight before confirmation was better.. when mawb played and dj m3 (hehe.. aka mike, the group leader) was spinnin' the beats. this year, we made paper flowers =x  ..but hey. $2 all you can eat pizza and chill time with some really cool people. :D 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Kevin Fox  has created a pretty damn cool site with a really creative idea. basically how it works is that he gets disposible cameras and gives them to random people. the instructions on the camera say to take a few pictures, pass the camera to a friend, and when it's used up, drop it in the mail.  after six years of planning, the site,  urlLink Randompixel , has launched. A new camera posted every tuesday. 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       okay let's see.. this week was hectic, this week was fast, this week was fun. tgif.  today was egg drop day for physics. we had to survive a 20ish foot drop preliminary first, and if we made it past that, we got to drop from the fire engine (which i heard was 90 feet..but i'm not sure.  urlLink see pic .)   one day earlier...   i had a trackmeet after school and spent the night finishing (and starting) my egg drop thing. my dad helped a lot with the design. the help of an aerospace engineer to build an eggdrop? naw. it's not overkill.   one day earlier...   i had my 2nd in-n-out interview. this one was with the store manager (after my previous interview with the shift manager). he seemed to like me. i haven't gotten an answer yet, but he said that he was impressed with what i have done in my life at my age (perhaps he thinks i'm like 12 years old? haha) but anyway, he said that he'd keep my application at the top of the pile for when in-n-out hires and that he would give me a call by next friday.  now let's hope that this job doesn't kill me like  urlLink john ,  urlLink simon , and  urlLink erika  warned me that it might. 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Big Mac boss dies of heart attack  The McDonald's chairman and chief executive, Jim Cantalupo, architect of a dramatic turnaround at the fast food business, has died of an apparent heart attack, the company said yesterday. McDonald's shares slid more than 3% on the news. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       it's about 11:30pm of the last night of spring break. i have to admit that this past week has been relaxing. even though i had practice every morning (including saturday), i was void of any real stress. i feel sorry for the oa peeps though. seemed like there was  a lot  of work they had to do.. actually, a lot is probably an understatement. i've avoiding anything academic for so long that i can barely remember what i'm doing in any of my classes.   good bye spring break. it's been nice. but now, i'm counting down the days 'til summer... 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       omgosh. only 23 hours left of spring break. :( 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink jennifer  told me on monday that "everyone and their mom has a livejournal," well, everyone except me i guess. :) it seems that  urlLink thomas  has taken the liberty of turning my blog into a  urlLink syndicated account  on lj.  so, umm, i guess you can click to  urlLink add me to your friend's page on livejournal .  p.s.  [b]   urlLink BLOGGER  still owns all. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       it's friday. wow. i cant believe how fast this week has gone by. its kind of a bummer because my day doesnt actually start until around 2pm because i have to wake up early and go to practice. when i get home from that, i'm just in a bum mood and don't feel like doing anything. kinda kills half your day.  it took me a month and three applications to get it, but i had my job interview at  urlLink in-n-out  earlier this week. damn. it is  tough  to get an interview there. and then afterwards, you find out that to get the job, you have to do  two  interviews. so i finished my first one w/ the shift manager, who liked me... and he scheduled me an appointment w/ the store manager next week. here goes nothing...    urlLink Melinda 's having a bonfire tonight.. i doubt i'll go because nothings more fun (or awkward) as going to a bonfire where you know only a few people, but everyone's invited, so if anyone cares to go, gimme a call. :)  annnd. thought i'd say hi to andie, who i've never talked to, but reads my blog more often than some of my actual  friends  do. hah. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Photomosaic  ...of Bush, made from portraits of Americans who have died in Iraq.   urlLink      
    
    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
        gmail me    i woke up this morning to find not one, but two invitations for a beta  urlLink gmail  account today. thanks sandy ko & jason shellen (if you havent heard by now, gmail is google's email service)  what makes gmail so different? first off, they don't give you 4 megabytes like yahoo or 2 megabytes like hotmail, gmail gives you a lovely 1000 megabytes (1gb) of space.  aside from that, theres a lot of other cool features. one of them is plus addressing, which lets you use username+anything@gmail.com. useful for signing up for services because as soon as you get spam for that address, you can set a filter to send all the email from that address to your trash automatically.  gmail groups your emails in coversations so that your replies w/ someone are all on the same page, and theres a handy reply box on the bottom of each conversation. let's see, composing emails. gmail has one of the best spell checkers online. this thing is FAST and i'd say is almost up to par with microsoft word's spell checker.  and of course, since it is google, you can search through ALL of your emails with pretty good accuracy. if i were yahoo or microsoft, i'd be scared. because even aside from the massive amounts of storage space, google still has yet to roll out all the planned features. and the current features are enough to beat out other webmail services. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
        new email address:  vincentpv [at] gmail dotizzle com 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Air Marshal Leaves Gun in Airport Restroom   CHICAGO (Reuters) - A federal air marshal accidentally left her gun in a restroom beyond the security checkpoints at Cleveland Hopkins International Airport, officials say.  The weapon was discovered by a passenger who alerted an airline employee.  The marshal remained on the job after Thursday's incident when she visited an airport restroom and inadvertently left her gun behind, Dave Adams, spokesman for the Federal Air Marshal Service in Washington, said Saturday.  The restroom was beyond security checkpoints, airport spokeswoman Pat Smith said. So the risk was that someone could have discovered the gun and taken it on a flight.  urlLink Read More...   ( vince: oh yea, this makes me feel  real  safe while flying.. ) 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The angel said to the women, "Do not be afraid, for i know that you are looking for Jesus, who was crucified. He is not here; he has risen, just as he said. Come and see the place where he lay. Then go quickly and tell his disciples: 'He has risen from the dead and is going ahead of you into Galilee. There you will see him.' Now i have told you."  So the women hurried away form the tomb, afraid yet filled with joy, and ran to tell his disciples. Suddenly Jesus met them. "Greetings," he said. They came to him, clasped his feet and  worshiped  him.  - Matthew 28:5-9 (Scripture courtesy of Lindsay H.) 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Blah blah, early morning practice yesterday.  And  urlLink Bluish LLC  had another photoshoot yesterday. Chelsea, Trent,  urlLink Krizia ,  urlLink Jenn ,  urlLink Brittny , and Brett were here. We got a lot of good pics, but I haven't sorted through them yet, but I'll put up some pics after I do.  Went over to Brett's place afterwards, where I grubbed on in-n-out, passed out about five minutes into a movie, woke up at 4am to go play video games in the hotel theater (hooked up a gamecube to the theater's projector.. woooh. that's a big screen. o.O), went to church (happy easter!) early morning. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       A collection of Oxford people's away messages; anyway, I'm going to go watch TV now.   "DUDE....looks like NO SLEEEEEPPP tonight... BOO to HW!!! >:o" "get 10 pages done by 11!! join me and eugene in our efforts!! :-)" "doing my homework.. leave a message or call the cell" "dont u wish u were doing something as fun as I am? [smirk] :-!" "9/15 pgs done!" "today's homework load is nucking futs!"   Oh yea. I ran 5:15 today for mile.. on four hours of sleep! Not too shabby. Four hours of sleep due to the four tests I had today.  I've been wanting to update the photoblog on this page, but I have yet to recieve the  urlLink adapter  so I can get pictures off of my phone without paying $0.25 for each pic.  Good luck to anyone working on the OA research paper tonight. 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       at first when i saw william hung, american idol reject, i was embarassed. i was ashamed that an asian, who falls into every stereotype possible, was being shown on a regular basis in commercials where after his audition, he would state, "I have no professional training."  Then i got to the point where i realized that he was just being himself. its not that he tried to make asians look that way, its really who he is. at this point, i was like "hmm.. go him for making some money off of this."  then i saw  urlLink this  article. based on what is in the article--i can now conclude that william hung is beyond arrogant. his new found fame has turned him into an extremely cocky person. when will he realize that he is famous because he is easy to laugh at? this is a joke that has gone on for way too long.  it needs to stop. but it's tough when the butt of the jokes is so willing.  quotes from the article:   William Hung blew me off the first time I tried to get an interview.  The University of California-Berkeley student and pop icon, who is best known for singing a rendition of ``She Bangs'' before being ejected from ``American Idol,'' had in his mind become big enough to bark:  ``Everybody wants a piece of me now. . . . I'm not interested.''  Just a day earlier, chart-topper Twista had given me 30 minutes. I couldn't believe Hung could be that full of himself.  [...]  Recently Hung has been on the other end, doing the criticizing. He's a judge for ``Cal Idol,'' Berkeley's version of ``American Idol.'' According to some contestants, he can be harsh. But he says he's nothing like the television judges -- Paula Abdul, Simon Cowell and Randy Jackson. ``I'm objective. They're not always objective. I'm always objective.''  [...]  One girl walks up and hugs him, but it's hard to tell if she's a friend. She's a former dorm-mate from freshman year at Clark Kerr dormitory, and she tells a story of how Hung criticized her. The girl, who also sings, said he had the gall to tell her that on a scale of good to bad music, ``Elton John is here, he would be next, then Britney, and on the other end would be me.''  
    
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Haha.. this is great. It's 9:20pm and I'm starting on a five page essay for AP Comp.  Feels like the Oxford days, but what's the best part? IT's NOT DUE AT MIDNIGHT!. WOOHOO.  This should be a breeze. Easy prompt: How does the first chapter foreshadow the themes throughout the rest of the novel. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I found a pretty nice service which was on  urlLink Evhead 's blog.. it's called  urlLink BlogRolling . It's similar to the Xanga subscription lists, but for Blogger. And you can can add a link to any site. Cuts back on work for the lazy guy. :) 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Okay, so I made some changes to the blog. Fresh layout, new tagboard, and a photoblog! I'm gonna throw pictures from the camera phone into the square on the top right. Yeaa. (Oh yea, click the picture to see past pics).  HOpe you like it. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
         xrunvincerunx    :     hi   btbraalclk  :    hello there    xrunvincerunx  :     just letting you know.. you may not see me around for a while   btbraalclk  :    why    btbraalclk  :    r u comminting suicide?    btbraalclk  :    lol    xrunvincerunx  :     first off, thats not funny   xrunvincerunx  :     its a umm.. really long story   if you want to hear it   btbraalclk    :    ya actually i do    xrunvincerunx  :     well it started like four monthes ago.. right before xmas   xrunvincerunx  :     i was in west covina and i stopped by a liquor store to grab some red bull   btbraalclk  :    uh huh    xrunvincerunx  :     and while i was there, the store got robbed and one of the owners got killed   xrunvincerunx  :     i guess it turns out that the store was some underground hub for like a chinese mafia type thing   btbraalclk  :    omg    xrunvincerunx  :     so the trial is getting started for it and they asked me to be a witness   xrunvincerunx  :     so im in this like relocation thing..   btbraalclk  :    omg    xrunvincerunx  :     took a long road trip yesterday.. not quite sure where i am   btbraalclk  :    isnt tht scary    btbraalclk  :    serious    xrunvincerunx  :     but im assuming its pretty far away from oc   btbraalclk  :    omg no u arent really    xrunvincerunx  :     why would i kid around about something like this?    :-(    btbraalclk  :    i dunno    xrunvincerunx  :     anyway. i still have my cell phone. so if you need to get in touch with me.. ya.   btbraalclk  :    wouldnt u have written this on ur blog    btbraalclk  :    how r u online    xrunvincerunx  :     i dont want a lot of people to know   xrunvincerunx  :     because like i dont know who reads my blog..   xrunvincerunx  :     anyway, i gotta go. bye   btbraalclk  :    wait    xrunvincerunx  :     what?   btbraalclk  :    how r u at a computer if u dont kno where u r?    xrunvincerunx  :     because theres a computer in the new house?   xrunvincerunx  :     i really gotta go.   btbraalclk  :    ok    xrunvincerunx  :     family meeting with some fbi agent or something   xrunvincerunx  :     bye   btbraalclk  :    good luck i guess    btbraalclk  :    byebye     xrunvincerunx  signed off at 7:19:23 PM.  xrunvincerunx signed on at 7:20:40 PM.       xrunvincerunx  :       APRIL FOOLS!!     btbraalclk  :    omg    btbraalclk  :    damn u!!!!!!!!!!1    btbraalclk  :    omgomg    xrunvincerunx  :     ahahaha    btbraalclk  :    i was so scared for u  
    
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       leaving someone hanging on a handshake should be something punishable by death. 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Congress.org:  urlLink http://www.congress.org/congressorg/issu...   The Draft will Start in June 2005  There is pending legislation in the House and Senate (twin bills: S 89 and HR 163) which will time the program's initiation so the draft can begin at early as Spring 2005 -- just after the 2004 presidential election. The administration is quietly trying to get these bills passed now, while the public's attention is on the elections, so our action on this is needed immediately.  $28 million has been added to the 2004 Selective Service System (SSS) budget to prepare for a military draft that could start as early as June 15, 2005. Selective Service must report to Bush on March 31, 2005 that the system, which has lain dormant for decades, is ready for activation.  Congress brought twin bills, S. 89 and HR 163 forward this year, entitled the Universal National Service Act of 2003, "to provide for the common defense by requiring that all young persons [age 18--26] in the United States, including women, perform a period of military service or a period of civilian service in furtherance of the national defense and homeland security, and for other purposes." These active bills currently sit in the committee on armed services.    
    
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i really dont have much to say other than it's late. and i'm not sure why i'm still up. just chatting with my insomniac-partner-in-crime, amelia.  i still have to finish my online lifeguard training soon (still have like three hours left). weekend of training's coming up and i need to get it done before then. = and check out  urlLink limewire  if you're looking for an alternate to the dying kazaa. it's pretty nice. thanks jeff. 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         urlLink SignOnSanDiego.com > News > State -- Assembly OKs $1 increase in minimum wage   SACRAMENTO  California's minimum wage would climb to $7.75 an hour under legislation that was approved by the state Assembly on Wednesday, an increase supporters said would still leave roughly 1 million workers with poverty-level pay.   The measure by Assemblywoman Sally Lieber, D-Santa Clara, would raise the wage from $6.75 to $7.25 an hour starting Jan. 1, 2005, and to $7.75 on Jan. 1, 2006.  It was sent to the Senate by a 45-29 vote.  The bill's supporters said the other West Coast states have higher minimum wages than California and the minimum wages in Oregon and Washington increase with inflation. California's minimum wage would have to be $8.92 an hour if it were tied to the cost of living.  Washington's minimum wage is $7.16, Alaska's is $7.15 and Oregon's is $7.05. The federal minimum wage is $5.15 an hour.  "You try to live on $6.75 an hour, even $7 or $8 an hour," said one of the bill's supporters, Assemblyman Manny Diaz, D-San Jose. "In my (district) nobody can live on anything less than $15 an hour. That's why many wage earners have two jobs."  Good news for a lot of teen workers. Looks like minimum wage might go up soon... 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       obviously, someone was very bored when they decided to map out all of springfield...   urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i went to the farm-wide orientation today for knotts. not the most entertaining way to spend two hours. after a short history lesson on walter knott, you learn about safety, cleanliness, service, and integrity through 30 year old videos. i've finished about half of the 7 hours of online lifeguard training. and i have a total of 26 hours of hands-on training next friday, saturday, and sunday... lookin' forward to that. should be fun. :)  it looks like bluish is getting past the planning and is starting to take off the ground. we have a few gigs lined up in june including two dances and one or two banquets.  anyway. i have to go work on my history project on walt disney (ironic, huh?). 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       need a photographer for your banquet, dance, event? contact a bluish representative today!  urlLink www.bluishphoto.com . 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Yesterday Vice President Dick Cheney gave a speech at the Coast Guard academy where he vowed that America would fight on in Iraq. Then he said, 'Not actually me, other Americans.' You know, we should have a law in this country, anybody vowing to fight on actually has to do some of the fighting." - Jay Leno,  The Tonight Show with Jay Leno     
    
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       kinda sorta. ;) 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       (picture courtesy of  urlLink brittny 's lj)    uhh keith? wtf.  eFz  d E a t h: omg ahahahaha eFz  d E a t h: is he stoned? xrunvincerunx: either that or drunk  mss anthrp: niiiiiiice 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       (courtesy of  urlLink john )  A German couple who visited an infertility clinic after eight years of marriage to discover why they couldn't conceive were dumbfounded when told that they just needed to have sex, reports The Sun. Both the husband, 36, and his 30-year-old wife were raised in strict religious households and had no idea how to have sex. "When we asked them how often they had sex, they looked blank and said 'What do you mean?'" said a spokesman at the University Clinic of Lubek. "[They] were simply unaware?of the physical requirements necessary to procreate." The clinic offered the couple sex-therapy lessons and is now conducting a study to find other people with a similar lack of sex education.   Sometimes you feel like an orgasm, sometimes you?wait, who doesn't feel like an orgasm? Soon you may get more bang for your buck when you buy new chocolate bars containing high levels of chemicals similar to those the body releases when sexually aroused, reports The Sun . The chocolate bars currently on sale in Britain contain 660 milligrams of phenyl ethylamine, which is related to dopamine and adrenaline ? natural chemicals that heighten bodily sensations and thus allow for easier orgasm. Testers reported orgasm-like highs from eating the chocolate. Consequently, new bars hitting the market soon will contain even more of the synthetic chemical.    
    
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ...or almost got it for sure. i went back for my second interview today for lifeguard at soak city! (hehe..  urlLink molica 's job last summer. :D) but ya. yay! they offered me a spot. i just have to get through the training. woohoo! 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i had an interview for a possible summer gig. i think it went pretty well. i dont really have time to tonight to add many details (tests galore tomorrow! ahh!). but ill write 'bout it tomorrow after my 2nd interview. 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    click for larger version. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       it's been a hectic week(end). since i was gone from school for 4 days, i have  tons  of makeup work to do. i havent had this many things to do in one weekend since i left the old school.  just gotta get through tuesday and i'll be good. tuesday...  so i'll probably blog again after then. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        R.I.P. Nicholas Berg  urlLink    he was beheaded in iraq. please pray for him and his family.  
    
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Going to Oxford is like self-inflicting pain. We're not students, we're masochists." -- Brett Griswold, an Oxford scholar.    
    
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i feel a little bit better now. it's been a long week i guess. i spent the majority of the day resting up.. got stuff done on miscellaneous things that i've been pushing off for a while (like cleaning my room to a managable state. :D)  hehe. one of the medicines i'm taking,  urlLink chlorpheniramine  (who makes up these names?), has five stickers on it...all different colors  do not chew or crush  may cause blurred vision  may cause dizziness  may cause drowsiness  do not use while breast feeding (ya, i prolly don't have to worry about this one)  gosh, all this just to get rid of a runny nose? it's a really weird pill though.. its like a clear plastic capsule and inside of it are little white balls that just roll around the capsule... perhaps i'm more easily amused when i'm drowsy/dizzy/have blurred vision? hah. 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm worth exactly $2,512,418.00. How about  urlLink you ? 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       okay. so i havent been to school yet this week, which under normal circumstances i would be ecstatic. but im not missing school to sit around, eat ice cream, and watch tv. i'm missing school so that i can toss and turn in my bed and try to sleep or mope (is that a real word?) around the house because staying still just hurts the aching body. anyone else really want this school year to just be over?  i feel like blah. 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       wow.  urlLink blogger  just got a huge makeover. pretty new design. comments. author profile pages. individual archive entry pages. comments. did i mention comments?  theres a lot of stuff they havent done yet since it was just done a couple hours ago, but wow. it looks good. comments! 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       lol. capital one sent me my very first credit card today. :D $20,000 credit line.. not too shabby.  .. it's been cut up and thrown into the trash. 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Marketing 101  (Stolen from  urlLink Andrea )  You see a gorgeous girl at a party. You go up to her and say, "I'm fantastic in bed."  That's Direct Marketing.   You're at a party with a bunch of friends and see a gorgeous girl. One of your friends goes up to her, and pointing at you says, "He's fantastic in bed."  That's Advertising.   You see a gorgeous girl at a party. You go up to her and get her telephone number. The next day you call and say, "Hi, I'm fantastic in bed."  That's Telemarketing.   You're at a party and see a gorgeous girl. You get up and straighten your tie, walk up to her and pour her a drink. You open the door for her, pick up her bag after she drops it, offer her a ride, and then say, "By the way, I'm fantastic in bed."  That's Public Relations.   You're at a party and see a gorgeous girl. She walks up to you and says, "I hear you're fantastic in bed."  That's Brand Recognition.  
    
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        The New York Times: Coutesy of  urlLink John    urlLink The Bionic Running Shoe   PORTLAND, Ore. --  SHOES have long been sensible. Now some are getting smart.  Smart enough, that is, to sense their environment electronically, calculate how best to perform in it, and then instantly alter their physical properties to adapt to that environment. In short, the designers say, shoes that can do whatever is needed to deliver improved athletic performance or just a better experience in the ancient poetry of feet striking the earth.  "The whole concept of an intelligent shoe would be great," said Christian DiBenedetto, a scientist here at the North American headquarters of Adidas. "Something that would change to your different needs during a marathon, or whatever you were doing, was always the fantasy."  Adidas, the 83-year-old German sporting-goods maker, is about to turn that fantasy into biomechanical reality in the form of a running shoe for men and women. Sleek and lightweight despite its battery-powered sensor, microprocessor and electric motor, the shoe, named 1, is expected to be in stores by December and will cost $250.  Adidas executives say the shoe is no gadget-dependent gimmick. Instead, its designers say it represents a leap forward in wearable technology. Each second, a sensor in the heel can take up to 20,000 readings and the embedded electronic brain can make 10,000 calculations, directing a tiny electric motor to change the shoe. The goal is to make the shoe adjust to changing conditions and the runner's particular style while in use. [ urlLink read more ]   (vince: damn. someone please buy me a pair of these for xmas. :D)  
    
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       okay. so i guess what happened last night was that a telephone pole or electrical transformer on the street behind me broke/fell/collapsed. because they had a crane on the street and they were putting in a new telephone pole today. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       as i'm sitting in my room. there are about five police cars parked behind my house. i'm really not sure what they're doing there other than blocking off the street and putting flares on the ground. but there's also a lot of smoke everywhere... so i'm assuming there was a car accident or something. weird. i didnt hear it.  the lights from their cars are lighting up the walls of my room. -_- 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        four days before the AP exam....  xrunvincerunx: so lets talk about something you dont know about xrunvincerunx: so it actually helps you on friday xrunvincerunx: _______ sailed the ocean ___ in ___  urlLink mss anthrp : columbus, blue, 1942 mss anthrp: :D xrunvincerunx: 1942?! xrunvincerunx: oh my gosh.. xrunvincerunx: you're gonna get a 1 on friday.. lol   [edit]  something john just pointed out...    urlLink BwoozKwooz : 1942? BwoozKwooz: that's the year after pearl harbor BwoozKwooz: haha 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Reuters:  urlLink BMW drivers get most sex    BERLIN (Reuters) - BMW drivers have more sex than owners of any other cars and are much more active than Porsche drivers, a new German car magazine has found. The German magazine &quot;Men's Car&quot; found in a survey of 2,253 motorists aged 20 to 50 published in its inaugural May issue that male BMW drivers say they have sex on average 2.2 times each week while Porsche drivers have sex 1.4 times per week.  Following BMW drivers were Audi (2.1), Volkswagen (1.9), Ford (1.7) and Mercedes (1.6). Drivers of foreign car makes were also behind BMW with Italian cars (2.0), French (1.9), Japanese (1.8), Swedish (1.6) and Korean cars (1.5) trailing after.    Among women, French car drivers were top with 2.1 times per week followed by Audi (2.0), Italian (2.0), and BMW (1.9) with Porsche again at the bottom of the scale at 1.2 times per week.    (well, there's one more reason to want a BMW...)  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i seem to have been lucky enough to contract the new  urlLink sasser  virus that's going around. goody. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       man. so much drama at oxford. hah, why does the interesting stuff happen after i leave? gosh. that school has called the police more often this school year than in the last couple years combined.  so girl A and girl B at oxford get their nipples pierced. girls A and B are pretty proud of them and show anyone who wants to see them. guy C comes along and girls A and B have girl D take pictures of their nipples in a bathroom stall. guy C is an idiot and posts them on his livejournal. oxford counselors find out about it. parents are called. cops are called. girls A and B get suspended for a while. girl D and guy C have to become registered sex offenders.  (ps. i heard that girl B has zits on her boob) 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       to whom it may concern:  please don't ever go to a waterpark (or beach) and lay in water face down with your arms out. it's not nice.  thanks,  vincent pv sc lance corporal 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       run. eat. soak city. eat. sleep.  it's an endless cycle of nonstop fun six days a week. :) 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i had a relatively bad day today. it was going great until about 10 minutes before i got off work. i didn't let a kid go down one of the fun house slides because he had rivets on his backpocket (which scratch the slide, so the next person that goes gets a lovely splinter). so his dad comes up to the slide and yells at me about how there's no sign posted and that he didn't come to the park and pay money for me to tell him that his son can't go down the slide. i pointed out the sign w/ the rules which was conviently..umm.. right next to the side and slide entrance. i offered to call a shift leader for him. so another guard flagged down a supervisor, and my boss (the area manager) along with two other supervisors came. the kid's dad promptly told them that i was being extremely rude and wouldn't let his kid go down for no good reason at all. :(  bleh. 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
           her name is isabel ngoc-chen phamvan (aka izzie); 6 lbs, 12 oz. born 9am this morning. :) 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i was on my way home today when i passed by a mobile home place and i saw a woman on the ground in the driveway. by instinct now, i went over there and pulled some gloves out of my fanny pack (which i still had on because i just got off work) and put them on. she was an 84-year-old who had fallen while going over the speed bump. by the time i got there, there were a few others around. i called 911 and waiting for the firefighters and paramedic to show up. (ever call 911 and get a busy signal? yea.. not so fun). when they showed up, they put her on a backboard and headed off to the hospital to get an xray. i didnt do much, but hey, all the better. just weird, because this is what i'm looking for for the entire day and nothing happened in the park today... but the second i get off.  on another note. where ever you are in soak city, chances are a lifeguard can see you. we're stationed in a way so that atleast one (if not more) lifeguards can see almost every guest within 10 seconds. so don't come to the park and do something stupid with your girlfriend/boyfriend. c'mon! it's a family park!   PG-Rated Story:  someone told me about a time once when a 13 year old boy was laying on top of a girl on one of the purple tubes (can fit two people) in the river. so the lifeguard says "can you please not do that, this is a family park." to which he replies to her, "i'm trying to start a family here!"   (edit: someone complained that the story above is not G-rated... so i've upgraded it to PG. :) )  
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       the bonfire tonight was a get together w/ a bunch of soak city employees and some of their friends. i brought greg w/ me... anyway. so we show up at the bonfire and greg's cousin just happens to be there (he goes to cypress and eats lunch w/ one of the groups i hang out with at lunch). small world. then cody (used to go to oxford, but got kicked out for grades) shows up. small world. then jocelyn shows up! woah. small world.  work bonfire, but atleast 7 people i know from other places were there.. it was weird. cody kept on putting lighter fluid into the fire, i thought for sure someone was going to get burned.  all in all, a pretty good night. quite a few guards showed up (maybe like 10ish). not too shabby for something thrown together at the last minute.  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i just came online to check the weather forcast before i headed off to work. i hate june gloom. sun! i want sunnny weather! 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       why people go to water parks on days like today is beyond me. it's cold, windy, and wet. but i guess its find by me since that's where the money for my paycheck comes from.  on weekends we have insane numbers of guards scheduled to work (you almost never get a weekend off and i heard that there were over 150 of us..with more being trained this weekend). so today, as usual--it being a weekend and all--there were lots of guards. but its cold. so theres not as many guests. on top of that, we had to shut down the river today. i guess it's a state law that if a dead animal is found in the water, you have to shut down the attraction for the day. today, a bird was found. so all the guards that would have been on the river.. were not on the river.  also, while i was at gremmie lagoon (little kid water playground), there was an AFR (accidental fecal release). we called a supervisor who came, confirmed it was uhh.. feces, and told us to clear the pool. so at one point, gremmie and the river were both shut down.  i must have the worst luck because i ended up in the crappiest places on the rotation. i did river twice (then the river got shutdown), then gremmie (which then go shut down, but promptly reopened) and fun house rover FOUR times--totalling probably over 3 and a half hours. the fun house is basically like a house full of different things that squirt, leak, or splash water. but the rover has to walk through the thing over and over again while kids try to get you wet--not so fun on a cold day. hehe. what i would give to have been put on the top of a slide today.  hopefully it'll be sunny tomorrow. :) 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       some kid today lost his prescription goggles in the river. i didn't even know they made prescription goggles.  on my way home, i was waiting for a bus on the corner of beach and ball (uhg, i hate that corner). anyway, there was a lady standing on the curb, and i walked inbetween her and the bench. she pushed me. i fell. and she yelled "MOVE!!" i think she thought i was trying to steal her ugly green purse which was sitting on the bench. which is odd, because she had another purse hanging over her shoulder.  oh sure, i'm gonna steal from someone when i'm wearing red shorts, a bright red jacket that says lifeguard on it, a lifeguard hat, and a nametag. gee. i'd be real hard to find. 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       so my nickname with more than half the shift leaders is "family van".. not sure if i like it or not yet. :D but i guess i'll get used to it. 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i already shut down a ride. one of the guests pulled his biceps femoris while i was on stand on the bottom of banzai (six lane slide w/ mats). i was waiting for him to walk out of his lane, but i just saw him laying on his side holding his leg.  i just thought, "aww crap." went to go help him, picked up the phone and called for help while the top guard started clearing the lines. within a minute, the two top dogs in the park arrived along with about four supervisors. super quick response. still not sure how you can pull a muscle on the slide..but i guess it's possible.  fun day. oh yea, it was really cold today and cloudy and gloomy. not very good waterpark weather.. or summer weather for that matter. 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        God's last name is not DAMN.  
    
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        so after thirty-something hours of training, today was my first day on stand. did river a, top of banzai slides, river h, and then exit area for stormwatch. it's a lot of fun. :) definitely more tiring than you would think though.  i have about three or four blisters on my feet. they hurt a lot, but everyone says that'll stop after a week or so.  today i got 136 high fives. (yes, i counted--it's national high five day at soak city.. so its a competition w/ the guards) 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i'm not sure why i havent blogged at all..but here it goes.  bluish -  urlLink bluish  is really starting to take off now. we have two jr high dances lined up in the next week. one on friday night and another one next wednesday night. scooore! kickin' it at jr. high dances!  soak city - i had department stuff on wednesday night. start this weekend. yaah! sat 9-2, sun 11-4. a lot of the guards are gonna be going to knotts on sat after our shift. so i guess that's where i'll be. part of the S.E.A.L.S. (serving everyone and loving self) motto is "I rock. I am the bomb. I am extremely good looking." it's in our lifeguard manual. i'm not kidding.  physics boat race - we spent waaay too much money on our boat. but it turned out really dope. our team name was "Yo Ho!" because freeman didn't like "Freeman's Seamen"..although he was laughing at it for about five minutes. we made it into finals and during finals, we were half way there and were in second place but we just said screw it and abandoned ship because we didnt think we could catch up. :)  finals - suck as usual. last one is the second half of my math final tomorrow. its EASY as hell, but the thing that sucks is that theres NOT ENOUGH time to finish it! i swear, its sooo easy. but theres way too many questions in the time period that we have to finish it. so everyone ends up having to guess because they dont have time to do them all. and i'm not even doing half of them, i'm just plugging in the answers back into the question and checking them on my calculator.. i couldn't imagine actually working all of them out. 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i have three  urlLink gmail  invites if anyone wants one. first come first serve.  (btw, if i don't know you and you're a random person that got here by searching for gmail in google, dont even bother asking)    
    
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       1 week - ...still available 2 weeks - Brittany 3 weeks - Vincent 4 weeks - Lianne 5 weeks - Reanne 6 weeks - Greg (wanted 4, but it was taken) 7 weeks - ...still available 8 weeks - ...still available x weeks - ...still available 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ...and i'm so freakin tired from this whole weekend. i'm going to bed now. 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       made it past the prelim stuff on friday. got past the swim test, treading water while singing a song test, and picking up a brick (the hard way) from the bottom of a deep pool test.  learned more in the past two days about lifeguarding than i could ever imagine. can't wait until tomorrow. got adult/infant cpr, team rescue, and final written exam tomorrow (which you have to get 90% or above on).  wish me luck. = GOLDFISH! 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        RIP Ronald Regan  urlLink    1911-2004  
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       probably won't be seeing much of me this weekend. i have a pretty busy training schedule w/ soak city. fri 4-10:30, sat 8-6, sun 8-6. if you need to get a hold of me though.. call the cell and leave a message or send me an email. ( vincent [at] gmail [dotizzle] com )  (  EDIT:  I was just kidding about that call the cellphone thing. my cell got confiscated by a certain history teacher today. :\ ) 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink So here's the deal... You sign up for one of these affiliate links. Like free AOL Broadband for 45 days (which u'll cancel in 44 days) or sign up for an ebay account and place a bid (that u'll kno u'll lose). Then u get 5 people to do the same thing. And then they send ya a free 20gb ipod (4th generation) or an iPod mini (color of your choice). one  of my friend got one, and online forums are buzzing with people who have gotten one too. Supposedly, it's legit. Worth a try I think. Click here for the link!  
    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         how gay are you? haha. leave a comment. :) 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ouch. i'm not sure why i'm still awake. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Reuters:  urlLink Bigger Breasts for Free: Join the Army   The U.S. Army has long lured recruits with the slogan "Be All You Can Be," but now soldiers and their families can receive plastic surgery, including breast enlargements, on the taxpayers' dime.  The New Yorker magazine reports in its July 26th edition that members of all four branches of the U.S. military can get face-lifts, breast enlargements, liposuction and nose jobs for free -- something the military says helps surgeons practice their skills.  "Anyone wearing a uniform is eligible," Dr. Bob Lyons, chief of plastic surgery at Brooke Army Medical Center in San Antonio told the magazine, which said soldiers needed the approval of their commanding officers to get the time off.  Between 2000 and 2003, military doctors performed 496 breast enlargements and 1,361 liposuction surgeries on soldiers and their dependents, the magazine said.  The magazine quoted an Army spokeswoman as saying, "the surgeons have to have someone to practice on."    
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       A woman in a hot air balloon realized she was lost. She lowered her altitude and spotted a man in a boat below. She shouted to him, Excuse me, can you help me? I promised a friend I would meet him an hour ago, but I dont know where I am.  The man consulted his portable GPS and replied, Youre in a hot air balloon approximately 30 feet above a ground elevation of 2346 feet above sea level. You are at 31 degrees, 14.97 minutes north latitude and 100 degrees, 49.09 minutes west longitude.  She rolled her eyes and said, You must be a Democrat.  I am, replied the man. How did you know?  Well, answered the balloonist, everything you told me is technically correct, but I have no idea what to do with your information, and Im still lost. Frankly, youve not been much help to me.  The man smiled and responded, You must be a Republican.  I am, replied the balloonist. How did you know?  Well, said the man, you dont know where you are or where youre going. Youve risen to where you are, due to a large quantity of hot air. You made a promise that you have no idea how to keep, and you expect me to solve your problem. Youre in exactly the same position you were in before we met but, somehow, now its my fault. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink ben  says that according to these surveys by the national constitution center, only 41% of american teens can identify th three branches of government. so i did my own poll.  no - IIIII IIIII IIIII III yes - IIIII IIIII  (interesting note, the non-oxford people did better than the oxford people. and jeff got it right because it was on a chart in his history class that he stared at when he got bored) 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       today was the first day that i didnt wear sun screen... because i ran out. never again. i got sooo burnt today. i'm pealing. :( 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       at sc, lifeguards are told never to get involved in or try to break up fights. one of the security guys told us that they are told never to go into the water at sc because that is the lifeguards territory.  ...so if there's a fight in the water, theres pretty much nothing anyone can do to stop it. well except blow a whistle. 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       happy birthday to me. 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       to whom it may concern:  soy sauce is highly flamable. yea, i found that out last night. :D  sincerely,  vincent pv sc sergeant 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         this is the picture from two nights ago. taken with a canon digital rebel. 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       today i walked past the wave pool and saw a yellow cone on the beach side of the wavepool where there's about six inches of water. on the cone were the words "caution: wet floor"  no shit? 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       so tonight my brother and i spent the evening modifying safe and sane fireworks to make them a little more fun. we had a pretty big group go over to the kmart parking lot. good times... lighting off modified piccolo petes and a few special fireworks that todd brought.   jocelyn showed up tonight, and i'm now convinced that she knows everyone in the world... because this is the second time that ive run into her this summer in a random place (first time was at a soak city bonfire).  then all the sudden a car pulls up and stops. both doors opened at the same time (it was at this point that everyone mumbled something along the lines of "oh shit.."). it was an unmarked buena park police car.  they started questioning ben, christina, and todd. ben said that all  he had were piccolo petes and mad dog fountains and boldly asked for his ID back (and it was true, that's all he had with him). so ben and christina came back to our group. but half hour latter, a freakin paddy wagon pulls up. police van with a steal cage in the back.. the works. they handcuffed todd and took him downtowm for fingerprinting and gave him a $1200 fine and a misdemeanor.  then josh and kyle followed the paddywagon to the station (where we found out that modifying legal fireworks is a felony) and the rest of us headed over to jocelyn's house to light off the rest of the fireworks before midnight and get some grub.  during this whole thing, i did snap a couple pics with my camera phone and i pulled out our bluish camera, which can take pictures better at night. phone picture is on the  urlLink photoblog . the other picture--the better one--will be posted later. also, here's  urlLink ben's blog , and i'm sure  urlLink john's blog  will have something by tomorrow. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       inservice is basically re-training to make sure that you still know your stuff. the worst part of it is the warm ups >.  so what's the best way to warmup? i forgot what they're called..but we have to do this thing that's like football drills. you know where you run in place and someone blows a whistle and then you gotta do a pushup. well we do those... except we do them on the beach of the wavepool in just a swimsuit. so everytime you do a pushup, you get completely submerged in water and it's freezing because the water is cold and the windy breezes that come by are enough to send chills down your spine..  pure torture.  we also played intertube h2o polo this morning. it's sooo much fun! think waterpolo but while sitting in intertubes. it was yellow intertubes vs. clear and orange intertubes. our team won. i got an assist. :) 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ...then the terrorist have succeeded in disrupting your life. besides, worst case scenario: bomb goes off, you get pulverized, and then you're with Jesus. He will cover you with His pinions,   And under His wings you may seek refuge;   His faithfulness is a shield and bulwark. You will not be afraid of the terror by night,   Or of the arrow that flies by day;" - Psalm 91:5    
    
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        i went to the block tonight w/ lianne to go see harold and kumar go to white castle. this is by far one of the best movies ive ever seen. (maybe not  the  best, but definitely in the top 10, maybe even 5) you should definitely go see this movie or rent it or buy the dvd when you get the chance. it got a  urlLink 73%  on the tomatometer.. which is pretty good by rotten tomato standards.  oh yea, after the movie, we went to starbucks and one of my old subs from oxford was cashier there. weiird. (for those of you who go to oxford, its the white guy with the shaved head who looked like lex luther.) 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         ROADTRIP!!!   ...be back in 36 hours. Hopefully. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i'm fucking stressed out without a real reason to be. someone cheer me up.... because i could use it. 
    
    
</post>


</Blog>