<Blog>

<date>23,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I proudly declared my love last night. That's right, I love one of my teachers and have for almost a year.  I do fear that I waited too long, for now he appears "taken". But I feel so much better now, I decided that it is really not the anwswer from him that was important. It was the telling by me.   Things have a way of working out, for the best. So if it was truly meant to be...well then it will happen, if not. Best wishes to him and his happiness.  
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Hi, well it is Friday...long weekend coming up. That is a good thing.  
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Howdy..welcome ...
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Hi Again,    sorry it has been so long. I am lazy and busy, I fear more of the former that the latter.  For that I am truly embarrassed. I promise I will be better.  As an updat to the declaration of Love. No news to report, we will have to see what happens when school starts again. Not  that I have another class with this person. But I will eventually see him in the halls, and I will let you knwo right away. 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,September,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Hi,     I have been up to my eyes in schoolwork. But on the plus side after this semester, I will officially transfer to a 4 year school and be more than half way to that pesky bachlors degree. I so shoudl have done this when I was 18 and living at home with the parents. What a drag, no time, no money. It will all be worth it in the end I am positive.   So, to the matter of previous record. I have nothing to report out of the ordinary. I have run into him a bunch of times, it has been no different. Which is good. The fear was that I would ruin the friendly rapport that existed. And the hope was that he would not be able to live without me and we would live happily ever after. Well, neither had happened, so I am no better off or worse off and that is good.  I saw one of the best movies the other night. Matchstick Men. Now, I actually had hopes for this one, so it is not a great suprise that I liked it. I have some very specific rules for movies, and find that most "hollywood" creations are not worth the film that they are using. And cannot believe that people would pay 9 bucks to see them. I will spare you all the critics view, just know that I do not think you or anyone would be dissappointed by this film.  It is one that will be just as good on DVD when released, however.  Well I have to get back to my FOOTBALL! Half time is over.  Cheers- Ann  
     
    
</post>

<date>26,October,2003</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink My Yahoo!   Well.. I have registered for Cal State Fullerton. One step done on the way to my goal.   Wednesday was my B-day. I have to say that I have the best friends in the world. I love them all very much. You all know who you are. Thank you for loving me back. :-)  Lets see what else is new in my world....I seem to have a lot of boys in my world... All of a sudden. I am not sure if I like it. Talking to a girl in my Tuesday night English class. It hit me...The reason that I proclaim that I will be 50, single and happily love it.   In a relationship, especially true of you are married. Every thought that you have, from a desire for a peanut butter and jelly sandwich to the desire to take a new job (or just quit the old one, ala Office Space) every little thing, no matter how trivial, meaningful..or meaningless, good or bad, affects someone else. So as soon as you have a thought ..you have to immediately consider how that thought will affect the other person. And..I do not want to do that.  Selfish? Probably. Too bad. I can take care of nobody but myself. Maybe there si someone out there whos opinion I will care about. Someone who will be able to change my mind once I make it up. A person who I will want to make happy, and will want to consider in my plans.   But I have wandered the planet for 34 years now, and I have not even been tempted yet.    So until then, I guess I will stick with what I have, A couple of boys that I really like, but who have their own lives. Some of them have girlfriends, some have wives(I am going to hell, I know) and some are just too busy or not around very much. If any of you are reading this, I really do like one of you more than the rest. I will not, however make you uncomfortable. I am happy with what we have, and until you make a move to change it, I will not push. Nick, you are a really great guy. See, I did not say that you are "nice" ;-)  You light up my day, when we talk...and the other stuff goes without saying. I am very happy that you took a chance, and I will try to keep being myself. I really am that cool, promise.  OKAY...I am off for the night ..homework to do and sleep to sleep.        
     
    
</post>

<date>26,October,2003</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink My Yahoo! 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Whew,     one week to go unitl graduation. I have a final test on Saturday, then I am off for the summer. So, I am off to study catch you all later. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>