<Blog>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We leave *now* -- much later than planned but that's ok.  Pray for a safe trip!
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The plan was to drive out this afternoon/evening sometime once we got things all packed up, but things are going a bit slower than we had expected (predictable, of course) and the likelihood of our getting out of here today is getting slimmer and slimmer.  We really want to get on the road today!  Getting out of here sooner means more time to get unpacked and settled before I have to start work (Monday @ 8:00 am).  We're just about to go pick up the rental minivan and then the real work begins.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Has it ever occurred to you that moving is one of the most stressful things possible?  Maybe it isn't like that for you; it is for me.  I find the uprootedness puts me into an anti-productive state that I have to fight tooth and nail in order to accomplish anything.  The concept of  home  is very important to me -- I need to have a home that is safe and familiar and can offer me a refuge from the rest of life . . . and when I don't have that waiting for me I find myself feeling lost.    I know that my childhood plays a big part in this (seriously) -- the amount of traveling my family did when I was young made it very necessary that we have a home base to return to.  "Home" really was very different from "away" -- and home is all the more welcome when contrasted with the stresses of an "away" that is on another continent with people who don't speak your language.  Now "away" may only be Starbucks but I still have that ingrained sense of need for protection, for refuge, for my home to be my fortress of defense against all that is not safe.    And to some degree I have not had that in a while -- we have been living with my mom in her house for the past 7 months while we have been in California . . . and while that has been very smooth and worked out very well, it's something of a sense of being in someone else's fortress for me.  Mind you, that's far better than being in no fortress at all -- but I long to have a refuge that is my own, designed to meet the needs of my own family.  Yet in the mean time our little corner of this fortress has been ransacked; familiar things packed away and replaced by the sight of their boxes, hard, cold, and unfamiliar.  To be fair, I have to say that all corners of this fortress have been ransacked -- Brewsters packing is a force that can hardly be contained to one room of the house.  There's stuff everywhere!  But all of that is to say that I'm kind of going crazy right now with the stresses of preparing for this move.  Please pray for our survival and sanity as we still have about two weeks' worth of work to cram into the next two days.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had hoped to be able to post my comments on having seen Mel Gibson's new  urlLink Passion movie  (caution: poorly designed Flash site) as the first content on the new address but it will have to wait another few days probably.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, the day has finally come.  I waited and waited because I had planned on changing my template to have a completely new look to go along with the new address but that can come when I get around to it.  So welcome one and all to the new (and soon to be improved) Onward and Upward,  urlLink oau.blogspot.com  -- I guess January 14 gets to be  urlLink CAFOTL Day .   ( Update:  Well, that's lame -- I never knew that Blogger's auto-generated links link to the whole archive page rather than to the individual post.  Oh well, that's why people pay for Moveable Type . . . )  If you're looking for past archives, they can be found at  urlLink retswerbdej.blogspot.com , the old home of Onward and Upward.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This will have to be quick -- borrowed computer time and all.  We're here and almost what you might call "settled" -- although there's still lots to do.  Sorry I haven't called, Hutch and E -- no phone service yet.  I'll make up for it soon.  Lots of thoughts to tell -- just got to figure out a computer situation.  Thanks for your prayers, everybody.  The trip was safe and uneventful.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      - Life is good.  I don't know how else to put it other than to say that it is simply wonderful to be back in the Northwest.  This recent time in So Cal gave me an appreciation (and maybe even a love??) for that area that I haven't had in a while, but it sure doesn't compare with the joy and comfort of being *home* back in the Northwest.    - Starbucks culture here is (as expected) quite different from what I've been used to.  Almost everything is done differently at my new store and it has taken a lot of adjustment.  But my new coworkers have been friendly and patient and that has made all the difference.  - Go figure:  moving from Pasadena to Portland got me a $0.26/hr raise and housing that is about 1/2 to 2/3 the price.  Not that I'm complaining.  - I miss my computer.  Actually I miss my mom's computer -- I've been using hers ever since she bought it a few months ago because it's faster and running XP.  We brought our machine with us but left the monitor and haven't had the money to replace it yet.  So my computer time has been borrowed (I'm currently blogging from the in-laws') and I have missed the outlet this normally is for me.  I'm hoping soon to get the computer hooked up but in the meantime I'm planning on carving out some regular library computer time.  - Now I remember why I appreciate all wheel drive so much!  - Fellowship is truly a beautiful thing.  Nothing beats face-to-face contact with beloved friends . . . including those who are willing to stop still on the 405 bridge over the Willamette at 2:30 am just to see the view.  Not that anybody I know would ever consider doing that.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We have now been in the new apartment for a week -- and I guess I've had a full week of work as well.  Doesn't seem like it's been that long already!  And yet it feels like California is a lifetime away in the past.  Funny how those things work.     urlLink Hutch  is letting me use his internet connection for a minute here as we still have not gotten the phone lines hooked up at our pad.  We are loving having a home of our own again -- I think we almost don't know what to do with ourselves as we bounce around our living room by ourselves.    Got to hang out with Joel,  urlLink Eli  and Punchbowl today and now with Hutch and Steph -- good day of fellowship and fun!  It is great to be back close to these friends.  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Are any of you actually using the RSS feed?  I'm just curious to know whether it survived the transfer from retswerbdej to oau.  Since I still haven't hooked my computer up yet I don't have a machine with an aggregator to check it out on.  Feedback, anyone?
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Ben  sent me a very encouraging email today that is part of why I have somewhat of a better perspective on life tonight.  He included this line from an email he got from Matt Tucker (Ben, does he have a website or blog?):   Ever notice that our best laid plans limit the Lord's ability to be a part of them in such a way that solicits total dependency upon him (aka: Faith)?   Hmm, that certainly throws things in a different light.  But how  do  you lay plans that have "room" for the Lord?  I think it comes down to making sure that we include the Lord from the beginning of our plans yet continue to stay open to adjustments along the way.  More importantly, however, this brings to my mind the fact that sometimes God's plan is to deepen our relationship with Him by putting us in situations that force us to be dependent on Him -- and each time He gives us a chance to see his trustworthiness we are more prepared to trust Him next time around.    PS Thanks for the encouragement, Ben.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Great, I'm now one of  those  blogs whose post titles consist of the mood of the author at the time.  But after my last post being from such a negative standpoint I wanted to give you the change of mindset right up front.  Melissa is feeling  much  better -- she really got under the morning sickness thing and was really miserable for a couple of days there.  The way the sickness works (for her at least) is that she has these small windows of time in which she feels a little funny and the idea of eating is completely unappealing.  But, counterintuitively, her only hope is to  eat something right then  -- otherwise she will immediately get really really sick and throw up anything she eats.  So we are getting back into the routine of always having food ready at hand so that she can choke something down when she feels that way and avoid feeling really terrible later.  Not that this regimen keeps her feeling wonderful, but it usually does the trick to keep her from feeling awful most of the time.  So now you know more than you ever wanted to know about the sickness patterns of the pregnant variety of  melissa l. brewsterius .  We went in for our first appointment with the midwife today and that was the first step toward the reality of this life change setting in . . . wheeee, here we go!  It sure is different going into it with all the baggage (both good and bad) of having gone through a pregnancy, labor and birth already.  I haven't really thought through that yet so all I can say is boy does this feel different.  In a good way, I think.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I applied today for a position at Multnomah working as a Seminary Admissions Counselor.  I don't know how we'll survive if I don't get it or something else soon.  I have not been getting the hours I need at Starbucks and this = no money.  I really don't want to get my car reposessed!  Moving got us behind on our finances already and now we are in pretty dire straits.  I have been close to as stressed out as I can remember being and this has made the hours I do get to work miserable because the last thing I want to do when I'm stressed is give caffeine-hungry Starbucks customers good customer service.  Plus Melissa has been sick as a dog (did I mention the fourth member of our branch of the Brewsters is on his/her way October 3rd?) and that contributes to my stress as well because there's nothing I can do to make her morning sickness go away and make her feel better.    I'm having a hard time remembering that God is in control.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just remembered the real reason I logged on here: to thank you for your prayers and let you know that Melissa did much better today.  She's still pretty sick but was able to keep her food down today and that's a big step in the right direction.  Keep praying.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Entomophagy  -- soon to sweep the nation?  Check  urlLink here  for some recipes if you're unsure about tonight's dinner plans.  Also, for those friends of  urlLink Molo  and I who haven't yet been sufficiently convinced of the dangers of homeschooling, make sure you see the " urlLink About Me " page.   Key phrase: "originally, I took up entomophagy as a means of shocking my elders and betters."    And finally, my apologies if you're already a  urlLink Dave  reader (you should be) and have had the privilege of seeing this already.  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The observant ones among you may have noticed the recent updates to my "movies" sidebar on the right.  It's about the only thing on this blog that didn't fall behind last month while my posts were few and far between; my movie watching was also few and far between.  But we managed to catch Finding Nemo and Winged Migration a week or so ago and that finally gave me something to update.    Finding Nemo impressed me -- I had heard it was good and I liked it well.  Pixar really has the formula down pretty well, and they do it in a way that appeals to me.  Have you ever noticed that all of their movies are quest stories?  Actually if you really look at it, most of Disney's cartoons are quest stories of one kind or another.  Winged Migration.  At least the title doesn't promise anything more than it delivers.  Billed as a documentary on, well, the migration of birds, WM proves to be, well, basically just a bunch of shots of flying birds stitched together and sold as a movie.  The narration is spare to say the least -- he cuts in only every couple of minutes to read a sentence or two -- and the random subtitles giving other details are too spotty to be depended on.  There is no plot or development whatsoever and with as little verbal and written content as the movie has I find it hard to consider it a real documentary.  The upside of WM, however, is some really awesome shots of birds in flight.  There are lots of really familiar shots of birds going by overhead that look as though they were pulled out of the film vault to fill time, but interspersed throughout the film are close-ups of flying birds that must have been shot with cameras mounted on planes and boats.  You know what I'm talking about here -- the camera is moving at the same speed as the bird and together you're just cruising along above the countryside -- these aren't really anything original either but they're still really cool as you get to see the precise muscle movements and aerodynamic adjustments that make bird flight work.  Watching these shots made me think of the concept (popularized if not coined by Michael Behe) of "irreducible complexity" -- it's clear that one little detail (anatomical or practical) missing and there's no way these things are getting off the ground.  Final analysis: not worth the time it takes to sit through.  But if you happen to have access to a copy to skim through so you can catch the flight close-ups, they're really quite a treat.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes, the puking goes on . . . so much for all my fancy talk about knowing how the sickness works.  Some days barf is an unstoppable force with no immovable objects in sight.  Melissa has been feeling awful again and even when she throws up she gets very little relief.  Ezra has really shown himself to be the little trooper, not demanding much at all while Mel feels so sick.  He truly does have a compassionate heart.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Melissa's misery continues unabated.  Puking.  Lots of puking.  Lots and lots of puking.  From a midwife's perspective, morning sickness is a really good thing -- it's caused by a hormone whose purpose is to keep Li'l Sprout safe and sound in the womb.  But from anyone else's perspective, it really sucks.  Really really sucks.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh yeah, just realized that I had totally forgotten about the early screening of the  urlLink Passion  I got to go see at the beginning of this year when I was typing my previous movies post -- the list has been duly updated.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, so scanning my blogroll just now led me to drool all the more over type pad since now both  urlLink Eli  and  urlLink Hutch  have fancy-schmancy blogs with cool features and all.  Just this morning I was griping to myself about the fact that blogging is now pretty much completely out of my normal life.  That is, I used to sit down to blog because I had something I wanted to say (most of the time), now I blog because I feel like I ought to and when I sit down to do so I then have to come up with something to say.  Which lately has been pretty much about Melissa being sick.  But lately my life has pretty much been about Melissa being sick.  Suffice it to say that I look forward to having blogging be a part of my normal life again.  Ok, bullet time:  - I just looked back over my recent posts and realized that although I have griped about Melissa being sick, I haven't really given an overall summary . . . not that you probably wanted one anyway.  Basically, though, here's the scoop:  Since the 14th of last month (that's Valentine's Day for those of you who, er, hadn't been reminded) she has been completely bed-ridden.  As in, the only thing that makes her leave the horizontal position is the call of nature.  Any other forays into vertical (or even semi-vertical, i.e. sitting) territory have been greeted with immediate vomiting.  She has been to the E.R. twice and they have been largely unhelpful -- although getting some IV fluid in never hurts.  Pretty much the current diagnosis is that she has really bad morning sickness combined with some flu bug or something else that is putting her over the edge.  Even when she's not actually throwing up she has such bad nausea that she is hardly coherent.  Earlier this week we seemed to have a bit of a break but the last two days have been back to more of the same.  She's now 10 weeks along -- 12 weeks is the end of the first trimester, when most women start feeling better.  But at this point two more weeks of this seems like an eternity -- and there's no guarantee that anything will change then.  Some women are literally unable to get out of bed for the whole 9 months.  (Footnote:  I don't know how their families survive.)  So I guess we're hoping that she  does  have the flu or something because that would mean that she will definitely feel better once she's kicked it.  -  urlLink Starbucks  will soon be nothing more than an entry in my resume.  I'm starting work for  urlLink CNF  on Monday.  I really don't know what to think yet -- time will certainly tell.  - I drove by  urlLink Krispy Kreme  this morning and thought, "mmmmm . . . donut" (yes that was exactly the first thing that popped into my head when I saw the sign).  I decided I would go in and buy a donut.  One donut.  I walked in the door and was greeted by a smiling face who said, "Welcome to Krispy Kreme -- would you like to try a fresh hot donut?"  As he said this he turned and pulled one of the conveyor belt and handed it to me.  As I ate my donut I wondered what to do -- I had just gotten my one donut.  I bought a dozen.  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      - Melissa has been in the hospital since Wednesday -- still no real word on the root cause of all this misery.  - CNF has been going well -- last night was my last shift at Starbucks.  - Life is busy and stressful.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      That's right, ladies and gentlemen, a post on Tuesday and now one on Friday too.  This may mean you'll have to start checking my blog once in a while again!  What was I going to say again?  Ever heard of  urlLink Sara Groves ?  If you're Hutch you have because you've loaned me her CD over and over in the last couple of weeks.  If you're not Hutch you really ought to give her disc a listen.  Good easy-to-listen-to music (read: not the ticket if you're in the mood for something edgy) and *great* lyrical depth.  Apparently she's got a brand new album out -- I'm planning on checking it out soon.  Listening to CDs all day long really makes you look at your music collection in a different light.  I come in to work, pop a CD in, plug my ears with my headphones, and that's pretty much what my day looks like.  It took me exactly two weeks of work to listen to every CD in my case . . . plus I was borrowing other CDs all the while.  Now I'm on my second trip through the case and already very much wishing I owned more music.    
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just read my Weekly Hutchy Goodness (no linkage today -- you know where to go) for the first time in a little while and was put to shame by the fact that he has a more recent update on my wife than I do.    Yes, she is home from the hospital.  And while she continues to be miserable all day, every day, she has taken massive steps forward -- like the fact that she now has not thrown up in 6 days.  Ahh, the things you take for granted . . .  She's still on TPN (Total Parenteral Nutrition) via her semi-permanent IV line, which means that she doesn't have to rely on what her stomach can handle in order to stay hydrated and fed.  The doc is pretty much saying that this is just really really really bad morning sickness -- one gastroenterologist at the hospital said that in his 18 years he has never seen morning sickness this bad.  But we seem to be taking slow steps toward improvement, so maybe there's light at the end of the tunnel.  CNF is going really well -- I'm starting to feel like I know what I'm doing most of the time, and that's a really good thing.  I'm still not really used to having my own space at work -- being a cubicle-dweller takes some adjustment.  I would sure love to be blogging more -- both the writing and the reading that make up the blog experience -- but for now this every-now-and-then will have to do.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alright, I  almost  got my movies updated.  Almost.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It may be rainy but the  urlLink Dodgers  are on top of the NL West and all is well with the world.    Let's not talk about  urlLink that basketball team  that plays here in Portland.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For the grace of God has been revealed, bringing salvation to all people.  And we are instructed to turn from godless living and sinful pleasures.  We should live in this evil world with self-control, right conduct, and devotion to God, while we look forward to that wonderful event when the glory of our great God and Savior, Jesus Christ, will be revealed.  He gave his life to free us from every kind of sin, to cleanse us, and to make us his very own people, totally committed to doing what is right.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Because it gives me an audience for stuff like this.    I've been reading a book from the library about JavaScript . . . so here's my  urlLink Random Ezra Picture Generator .    There's 9 images altogether -- keep clicking to collect 'em all!
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just realized (again) that I'm way negligent on posting a Melissa update.  Here it is in two words:  Lots Better.  The line in her arm has been out for a while now and she has returned to being a vertical human being after way too long of being a horizontal one.  She is still regaining her strength and is still on some anti-nausea medicine but is really doing a whole lot better.  After weeks of staying in Vancouver with her mom (easy access to babysitting and another person to care for her and Ezra) we have been back home for a couple of weeks now and it is great to be back here.  The doctor is still keeping a close eye on her but is telling us that everything looks great and she should be feeling all the way better soon.  Praise the Lord, I've got a wife again.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, the results are in . . . the Lord is blessing us with one of each.  Sprout is a girl, or at least so it appeared to the sonogram tech yesterday.    I'll post some porn once I get it scanned in.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink      No, I won't be celebrating at work.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Peter Blegvad must be one of the strangest people on the planet.    At this point I really know very little about the guy -- he doesn't seem to have a website about himself and the important things about him (as far as I can see with a couple of google searches) are that he was born in New York, lives in London, is married with two kids, and he's a musician and a comic-strip artist.  I was at the library yesterday and my eye happened upon a book in the comics section (don't ask) titled 'The Book of Leviathan.'  This is one of the quirkiest and coolest books I have ever seen, written about a baby (who happens to not have a face) and his stuffed rabbit and live cat.  He combines crazily different art forms with awful puns and references to everything you've ever heard of (and lots that you haven't heard of).  This stuff is pure genius.  Oh yeah, lots of philosophical underpinnings too.  Think Calvin and Hobbes on big-time drugs . . . only not.    As far as his music, I know nothing.  He apparently describes it as "what happens to rock when it percolates through the strangeness of my brain" (that's a rough paraphrase from what I remember of a quote I read a half an hour ago -- take it with a grain of salt).  Two links for you:  urlLink Leviathan  seems to be the only site around with any examples of Leviathan.  urlLink Amateur  is a random side project done by Blegvad (and others, maybe) and should win an award for being one of the strangest sights on the internet. Check 'em out.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      That's right, we go in for  the  ultrasound today -- and if the alignment of the stars is correct, we'll find out whether Sprout's a he or a she.   Here's hoping for one or the other.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Blogging from home is a beautiful thing -- and now that we're back flush with a phone line at home it will hopefully become a more regular event again.  If any of you want our new phone # you can  urlLink email me  and I'll pass it around.    I guess that's about all I have to say for now.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      for those of you with  way  too much time on your hands:  urlLink GBKAP !
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've tweaked with the template a little more -- hopefully I've fixed the sidebar display problem.  I'd love to hear from a couple of you what you're seeing this on and whether it looks like it's displaying right.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Congratulations to Craig Muelheim and Jackie Thomas, who is getting married today (to each other, none the less).  We'll be heading off to the wedding this afternoon.    The wedding season has begun!  Jon Brown is also getting married today . . . then in 27 days Joel and Britney will wed on the same day as Eren McNeal.  It's almost like being back in Bridal-- I mean Bible College!
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      After my little episode with comments last night (which I don't think anyone saw, thankfully) I am now back to good ol'  urlLink Reblogger  for my comments.  When I saw that Blogger was hosting comments I thought I might be able to do the cool 'recent comment' sidebar and that was enough to suck me in.    But no, in fact, you can't do that.  And by the way, no, in fact, you can't delete other people's comments even if you're the owner of the blog.  And no, half the time you can't even delete your own comments (even if you're the owner of the blog).  And no, you definitely can't have your comments without trying to get people to sign in (and having that obnoxious little 'Anonymous said' at the top of comments by un-signed-in-commenters).  And of course don't even think about the now-requisite email address and URL fields on the comment form -- we're not going there.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Any of y'all familiar with them?  I've seen their stuff around for a while but for whatever reason have never paid it much attention.  I picked up their CD  The Only Reason I Feel Secure  at a garage sale last weekend and it's way cool.    Criticism as Inspiration   I saw in your bedroom The drawers had been emptied Looking for answers But you won't admit it now You don't need a reason That's what you tell me But I still don't buy it Drink yourself silly Night after night  It makes me feel so good To always tell you when you're wrong The big man that I am To always have to put you down  Then there's your girlfriend She opens her legs and Gives your life meaning Is that what you love her for The angels are always looking down He's perfect with a frown The bully always wins  It makes me feel so good To always tell you when you're wrong The big man that I am To always have to put you down It makes me look so good To always put you in your place I can write it in a song But never say it to your face   Lyrics are always so much better when accompanied by their music.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Saw this on  urlLink Bill Lueg's blog  (and I'm a sucker for these things):  1. Grab the nearest book. 2. Open the book to page 23. 3. Find the fifth sentence. 4. Post the text of the sentence on your blog along with these instructions.  So here we go, from C. S. Lewis'  The Dark Tower & Other Stories :   "'In fact this occurs so often that it has become the basis for the religion of half the world -- I mean, the belief in reincarnation -- and of all theories of the Eternal Recurrence, like Nietzsche's.'" 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So whaddaya think?
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I was just getting back into the swing of blogging when my 10 free hours of Juno ran out for the month . . . Curse the lack of good free internet access . . .
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      That's right, this weekend I celebrated one full year as a blogger.  Of course I had intended on posting on the one year blogiversary (which was Saturday) but I had to remind myself that real life trumps blogging and I had a busy weekend.  If I had posted on Saturday I would have put my actual first post ever (which can be found  urlLink here ) but since I'm late instead I think I'll put up my post from one year ago today:  Saturday, May 17, 2003 So I've now had a whole 24 hours as a college graduate. Saying that makes me feel a lot younger than I feel most of the time. Real adults have college far behind them in their past. I read a study in the paper today that said americans consider 26 to be the age of the beginning of adulthood. Great.  Graduation was a bit of a strange experience, I guess. Rather, perhaps I should say that in retrospect it is a strange experience, far more so than it was as I went through it. Let me explain: We have this strange conception regarding big events in our lives -- weddings, graduations, the like -- we conceive of them in our minds as momentous occasions, we think of them as moments where time stands still and somehow we change during that moment. Yet my experience has been that time passes very normally and I am still the exact same person, even as I walk across the stage or kiss my bride.   In reality it is not the moment that bears the deep significance, it is the whole of the experience -- 6 years of college, not the moment of receiving my degree; crossing from single life to married life, not the wedding ceremony itself. Yet something has to stand in our minds as a reference point for these big events, so in retrospect the moment tends to be preserved under glass, frozen to stand as a symbol in our memory.   And I had a strange awareness of this last night -- I sat there watching professors on stage doze off during the address, cheering for friends as they crossed the stage, thinking about how warm I was in my cap and gown, and altogether feeling very normal. I walked across the stage and time passed completely normally, not moving in that slow motion way we associate with such events. But I realized that despite the apparent normality of these moments as they passed, some selected memories were to be imprinted into my consciousness to be repeated throughout my life as I look back on my years of college. And as these memories are repeated and relived, they will gradually slow down until they have reached that nice half-speed, embellished with whatever my mind decides to add to the experience (no memory is recorded exactly as the event happened) -- and that is how they will stay until I die or get Alzheimer's.  After graduation came the reception, a truly enjoyable crush of people -- largely utter strangers, but interspersed among them were individuals I love and whose friendship I have cherished deeply over the last few years. Yet I am very likely never to see some of these friends again. I used to think otherwise, to convince myself that despite my failures at keeping up distance friendships in the past, I would succeed this time. I don't try to deceive myself now. I have gained true friends during my time at Multnomah, and some of them will remain dear to me for many years to come. But most will fade away, to be forgotten until some future reunion or until I read their name in an obituary. And that's ok. I said my goodbyes last night -- gentle goodbyes, mostly stated as a "see you later" even when both of us knew they should have been "have a nice life."  It feels strange to me to actually be feeling some of the stereotypical "graduation feelings" -- I thought I was beyond them. I tested out of high school a year early, so this is my first graduation -- chalk my sappiness up to naivete if you like.     // posted by Jed @ 11:13 PM 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ever since we've been back in Portland there has been this occasional recurring thought running through the back of my head:  find an  urlLink Odon Soterias  show . . . find an  urlLink Odon Soterias  show . . .   The thought finally ran through at a moment when I was sitting in front of the computer anyway, and a brief search was productive:  They're playing at the  urlLink Portland Scottish Highland Games  on July 17 . . . definitely should be fun.  Plus don't forget that  urlLink Stavesacre  and the Clergy (anybody know of a website?) also have shows in June . . . and  urlLink Pedro the Lion  will be around in July . . .  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Another mission board we have been impressed with has been  urlLink International Teams .  They seem to be really well grounded, have a great support system for their people, and be very open to new ways of doing things.    In perusing their website I was particularly impressed by what they had to say about themselves.  Click on their  urlLink About Us  link and this is what they have to say:   Here is a snapshot of who IT is…  We are a nondenominational Christian, evangelical ministry embracing a wide range of backgrounds and styles.  We identify with the lostness of the world. We ourselves are utterly lost apart from the grace of Jesus.  Expressive worship of the living God is humanity's highest calling and ultimate end. We do it with joy, as often as we can.  God is both dangerous and good. Following him is a risk-taking adventure dependent on a miraculous God.  We are relational and strategic, living among those we serve.  We believe the Church is God's agent to reach the world. Really. Therefore, we are profoundly committed to the local church in its mission.  There are no marginalized people in God's Kingdom. Never is the gospel of reconciliation more clearly demonstrated than when hearts of hatred are turned to love.  We believe in people coming from everywhere, going to everywhere. Missions belongs to the whole world.  We want to be there before and long after the big campaign rolls through town. We want to build deep and long-term.  Faith is more than a decision. The call to "follow me" means transformed people building transforming communities.  Fail Forward!  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Sara Groves  has a song on her new album called  When You Said this was a Fight  or something to that effect.  "When you said this was a fight / You weren't kidding" -- written at a time in her life when she was feeling the fight pretty intensely.  I have felt the fight fairly intensely at times lately too.  And I've wondered if it was really worth it to keep trying to win.  I was listening to the song at work about a month ago (when things were substantially more hectic than they are now) and this spontaneously flowed out of me.  I emailed it to Hutch and he suggested I should post it here but I wasn't quite ready then . . . I guess I am now.  When you said this was a fight . . . you weren't kidding.  When you said this was a fight . . . you must have forgotten some details.   . . . was it an oversight?          --you never mentioned that sometimes I'd want to fight for my enemy.  You never told me that sometimes I wouldn't know which side my actions were benefitting . . . you must have overlooked that.  You didn't give me the heads up that I could switch sides so easily and so often.  You didn't tell me that future briefings would be so few and far between.  What happened to letting me know that I wouldn't recognize the battles' beginnings until after I'm already beat up?  Were you planning on clueing me in here?  When you said this was a fight . . .  . . . you didn't say enough.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alright, before you read any further, go read  urlLink  this .  Go do it -- it's important.    Go read it because it's what I want to be when I grow up.  Really.  Ok, just in case you didn't or couldn't read it, that's a link to a job description of a guidance counselor position at a high school for MKs in Camaroon.  Wycliffe would like to have the position filled by fall of this year at the latest.  That's a little soon.  According to the Wycliffe guy who calls us every few months or so (and is awesome) Wycliffe has recently changed their limits for how much debt they'll take someone with.  A couple can now join Wycliffe with as much as $36,000 in debt . . . we've got more like $20,000 between us.    I'm kind of stumbling over my words here because there's lots of pieces to this that all need to be communicated but still won't add up to any of you what they add up to for us.  Here's the deal:  We have known for a long time that we wanted to go serve the Lord overseas somewhere.  Have we been "called"?  I don't know.  What I do know is that we're willing and lots of other people aren't.  The other thing I know is that we're excited about the idea of it too.  But ever since Melissa and I met (and before that as individuals) we have wondered what capacity we would serve in -- lots of things sound appealing, but few really seemed to *fit*.  Plus there's been this whole debt issue -- we've got to get our debt paid off (or at least paid down some more) before we can even consider going anyway.    But this weekend we simultaneously find out that we could be going  right now  if we raised enough support to pay for our debt payments  and  we find a position that, as far as we can see, is just about the best fit possible.  I had never before thought about being a guidance counselor . . . just not the first thing on my mind, I guess . . . but the more I think about it the more sense it makes -- it seems to fit perfectly with who I am, how I interact with people, and what impact I would like to make.  Which is of course not to say that I want to do it forever, but it sure does sound great for the near future.  The position in Camaroon will (hopefully) be filled well before we're available, of course.  But it has given me a glimpse of vision again, of something to reach for again.    And we are moving forward again . . . maybe quicker than we yet realize.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was talking to a coworker this morning who told me that "sometimes it gets a little monogamous around here."   . . . well, I guess that's better than the alternative.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sleep is like a capricious spirit when you're two years old.  Sometimes she comes like a flash flood, overwhelming the senses in an instant.  Other times she waits just out of reach, flitting back and forth in front of you like the tease that she is.    And then, of course, there are those times when she decides arbitrarily that 3:00 a.m. is a wonderful time to practice a fire drill and evacuate the premises of your being as quickly as possible.  This has an immediate cause and effect relationship on the sleep your parents may be enjoying at the time, as in: they get to enjoy being awake with you!  How wonderful!  I love watching Ezra fall asleep.  He usually has nothing against going to sleep when he's tired, so the nightly ritual begins with Melissa asking him if he's ready to 'rocky-rock' and go 'nite-nite'.  She sits down in the recliner and he readily climbs up into his lap, bringing his beloved 'woof-woof' with him.  Usually things get started with a book or two, then Melissa runs through a recap of the day's events and a preview of tomorrow.  This seems to work really well to reassure him that tomorrow will bring as much fun as today did -- and that he's not missing out on anything by going to sleep now.  Once this is done we're into serious sleep mode and Mel will sing softly to him until his consciousness evaporates.  Generally speaking, I'm at  least  half asleep by the time Mel drops him into his crib -- sometimes I'm fully gone, collapsed on the floor or the couch or wherever I happened to be when we began.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Time Magazine  this week has, in addition to lots of good stuff on President Reagan, a little two page spread on the  urlLink Beastie Boys .  Turns out Adam Yauch will turn 40 in a couple of months here, not long after the release of their first new album in a while.  Favorite quote:  "When they're being idiots, the aging Beastie Boys are still quite brilliant."  (Disclaimer:  I'm not the world's biggest BB fan . . . most of their stuff just doesn't grab me, nor is it the most uplifting, "fix your mind on these things" kind of stuff.  But if you've never heard  The In Sound From Way Out , you're missing some great (instrumental!) grooves.  Make sure and get the full length version, though, not just the  urlLink 13 track version  (may be very hard to find).  As Joel often attests, the final tracks are the best material on the whole disk.)  [Update: Hey look, Time posts stories online too . . .  urlLink here 's the story for ya.]  [2nd update:  Anybody know anything about  urlLink this ?  Apparently the title wasn't as original as I had assumed . . .]
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       . . . and He  urlLink loves you very much .
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Saturday we went down to Portland's  urlLink Saturday Market .  We were walking through the park by Lloyd's center to catch the Max downtown -- Ezra running ahead as usual -- when a homeless guy caught my eye.  Head half shaved, half dyed, metal sticking out of various holes all over his face, tattoos all over his arms and face, classic punk clothes.  Early 20s.  You can see him in your mind's eye, I'm sure.    He was sitting on the edge of the sidewalk with a piece of cardboard in front of him.  On it was some of the coolest looking craftsmanship I have ever seen.  In his hands were a pair of pliers and a small chain that he was making, fastening little metal rings together.  Also in front of him were two other pieces of cardboard that had been neatly lettered in black and silver ink: "Hand Made chain malle jewelery" and "Don't just walk by.  At least take the time to say hello.  I'm not invisible."    That second one caught my eye.    I called Ezra back and stooped to see his wares that were spread out for sale.  Using needle-nosed pliers he was forming intricately patterned chains out of all different sizes of copper and steel wire rings.  Perfectly even in size and perfectly shaped, the rings were connected to form bracelets, necklaces, and keychains.  He didn't look up.  I thought of telling him that it was really cool stuff and leaving, but decided to see about striking up a conversation instead:  "How's it going, man?"  His voice surprised me -- nasal and so quiet I could hardly hear his words.  "I'm kind of discouraged.  Nobody's buying anything.  Everybody stops and says, 'that's really cool stuff, man' but nobody's willing to buy anything."  Hmmm.  He told me that he had learned his craft from a friend of his from Alaska and that he was more than willing to take special requests.  He could make them seamless, fastening them permanently around your neck if you like so that the only way to get it off is to cut it off.  Don't worry about the copper, it's great as long as you don't get it wet.  Get it wet and it will turn your skin green.  His hands were busy with his work the whole time.  People don't understand, I'll work with budgets.  It's not like it's that much to pay for something that takes so much work.  At least I'm not just begging, you know?  I make the clasps by hand, too.  Except if you want it seamless, then there's no clasp.  I made one for my girlfriend, a big thick one for her neck.  It was real nice -- I could have sold it for forty bucks.  I picked one up and fingered it in my hands.  This was some of the coolest stuff I have seen in a long time.  I asked him the prices and he pointed out the $10 bracelets, the $15 necklaces, and the $5 keychains.  I cursed inside at my lack of money to spend.   I can't say strongly enough how much I wanted to tell him that I appreciated his art, that I wished I had a basement for him to work in, that maybe I could help him get set up to sell his work in a shop for what it's actually worth instead of for the pittance he's getting.  I wanted to tell him how much he is loved and how much value I saw in him and how much there is out there for him to experience.    Instead I handed him a five dollar bill for this piece of handmade craftsmanship:     Melissa handed him the apple she had been saving in her bag to stave off morning sickness later and we left.  Sometimes you just wish for more, I don't really know what else to say.  And sometimes you need to turn those wishes into action, and you don't do anything about it.  Sometimes you feel entirely inadequate and, in your unsure-ness, you do and say nothing at all.  Sometimes the cost of friendship is just too high.  Sometimes your plans for your day get in the way of Someone Else's plans for your day.    Sometimes you go home and your heart aches for days.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Taken by the TRACE spacecraft today.  Check out more info  urlLink here .
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have no idea if any of this is true, but  urlLink this  is an interesting article about the origins of the children's rhyme "Sing a Song of Sixpence" . . . nursery rhymes are funny things.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The phone rang this evening and I let the answering machine pick up.  I listened to my voice speaking on the recording and thought, "no, that's not right at all . . ."    Here's what it would have said if it had been directly connected to my cranium:  Hi, you've reached Jed's brain.  Sorry I'm not picking up the phone right now, but, well, I didn't exactly want to talk to you right now, whoever you are.  You see, I set out to make some biscuits this evening and was two eggs short, having just put all the eggs on to boil.  Going to the grocery store involved leaving all my groceries with the checker and driving back home before driving back to retrieve them (it's a long story) and when I got back things just didn't, um, work out quite right with these biscuits.  (Was I doubling or tripling this recipe?  I can't seem to remember quite right.)  Then there was this pyrex pan that had just come out of the oven, see, and I didn't want to have a mess to deal with later, so I poured some (nice and cold) water into it . . . then there was a loud bang . . . and right now I'm sweeping up lethal glass shards from off of the kitchen floor.  So, um, could you call back some other time?  Thanks, I'd appreciate that. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just realized that Joel and Brittany have got a scheduling conflict coming up on Saturday:  urlLink honeymoon activities  (which can happen anytime) or  urlLink this , which only comes around once a year.    Man, I'd hate to be having to make that decision.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Lakers dynasty is  urlLink over .  And I'm not crying.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Looks like the  urlLink X Prize  may be about to be won.   urlLink NPR  ran a story this morning on  urlLink Scaled Composites , who may take the cake within the next month or so.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alright.  I know it's been mentioned before, but here's the little bit that  urlLink imdb.com  has to say about the upcoming 2005 movie,  urlLink The Lion, the Witch, and the Wardrobe .  I'm a little wary (to say the least) about it being put out by Disney.  (Thanks to  urlLink Draper  for mentioning this often enough to finally get me to check it out myself.  And what was that about updating your blog all the time now?)
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Real life trumps blogging.  Nuff said.  Come back in a week or two.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I saw a bumper sticker on my way home from work yesterday that read:   My Dog Donates Blood   And it had the name of a local animal hospital underneath. I guess the idea makes sense . . . but still, something about that was just a little weird to me.  Stavesacre update coming soon,  I promise  maybe.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alright, so after all my whining last night, here we go:   Yes, I was the geeky guy at the show with a scrap of paper and a pen, writing down every song so that I could later post their complete set right here. Yes, I'm also the geeky guy who right now can't find that scrap of paper even though it's been floating around the house for the last few weeks.   The show was in a gym down in Eugene. Opening for Stavesacre were  urlLink Ripe  and  urlLink Edict  . . .  if you can't say something nice, don't say anything at all  . . .   Then Stavesacre took the stage.   The gym was really a bummer of a venue . . . massive gym, 150 people. When we were all in close to the stage we all fit within the 3 point line . . . and behind us was a whole heck of a lot of empty space. Adding to the poor ambiance was the fact that the lights couldn't be turned all the way off -- so there was definitely no way to forget where you were. Plus with the amount of hard surfaces in there, the acoustics were awful.   But enough complaining -- Stavesacre rocked anyway. This is going to be fairly random, so it's bullet-time:   - Last time I saw Stavesacre they were touring in support of the self-titled album . . . and their show consisted of two songs from that album and everything else was off of Speakeasy. This time they dove right in with Shiv for their opening number and the show was a pretty good mix of their albums . . . except that they played nothing from Stav.zak.er -- long set, too. They did play two new songs (no word on a new album, however).   - These guys are focused on their music . . . very little talking, just playing the songs and connecting with the audience. Lots of eye contact, especially with so few people there and it being so light.   - Neil (guitar) is no longer with the band -- but Ryan Dennee (guitar) and Dirk Lemmenes (bass)&nbsp;are doing&nbsp;a great job of making the songs sound complete. Ryan's not a flashy guitar player, but I really like his style. I had never really realized how much of  Gold and Silver  is harmonics . . .   - I bought Mark Salomon's book,  Simplicity  . . . that's a whole 'nother post waiting to happen. Those sure weren't the spins  I  had put on those songs . . .   - Listening to great music is a really awesome experience . . . I wish I had the chance to do it more often. Going to a concert by yourself is a really weird experience . . . not sure if I want to do it more or not, but it does have its advantages.   - I guess it's kinda been a while since the show, so that's all that comes to my mind to say -- and after all that buildup, too . . .     
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, here's a post for anyone who may happen to be out there still . . . it's been a while.    I have discovered about myself that I have one basic introverted drive. When it drives me, I respond. How I choose what way to respond I still don't know . . . sometimes it drives me to read, sometimes to play my guitar, sometimes to try my feeble hand at visual art. During the last year, it has often driven me to blog.     Lately it hasn't.    Lately it has found its expression in all the other avenues -- I've done lots of reading, gotten back into playing my guitar, and have been putting pen to paper in artistic ways on an almost daily basis. And the drive to blog just hasn't been there.    Don't ask me; I just work here.    Will I be back?  Most definitely.    Will it be soon?  I have no idea.  Will I be a better blogger for it?  I hope so.    Sometimes I wonder with these things: should I go with the flow and not blog because I don't feel like blogging, or should I force myself to blog (even though I don't feel like it) because I know it's a worthwhile discipline and maybe  doing  it will make me  feel  like doing it? For now I'm going to go with the flow. Maybe having thought through this and typing it out will make me be ready tomorrow. Maybe not.  Will I get to the updates I've promised?  I don't know.  Yes, I would still like to post about Stavesacre and Joel and Brittany's wedding . . . yet at the same time, maybe it's dreading sitting down and writing these things out that has kept me from posting.  Maybe I'm just being over-analytical (gee, that would be a first!).      To quote someone we all know and love,      I'll be back. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>