<Blog>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      happy pentecost!  what a brilliant commemoration.  as i've been saying over the last several posts, God is really impressing upon me how important the Holy Spirit is in redemption.  the Spirit is amazing... and i'm just feeling it move in my life right now.  father tom made a great point in his homily this morning... if you read acts, you see that before pentecost, the believers were meeting behind closed doors because they were full of fear of persecution because of the message of the gospel.  the anointing of the Spirit totally diminished the fear and anxiety and gave them the courage to step out and declare their faith publicly.  the Spirit comes to take away our fears.  that's awesome.  i'm reading "changes that heal" by henry cloud and it's just cementing some ideas that God had already planted in my heart about the things i need to do to become the woman he wants me to become.  dr. cloud talks a good deal about how we become whole through the perfect blend of grace, truth, and time... and i can testify that is absolutely true.  well, the academic messes are better - i wasn't able to register because, get this, they didn't have my immunization records on file.  ugh.  so i gave them a copy of my mmrs and i'm good to go.  i still am not going to be able to take all the courses that i want, but i was able to register for personality and abnormal, so that's a good start.  i also realized that i guy i used to work with is in the graduate program in psych at UNO so he suggested some profs that i talk to to see if i can get some waivers or something for the honors/grad-level courses.  keep praying :)  cds i bought this week: teitur (poetry and aeroplanes) charlie mars (st) iron and wine (our endless numbered days)  i really dig them all.  very chill and relaxing and meditative.    i'm in the hunt for new music right now (mostly gym playlist material) so if you have any ideas, please send them my way.  i'm looking mostly for quality, mostly positive, fun, uptempo stuff, either new wave or hip hop.  right now the gym playlist is mostly kayne west, hot hot heat, the faint danse macabre remixes, and then your occasional top forty hook (toxic, milkshake, work it, etc.).  i'm currently auditioning pieces by !!! and blackalicious, so that's a start, but i need more.    anyway, the holy spirit rocks.  i can't say that enough.  more later...
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i am beginning to feel more and more confident that the Lord would have me pursue a graduate degree in theology and psychology.  unfortunately, i do not have the undergraduate pre-reqs to enter the psych programs that i'm interested in... as such i took a class this spring at the university of nebraska in omaha and am hoping to take several more this fall so that i can enter a masters' program next fall ('05).    unfortunately, i keep encountering difficulties... one of the classes i really want/need to take is closed to "non-degree" students and another is limited to honors students.  despite my harvard degree and an A+ grade in the class i took this spring, the psych department at UNO is refusing to allow me to register for these courses.  furthermore, when i try to register for the class that is open to me, the registration program keeps telling me that there are "problems with my student id number" and that i am "not eligible to register for the fall term."  huh?  i am going to go talk to the department secretary on friday, so pray that i will be allowed into these classes.  i am not certain if these roadblocks are from the Lord or from the enemy.  i just ask for your prayers :)
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've recently been accused of "leaving Christianity for a mess of pottage" by a conservative Lutheran, mainly because of the things I say on this blog.  I think I agree with Luther on most things, especially his definition of faith:  "Instead, faith is God's work in us, that changes us and gives new birth from God. (John 1:13). It kills the Old Adam and makes us completely different people. It changes our hearts, our spirits, our thoughts and all our powers. It brings the Holy Spirit with it. Yes, it is a living, creative, active and powerful thing, this faith. Faith cannot help doing good works constantly. It doesn't stop to ask if good works ought to be done, but before anyone asks, it already has done them and continues to do them without ceasing.  Anyone who does not do good works in this manner is an unbeliever.  He stumbles around and looks for faith and good works, even though he does not know what faith or good works are. Yet he gossips and chatters about faith and good works with many words.  "Faith is a living, bold trust in God's grace, so certain of God's favor that it would risk death a thousand times trusting in it. Such confidence and knowledge of God's grace makes you happy, joyful and bold in your relationship to God and all creatures. The Holy Spirit makes this happen through faith. Because of it, you freely, willingly and joyfully do good to everyone, serve everyone, suffer all kinds of things, love and praise the God who has shown you such grace. Thus, it is just as impossible to separate faith and works as it is to separate heat and light from fire! Therefore, watch out for your own false ideas and guard against good-for-nothing gossips, who think they're smart enough to define faith and works, but really are the greatest of fools. Ask God to work faith in you, or you will remain forever without faith, no matter what you wish, say or can do."  More thoughts later... I just wanted you all to see that Luther had a place for sanctification, even more than I initially thought in my post last week. 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Our pic of the day (of Kori, Mattie, and Salvo walking to the river) comes to us courtesy of  urlLink Bonnie Poon ...  urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm thinking a good deal lately about "waiting."  (I mean, I am a waitress...) Why do we say that we "wait on" a table?  Apparently it comes from the Old North French work  waitier   which means "to watch."    More importantly, lately I've been thinking about the concept of waiting... on God, on my future, on my hopes, on people, on plenty of things.  Everything in this world is so instantaneous that we have become entirely too impatient.  To go minutes while waiting for a meal to be prepared can feel like forever.  To go hours without a reply to an email seems too long.  To go a few days without talking to a close friend can seem like eternity.  So how long does it seem when you wait weeks, or even years, for an answer to a prayer?  God's timing is so different than ours.  I want everything to make sense NOW, to fall into place NOW, to be resolved NOW.  And yet, God tells me to wait.  Wait.  Wait.   Out of the depths I cry to you, O LORD!     O Lord, hear my voice! Let your ears be attentive to the voice of my pleas for mercy!  If you, O LORD, should mark iniquities, O Lord, who could stand?  But with you there is forgiveness, that you may be feared.  I wait for the LORD, my soul waits, and in his word I hope my soul waits for the Lord more than watchmen for the morning, more than watchmen for the morning.  O Israel, hope in the LORD! For with the LORD there is steadfast love, and with him is plentiful redemption.  And he will redeem Israel from all his iniquities.  Psalm 130  The dictionary (this is cliche, but relevant, I promise) tells us that to wait for something is "to look forward expectantly," as well as "to remain stationary in readiness or expectation," but also "to remain  temporarily  neglected or unrealized."  While this can be frustrating, what I find refreshing about these ideas of waiting is that it is hoping, but not in vain.  Waiting is temporary because God always comes through.  Days, weeks, even months are but moments in his time and in our lives.  We just need to operate on his timing rather than ours.  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       some of us wouldn't be lyin' if we said were tryin' too hard but, it all works out in the end. some of us would be tryin' too hard to begin lyin' but, but, it seems to all work out in the end. oh no, she's not a secret now. but, nobody cares. oh no, she's not a secret now the wolves have smelled her scent.   hot hot heat  in the song "no, not now"   it just seems to fit so well with how i'm feeling today.  i try too hard and i think too much and i share too much of myself and yet, it  will  all work out...   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today confirms it - God really wants me to think about the Holy Spirit right now.  Today Father Tom gave a great homily on John 14.  Yes I know that every Catholic in the world heard that same reading today, so I'm not claiming that God is talking to me and me alone here.  But it's just cool that the Spirit has been so strongly on my heart lately and then the lectionary coincides with that.  "If you love me, you will keep my commandments. And I will ask the Father, and he will give you another  Helper , to be with you forever, even the Spirit of truth, whom the world cannot receive, because it neither sees him nor knows him. You know him, for he dwells with you and will be in you... But the  Helper , the Holy Spirit, whom the Father will send in my name, he will teach you all things and bring to your remembrance all that I have said to you. Peace I leave with you; my peace I give to you. Not as the world gives do I give to you. Let not your hearts be troubled, neither let them be afraid. " (John 14:15-17, 26-27)  What a great way to think of the Holy Spirit - as the helper.  Other translations call it the counselor or the advocate, which are also amazing things that I am completely and totally in need of in my life.  I think God is just telling me now that He is with me so much more than I ever realized and no matter what I am going through, all that really matters is Him.  He is dwelling in me and he has the ability to comfort me and relieve my stress and fear and pain more than any human being can.  The Spirit is my help, my peace, and my hope. 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Current I-Pod playlist:   Faith, Hope, & Love: The Reunion Remix '04  Follow Through   Gavin DeGraw  This day   The Sleepy Jackson  Theologians   Wilco  Holdin’ On Together   Phoenix  Let's Embrace   Joseph Arthur  It's Our Job  Sondre Lerche  Born Again   Starsailor  Don’t Blow It   The Elected  Paradise  Richard Ashcroft  Love Will Come Through  Travis  Wonderwall   Ryan Adams  The Only One  Michael Pritzl  To Be Alone With You   Sufjan Stevens  Gloria 34  Taylor Sorensen  The Dead Sea   All Things Bright and Beautiful    Lyric of the Night:   You're so good You stopped me where I stood And let me look at love and I feel better Oh I feel good  Gavin DeGraw  (Overrated)   CD to Buy:  The new  Faultline  album.  Some of my favorite semi-Christian artists guest on it, including Chris Martin and Joseph Arthur.  The later does a kickin' cover of the Stones' "Wild Horses" - listen to it  urlLink here .  It comes out in the states on Tuesday.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So below this are some pictures from my week in Boston.  It was wonderful and refreshing, but also difficult in many ways.  I love so much about that place - and yet, I equate it with a difficult time in my life.  I suppose I will always have to work to reconcile those conflicting feelings.  Regardless, each day I was there I came to realize more and more how really freaking blessed I am.  I am friends with some of the most amazing people in the world, and that is not an overstatement.  Enjoy the pictures!
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      After a great night playing poker with the guys (and throwing Krispy Kremes out the windows of the Kirkland annex)...  urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      There are so many things wrong with Simeon in a fleece toddler onesie... but that's the Spee pajama party for you...  urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Matt and Simeon told me to order them a "cool" drink, so they ended up with some funky blue Martinis...  urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The girls and I hang out at the Quincy Grille...  urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This was taken around 3am after a wonderful night of 21+ JLDC as we were smoking cigars and enjoying a crisp night on the Charles...   urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Here is a nice pic of Bonnie and I hanging out late night at the Richardes' house:    urlLink      
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I adore this picture of Simeon and Sorcha.  I have no idea what they are doing and yet it seems to make so much sense... urlLink    
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This picture was taken on the boat from Logan to Litt's house.  The Boston skyline, great friends, the sunset... what more can you want? (Okay, maybe I wish that Russ had his eyes open when I took the picture, but a girl can't have it all)  urlLink    
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm thinking a great deal lately about salvation.  Last night reading 1 Corinthians helped to solidify the viewpoint I recently made to Jeff Dean that salvation consists of more than justification; in fact, salvation is justification as well as sanctification.  for example:  "He [God] is the source of your life in Christ Jesus, whom God made our  wisdom  and our  righteousness  and  sanctification  and  redemption ." (1 Corinthians 1:30 ESV)  I think the ESV translation gives the most explicit explanation of this, though the King James says pretty much the same thing.    Jesus is our: wisdom righteousness sanctification redemption  He died on the cross not only to give us eternal life (which to me is redemption and righteousness), but also to give us earthly components of salvation such as wisdom and sanctification (which simply put is holiness or purity).  Yes, Jeff, this might be dangerous thinking, but it is  not  Pelagian (or even semi-Pelagian, as Luther might accuse).  This is a holistic understanding of redemption that treats faith in Jesus as a radical, life-changing act.  This is about believing that grace can do more than erase sin - it can make love possible.  This isn't about being "holier than thou," rather, it is about living each day as though Christ's crucifixion makes a difference in  this  world as well as the next.   Wow.  Maybe I am a Catholic.  What is most crucial to understanding this theology of a multi-faceted salvation is the power of Holy Spirit.  It is not about being good, because we are really bad at that - we've proved it time and again.  Being good is being loving.  And we love because he first loved us... and gave us part of Himself to make us more like him.  God has really placed the book of 1 John in my heart and mind lately.  Hear these profound verses:  "By this we shall know that we are of the truth and reassure our heart before him; for whenever our heart condemns us, God is greater than our heart, and he knows everything.  Beloved, if our heart does not condemn us, we have confidence before God; and whatever we ask we receive from him, because we keep his commandments and do what pleases him. And this is his commandment, that we believe in the name of his Son Jesus Christ and love one another, just as he has commanded us. Whoever keeps his commandments abides in him, and he in them. And by this we know that he abides in us, by the Spirit whom he has given us." (1 John 3:19-24 ESV)  This is the best summary of what I believe the Gospel to be - God loves us.  He knows us.  He sent His son to die for us, and by faith in him we receive His grace.  Because that grace is transformative, he has given us his Spirit to dwell in us, just as he is with us.  This is the Trinitarian mystery - God is simultaneously completely separate from us, next to us, and in us - Father, Son and Holy Spirit.  Or maybe I'm a Pentecostal.  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm just happy lately.  That doesn't mean that life is perfect or that I've made peace with myself.  But, generally, God is really teaching me how to live life more completely.  Work is wonderful, I have friends who love me, and I have a vision of myself and my future that makes me smile.  Last night I went to Sullivan's with Sarah, Erin, and Heather and sang karaoke, which was such a blast.  Yes, it did take a bit of Maker's Mark to get me up there, but we just had so much fun... Worked a double today and I have another one coming up tomorrow, which while tough, is an answer to prayer since it will fund my Chi-town trip next week :)    So, there you have it, an update, finally, for that person (yes, singular, and yes, you know who you are) out there who has been disappointed in my prolonged absence from this self-indulgent site.    
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I wanted to share with you all the scrapbook page I made last night.  I think that it is pretty rad.  I found this book at the thrift store put out by some random Catholic publishing house in the 70's and it had all these cool spiritual quotations in psychadelic colors, so I bought it for 26 cents and used one of the quotations to create a page that reflects some of the members of my "human community of sharers."  Unfortunately, the colors didn't scan very well, but you get the idea.    urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i've been listening to an old ryan adams song called "dear chicago" a lot lately.  it doesn't exactly epitomize how i've been feeling, but it comes pretty darn close.   some of the high (low?) lights of the song:  life's gotten simple since but it fluctuates so much happy and sad and back again i'm not cryin' now too much..  think about you all the time it's strange and hard to deal think about you lying there those blankets lie so still...  nothing moves here in the corn nothing breathes or even smiles i've been thinking some of suicide but there's bars out here for miles...  i think the thing you said was true i'm going to die alone and sad...  i think that i've fallen out of love i think that i've fallen out of love i think i've fallen out of love with you 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      it's been two weeks since my last post, and i guess it is time for a new one.&nbsp; i wish i had something profound to say, but i really don't.&nbsp; life is a bit stagnant.&nbsp; i'm trying to grow, but i feel that attempting to grow on your own is horribly futile.&nbsp; i know there are things in my life that are catalysts for growth and that i'm likely moving forward without realizing it, but right now i just feel stunted.&nbsp; there are so many things in my life right now that i'm upset, disappointed, and frustrated by, and yet, i feel so powerless to make things change.&nbsp; my prayer is that i just my will becomes in line with&nbsp;God's will.&nbsp; and yet, when you don't know what God's will is, you can feel paralyzed.&nbsp; i wish i know what God's will is... but then i suppose i'd be God and that surely isn't his plan.&nbsp; and if i knew what God's will was, i wouldn't have to have faith.&nbsp; ugh.&nbsp; frustration.&nbsp; good night.   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      below are some pictures from the heck wedding in chicago last weekend.  i hope you enjoy them.  first, my favorite picture from the weekend in chicago.  All the harvard kids at the wedding in one shot...    urlLink     next, me and bonnie.  darn, we're cute.  urlLink     bellis, phouston, and barth smile at the reception...  urlLink     The head table (with a beaming soon-to-be Mrs. Dupee)...  urlLink     the hecks prepare to leave the ceremony in a vintage sedan.  how cute!  urlLink     here is roberto and lauren doing "blue steel" at the rehearsal dinner (at least I think that's what they were going for)...  urlLink     and last, but not least, what is likely the most random picture from the weekend: jamin and sorcha on a large two-headed rubber duckie.  hmmm?  urlLink     what a great weekend with great friends.  the rest of the pics will be on litt's website at www.strength-and-honor.com at some point in the future...
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      the gospel today was the parable of the good samaritan... and i've been thinking a lot about the message of the core of that reading.  the main verse is luke 10:27 -- "you shall love the Lord, your God, with all your heart, with all your being, with all your strength, and with all your mind, and your neighbor as yourself."  To this Jesus replies, "do this and you shall live (eternal life)."  i guess the thing that i struggle with the most when it comes to this verse is the idea of loving your neighbor as yourself.  i suppose that was a great answer two millennia ago, but today it seems a bit more complicated than that.  we live in a world in which self-help books clog the shelves, therapy is commonplace, and suicide is prevalent.  what good is it to love your neighbor as yourself when you hate yourself?  does that mean we should love our neighbors more than we love ourselves or simply love ourselves more?  how does one love oneself without becoming egotistical or self centered?  how does one love oneself while still acknowledging all of one's flaws and mistakes?    in that vein, i've been thinking a great deal about what it means to love yourself when it comes to relationships (romantic and otherwise).  it seems like there are two schools of conflicting advice, even within the so-called Christian community.  one side tells us to be selfless (especially women), give of yourself completely, and to expect nothing in return.  adherents of this perspective tell women that we should sublimate our feelings, wait on men to make the first moves, put up with it when men refuse to share their feelings, and let men be in charge.  (granted, perhaps this is an oversimplification of such a viewpoint, but it seems to be the thrust of a great deal of evangelical Christian "singles" and "dating" books).  on the other hand, mainstream society tells us to stand up for who we are and what we believe, to expect reciprocity, to demand equality, to not be afraid to make the first move, to not be afraid to cut ties when the going gets rough and to generally not put up with playing second fiddle to anyone or anything.    i guess, as with all things, the best way is somewhere in the middle.  i think it is important to give completely of yourself while still "guarding your heart" - but how is that possible?  is it possible to be selfless and yet protect yourself from getting trampled?    i suppose it all comes down to the first part of the lesson - love the Lord your God with all your heart, soul, and mind - because that is a prerequisite to loving someone else.  when we let the world cloud our vision and allow others to distract our gaze from God is when we find ourselves unable to love ourselves, and subsequently, unable to love our neighbor.  we love because He first loved us, and we love Him first because He is love.  that is my prayer today - that i focus on loving God first and foremost with all my heart, soul, and mind.  then, with His grace and by the power of the Holy Spirit will i be able to love myself and, in turn, my neighbor as myself.  amen.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      what is the difference between regret and repentance?  i've been thinking about that for the last couple of days.  sometimes we say or do things that we want to take back... and i suppose that is regret.  i think that is the same as repentance, except for when we repent of something we not only wish it hadn't happened, but we also try to ensure that it doesn't happen again.  i think that repentance is regret with understanding.  but it is even more than that.  i've done many things in my life that i have regretted... and some of them i have dwelt on for days or even months, chastising myself for my stupidity or my insensitivity or even simply my naivete.  my relationship with God has taught me that beating myself up does nothing to draw me closer to Him or to repair the damage that i may have done to myself or someone else.  that is repentance... a willingness to grow and change and heal.  and in that respect, repentance both requires and triggers grace, because repentance (unlike regret) allows us to continue to love ourselves and one another while still recognizing our mistakes.  just a thought.  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>