<Blog>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Presenting Okie, the Demon Cat.&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm loving this hot pink template that Blogspot has decided to offer the discerning user.  No matter where my web exploits take me, I always end up all too fond of pinks and purples.  And bright white text.    
      
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It surprises me, sometimes, how little I have to say.  I'm always thinking, but not enough seems to make it "out there."  But maybe that's a good thing.  Let's just say, I have an active (and precise!) brain-to-mouth filter.  Campus was strangely crowded this morning.  Sure, it's the start of Summer Session II, but I can't imagine that there is very much variation in enrollment as compared to Summer Session I.  Perhaps more students just opt to attend their classes on the first day?  The activity made me reflect on the approach of Fall.  And I'm not the only one.  Browsing through a silly women's magazine in the supermarket checkout line yesterday, I spotted a reccommendation that we chickas dress in light layers, as they are "perfect for the transition to Fall."  Wow.  But summer's just begun, I know this, and I can't get my hopes up.  Many more humid days lie ahead.  Excitement abounds, though, as we move to our new apartment in a couple of weeks.  It seems almost silly to be SO enthusiastic about it, when compared to life in Boston.  Silver Spring ain't no Beacon Hill.  But to be in the middle of things, activity, energy, public transportation, and coffee shops...well, it occurs to me that I'm very much a city girl.
      
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It startles me, really, that the memory is so close to the surface.  I am so good about moving on, and not sentimental, not in that way.  But every time I walk on campus, through the vast empty space in front of Memorial Chapel, where the marching band practices in late August, I notice the sky.  This is Maryland, and so there are almost always clouds, gathering for the usual 5:00 thunderstorm.  Sometimes, though, the sky over me is impossibly clear and pristine.  I enjoy it for a split second.  And then my stomach turns, and my mind says "I remember another day when the sky was so perfect and blue."  Of course I know what I mean without actually saying it - that day was 9/11.  We were all so shocked that a massive tragedy could happen on such a beautiful day, as if the juxtaposition was just too cruel to bear.  9/11 changed the very character of the sky.   That day, well, my story is not unique.  I went to work, blew off the inital reports as "some idiot in a Cessna," but understood the magnitude of it in time to see the second tower fall on live TV in the conference room.  In how many offices, how many conference rooms, did the very same scene play out?  We were all so quiet.  My life was in Boston at that time, and like most major cities, all of the tall buildings downtown were quickly evactuated.  My building, only six stories, was not among them.  And so I remember watching from Allison's corner cubicle, as the streets filled with commuters, how odd it was to see them all heading home at once, in the middle of the day.  Some other things stick with me, too.  We had a number of women on staff who lived in Cambridge.  They decided to walk home, as they were scared to take the T.  Another co-worker cried hysterically, worried about a friend who worked in the towers (thankfully, he turned out to be fine).  We did get dismissed early, but my boss didn't go home.  "I live right down the street in a high-rise, so why bother?" she remarked, "I'm no safer there than I am here."  She had a point.  I remember worrying about her.  I also remember showing little emotion.    What I do not remember is any blue sky in the months following 9/11, though no doubt there were some good days.  The whole world seemed to be surrounded by a sort of darkness.  This wasn't, admittedly, just because of 9/11.  I was experiencing a bit of personal tragedy, too.  The horrible end of my horrible marriage had finally come.    What hell it was!  My ex-husband is a frightening, demanding, abusive, unstable man.  I was so afraid, so angry, during those months.  Why did I squander my youth with him?  Why wouldn't he just let me go?  Why did I end up with a lifetime of regrets by the time I was 24?  What great sin was I paying for?  I still don't have the answer to those questions.  And I still don't really understand why 9/11 happened, still don't really understand what it means.  A few days after 9/11, life was pretty much back to normal in Boston, at least externally.  We went back to work.  They were constructing a new building across the street from my office.  It's finished now, it was ready right on time.  Anyway, the construction workers had draped a huge American flag over the steel girders, the skeleton of this new structure, and I could see it perfectly from Allison's window.  I spent a lot of time staring at it, and thinking.  Against the perpetually gray sky, I saw sparks shooting out around the flag.  They were welding, no doubt.  But it looked like so much more, so beautiful, these white shimmers of light, small but so bold, fighting the hopelessness inside me, and around the world.  Americans were still building then, and we are still building now.  And I personally kept going, despite my ex. If America could go on, I sure as hell could, too.  Today I am much happier.  I cannot say the same about my country, really.  It is a daily exercise now, especially here on a university campus, to defend the U.S.  That's heartbreaking, sometimes.    But more often than not, we have gray skies here in Maryland.  And I can still see the sparks, the hope, the flag, the building, as though it were yesterday.  I know that even if the sight of a perfect sky is marred forever, we will always have this.   
      
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      We made it back safely from Florida, but not without a little emotional trauma.  Oh, the trip itself was fine.  But the airplane that was to sprint us back to Maryland was experiencing mechanical problems.  Hardcore, six-guys-sticking-their-heads-in-the-engine-and-looking-confused kind of problems.  I'm quite frightened of flying, anyway, and this didn't help.  The gate announcements didn't help, either.  "We won't put you on this plane until we figure out what the hell is wrong with it."  Um, thanks?    Have you ever had a cold?  Have you ever thought you got rid of the cold, successfully defeated it with the only tools you have at hand (chicken soup, OJ, and Day-Quill)?  Have you then woken up the next morning feeling like a Human Phlegm Factory, realizing that not only had the cold not gone anywhere, the germs were just apparently regrouping for an even stronger attack?  Well, our plane had a cold and I was terrified of a mid-flight relapse.  Thankfully, the problem was so bad that they couldn't fix it in time for our flight, and they put us on another plane.  So my panic was mostly abated - at least I wasn't on a plane known to be ill.   There's another element to the problem.  We were flying on AirTran.  And as much as I value the low fares, I haven't been able to entirely forget that AirTran used to be ValuJet.  And a ValueJet plane crashed mightily to the ground because of shoddy maintainence practices, just a few years ago.  Sooooo...  Next time, it's Southwest all the way.  At least if they kill me, I'll have a little more leg room.  In other news, I spent the last class of university Summer Session I embroiled in a heated argument about the value of socialism.  The course was about the culture of post-USSR Russia, but this topic lends itself surprisingly well to "current event" type arguments.  Since Russia is now dealing with an identity crisis of sort, it was natural to discuss what is right about the free market, what was done wrong in the past, etc.  The professor also encouraged this sort of discussion.  A lot.  She seemed to really enjoy debates.  Thank God, she is sympathetic to capitalism (yes, Virginia, there is a university professor who believes in capitalism!) so it wasn't a horror show.  Still, though, the classroom can be a pretty harsh place for libertarian nutbags like me.  I'm hoping my next Summer course isn't quite so volitile!  All things considered, though, I'm glad I took this course.  The material was interesting, I learned a lot, and the professor was, overall, absolutely top-notch and amazing.  And not just because she is in favor of the free market, heh.  I'd never have expected it, for all the criticism I throw at Maryland and its environs, but my educational experience here has been surprisingly positive.  There are a lot of great professors at this school.  It is hard, even with all my years of taking college courses and all my natural snarkiness, to feel anything but proud that I'll end up graduating from here.  Go figure.
      
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've got nothing so interesting as a picture of Okie, today.  Though I am seeing the new Spider Man movie this evening.  That will be a fun diversion from the ordinary.  Well, unless one counts seeing movies as ordinary.  Which I guess it is.  Don't I just know how to suck the fun right out of everything!  And then tomorrow, the work week ends at last!, and Lor and I head to Florida for a whirlwind weekend.  We'll be in  urlLink Celebration , the town created by Disney, paying loved ones a visit.  I dread the flight but look forward to the fireworks.  You take what you can get in this world, and certainly Disney Town will know how to light up the sky.  The heat down there will be brutal.  Thinking about it reminds me of good things, though.  The heat always ends, and Fall always comes.  The time of new beginnings, and air that isn't pea-soup thick with humidity.  Often Fall is ubearably tardy, and it's always too short.  But the best thing about the summer is knowing that just around the corner are crisp afternoons, falling leaves, and pumpkins.    Frequently, I flip the calendar pages ahead a few months and glance at the picture they have for October.  It doesn't matter what kind of calendar it actually is - somehow October always involves orange colors and cool skies.  Even, really, this one calendar I had as a teenager, which was entirely about cows.  The October cow had an orange border, and there were leaves on the ground by her feet.  Because of that calendar, I still think of August as "Au-cud-gust," incidentally.
      
</post>


</Blog>