<Blog>

<date>30,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
      k..so today i woke up quite late..arnd 6.40.."studied" till quite late last night. hehe. i was looking outta my window, staring at the expressway. went to school, got caught for not tucking in my shirt..pls l0r, can't blame me, i was too engrossed in my notes. anyway, yup had 2 papers today. chem n chinese. i'm so dead for ch3m. stupid teachers threw in so many red0x questions. lololol. n the questions kept asking for oxidation numbers? dammit la. din know how to do. so left most of em blank. maybe except for the (no. of moles of xxx chemical = mass/mr) part. perhaps i could get 1 or 2 markz. lol. HAHAHA. at least i think i can get 10 full marks for last ques. cos its all on atomic structure. hurhur. my fav topic~ :D the rest fail liao la.  yeah, then had break which was supposed to be 1hr 15 mins, but ended up being 30 mins. wth. ate lor mai kai n some shit curry potato bread. then chiong to hall for chinese. HAHAHA. chinese was surprisingly easy~ with the exception of the compre tho. damn philosophical. shud be able to do well la. but the whole thing was  PURE  torture. the chair was like shit, so hard, really strained my back. and there was some idiot tapping the floor. damn irritating. felt like juz telling him to farking hell stop it or i'll grind my pencil thru his damned shoe. hurhur. nonetheless, i finished my paper in 2 hrs, spent the last one sleeping. :) couldn't really sleep also, damn stuffy. lousy hall.  yeah, after both papers, went to l0t1 to meet alv(angry m4n) n jy. ;) sat down in mac for a while, then went to buy a billab0ng shirt. kaoz..damn small. XL lor.  shit. then alv bought this quite c00l sleeveless billab0ng shirt. @%^^$&& oh well, i think i'll buy the nike one. hehhe. yeah..then went home, changed and went to l0t1 again. to study econs with alv n eileen. st0ned in macs for god knows how long, then eileen left and alv said "aiya fuck la, i dun feel like studying liaoz". so i said "okay" and we both went to the arcade. he played drums, then we played virtual cop 3. lol. damn c00l. :D then went home. argh, damn tired. tmr paper at 12. heng arh. but i'm not sure if i've gotta go for the flag raising. sighz. well, tmr will be a better day! :)
     

        
</post>

<date>29,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
      damn it la. stupid mum naggin her guts off. if she was a mat i would haf slapped her l0h. call me an infidel. i am one. well, so much for her..i'm gonna go offline now. try to study for STUPID exams. fuck em all. make my day.
     

        
</post>

<date>28,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
      damn it la. stupid mum naggin her guts off. if she was a mat i would haf slapped her l0h. call me an infidel. i am one. well, so much for her..i'm gonna go offline now. try to study for STUPID exams. fuck em all.
     

        
</post>

<date>28,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
        urlLink       urlLink   A GOLD Dragon Lies Beneath!    I took the  urlLink Inner Dragon online quiz  and found out I am a Gold Dragon on the inside. My Inner Dragon is the most honorable of all. Golds are the third rarest of all the dragons (after Platinum and Chromatic dragons) and have a station in society that reflects their rarity. I am what one might call a Draconic Knight. Golds live by a strict code of chivalry and commitment. Remember Draco? Yep, Gold Dragon. My appearance is fearsome and all-mighty but I'd never stoop so low as to bring any harm to a human. I'm one of only two dragon types that are aligned "Lawful Good" and demonstrate great magical proficiency. My piety, beauty, wisdom, and inner strengrth are absolutely without parallel.    Of course, being a Gold  Dragon isn't all high ethics and codes. I like to fly around scaring things, advise humans in their affairs, and shapeshift. Strike that, I  LOVE  to shapeshift. And I'm great at it. In fact, who's to say I'm not really a Gold Dragon after all? My favorable attributes are honor, truth, kindness, gold, wisdom, bravery, and trustworthiness. If anyone threatens or tries to kill me, I could strike back with my breath weapon - Fire. But then, no one's tried anything that stupid in the last couple thousand years. After all, I'm about 54 feet long.   
     

        
</post>

<date>28,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
      i'm really kinda depressed now. sometimes, even if both sides like each other, it might not even work out at all. guess i'll just have to move on then. hmm i think i shall just immerse myself in work n training. afterall, i'm aiming to be capt of pjc's canoeing team. :) yupz, no girls for the time being. 
     

        
</post>

<date>28,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
        You are Agent Smith, from "The Matrix." No one would ever want to run into you in a dark alley. Cold as steel, tough as a rock, things are your way or the highway.    urlLink   What Matrix Persona Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    haha..so much for all those quizzes. juz woke up, couldn't find anything nice on tv. so that's why i'm doing all those stuff. :D hmm, people who wake up as early as me on weekends are rare, don't u think? lolol. oh well, gotta log off soon..parents gonna come back frm market soon. heh.
     

        
</post>

<date>28,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
        Playful    urlLink   What's your sexual appeal?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      Glock17. Everyone loves you. G-Dawgs and Cops alike fancy you. Aren't you just special?    urlLink   What handgun are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     

        
</post>

<date>28,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink     What Finding Nemo Character are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    ooh. nemo~! :D     You are Peace.  You are at peace with your self and the world around you.  You have balance in your life and exude tranquility from every pore of your body. People are constantly asking you "what is your secret?"    urlLink   What Emotion Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     

        
</post>

<date>28,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
        Yellows are the most fun-loving, free-spirited, energetic, and childlike personalities in the aura spectrum. Yellows are wonderful, sensitive, optimistic beings, whose life purpose is to bring joy to people, to have fun, and to help heal the planet.    urlLink   What Is Your True Aura Colour?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     

        
</post>

<date>28,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
        You're the loving smile,the one that is entirely devoted to others,especially that one person.You really can't get them out of your head,but then,you don't really want to.    urlLink   What Kind of Smile are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    lol. quite true. :) one last one.~    You have an entrancing kiss~ the kind that leaves your partner bedazzled and maybe even feeling he/she is dreaming.  Quite effective; the kiss that never lessens and always blows your partner away like the first time.    urlLink   What kind of kiss are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    lolololol. :D 
     

        
</post>

<date>28,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
        Your Heart is Blue    urlLink   What Color is Your Heart?      brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      -Sensitive- You're Sensitive, and you'd like to stay that way. Sorry,listened to a bit too much Jewel there. You're sweet and very emotionally charged. You definitely love the person you're with, and always want to know how they're feeling so you can make sure they're happy.    urlLink   What Kind of Girlfriend Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    HAHa, don't blame me. i love taking this kinda quizzes :D
     

        
</post>

<date>28,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
             jinyu      Magic Number    19      Job    Sporting Great      Personality    The Glass Is Half-Empty      Temperament    What You Lookin' At?      Sexual    If I Have To      Likely To Win    Another Gold Star      Me - In A Word    Startling      Colour        urlLink Brought to you by MemeJack                      urlLink  What  kind of clothes should I be wearing?    by  urlLink Evelyn  
</post>

<date>28,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Have you ever had a feeling that such that all u wanted to do was just to love a person wholeheartedly? such a simple thing, yet sprouts so many problems. from my own point of view, me being nice to someone doesn't mean i want her to give me back anything, afterall, love IS sacrifice. yupz..frankly speaking,  i tried giving her up. maybe cos of advice frm other pple? i don't know. yet i can't. i know i'm the sentimental type. some people say its a blessing, i think its a curse. sighz, other guys just forget and move on. and they find better people. i wish i could do that easily though.. 
     

        
</post>

<date>28,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
      yupz. so now i'm kinda blog illiterate. don't mind those lousy links and that crap advert. lazy to get rid of em. heh. hmm, listening to Gareth Gates - Too serious too soon now. damn nice. my type of song. ;) 
     

        
</post>

<date>28,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
      yeah my first blog. blogs are stupid. didn't know why i created one anyway. oh well, inspiration frm allah i suppose. exams are round the corner, and here i am sitting in my lousy chair typing away. guess i'm used to all this failing stuff. hey, 4 yrs of doing nothing can really change a person. =) afterall, pjc is what i'm in now. can't do anything abt it. sighz. dun feel like doin anything now
     

        
</post>

<date>30,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      had my dinner..juz got home frm cck stadium..where i went to buy camping stuff. feelin really tired now..but i've not even packed my stuff for tmr's ltc yet..:\ saw a lotta nice nice stuff today...but kinda lazy to type it all out..hmm, niwae..i'll not be bloggin for the nex 5 days..cos i'll be away at camp..but i'll be bringing my hp, so feel free to call or msg ya? :) esp when i'm on solo night, i would really love to talk to someone..hahaha..yup..oh well..byebye bloggie. :)
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      heh..juz returned frm training..:) all i've got to say is.. "ShIOk AhHh" lol..today was weights training day..so ya..all the gym stuff lor..but b4 that our warmup was 4 rounds arnd the outer track. then stretch..then ya..on to weights.. Did six stations, 3 sets of fifteen each. hmm..lets see.. 1. Benchpress 2. Bicep Curl 3. Squats using the benchpress machine 4. Diamond Back 5 & 6.. ?! duno la..juz do..heh. ya..then 90 crunches..all that usual stuff..heh. isn't canoeing fun? :D whee..but so sad..tmr canot go trng..gotta go shopping for my LTC stuff..argh!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! stress lar..must buy what camera..broomstick..all that shit..5 days of suffering..damn it. :\ nvm la..i think i shall bring a few cartons of milk to the camp..then drink all on the same day..HAHAHA. i juz finished one litre of i-cal again..shit..this sounds like drugs l0h..ahha..ya..like those people who got caught for smoking outta college..i think that's quite dumb lor...of all the places..they had to smoke nearby..ahhah..serves them right..actually i'm not suprised..hmm..nvm..racist stuff.. anyway, juz wanna say..angie u stupid girl, u hit me so many times for nutz! i din even do anything lor! what nonsense la..and my class is seriously traumatising me..dunno wtf ben said my body damn hard la..blah blah..then everyone come touch me..wth. SIAM LAR U ALL BODY TOUCHERS. OR I"LL SUE UR ASSES OFF FOR MOLESTATION. hehe..eh..i'm thinking of forming a new club in sch..its called the F.T.G. (Fraternity of Traumatised Guys). yup, strictly for guys only..no girls allowed. Every meeting sure got CIP hours. Then every wed meet at one table..then got sharing session..where one by one the guys share their traumatising moments..ya..then end of the month got prizes one..like "Best Traumatising Experience" And "Best Traumatisee"..cos since got traumatiser then must have traumatisee rite? it all makes sense..yup..my brain's cracking up..everything i say is outta point.. tEEhEheeEhHEhehEhEHhEhHEhEhHEhehHEEtEEhEHHEhE. k. 
     

        
</post>

<date>28,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      k..kidding..ahha..
     

        
</post>

<date>27,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      oh ya..juz one thing i wanna add..eh why am i like the last link on everyone's blog?! sweet mother of mary man..lolz. :)
     

        
</post>

<date>27,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      my fingers are trembling even as i'm typing now...haha..had training juz now..and boy oh boy was it shiok man. Did circuit, pull ups, and one hell lotta crunches...haha..whole body feels damn good now..cos i can't feel anything. :) what's   VBALL   compared to canoeing man. heheheh. :P kidding..at least vball has quite good team spirit..of cos la..since inside there got so many scandalZzZ..lol..yup..and to add on to my numb body, i fell in the toilet juz now..i suppose its due to my trembling legs..ahha.. hmm. speaking of falling down..i have a riddle..which animals keeps on falling down?  Ans: a f0x. cos its "jiao3 hua2" ahha meaning sly! :D slippery legs! woo! anyway, that's besides the point..haha..i fell on my butt..but like got no feelin liddat..cos numb..kewl~ :D muhAhAH..yup, and i had 2 litres of milk for dinner. 1 litre NUtriSOy..and 1 litre I-cal..hEHhE..hOH sEh lAz. milK R0X. :) yup..and i saw hockey galz jamie and eugenia running on the track..so hoh seh..so hard working..but how come only 2 girls? so weird..must be some sorta secret training..heh.  k la..today i was kinda in a bad mood..cos i was having a really bad headache..largely due to not drinking water..so that's why i was kinda anti-social...eh sorry ah angie..no hard feelings? :) hahah..hmm..i had a really nice story..last time i was like that..some sec 1 guy came n pissed the living hells outta me..so ya..u know what happened..he went home crying..aiya..not that i'm mean la..but i have my limits too ya? blame himself for being irritable. heh. yupz, sorry guys :) k la..my fingers are trembling till cannot tremble liao..shall go sleep now..:) nitezZ
     

        
</post>

<date>27,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      asd
     

        
</post>

<date>26,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      a
     

        
</post>

<date>26,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      ad
     

        
</post>

<date>26,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
        Your Flower Color Is Yellow, Your Filled With Joy, Care, And Love.    urlLink   What Color Flower  Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    oh bright and cheery me~ :) had another really borin day..lol. watchin bean now. woo~ juz love him man! hAhAHa
     

        
</post>

<date>26,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      wooo~ today has been a really how should i say...Good day? heh. all i did was use the comp, n watch tv. yup, i went on a slackathon. :) then in the evening i went to watch t3. ahhaha..i've got nothing to say..but juz give 2 thumbs up for the REALLY REALLY cool explosions :D alotta pple said t3 sucks..but i dun really agree..k la..maybe for the last part..the 2 heroes juz end up in some underground bunker. bah. so much for some finale explosion i was expecting. oh well, there was a part which i found funny. this part where Arnie said " You cannot self- terminate." hahaha, k fine..but it tickles my funny bone. :) yupz, and i found the T-X model damn nice. with all the metallic stuff and blue lights. woo whee~ i think i shall go buy one and put in my room~ then i can stare it everyday! but sadly..there's a hole in my pocket..cos i bought this new adidas climalite shirt which costed 40 bucks. oh well, i'm an impulse buyer! hehehe. i dun mind eating one-tonne mee for the rest of the week. :D hmm..jiahui's having trouble with her blog..gotta help her..maybe blog later. 
     

        
</post>

<date>25,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      oh yea..and juz b4 i turn in, i juz wanna announce that Alvyn Cheong Wei Hao is afraid of   MICE  . HWHAHAHAH. :D cos my dad saw him run away at the sight of a teeny weeny lil rodent~ lolololol. gotcha there alv~ tEEheE. :P
     

        
</post>

<date>24,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      lol. juz helped jiahui get rid of her ugly "your title" thingy. oh well, gotta sleep now..mum's naggin..heh :)
     

        
</post>

<date>24,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      nothing much to say these days..guess nothing special really happened in my life. sighz, sometimes i just wish that life was a lil bit different. sometimes i juz wish that i could be in part of a video game..
     

        
</post>

<date>24,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      dammit. i juz realised that that pic can't show on other comps cos i din upload it. darn darn darn. nvm. i go get one t3 pic. :)
     

        
</post>

<date>24,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      hahaha..i made that pic myself. any comments? :)
     

        
</post>

<date>24,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
        You represent... playfulness. Playfulness can often be mistaken for sluttiness or flirtiness... Flirting is something you enjoy doing, but you're mostly just about having fun. You're into partying, and it's seems that people enjoy your company as much as you enjoy their's.    urlLink   What feeling do you represent?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    hahah..i think that really suits me! :D well, at least its better than being angsty! tEehEe.
     

        
</post>

<date>24,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Eh pple, tmr pon sch go support pjc canoeing ya? :D
     

        
</post>

<date>23,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Read below. =)
     

        
</post>

<date>23,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      just returned frm the comp as red as a lobster. damn tired. shall go sleep now.
     

        
</post>

<date>22,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Alright! Revamped my entire blog! Added Commentaries and TagBoard. Yupzz...must write stuff in it ah! :) hahah..feelin quite happy now juz lookin at my blog. so nice!  fine..enough of all my crap. well, on to my day!  I attended some Senior Civil Servant Talk..which was quite okay la..the Brigadier General was quite a good speaker..but the last part of his talk was the best! Cause he showed us some really funny and cute pictures of animals..yup..but it wasn't that funny in the end. Cos he took up our recess time. lol.  Ya..then went for chem prac..on Chemical Kinetics..woah..never been so shiok...got timing to keep one..haha..then in the end i poured all the chemicals into the sink..kinda like making rojak..haha..then din know they reacted to produce some gas which made me tear. lolx! mmm..then the rest of the day went by quite okay..quite irritated during maths..cos i was having a headache..really hot weather i guess. Yupz, so i've gotta drink more water! :D  Ya..then wasted 1 and a half hours sleeping in the Lt when i'm supposed to be listening to PW stuff. heh. Afterthat...angie and I went to bukit panjang plaza..on the way met Hong yi, so asked him to join us. went to macs to have SHAKER FRIESSSS!! woo! then talk nonsense, eg. scandals, gossips..blah blah. heh. both of em were kinda blackmailing each other with their own scandals, so i juz sat back and listened. :) free show. nothing they can do to me anyway..hahah..i've got no scandals! i'm a very faithful boy. :D hehehe..yupz..then went home to have my dinner. sian..tmr still gotta wake up early..gotta be at kallang at 7.30am lo..meeting teammates at 6.30 at clementi..which means i gotta wake up at 5!! omg! .. -.- k..shan't whine.. 
     

        
</post>

<date>21,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      juz added comments part
     

        
</post>

<date>21,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      hoh seh la..i juz love matrix stuff :)
     

        
</post>

<date>21,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      asd
     

        
</post>

<date>20,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      tryin to get tagboard to work 
     

        
</post>

<date>20,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      asdasdasd
     

        
</post>

<date>20,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      asd
     

        
</post>

<date>20,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Hmm. Today was a REALLY lousy day, and i Dun wanna comment about it.  Anyway, Angela shared a few racist jokes which i din even know she knew. hurhur. okay here goes  Racist Joke #1 What do u call a Westerner wearing a mask?  A Knight.  What do u call a Chinese wearing a mask?  A Warrior.  What do u call a Japanese wearing a mask?  A Samurai.  So...What do u call an INDIAN wearing a mask?    A   GRASSCUTTER         Racist Joke #2  Why shouldn't u let INDianS take corners?   Cos they'll set up a MAMAST0re there.  That's all. MOre to come. COurtesy of angela toy. :)
     

        
</post>

<date>17,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Have u ever felt that at one point in your life, all you wanted was to spend quality time with ur loved one? Just holding hands, and just walking slowly down a long long stretch of road..there's no need for any talking..for both sides already understand each other? Right now, if i could have one wish..I would just wish to walk with her down a never ending stretch of road..quiet, yet serenaded by the sound of crickets chirping. Simple isn't it? Yet it isn't so easy. Sometimes, simple things are the hardest to come by. I don't know how to make you trust me..I've tried to shun her, leave her alone and not talk to her. But yet..i can still see that u're uncomfortable. I really don't know how. You know what kinda person i am, and i mean EVEN IF i like someone, i'e always put faithfulness above like. And you know that. I really miss you, i really do.
     

        
</post>

<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Today, i saw a horse shoe crab. OMG!  Please Refer to http://www.assateague.com/horsesho.html ooo..aren't they cute? :)
     

        
</post>

<date>15,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      okay. all i can say now is one word. "sian". today was a damn sian day, with sian lessons, sian breaks, sian recesses, sian pple, sian after sch activities. just one of my typical days in PJC. hehe. pjc juz r0x l0..nothing to say..  yeah..d/ling t3: rise of the machines now. broadband juz rox..ahha..can juz d/l n d/l. so song. darn..really tired now..argh..zzz.
     

        
</post>

<date>14,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      hahaa..k..juz finished doing the pw surveys. okay. for the mid yrs, i got   Quadraple   Fs and 2 Bs. B for GP and Chinese. HAHAH. i rawk. tEeHee. aiya..sianz..meet parents liao l0r..yeah..that's all...but i'm juz afraid it'll affect the teacher's decision to put me as capt..sighz..then today also late for sch..wtf lor..   oh well, kanasai day. but yeah..its time i studied la..been playin for like god knows how long..yup..i've gotta STUDY STUDY STUDY. i'll show those low down "PJC CANNOT MAKE IT MUGGERS" THE TRUE POWER OF THE CHINESE HIGH. WHHAHAHA> AFETR ALL I DIDN"T GET INSIDE FOR NUTZ> I DIN PAY MY FRIGGIN WAY IN. HELL YEAH> I"M GONNA RAWK PJC TO DA CORE. Mark my words. :) hoh seh la.
     

        
</post>

<date>13,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      hmm. i'm happy today. :) don't know why. but i juz feel happy. lol. doing my gp work now. Its about " Crime And Punishment ". Don't know what to write..but wrote crap..juz for the sake of doing. At least my teacher wun have any excuse to say that i din make and effort to do her work. yupz..and i still have maths..trigo..urgh..sucks. i'm dling "findin Nemo" now. lol. such a cute show! haha..my mum actually subscribed to the lousy jetpack plan. supposed to be 19.90 for 250 mb only..but i d/led like over 2gig of stuff. hurhur. so she got pissed and changed the plan to unlimited. so now i can d/l n d/l~! :D woooo  i've come to realise that i still like her. yupz.. altho i pretend that i do not in front of her, i still do..deep down inside. oh well, its a good thing i suppose. afterall, there's no point brooding over "she likes me, she likes me not"..haha..i believe she does. and that's my p.o.f. don't know if she still does tho..if u're readin this, do u? haha..kinda dumb..but ya..afterall this is a blog. my blog. all my thots are supposed to be in it~ mmm..gotta do work now..maybe blog later 
     

        
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      juz woke up.. ZzZ..fingers to tired to type..haven't had bf yet..bah..blog later.
     

        
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      hmm, okay. juz watched "Final Descent". not bad..its a show abt mountain climbers involved in some money laundering. plot is quite nice. nice scenery and all. but most of all, it juz potrays man's greed. :)   i'm wearing my pjc canoeing jersey now. eh..not exactly jersey la..the singlet. hahaha..its black n its damn comfortable~ so darn cool. better than waga also. hurhur.   boring day. bah. still got maths hw to do. i'll do it tmr la..sianz. maths sarkz. yupz..i'm so looking forward to ltc man. shud be one helluva experience. :)  
     

        
</post>

<date>10,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      today was such a wasted day...had chinese A level listening compre in the morning..kinda easy..piece of cake really..heh. :) my chinese is juz too good la..i flunked the whole mid yrs except for my GP n chinese. hurhur. this goes to show that my lang. is juz too pro liaoz. yar..then after that the weather was practically shit. raining cats and dogs..so couldn't go anywhere. stayed in sch to r0t lor..  stoned and stoned...then went to library to accompany nancy. read a book entitled "7 habits of Effective Teens" 2 words. bullshit. really l0r..haha..then went for lunch at kopitiam. ate chicken rice..cos it was not bad..then went back to sch for LTC briefing.  Dammit lor. i thought the briefing would only be a while..didn't know it would last for 5 hrs. fark. wasted my whole day going thru so much useless shit.. argh...then summore i was cold, hungry and miserable..pure torture.   went home, bathed, watched cartoon, ate. the end. will blog later. damn sian now.
     

        
</post>

<date>10,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      ....... today was quite an okay day la...nothing much happening. sianz..juz had my dinner..feel damn sleepy..yawnz..  anyway, i had Pe for first period today..got orientation. yup, ORIENTATION. dunno for what fark. all we had to do was run arnd the whole sch, looking for checkpoints. total of 12. then some pple damn knn lor..i found the damned clue, and then they juz come n leech. Conversation as follows.  Me : "eh guys i found the clue liaoz, its over here"  Gary : "wah eh pple they found the clue! lets go see!"  Me : *frowns*  damn lame l0r..blooder leechers. then when they got the clue, some guy called kee chern ran like a fag lor. cos he saw angela running also, then he did some martial arts move, more commonly known as Qing Gong. wah, then run damn fast, even faster then angie, altho she was a sprinter. so pro siaz..nex time can take part in olympics.  oh well, ya then i was damn pissed off. cos of idiots like that in my class. but nvm la..at least the pe teacher was nice. he was a njc canoeist, which means that he'll be the new teacher in charge of canoeing too. that makes 4 teachers now. i juz like his face, cos he has these really small eyes, which make him look shy..aww.. i think i'll go make friends with him, then can slack durin pe. hehehe...anyway he let us off early so after pe was recess, i went to buy chicken rice. then i left it on the table, and went to talk to classmates. then my seniors shouted something which sounded like " fish! got bird eatin ur rice!" .. so i turned and saw the DAMNED bird pecking at a piece of chicken on my rice. dammit. then the auntie who was cleaning tables came and scolded me...i think cos she thot i fed the bird or sumthin. basket. who would wanna feed a bloody mynah.   then the rest of the day was quite okay la..getting back results n stuff..of which i failed like every subj. dun ask me why..i juz failed..cos i din touch my notes? gaahaha..i think i'm still sleeping..lol..and i'm lazy to wake up..sighz.  yeah then after sch hung out at bpp with angie and ben. went to kfc to eat the snack pack thingy. but they din have banditto. only had what crispy strips. so i bought that. not bad la..juz that its the extended version of popcorn chicken. oh ya, i realised popcorn chicken goes damn well with cheese too. :) ya..then walked arnd. then went home. basically i juz haf no life.   oh well, something good happened today tho. Me and 3 other pple frm the canoeing team got nominated for LTC ( leadership trng course). heheh..damn excited..lookin forward to it..:D cos dun hafta go to sch~! and the programmes seem quite nice too..got 20km land ex, half day kayaking, abseiling, all the usual OBS stuff. but ya..i'm looking forward to meetin new pple. i sure hope they're normal..i mean..they have to be..or they wun be future capts ya? hurhur..yeah..hope got chiobu also... :P  sometimes you tell urself u've found the perfect girl, and u're over the moon. then after a while, both sides break up, and u realise that the girl which u've been lookin for has always been before ur very eyes. someone which u'll commit to, and share ur life with.   isn't it funny, that we, being humans, always go for things which we will never get, or which other pple might not approve of? is it the thrill, the challenge, or the feeling of rebelliousness? whatever pple tell us not to do, we do it. why? lol. how funny. one word of advice : always cherish the people arnd u, for u might one day fall in love with em. :)
     

        
</post>

<date>09,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Okay..yesterday was my first attempt at trying to write a racist blog which was compatible with jj's. haha..so far i've received negative comments..so ya..i'll stop. or at least try my best la..hehe. today was quite a short day..cos of ccas..yupz..so i'll elaborate on different periods of the day.   first period was chinese..generally okay la..new teacher and all, but she's quite nice. she juz came back frm maternity leave..so i guess she must be feelin kinda motherly now..yupz, maybe that's why she's so nice. anyway, she made us practise for mungen oral..read passages, blah blah n stuff..quite sianz..  then later on to chem lect..got back our papers..i got lousy marks. dammit l0r..but kinda expected it anyway..can't really get good marks if u dun study rite? so ya..can't blame anyone but myself. sat there n sulked. hehe. :P angela did quite well tho..really envious. :) ya..then i felt damn sleepy..so after that i went to the classroom to take a nap..ZzzZ.  after that was Gp. the new teacher was Steph Chua. she made us do some lousy mind mapping shit..on which i wrote lotsa racist crap..  ya..then had chem tutorial. then went for trng..  aiyar..dun feel like bloggin today..sianz. damn tired. juz came back frm trng.  eh want funny laughs? go to this blog. mamast0re.blogspot.com .. bet u'll laugh ur balls off..even if u don't have any. h0h seh la. my life r0x0rz. Does yours?  
     

        
</post>

<date>08,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      CHINESE > INDiAN > MAlaY   hoH sEh lA jJ. u Da mAn, mAn. loLZ.
     

        
</post>

<date>04,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      ...wah lao..i damn long nv blog..cos busy during these few days. knn. spent my time selling drinks to mat kids. The whole "diva la futbol" was like some underground mat n butch meeting ground l0hz..dammit man..talking abt bucthes, i juz feel like slapping em l0r. bu4 nan2 bu4 nu3. what the hell. dun even know if they're guy or girl. screw em la. so ugly. posers. i think matS are still better poSers lor..even tho they both sark. but nvm la. got 84 hrs of cip juz by selling drinks at 1 dollar per can. h0h seh lar dun hafta do anymore shitty cip.  hAhEz..today r0x lor. timetable changed like no one's business. got new maths n physics teacher. hurhur. physics teacher looks damn tan lor. then durin lecture always flex her arm, like some bodybuilder liddat. damn scary siaz. even tho she's those kind of pple whom even xu en can whack. lol. got even more hoh seh stuff l0rz. our maths teacher got moustache one man! so HIP SIA. SO MAcHO. makes me swoon. hAhAre. her voice also damn manly..like those hIpStEr mAt RAppEr liDdAt. cannot make it.   yA..then after sch..went delifrance..wanted to go GelArE..kaoz..go there that time, then realise no more ice cream. really l0r. who wants to eat cream..looks like shit l0r. i wont pay 5 bucks for juz maple syrup and lousy whipped cream slapped on some lousy "AUTHENTIC BELGIUM WAFFLE". rEAllY lor..more liKe BouGht frm Cold Storage one...butthen made in BelGium. STill The sAme what. tRiCkstErS sia..must be some underground mat org. raising funds for the war effort. wah not bad..at last some not bad idea. but they're still stupid la..remove ice cream for what..ya anyway, went to delifrance to eat kentang. wah lao..seriously sucks bad lorz..at first still quite okay..then later wanna puke. yucks lar..left half the potato there.   hAh...then later went home..saw some mat skAtErzZ at the void deck tryin to SkAte ArnD..wah DAmn pRo..likE Tony hAwk'S tWin liDdat. cAn Do bAckFlipS And StuFf..So HIP SIA..h0h SeH La..i Think tmr i go join em..oh ya..but i dun have c00l skates..how? nvm l0r. go steal tmr.   juZ hAd mY DinnEr. GonnA SlAck mY niGhT AwAy. liFe R0X. HoH SEh lArZ.  
     

        
</post>

<date>04,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      wAhz. today was a damn tiring day..started off by going to town to meet angela..we then had lunch at scotts there, the underground kopitiam. dunno what's it called. hehe, then as usual i had kuay chap. i juz love it! got pig intestine, fish cake, salted vege..and the chilli was damn nice too. hahah, yeah, then went to ps to watch movie with angela. wanted to watch Twins Effect one..but then when we got there, only the first 3 rows were available. so din watch. watched dumb and dumberer in the end. HAHAHA. damn DUMB. hmm, my verdict is, u'll enjoy it more with a grp of friends, nv with a girl/guy. ahhaa..cos its kinda corny..lotsa sexual jokes also. yupz, so we luffed n luffed. then met jamie n some other girl after that. had to buy carnival stuff. THIS is the worst part of my day. I'll list out where we went.  Ps ---> Tanglin Mall ---> Forum ---> Lucky PLaza ---> Far East PLaza ---> Taka ---> Youth park. THE WHOLE TIME IT WAS FREAKIN RAINING. BASKET. spent arnd like 30 mins walking arnd, searching for stuff like fabric paint, darts, ribbons, etc. then hurried down to youthpark to pass the stuff to the gal in charge. she passed us the t-shirts that we were supposed to wear tmr. ITS RED, with girly shit stuff on it. dammit la. really makes us look like fags. oh well, at least pple will see me wearing a different colour. which is a really really rare sight, cos i always wear white. hahaha. yeahz. gotta go liaoz. tmr hafta wake up at 5.30. knn. EH THOSE PPLE READIN THIS, GO YOUTH PARK TMR N SUNDAY TO SUPPORT K? :D nitezZ
     

        
</post>

<date>03,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      damn..i was playing with jiahui minesweeper flags. and I LOST 4 TIMES IN A ROW! ARGHhGHgHGhGh..she won BY PURE LUCK. SO LUCKY LOR. NO SKILL AT ALL! LOUSY! I'll TRASH u nEX TIME.. GrRrRR. :P:p;P;P
     

        
</post>

<date>03,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      hahah..woke up at eight today! one of the latest times i ever woke up. lol. yes LATEST. :D i brushed my teeth, emptied listerine into my mouth, cried, then spitted it out. AHahha, ever thot of using the listerine bottle as ur water bottle? it'll look really really neat! LOL. i was really hungry, but much to my chagrin, THERE WAS NO FOOD! Allah didn't bless me with food today, maybe cos i had pork chop for dinner yesterday. :P so i had to wait till lunch time. sighz. hahahAH, angela juz called me. said she couldn't print the stars out. HAHAHA, really l0rz..they were supposed to get it done by yesterday. lousy logistics. :) yupz. so i'm talking to jiahui on msn now. suprisingly she woke up real early today~ maybe cos she knew i was online. hehehe. sighz, got a long day ahead of me..gotta go town n do this and do that. all i wanna do right now is sit in front of my comp and play games! bahz..exams over already n yet i still feel so sian. someone cheer me up by treating me to a movie ya? :D anyway, gotta meet alv in the afternoon to go town together. that lucky guy got a date. i'm jealous. :P buy balls, i think mine will drop off first. SIAN LAR. hahaha, anyway, to pple taking the oral today, all the best to u guys! Mao Zedong Wan4 Shui4~! :D
     

        
</post>

<date>03,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      its been a few days since i last blogged..was busy with exams n stuff. and also had to put up with my mum terminating my pacific net pdu account. so now i'm using singnet. damn. so lets take a step back, and see how i "think" i did for my mid yrs. 20% of promos. hurhur.  Gp - Quite confident. spammed 5 pages of politically correct english. :D  Chinese "AO" - don't ask me why i'm takin this. I failed my higher chinese b-e-a-utifully with a D7. :P hmm, quite okay la..except for compo.  Economics - Quite bad. Mcq was okay. but essay part was like shit. didn't even know what i was writing. questions were dead easy, but i didn't study. my fault.   Chemistry - one hell l0t of red0x. REALLY lucky if i can pass.  Physics - shud be able to pass la. one hell lot of dynamics questions tho. fark.   Maths C - Don't even ASK. :)  Muahaha. that's all. i think outta the 20% i get 5 percent i'm happy enough. heh.   yeah, so today the exams ended. went out to town with angela, went to get liz's prezzie, then walked around for a while, then met jamie at Hmv. jamie suggested to take neoprint. so we went up to take. kaoz..damn hungry lorz..so i was like half sulking..haha..the pictures turned out good tho, jamie had a boogie on her nose n mouth, made her look like a doggie. :D hAHah, laughed my balls off. yupz, then walked to cine to have my meal. jamie wanted to eat bk. yucks. hate bk. :\ but nvm. lol. gotta give her face. heh. yeah then after eating, felt really bad. cos i spent 25 bucks already. shit larz. no money. a lotta pple still owe me money lorz. knn. nvm. then went to walk walk. angela n jamie kept goin to those "girl" shops to look at stuff. so all i could do was follow. wah lanz, they kept on looking at bikinis n stuff. wth could i do. try em on? so i stoned down there. pretending to be interested. :p lololol. then went home l0rz..190 was farking crammed. stand until leg cram. ya..then reached home, had dinner, bathed, n now i'm sitting down in front of my com blogging. :) 
     

        
</post>

<date>12,August,2003</date>
<post>


           
      BLASTED VIRUS IS SCREWING UP MY BLOODY COMP. ARGH. DAMN THE PERSON WHO CREATED THAT PIECE OF SHIT. BLOODY SLAVE OF ALLAH, DOG OF OSAMA. ROT IN HELL. @#^#&$@@!#$~#~
     

        
</post>

<date>10,August,2003</date>
<post>


           
      oh yeah, btw..the pics are at jiahui's site. go check em out ya? :)
     

        
</post>

<date>06,August,2003</date>
<post>


           
      juz finished my gp essay. 564 words. damn. that's too lil. gotta write more nex time..dunno why la..but feeling kinda sleepy..*yawn* haha..i'm looking forward to nex wk man. i've got like 3 tests...of which i've studied for none. MOst people will say " then go study now! watcha doin online? " i would tell em, " screw all those tests ". goddamit. i'm sick of studying, esp if u study in a class with no life. i mean like u need motivation to study rite? and where else do u get it but frm ur class? my whole class is as dead as a dead fish. wth. NO BLOODY LIFE. the only life i can find is durin canoeing trng.. yeah. dunno la..somehow i lost my competitiveness which i had since pri sch. my life in tchs n pjc is  full of shiit  . lalalla.amazing life i've got. wanna be a statue? come to pj! kthnxbey.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,August,2003</date>
<post>


           
      oooooo...sentosa pics are uploaded. go check em out. :)
     

        
</post>

<date>06,August,2003</date>
<post>


           
      eh..i juz changed my blog layout. comments anyone? practical ones please. i don't want comments like "eee..i dun like ur picture.." or "eee..so fugly..".
     

        
</post>

<date>06,August,2003</date>
<post>


           
      came back frm sentosa yesterday. gotta say that i was quite disappointed at first..cos i seriously hate it when people start calling u up and say that they cannot make it at the last minute..damn. anyway, only 7 pple went..but we had our fun too. which was good i guess. haha..too bad liz couldn't come tho..oh well oooohh..i've gotten darker~ lol. i look much better now. heh. as chel always says " we shouldnt waste SUN! "..lol. so i din waste it! yeah..then after sentosa.. we(me betz n jia)  went to cine food court to makan. i had a beef steak. but it wasnt enough..i supposed i needed 2. lol. umm. yeah..then we went to jia hui's house. dunno do what also..but they needed my help to correct their blog's html. lol..talk about free labour..heh. kiddin :) yup..then i took a while to correct betz blog's html..then went home..by the time i reached home, it was like 11 plus n i was dead tired..haha..so i juz went straight to my bed n plonked down. and just this morning i could hear my dad complain abt me not switching off the lights yesterday. oops~
     

        
</post>

<date>06,August,2003</date>
<post>


           
      yeah man. came back frm LTC yesterday. whoo..dead tired..so decided to blog only today..umm..about any LTC stuff, ask me. i'll tell u all bout it..juz that i'm lazy to type it down la..ahhaha..a lotta nice n interesting things happened. :)  okay. on to today. i went back to sch. owing one whole shit load of hw. whee..lol. u know that feeling where u juz owe so much u juz dun wanna do? i'm feeling liddat now haha..oh well. shan't talk abt hw.. had canoeing today..got scolded by some china man for rowing past him while he was in the water. haha. then my coach scolded him back.. wah lao..i felt damn bad..might not be his fault..but i juz feel damn bad la..causing this unneccessary quarrel..lol..oh well..i finally can row k1 with power stroke..heh. feelin proud of myself now.. :) i can see a bright future in canoeing for me.   sighz..feeling bored now..the aftermath of ltc..in ltc i had so much fun..now like damn sian..bah.
     

        
</post>

<date>30,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      didn't go to school today. much thanks to the oysters i ate yesterday. gave me a diarrhoea( is that how u spell it?) haha. nvm. but anyway, the good thing is that my ct didn't come today! HAHAHA. what luck man. woo. hell yeah. guess she must have had a "rough" night. oh well, really miss those guys i hang out with everyday..and of course, her as well. :) hmm, so i stoned at home, watched cartoons till the afternoon, then played my "pearl harbour" vcd as i ate my lunch. haha. i like that show..damn cool. yeah, then slept, woke up, had my dinner, watched holland V, did my work. and i'm now bloggin. yup. *stretches* so happy. tmr will be a really short day. ends at 1. muAhhaz :)  hmm, looks like i was wrong abt angela being angry. she never gets angry. *shrugz* sometimes i wonder if she does irritate herself? hahaha. kiddin. :P but whatever it is, u rawk babe. heh. oh guess i hafta add in sumthin. *beseeches allah to rain holy fire and whatever there is up in allah land on (ben, u know who)* muahhaha. yup, a good deed for the day. :)  oh yeah, and another thing i must mention. i'm now officially against s'pore aunties. basket. i've had enough of em lor. all they do is bother about other pple, never about themselves. bloody busybodies. darn. now she's feeling flustered. can't do anything to help her tho. sigh.  anyone wanna join my club? :)  
     

        
</post>

<date>29,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      
     

        
</post>

<date>27,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      argh..feeling damn sleepy now..dunno why. my eyes juz feel like closing..shall go answer their call after blogging then. today was quite okay..only 4 periods. then after that went to meet alv, then went home, then went to lot1 again. went to arcade to watch him play his stupid drums for 2 times, then went to macs and tried to study. didn't do anything. went to arcade again. wacthed him play. basically i was his doggie following him arnd..not like he has enough doggies already.. lol. :P eh..ya..then kinda met her at kfc..ahha..her friend saw me, so she came in to sit with me. yup, then i showed her his neoprnts with abby.   Abby = Santa Claus And Alv = Elf. alv the elf. muaahhz.kk. 
     

        
</post>

<date>27,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      had a relatively okay day today..let's see..stayed at home for the whole day..did nothing much. haha..oh well, juz another saturday...Zzzz. hmm, dunno if i shud blog about this..but alright i will. i feel that angela and i are kinda like drifting apart. i dunno if that's how u feel angie, but yeah..that's what i feel. its like we're not as gossipy or whatever as we used to before. but i hope this gap is nothing much, only that we're not talking as much as we used to. but yup, tho i'm attached now, i'll still treat u as a good friend. my half "brother" in fact. so yeap, i'm always there to listen and talk to u if u want me to. :) really miss the times we spent talking crap at macs. hehehe. yup, if u're readin this dear, juz wanna say "love ya always" *hugz* :) dunno what to do now. shall go watch tv or sumthin. lol.
     

        
</post>

<date>26,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      haha..i'm bloggin only cos u told me too :) k. i shall list today's events out.  1. Ponned Chem Lecture and got caught by my chem teacher. 2. Pe. Ran 3.6km in 18 mins. 3. Went out to study at west mall. Yay! i made 2 new friends today! their names are cameron and grace. cameron is tall, and is also a naughty boy. and grace is short! lol. (jiahui suggested that)  That's all. :D
     

        
</post>

<date>25,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      today, was a nice day. "nice" weather and all. ahha. sian la..went out with her and ben ben juz now. juz came home. bah. shall go call her now. :)
     

        
</post>

<date>24,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      ahah. today was a really slack day.. *yawn* ended sch at 1. then went to town with angela, hongyi and jiahui. haha..basically it was like a double date la..me and jiahui, angela and hongyi..heh. yeah we went to crystal jade to eat xiao long bao and i shared the la mian with jiahui. quite nice, tho abit dry..and the xiaolong bao was the best! really like it when the juice flows thru ur mouth. woo..so exhilarating! haha. yeah then we walked to taka..walk walk walk..then suddenly angela and hong yi disappeared. dunno where they went to. apparently they kinda "missed" us. so they ended up elsewhere. dunno whether they did that on purpose or not..but yeah i'll give em the benefit of doubt. hehe. :P yup..then jiahui and me went to great world city. she went there to change her shirt which was too small for her. while i juz accompanied her. haha..i feel really happy just being around her.. :) yup..then we walked arnd..till 6.30. then we went home.. haha..then on the way home. i didn't know alv was on same train as me. so met him only at jurong..yeah..then went lot 1 library..then went home.  woah..damn tired now..eyes are like almost closing..-.- *yawn again* guess i must be really tired. oh well, since i dun have any hw to pass up tmr..shall go sleep eaerly today..hehe. :P promos..shall wait..*yawnnnn..*
     

        
</post>

<date>23,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      today was a generally long long long long day..haha..ended sch at 5.30pm..sighz..tired..then went to some com lab to read pples' blogs. read and read till arnd 6.50..then went to canteen to sit down to chat for a while, before walking to lot 1. haha..i live near lot 1. so its kinda okay for me. outta the 3 pple i was with, 2 of em live arnd the cck area..so yup. lot 1 it is! :D mm..then i met her for dinner. she looked kinda lethargic and tired, like some walking zombie.. hehe.  i guess its the after studying effects. so yup. tried to cheer her up by cracking lotsa stupid jokes..apparently, that livened her up a lil..heh. :) yup, then we talked and talked..blah blah blah..till arnd 9..then she had to leave..cos she was staying in tiong bahru. wanted to send her home. but if i did, i would only reach home at 11. and i had a chem test tmr. so she din allow me to.. :) so considerate right? haha..yup, anyway..i at home now. juz finished watching s'pore's brainiest kiddo. turned out that perry lam won. ahha..at least he looks a bit normal..:P yeah..then bathed..and i shall go study for my chem test now. or rather,  TRY  to. hEheEheh. :D
     

        
</post>

<date>22,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      talking to her now..:) cos someone no more sms wor..k. juz finished talking to her. kinda irritated. dunno why. but i seriously need pple to comment on this. the conversation went like that.   me: okay so tmr i'll go to some corner of lot 1 to study by myself until u wanna eat dinner k?(cos she said i'll distract her) her:huh..but like that u'll be so alone. me:i'm okay la..i dun mind studying by myself. her:den nvm la..we'll meet on thurs then. me:but i told u its alrite. her:dun wan la..so waste time for u.  fine. so the problem is i'll be wasting time "trying" to study. what nonsense? i'm wasting time studying? k la..i know i've not been studying and whenever i try to study i end up talking nonsense. but i'll be alone, and what's more the god damned promos are comin. i might be jokin about getting retained. but who in his bloody right mind would get retained anyhow?   oh well. nvm. had another interesting conversation today, or rather, "confrontation". it went like this. Frank:*pushes roy* and said "ni3 hun4 na2 li3?" roy: huh? i dun understand. me:he means, "u zhup where?" roy: *gives me blur look* peter: oh, he means, "where do u fool around?"  HAHA. lol. might lose out some of the effect. better if said in person. heh.  argh. shall go do my work now. at least it'll douse my "irritance".
     

        
</post>

<date>21,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      today, was an absolutely boring day. sigh. fell asleep while doing my physics revision. come to think of it, i think there's both physical stamina and mental stamina. my mental stamina = 0. lol. i think my brain has kinda decomposed after 4 yrs of not usin it. sigh, she's havin a lot of work to do now..pw, history and gp. both hist and gp will take her 5 hrs...plus pw..i really dunno whether she'll even get any sleep..i told her i want to accompany her. but she told me to sleep. hmm, shud i or shud i not? i'm worried that she might not get enough sleep..if i could, i would help her do something..feelin kinda helpless now..:( oh well, i can't do anything but listen to her and go and sleep. dear, if u're reading this as u're doin ur pw, i'll try to stay awake as long as possible..until i fall asleep...to give u all the support u need. remember..i'm always there for u.. just a phone call away. :) 
     

        
</post>

<date>18,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      went to sch. went for lessons. took maths test. stoned in classroom. went home. 
     

        
</post>

<date>17,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      lets see. today was a darn short day..ended sch at 1.. so met her. so lucky her tuition was at 7.30 pm. otherwise couldn't go out with her. was really looking forward to today. :) mm hmm. went ikea with her. ate the meat balls thingy..haha..she taught me how to eat em. like must cut em into two.. spread the cranberry jam over it, and then eat it. hmm, otherwise, i'll juz eat it my way. pop the whole ball in. :D yup, after eating, walked around ikea...she wanted to buy a cushion for me..haha..yeah i guess my life isn't warm enough. :) so yup, she bought me a cushion..some green colour one. got blue also. hehe. yup, very nice. thanks dear. :) mm..then after that we went great world city, and i saw my WHITE NIKE SLEEVELESS SHIRT! OH MY ALLAH man! finally found it after like dunno how long. lol. gonna buy it. hehe. b4 someone else snaps it up. yup, she bought 2 shirts too. one with a pink dolphin for her teacher who was flying off, and one for herself. :) those shirts look quite nice. got swarvoski crystals one. lol. k. nice nice. then she went to buy some tiramisu cake for her teacher's bdae. :) yup, then went off, cos she had tuition and i had to go home. mm hmm. had a nice day today. ahha..darn..tmr maths sure die. don't know how to sketch curve. hehehehehhehehZzzZzz. :D fux lor.
     

        
</post>

<date>16,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      lets see. today was a rather fine day. nothing much happened. but on my way home, a scene of children playing hide and seek under my block made me think back on my childhood days. when i was young, i was really carefree and boy was my life good. i've not experienced stress when i was young. in pri sch, all i did was sit in class and talk, yet i still get band 1s. yup, then after sch, i would go to my child care centre, where i would stay till my mum picked me up. i loved my friends there. everytime we had outdoor time, we would play catching.."boys catch girls" or "girls catch boys", or hide and seek. come to think of it, playing catching was free, yet exciting. unlike now, i've gotta pay to be excited. lol. i really miss those days, where everyday in my life was juz to look forward to playing catching.  :) right now, if u were to go around asking pple " hey u wanna play catching under my block?" all they would say is "u siao ar?" or "so childish. grow up la". yup, that is what most pple would say. but for me, i'm game for anything. i'm a childish boy at heart actually. yeah..and i still watch cartoons every sat and sun mornings. lol. okay..gtg now..:) ciao~
     

        
</post>

<date>15,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      hmm, shall blog now in case i dun have the chance to blog later. hah..mum went out to some wedding dinner. so right now i'm alone till 7.30 when my sis comes back frm tuition. :) oh well, lets see. nothing unusual today..haha..got scolded by teachers for not finishing the hol assignments. yup. that's all i guess. then after sch, went to the popular megastore to buy bdae card. but ben din want to cos the cards were not nice. so he went home. wasted our time. bah.. :P. yeah anyway, angela and i went to macs to talk nonsense again..haha..waste time..then ya went home. shall watch holland V now. :) ciao~~
     

        
</post>

<date>14,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      okay lets see. today has been a really dead day. i stayed at home the whole day, trying to finish up my chem hw. darn. juz realised that i've got one whole shit load to do..sigh. :( oh well, the impt thing now is not to dwell on it, but to get it over and done with. hmm, to all couples out there. i've got a phrase for u guys. "Love is a gift, not an obligation". If u ask me, i would say that normally, most couples quarrel and break up, mainly due to them thinking that their partner should change for them. but no, that's not the case. both should change for each other, and if possible, one should take one step back. if someone loves you, take it as a life long gift, always feel grateful, never take it for granted that that gift will be with u all the time. :) yup, and   ben  ..relax la bro. why the heck are u fretting about girls? if they come, they come. u'll find the special one in ur life, ahha..like me..took me 9 months. but it was worth it in the end. the longer u wait, the better ones u'll get. why get someone now, and regret it when someone better comes along? take things in ur stride, and cheer up. cos life's more than just girls. :) 
     

        
</post>

<date>12,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      went out with her yesterday to watch turn left turn right. lol. its quite an interesting love comedy i would say. :) mmm..then after the show, went to eat ice kachang with her at the food court..and haha it seriously sucks. the syrups din even taste nice and sweet at all..bah. anyway, after eating with her, walked around tiong bahru plaza, and frm there i walked her home. haha..and THAT was her first time walking home frm tiong bahru plaza~ :P the walk wasn't really long..distance is quite the same as walking frm lot 1 to my house. yup yup, the walk was really nice, esp if u're with that special someone. :) she sent me to the bus stop, then we waited for the bus together. hmm, i still think i shud've sent u home. lol. shan't say any mushy stuff on my blog. ;) hope u'll have a fine day today! 
     

        
</post>

<date>12,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      hmm, been coming home late quite often these few days..so could only blog today..haha..but this shall be a special post..just for yesterday. =) mm..yesterday, the whole day was quite boring, went to lot 1 to play pool with alv first, then went home to sleep for a while, before going to chinese gardens to see the hello kitty exhibition. yup yup, 5 of us went,me, ,jh, liz, angie and jamie. the whole thing was quite nice..enjoyable in fact, to be able to see all those wonderful lanterns with her. :) haha..we paid 12 bucks, and walked for like say..2 hrs plus, then we all had to go home. i saw her home as usual, but on that night, i did something really different. something that i did for the first time. yup, feels great. even tho it was only for like 10, 15 mins, i really enjoyed every moment of it. if i had a choice, i would want it to last forever. :) sometimes she calls me stupid, and silly..but i dun mind being silly and stupid, if it makes u happy. :) if i were to say something now, i'd say "i really want u by my side all the time". and i mean it. =) heh. gotta go..mum's comin home soon. :P
     

        
</post>

<date>09,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      haha..changed my blog layout and colours, lets just say that the colour is to suit my taste, and the lil cute kittens are to suit hers. :) lalala. had a REALLY MONOTONOUS day. wasted my whole afternoon rotting in food court and macs. shan't comment bout it. damn irritating. had to go home with kee chern summore. kee chern, if u're ever gonna turn on a comp, go online, and come to my blog, i juz wanna tell u that u're a really boring person filled with dry humour, amen. i've always wanted someone frm my class to live near me so we could go home together. apparently, i'd rather he not exist. sigh. juz finished watching s'pore brainiest kid. lol. althea had to look the most decent of em all man. too bad she din get into the last round. bah. stupid goldfish desiree got in tho. i've gotta say that she's got this really interesting way of answering questions. quite alike a tortoise. she kinda sticks her head out whenever  she says something. damn irritating. bah. and there was a luo han fish lookalike also. HAHAHAH. HAHAHAH. k. i juz saw the president's star charity commercial. it shows tay ping hui and sharon au with 2 spastic kids asking pple to help those kids realise their dreams, their hopes, and whatever. i don't wanna sound mean, but can i ask what aspirations or any REALISTIC dreams could they ever have? i don't think they even know the meaning of dreams. its quite pathetic come to think of it, that they juz live their entire lives being spoonfed and being incapable of doing anything on their own. plus with fanatically and blindly loyal muslims running around blowing things up, what more can the world ask for? speaking of mats, i juz 2 mat kids throwing stones at a poor kitten at the park downstairs my block. since i was just looking down from my 15th floor window, i couldn't do anything. but seriously, i swear that if i was down there, and if i see them doing that, i'll literally whack em. i dun give a damn if their mat minah mum is nearby. FUCK THOSE BLOODY MAT KIDS. i'm not a racist wannabe juz because i do not like their face or skin colour, but because of what they do. if even they themselves do not respect themselves, how could they expect us to respect them in return? i'm not referring to the malay population in general. juz some pathetic malays who give pple like me the wrong impression. everywhere i go, i see malays cutting queues, littering, abusing animals, hugging and kissing each other in public. seriously, what got into allah's mind when he decided to create such a pathetic race? lol. i juz wanna laugh. 
     

        
</post>

<date>08,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      oh cool. suddenly i remember the pword to my blog. it juz popped into my head juz now. lol. :) oh alright..i've been feeling lazy..so like damn long nv blog..hehe. right. so i'm bloggin now! eh..k shall start frm today.   Today, i went to sch for some sat workshop. lol. what an extreme waste of time. wanted to zhao..but oh well, stayed thru the end. haha..but i learnt how to inteprete analogies wor. so cool. yup. then, went out with the vball guys. all i can say is, u guys are one cool bunch man! all of em damn on & damn sporting, hard to find this kinda pple in pj now if u ask me. wish the canoeing pple were a like that..sigh. haha..yeah anyway, we went to cdans, and played 40 mins of lq. (Buy 30 mins get 10 mins free) hehe..free advert. :D heheh. and then the fun began man. a total of 10 pple went. Lets see, me, frank, angela, hong yi, su-ne-ne, carol, daniel, cindy, gavin and regine(another canoeist. my vice capt.). Yup, so for the first round me frank angela hongyi and regine were on one team. Yup, and after that experience, i realised that LQ is a REALLY merciless game. Want examples? heh. eg1. Cindy and carol kinda cornered themselves, so frank hongyi and me were kinda ganging them. then frank suddenly had his gun hit cindy's eye or sumthin. and she was like "wah lao u hit me! so pain!" however, no one stopped to care for her. the 3 of us were just like laughing maniacally and still continued shooting at both of em. Afterall, free frags are what they are, right? :) the same happened to gavin when he tripped and fell, and when some other pple fell too. haha. they're juz really damn "xia4 jian4" :D oh well, i got 1st for 1st round. dun ask abt 2nd round. we changed the girls in the team. so now cindy and carol were in our team. hahaha..then got this part which i found damn funny. Carol was like being cornered by 3 guys, and at that time i juz about ran past her. she saw me, and screamed for my help. I looked at her, looked at her 3 assailants, and all i said was "BYebYE". then i ran away. LOL. left her there to be "raped". I realised i shud nt have done that..cos it lead to the other team winning. And stupid toylet and regine were like insane lunatics, all the gun snatching etc. plus gavin and su-ne-ne were covering their chest pad. so how to shoot em?! lol. but it was damn fun, damn exhilarating. hohoh. shud do that again! :D   oh well, damn tired now. shan't go to sch tmr. shall go swim or sumthing. hahah..i think this hols is so gonna be wasted man..lol..RETAIN-ACY here i come! :D
     

        
</post>

<date>28,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      gAHAHha. went to sch today even when i didn't feel like it yesterday. damnit. all thanks to the "good" influence i had today, i attended all the stupid, uesless lectures. HAHAHA. i';m gonna go nuts soon. but luckily, i was still sane enough to pon pw. hurhur. fark pw. i'm gonna have to take pw again nex yr. lol. eh ya la. nothing else. gonna play gunbound now. oh ya. got friendster account? add me in. i've only got 2 friends. :( email's chromium15@hotmail.com 
     

        
</post>

<date>27,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      haha. someone fuck me up please. :) 
     

        
</post>

<date>22,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      bah. kinda long since i blogged. hurhurhru. lazy to. :D but oh well. what do i have to say. elf told me some stuff which left me severely traumatised. lol.ya. umm. and i dun feel like going to sch tmrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr.........cos its a suckie day.....damnnnnnnnnnnnnn.....i'm gonna lose my sanity soon if i continue wasting my youth in school. lol. i dun really care if i get retained or whatever shit. i juz want hols to come! COME HOLS COME! I IMPLORE YOU. bahz..shitty life. "i think about you baby, and i dream about you all the time..:) " bahz. shalll stone now. hurhur.
     

        
</post>

<date>22,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      juz came back frm trng. dead beat. lotsa things happened today. glad i din pon trng. haha. no gunbound for today tho. lol. argh i'm damn hungry...gonna eat now. then call jh ltr. ahha. what a life. :D
     

        
</post>

<date>21,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      lol. what else can i say but "Gunbound rox ur b0x". lOL. :D that's all. more gb! mUAhaHAhZ. i rawk at raon launcher. ;)
     

        
</post>

<date>13,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Brian Adams & Rod Stewart & Sting - All For Love  When it's love you give I'll be your man of good faith When it's love you live I'll make a stand I won't break I'll be the rock you can lean on Be there when you're old To have and to hold  When there's love inside I swear I'll always be strong And there's a reason why I'll prove to you we belong I'll be the wall that protects you From the wind and the rain From the hurt and the pain  Let's make it all for one and all for love Let the one you hold be the one you want The one you need Cause when it's all for one it's one for all When there's someone that you know Then just let your feelings show And make it all for one and all for love  When it's love you make I'll be the fire in your night Then it's love you take I will defend I will fight I'll be there when you need me When honor's at stake This vow I will make That it's all for one and all for love Let the one you hold be the one you want The one you need Cause when it's all for one it's one for all When there's someone that you know Then just let your feelings show And make it all for one and all for love  Don't lay our love to rest Cause we could stand up to the test We got everything and more than we had planned More than the rivers that run inland We got it all in our hands  Now it's all for one and all for love Let the one you hold be the one you want The one you need Cause when it's all for one it's one for all When there's someone that you know Then just let your feelings show When there's someone that you want When there's someone that you need Let's make it all all for one And all for love   lol. nice song. :) suits my kinda mood now. heh. 
     

        
</post>

<date>11,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      muAHhaz. finally i've got some time to blog. been busy playin games n slackin for the past few days. promos are over. re-exams are comin. hurhur. farkz. but nvm. play first. :D woo completed Jedi Knight : Jedi Academy. damn nice. played light saber fighting with alv yesterday for 1 hr. beats playing with lousy comp A.I. hehe. okay okay. gonna zhao liao. meetuing alv to go town. gonna change first. hope today will be a fine day. :)
     

        
</post>

<date>07,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      haha. tmr is my maths exam. and i'm studyin physics now. :D lol. screw maths. nvm 2 more papers. 2 more days. eh no. 1 day and 19 more hrs. muahahah. which is = to 24+19 hrs = 43 hrs = 2580 mins = 154800 secs = 15480000 millisecs! woowwee. can't wait. hurhurhurhur. :D
     

        
</post>

<date>06,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      muahaz. one paper down. three more to go. hell yeah. :D
     

        
</post>

<date>05,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      mm..been kinda "muggin" the whole day...haha..and i've gotta admit that i'm kinda rusty at it after 4 yrs of not muggin. :) sigh..i wanna pass my promos..but i dun wanna juz scrape thru..i want to understand every single concept and formula. otherwise, when i get to j2, i'll juz die la. everyone's saying "aiya, juz promote first. nex yr then can buck up." haha..to that, i'll juz give em this ..|.. bloody hell, u expect me to cram 2 yrs of work together? i mean like, science is not sumthin u can juz look at it and say "oh i understand". rather, the impt thing is to know how to apply it. very frequently, in exams, the examiners juz hafta twist the question arnd and taa-daa. u won't know how to do it. so my point is that the basics have to be strong before moving on. everyone's afraid of retaining. and so i ask them "what's there to be afraid of?" because u'll waste one yr? because people will laugh at u for being stupid? or because u juz want face? frankly speaking, i dun give a shit about all those things. tchs has taught me a lot of things, because i literally advanced my way thru. i dun see the point of advancing to j2 when ur basics can juz be toppled with the flick of a finger. ultimately, the A levels are what counts. haha..maybe the common stereotype of retainees is that they're "dropouts", they're lousy students, they're losers of the sch. if u think that way, well, fuck you. i think they deserve some respect at least. just because u get good results, top the class or become the teacher's pet, doesn't mean u're god or sumthin. well, if u're muggin, u work hard, naturally u get good results. so be it. respect those who don't. hahaha..because u'll never know when its ur turn. :) ah well. the above post was juz to de-stress. no targets in mind. :) yup, back to my work. 
     

        
</post>

<date>04,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      muahahz. lazy to blog. nothing to blog. had a boring day. that is all. :)
     

        
</post>

<date>02,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
        I am  Mario .   I like to jump around, and would lead a fairly serene and aimless existence if it weren't for my friends always getting into trouble. I love to help out, even when it puts me at risk. I seem to make friends with people who just can't stay out of trouble. 
     

        
</post>

<date>02,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      sian. There's gp paper tmr. yawn. shall go sleep now. arghz. 
     

        
</post>

<date>01,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      hm, had a really boreeng day todeyyy. haha. after sch went to macs. sat down with jj and his "friend" huiqi. dunno what they're up to la..kept looking at each other..winking, smiling, etc. then still tell me is some "secret" hcjc canoeing team signal. wtf. must as well tell me that Allah eats Kuay Chap man. k watever. i'll find out the truth sooner or ltr anyway. :) wah lao jj, really lorz..nothing to say. hehe. yeah..then they left soon after and elf(frm now on alv = the elf) and i were left doing our own work. i didn't do much. did maths. and did only log and exponential crap. ahha. darn. yeah..then accompanied him to buy his gio jeans. looks okay la..at least its not tapered. so u dun look like a low down poser shit mat. but that's beside the point u see, we chinese have gotta look MUCH BETTER then them! :) heheheeh. kiddin. k la. must i add a disclaimer? lol. eh..nothing else really.. juz wanna say " eh ben, have faith in urself..whatever will come, will come. no hurry. focus on what's impt first ya? :) " hahaha..yeah..and also wanna end off with my currently most fav word...yep u guys guessed it. "CHIWAWA MAN" woo! :D muAhahAHz
     

        
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


           
      haha. i'm a retainee wannabe. :) 
     

        
</post>

<date>01,November,2003</date>
<post>


           
      hahaz. after all that piaing in gb, i'm finally a bloody metal axe. lolz. anyway, had SAT juz now. bah. ultimate torture. i can't stand sitting in a bloody chair for 4 hrs in a go. yeah, but it was fine tho. so yeah. lolx. nvm that. then had trng..today's trng was quite okay.. dunno why la..but i felt sian at the beginning. hahaz..sighz. fark. nvm. a message for my nice darling capt LYON. :) if u're feeling well now, good for you, but if u're not, get well soon u asshat. :) that's all. gonna find my WIN XP cd and pass to elf the alv. oh yeah. while eating in kfc, i learnt that lor mai kai = chicken pudding. :D LOL~ fark la. i'm damn scared of kfc now. hurhurhruhruhruhurhru
     

        
</post>

<date>31,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      juz received her xmas present. might be late..but oh well..better late then never..right now..i juz feel forgotten. looking back on all my posts now. i juz feel that its wishful thinking on my part. i'm juz so bloody naive. yeah. naive. cos i still watch bloody cartoons. but that's besides the point. right now, i feel that the situation, is juz "i love you, but u don't love me no more". yeah, and i juz cant help but feel depressed. all over again. because i seriously do not know how u feel towards me now. good or bad. i dun wanna know anymore. i juz don't. its juz so hard to be a "friend" to u all over again. its so hard, its bloody torture. i read ur blog, and i agree with what jolene said. u said u were afraid of ur parents knowing. maybe they knew? or maybe they didn't, but perhaps they would juz nod and say "i'm happy for u" when they knew u had a boyfriend? nothing happened at all. and u chose to give it all up. as for studies, A levels might be coming, for u at least. and u were afraid u couldn't concentrate. that was ur problem, which was mine too. aren't couples supposed to solve each other's problems together? u might say "i'm afraid of becoming a burden to u". u know jolly well that i wouldn't mind, in fact i'd be happy to shoulder ur problems with u. but no, u chose to give it up. u chose the easy way out. by juz going to the root of all problems and eliminating it. which was me. but if u'd ask me "why would u still wait for me even when i already broke up with u?" i'd reply "because i believe its something worth waiting for. i love you."
     

        
</post>

<date>30,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      sigh..its times like now that i really miss her. not like i dun miss her all the time. but whenever i'm not busy or immersed in something, i'll start to think of her. bah..i miss hugging her, holding her hands when she's cold, poking fun at her, etc. i miss u so much that if i'm a girl, i'll cry myself to sleep every night. sigh..
     

        
</post>

<date>29,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      haha. not irritated anymore. guess i was juz feeling hot and angsty. :P oh well. today was boring..woke up, went to lot 1 for lunch..first time i had teppanyaki. heh. the beef with chilli and garlic was really nice. :D hmm. wanna eat it again. lalalala. then went to alv's house. stoned, played XIII, and played with stupid bots PLUS this irritable piece of shit called "the death" which juz runs around singing "u can run but u can't hideeee". yeah basically when it touches u, u juz die. irritating. lol. then went home to sleep. woke up, played gunbound. haha..going off to kopitiam later to drink iced teh tarik. hehe. boring. :|
     

        
</post>

<date>28,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      grr. i'm feeling irritable now. dunno why. i'm juz irritated at nothing. argh.
     

        
</post>

<date>28,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      lolololol. I AM UTTERLY BORED. HAHAHAHA. lololoolooololool. 
     

        
</post>

<date>28,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      lololol. juz added some "nice" pics taken by my mum's newly bought minolta dimage xt. :D not bad. but i'll have to fiddle with it a lil more. hohoho. 
     

        
</post>

<date>28,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      U2 - Sweetest thing  My love she throws me like a rubber ball Oh oh oh, the sweetest thing She won't catch me or break my fall Oh oh oh, the sweetest thing Baby's got blue skies up ahead But in this I'm a rain cloud You know she likes a dry kind of love Oh oh oh, the sweetest thing   I'm losing you Hey hey hey, I'm losing you yeah Ain't love the sweetest thing   I wanted to run but she made me crawl Oh oh oh, the sweetest thing Eternal fire, she turned me to straw Oh oh, the sweetest thing You know I got black eyes But they burn so brightly for her Mine is a blind kind of love Oh oh oh, the sweetest thing   I'm losing you Oh oh oh, I'm losing you yeah Ain't love the sweetest thing Oh oh oh, the sweetest thing Oh oh, yeah   Blue-eyed boy meets a brown-eyed girl Oh oh oh, the sweetest thing You can sew it up but you still see the tear Oh oh oh, the sweetest thing Baby's got blue skies up ahead And in this I'm a rain cloud You know we got a stormy kind of love Oh oh oh, the sweetest thing Oh oh, the sweetest thing Oh oh oh, the sweetest thing Oh oh oh, the sweetest thing   
     

        
</post>

<date>28,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      some people say "fish, u're an idiot. u've already broken up with her, why do u still care about her so much?" or "since u've already broken up, why do u hope that she might be free so that u can ask her out?  are u that desperate?" my answer: no, i'm not an idiot. i'm no despo either. perhaps i'm seriously sentimental. perhaps i'm nuts. but there's one thing i'm sure. that is, i love her. i loved her before, i loved her after. and i loved her still. it breaks my heart whenever i talk to her now. its like going back to square 1. like as if we didn't know each other. like as if we were strangers. its so hard to talk, so hard to express anything. i know i haven't been a perfect guy for u either. always playing gunbound, neglecting u, being insensitive at times, and most of the time, its u who takes the initiative. i know now. but i might never have the chance to make up for it now. if u ask me what do i have to offer you, i can tell u only two things. my love, and my loyalty. people might ask, what loyalty? i can tell them, or rather list out all the shit i went thru. if they can tell me, "yes i will still stay by her side after everything, and still love her as much as i did before, no matter what kinda crap happened.", then ok, they're good. u mean a whole damn lot to me. i know its fsking mushy and lame whatsoever. but if u ask me, that's all i can come up with. i'm not some prime minister or muhamud ghandi who can come up with strong words to move people. but all of it, all that i've typed above, comes frm my heart. the bottom of it.
     

        
</post>

<date>31,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      haha..boring day. watched tv and stoned around. but spent most of my time trying to finish it up. left 2 more days. i sure hope she'll like it. haha..gotta hurry. hmm. bored. zzz. gunbound now. hehe =D
     

        
</post>

<date>30,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      wow. something great juz happened. i smsed my teammate to ask what time's trng tmr and where to meet. and his reply was "there's no trng tmr.sorry for not informing u". WTF. "SORRY FOR NOT INFORMING U". IF I DIDN"T FUCKING SMS HIM, the following stuff would have happened.   1.waking up at bloody 6am to get ready. 2. having a lousy breakfast which consists of plain bread with butter. 3. taking 1 hr to get the kallang 4. going there to find nobody. 5. swearing my guts out. 6 taking 1 hr to get back.  all in all, that's my whole morning wasted. IF i didn't sms him. cool eh? praise allah. 
     

        
</post>

<date>28,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      haha. today was a really short day. ended at 1. then had to chiong down to lido to watch "the last samurai", which was at 1.40pm. well, as usual ben was bullshitting. cos there wasn't any 1.40 show. lol. so we bought tix for 2.45 instead. had kfc, then talked nonsense for a while. then jamie told me she was watching at 3.45pm lar..and "she" was watching too lor..bah..wanted to wait till then so as to watch with her..but aiya..can't pangseh ben n scandal boy..so yeah..can't refund my tix either. heh. so yup, went ahead to watch. hmmm, gotta say that its one awesome movie. i really admire their spirit and courage. very often, its usually the going against of one's own morals and principles, and also fighting a battle which they know they would lose, not with cowardice, but the very act of pushing till the end, that sparks respect for the characters in the movie from the audience. it might be cliche, but hell yeah i love this kinda scenes. juz like lotr. hmm, but i liked the ninjas better tho. haha..they look kewler. :D 
     

        
</post>

<date>28,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
        You are one of the few out there whose wings are truly  ANGELIC . Selfless, powerful, and divine, you are one blessed with a certain cosmic grace. You are unequalled in peacefulness, love, and beauty. As a Being of Light your wings are massive and a soft white or silver. Countless feathers grace them and radiate the light within you for all the world to see. You are a defender, protector, and caretaker. Comforter of the weak and forgiver of the wrong, chances are you are taken advantage of once in awhile, maybe quite often. But your innocence and wisdom sees the good in everyone and so this mistreatment does not make you colder. Merciful to the extreme, you will try to help misguided souls find themselves and peace. However not all Angelics allow themselves to be gotten the better of - the Seraphim for example will be driven to fighting for the sake of Justice and protection of those less powerful. Congratulations - and don't ever change - the world needs more people like you.    urlLink   *~*~*Claim Your Wings - Pics and Long Answers*~*~*     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    haha. what an angel i am. =D juz had my dinner. went for trng juz now. sian..trained in the damn rain. luckily i had a cap on. lol. garh. what else. i'm drinking qoo orange blast now. tired like hell. gonna sleep soon i suppose..wahah..zz
     

        
</post>

<date>18,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      omfg. i'm so burnt. god damn it. =(
     

        
</post>

<date>15,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      i miss you all the time. 
     

        
</post>

<date>13,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      lol. and the 2 words are, "Fuck Off" =) kthnxbey.
     

        
</post>

<date>11,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      life's a bore..i wish i had something else fresh and interesting to do. practically slept the whole day. really lor. asdf. someone pls tell me my purpose in life.
     

        
</post>

<date>08,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      haha..supposed to sleep early..but ended up playing gb instead..*cough cough* guess i've got a sore throat coming up..gotta drink more water. sigh. nowadays life is so boring. wish i had something or someone to spice it up. garhh. oh btw, oreo is alright after those 2 jabs. i'm so happy for it. =) gonna visit it soon. heh. ah well. i guess that ends my day for today. oh..its sunday already..hahaha..alrighty then..gonna listen to her and sleep early..lol its 1.11am. that's early =) yeah..off to sleep now
     

        
</post>

<date>08,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      ahha went to school today. how fun. my class is dead. lollers. i'm gonna suffer for 3 months man. hohoho. ah well, better than 9 huh. lol. screw it. yeah..btw my fav dog is infected with heart worms. god damn it lar. of all dogs it had to be oreo lor. fsk. i juz hope it'll be fine, even tho alv told me it has just 50% chance of surviving..i wanna play with it again..bah..sometimes, the things which are closest and always with us, we do not treasure, yet when it's gone, only then will we miss and regret. but unfortunately, that's all we can do.
     

        
</post>

<date>04,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      wtf lar blogger is screwed up.
     

        
</post>

<date>03,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      juz came back frm trng. woah damn tired. sunburnt too. oh yeah. got a new jersey. a black adidas one. ahha..tho its a lil small. =\ oh well. shall be going to lot 1 to makan my dinner soon. bah. still kinda full frm bk tho. ate that 4 before coming back. argh. 
     

        
</post>

<date>02,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      ahah oh yeah. hope got pple join canoeing. muahhaha. sian loh if no one join. or if all the retards join. i'm gonna fsking kill myself. lololol.
     

        
</post>

<date>01,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      lollers. had orientation today. haha. nothing much. pretty boring. guess i haven't gone to the fun fun part yet. :D oh well. hope monday will be better. haha. er, ended quite early. then went to a teammate's house to play xbox. yeah..only 2 games. lotr and dead or alive beach volley. hohohoho. that game pwns. XD ya.then the rest went to buy the new canoeing jersey. i haven't seen it yet. but they said its damn chio. so ya i bought one. lollers. its a black adidas singlet if i'm not wrong. lol. hope it looks nice. hehe. then can show off. :P ah well, gonna sleep early. trng's at 8 tmr. lollerskateZzZ.
     

        
</post>

<date>01,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      lol. juz came back and bathed. drank teh-c juz now. hoho. in 9 hr's time will be orientation 2k4. hope it'll be good. and hope i won't meet more weird people.bah. muahhaha. and alv, i shall pray to the almighty ONE up there, to let someone whose name starts with C ends with Y be in my og. kthnxbey. uahahahah. NITEY
     

        
</post>

<date>01,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      lol. juz played gunbound. perhaps this might be my last day playing. oh well. heh. i had my fill for the past 2 months. lol. today has been an extremely boring day. nothing much happened. woke up, played gunbound, went to lot 1 to have lunch. and really lar lot 1 cinema dun have sch of rock.so didn't watch. lol. er..then came back, slept, woke up, had dinner, played gb. going for supper at 9.30pm. yeah..haha..oh well. tmr's orientation day. hope i'll have fun. altho there'll be those j1s giving me weird glances. heh. but oh well. :)
     

        
</post>

<date>01,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      had a talk with her this morning, not really a talk, but an exchange of words. hey..i'm not forcing u to do anything ok? take things at ur own pace. but know that, whenever u're down, whenever u're depressed, i'm always here for you. alright. i'm off now. gonna have my lunch and watch movie. hope she'll enjoy her day too. :)
     

        
</post>

<date>01,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      haha..oh well..i like her prezzie. so i'm changing the picture to it. :)
     

        
</post>

<date>29,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      hmm. just when i msged pinkie on msn, she went offline. waffak. silly girl probably went off i guess. but its so unlike her to sleep at 12.26am. lol. oh well. i'm juz waiting for my dad to come into the room for a second check before playing gunbound. whaha. imma trixxy lil biatch. keekles. nothing to do now tho. wanted to take a before and after pic of me brushing my teeth juz now. but the tooth paste dropped onto the camera. damn. and i nearly wanted to put it under the tap to wash. then i was like, "hmm, if i put it under the tap. won't it spoil?" lolololol. bored lar. faster come into the room leh nabei. 
     

        
</post>

<date>27,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      heh. today was a really slackish day. stayed at home for the whole day, save going to lot 1 to have my lunch. juz had my dinner. but i only ate a lil. dunno why i felt damn full. so i only ate the dishes and threw the rice away. heh. how boring. haha. i can still recall, 1 year ago, at this very day, the O lvls came out too. cant see why everyone's so worried about their results. maybe the diff is when u put in effort and when u did not. yeah for me i juz strolled to sch, took my result slip, opened it, and say, "oh myes." lol i thot i would get over 20 for not studying lar. then i'll be the first chinese high dude to get more than 20. hehehe. but oh well i didn't. hmm. so lets see now. gunbound biatch got 15, shanna got 16, shujun got 10 and zhiwei got 14. hmm. not too shabby. i think they all did alright. ahha esp zhiwei, who sounded really happy. both gunbound biatch and shanna were kinda disgruntled about their results, xb with english, shanna with erm, i aint sure either. and shujun sounded sad too because her friends around her were feeling disappointed. hmm, u cant be happy abt ur results when the others around u are not. i guess that's why she's feeling down. well, here's a shoutout to u guys. no matter what u get, no matter where u'll be going next, Life's a road we all gonna take. We've crossed paths once, and have bonded together quite well. Let it stay that way, while u make new friends in the place u're gonna go next. no matter whether u got 14, 15 or 16, take pride and tell urself u've done ur best. no worries. Life still rocks. and yeah, please remember the fishie in pjc always yeah? haha..i'll miss u guys. Peace out. =)
     

        
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      woohoo. long holiday ahead. with all the jae shit. whahha. no sch till tues i think. keekles. retaining rox. :D woke up at 6 am. dunno for wad. played gb. and then there was this match where 2 noobs in our team quit. which left me and alv on 4 people. waffak. but nvm. in the end. alv got 3k dmg. i got 2k dmg. whahaha. bunch of shit. 2 on 4 lar. =D pwn pwn. 
     

        
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      hurhurhur. as usual i was pwning noobs with alv jy and the gunbound biatch. keekles. here's a l33t screenshot of the lightning ss. its damn chio. =D i'm not going to sch tmr. keekles. gunbound day for me. =D    keekles. lightning pwns j00. :D
     

        
</post>

<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      whahaha. was just playing gunbound. it was quite a screwed up night for me, xb and jy. until. i got a keeklish knight. =) check it out. =D knight owns u. but my physics practical owned me. cos i haven do yet. KEEKLES. =D   >  KEEKLES. I RAWK. =D WOWSA KANINA 
     

        
</post>

<date>21,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
        Hello Ladies and Gentlemen. This girl above. This SMILING girl u see above is the oneth who madeth us wait for so darnnnn longggg before we could have our haojianz. And there she is, still smiling to herself, contemplating on what FUNNY TRIX she shud pull nex. tsk tsk. so anyone who knows her, pls be wary. thanks. =D keekles2her. but its alright. because she's DA PRincess afterall! HAIL HAIL! ALLAHU AKBAR.   Disclaimer: The above written was completely ficticious(except for the "made us wait damn long" part) , and anything religious, reputation smearing, thought provoking words/images u see here are not done on purpose. Well, maybe except to one girl. And that's her! =D    KEEKLES2HER 
     

        
</post>

<date>21,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      keekles. my mum finally opened the door. thanks to my trix. =D lololol. yesterday was gunbound/haojian day lar. whole day was about gunbounding, literally. xb wanted to go pjc but i trixxed him. AHAHHA. OMGHI2U. so he came to my house to play gunbound lor. alv and him were like pigs lar. come and dirty my room nia. with all the sprite ice and mamies and shitty candied biscuits which alv tried to throw into the kitchens of the nearby block. so childish and deprived can. =\ nvm. lol. i had fun laughing as well. ya then went to kopitiam at 11. DONT ASK ME WHY. SOMEONE HAD A BRIEFING AT 11 CAN. LOLOLOL. then we all met there and had teh bing and haojianz. lol. and waffak lar stupid zw took my belt home can. see bye. i dunno how i'm gonna wear my pants to sch on monday can. =\. NVM GUNBOUND TIME. AHAHHAHA
     

        
</post>

<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      juz finished playing gunbound. hehe. break i guess. gonna play again later. sekretly. =D hmm. come to think of it. i was wondering what the diff would be if i didn't retain.  IF I DIDN"T RETAIN: I'd be in j2 now slogging on sch work. I'd have no time for leisure stuff.  I'd be still stuck in the same dumb assed nerdy class with only angie and frank to talk to. I'd turn into some pjc guai tai who'd be obessed with A levels.  Overall, No God Damned Stinking Life.   well. how bout if i retained?  I RETAINED: I've got lotsa time for my own stuff. 1 more year in fact. Sch work is still alright. Can still manage. Got a new class, but sadly, still the same. Cos its PJC. Overall, I'm still rotting in PJC.  BUT, fortunately, i made quite a number of NEW BUDS, mainly XB the gunbound biatch, Shanna the Lumberer, Zhiwei the "i seriously don't know what to say abt him", and lastly, Shujun the "Princess Pinkie". Lol. thanks to them, i'm still alive. thanks to them, the first 2 months went past smoothly. thanks guys. u all add colour into my life. rock on. =) keekles2uall. lollerskates.=D 
     

        
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      sian. got headache. pjc life is juz so damn stressful. sigh.
     

        
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      lol today was a KAN boring day. tmd. not ONE of my clique came today. or whatever that's left of it. lol. and in class, i was sitting in the MIDDLE of 5 EMPTY seats. LOL. suddenly i juz felt like the guai tai of my class. the kwok keong number 2 of my class. wowsa. really lar. then i couldn't take it. and then i zhaoed half way. KAN SIAN KAN BORING. ARGH. and tmr still got the lansai OC shit. screw OC, screw 04s20, and most of all, SCREW PJC. =D
     

        
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      lol. today was a damn huaji day. made one new friend. teehee. =D
     

        
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      wahahha new pics added. this time its THE "PJC BRUDDERS". LOLOLOLOL> TAKE A LOOK YEAH? =D
     

        
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      HAHA today was a fun/boring day. fun at the first part, boring at the 2nd. lol. ok. went to sch till 11.30, of which i only attended 1 tutorial. the rest of the tiem was spent talking cock. damn fun. but..shanna and xuan bin are gonna fsking withdraw lar. leaving me with the looney zhi wei who's obessed with kok keong. wtf man. i'm gonna fsking die. teehee. but who cares. 1 month left. lol. then zhao sch on pretext that we're going poly at 11.30am. AHHAHA. ben and xb went to my house to gb. and now xb is HOOKED on gb. WHAHAHHA. ANOTHER GUNBOUND FREAK. LOLOLOL. played for 4 hours. and that ends the fun part of the day. now on to the boring part. after playing, went back to sch, studied there frm 5-8 cos the canoeing teacher wanted us to. lol. did only 4 chem ques. but who cares. wahah. then went loh tuan. watch pple eat. met alv. came home. had sucky dinner. LOL IS THAT BORING OR WHAT. TEEHEEHEEHEEHEEHEE
     

        
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      had kinda a long day today. monday was as usual, then after that had gym training. but i only went for a while, and then went to meet alv to go jp to buy some cross stitch stuff he wanna make for abby as a vdae prezzie. lol. copycat. heh.yeah. then came back arnd 9. ate quite a huge bowl of yucky shark's fin. then did a lil work. aiya..really sian diao. lol 
     

        
</post>

<date>08,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
           The Completely Pointless Personality Quiz     why in the blazing hells am i "GRAPES"? lol. wtf?
     

        
</post>

<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      lol. juz added some shit about myself. heh. bored. i've got a chinese compo to do. =\ but i don't think i'll be doing it. lololol. oh yeah..i downloaded 2 nice songs, ballads in fact. anyone who loves ballads shud download these songs!  1. Bob Carlisle- Butterfly kisses 2. Martina McBride- My Valentine mmm..i juz love these kinda songs. fuels the passion, and rejuvenates the soul. hell yeah.   here's a phrase frm "Donna Lewis's  I love you always forever", "You've got, the most stumbling blue eyes i've ever seen. Under a blue sky of pure white stars. Exotic sweetness, magical time."  mm..nice. =D Say u'll love, u'll love me forever. Never stop, not ever. Near and far, and always and everywhere, and everything.
     

        
</post>

<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      haha. sian ji pua. spent the whole damn day trng. now i'm burnt and worn out. =\ but ah well. at least i accomplished something, better than sitting at home, rotting away. ahah.sigh. bored. shall go watch teevee =)
     

        
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      haha i dun give a damn anymore. screw it. today's training was butt lousy. really not fucking low tide. low until u can even walk out to the middle of the sea and capsize the other canoeists. and i was so bloody lucky, my legs now have uncountable punctured wounds. fuck. i'm literally lame now. and juz now we still got scolded for leaving the fucking boat BACK AT THE TRAINING AREA. had to go get the damned boat back and by the time we were done, its bloody 7.30. screw it lar. shall go sleep lar. tmd.
     

        
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      had quite a boring day. ponned most of the lectures juz to go library and talk crap. yeah that's about all for today. handed her the cross stitch which i've been doing for the past few days today. really glad she liked it. yet i juz read her blog. and she said it wasnt worth it. to me, its worth everything. would u not want to give that someone something as special as her for her birthday or for any other occasion? the money spent, the time i used to make the cross stitch, everything, is worth nothing compared to just knowing that u like it. the thing is, i'm not doing these things just to compel u to return to me. i'm just doing it for your birthday. that's all. no strings attached. yet i don't know why u always feel so stressed whenever i give u something. you know how much i love u, and that's all u've gotta know.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
      HAHAHA. 
     

        
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
      lolol gb rox u. here's a l337 pictar. keke.  
     

        
</post>

<date>27,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
      hahez. today was a guy's day out. sibei shiok. anyway, i'm off to gb now. before i leave, xb requested that i upload this equally l337 pictar of him. comments, anyone? KEEKLES.   
     

        
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
      fuck. i've got nothing much to blog about today. except that campfire was alright, the atmosphere was there, but somehow, someone had to come and dulan me. lol. whatever. i'm only giving that a damn cos i hate it when pple give me the cold shoulder out of the blue. that really pissed me off lar. spoilt my fucking day. plus with a headache thruout the whole thing, what could be better. and after that. i met ODAC biatch. and this time, the conversation went like that. ODAC biatch: Hey fish, made more new friends thruout this campfire? Me: er..nope.. ODAC biatch: oh okay. i give u an apple. so what do u see? Me: i think i heard that before. An apple tree i suppose. ODAC biatch: No no, i see an APPLE GARDEN! Me: oh okay. well, hey my bus is here. gotta run. cya.  WHAT THE FUCK. SERIOUSLY THAT WAS THE ULTIMATE. 
     

        
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
      hahez. ponned sch today. didnt wanna go for orientation and play games with my og. no, i'm not anti social, but the fact is my og = my 1st 3 months class, and its dead boring. so yeah. to hell with it. if i'm in the same class with them again, i'll juz die on the spot. nonetheless, the stupid og teacher called me tho, and demanded that i give her an mc. wasted 1 hr 30 mins in the polyclinic and $6.10 on the medicine can. life is so darn meaningless nowadays. and with the thought that i might be in a class filled with weirdos, somebody please enlighten me on what the hell i shud do. 
     

        
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
      hmm, btw i was trying to find the malay translation of the phrase, "I OWN U UPSIDE DOWN". if i'm not wrong, its "aku own yuo tomabaleh." i couldn't find a translation for "own". that explains how refined the malay language is. guess allah must be stupid too. if one day, some virus were to infect all the chickens, ducks, cows, and everything except dogs and pigs, i wonder how those mats will survive. will they discard their religion, and eat pork? or will they juz die in the name of allah. lol. well, they can always turn to vege for a change. or i'd be glad to recommend them Fatty Weng's Delicious   Kuay Chap  . Try it, cos it OWNS YUO TOMABALEH.  
     

        
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Life's a darn bore now. sian lar. no one's really online nowadays. sigh. now i regret not talking to em more before. oh well. cheryl seems to have disappeared frm this world. i wonder how she is now. guess her mom took her fone away and grounded her. and pinkie's always running around like some busy woman. sian lar. and my games are downloading so fsking slowly. cheesebun. 1k per sec. seriously nothing to do lor. argh. 
     

        
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
      hmm, btw, changed the pictar to another sunset which i took yesterday. quite nice. took it at arnd 7pm juz when night's comin. hurhur. 
     

        
</post>

<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
      lol. guess what dudes. i duplicated the key. keke. NO MORE TISSUE PAPER TRIX. HAHAHAHA. 
     

        
</post>

<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
      lol oh yeah. did i mention that some stupid guy frm odac talked to me after getting back the AO chinese results? it went like this. I shall call him ODAC biatch. ODAC biatch: Hey what did u get for ur chinese? Me: oh i got a c5, how bout u? ODAC biatch: Oh. i got an A1. *laughs* Me: oh ok. ODAC biatch: well dun be depressed, let u tell u something really inspirational. Me: oh ok. ODAC biatch: ok, i give u an apple, and can u tell me what u see inside the apple? Me: erm..seeds? ODAC biatch: yup, a lot of pple said seeds, but i can tell u my answer. Me: which is? ODAC biatch: I see an APPLE TREE within the apple. Me: *thinks* right. ok. ODAC biatch: yup so u see, that's the moral of the story. everyone has potential. Me: yeah whatever. and he went yakkity yak yak yakkity yak yak all the damned way to the busstop. really lar. i was condemned to listening to his nonsense. sigh..pj. fully fits my description of guai tai sch.  lol. ok. damn i wanna play Q-bert now. never fails to crack me up juz by suiciding the lil fella, or by touching a monster and watch him spout gibberish. HAHAHAHAH. @#%#^
     

        
</post>

<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
      WOO WHEE. I FOUND A WAY TO TRIX THE TRIX GURU. IT INVOLVES STUFFING TISSUE INTO THE HOLE WHICH THE LOCK IS SUPPOSED TO FIT IN. SUCH THAT THE LOCKED EFFECT IS THERE, BUT ALL I HAVE TO DO, IS PUSH HARDER AGAINST THE DOOR, AND VOILA THE DOOR OPENS. HURHUR. IF I PULL THIS OFF, THE STUPID DOOR SHALL HINDER ME NO MORE. WOO HOO. TRIXMASTA ROX YUO AND PWNS j00. ok anyway, today me, ben and jamie went to palms gardens to play bowling. 8 bucks for 2hrs. keke. yeah. not bad lar. i got 125 pinfalls. which is the highest i ever had in my life. so yeah dun laugh. oh btw, we were supposed to play bowling yesterday too, but cheryl had parental probs, and PINKIE conveniently pangsehed us. =P so left ben and jamie, but since the booking of the alley was based on an hourly basis, we din have enough time to get there in time. so decided to chuck the idea. i was kinda irritated cos everyone juz left like that. but woo, it was kinda a blessing in disguise. because today i saw the notice on the board outside the condo admin office. it read " The bowling alley will be closed on 8th and 9th march for reservice and maintenance." keke. so luckily we din go yesterday lar. hurhur.and to pinkie : eh rilak lar im not angry can. i was juz having a headache due to excessive dehydration. :D so cheers. asdfasdfasdf
     

        
</post>

<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
      today was a butt lousy day. =\
     

        
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
      eh damn it lar. praetorians is a 2002 game can. its an ANTIQUE. nvm, ben can play. hurhur. shall bring it for him tmr. 
     

        
</post>

<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
      keke. went for a movie juz now. watched "Honey". hmm, frankly speaking i wasn't really a big fan of hip hop and stuff before, but watching that show seriously made me change my mind. hurhur. sup y'all man in black wannabes. :D i loved that line. hurhur. altho imma trixmasta, trust me, the movie is good and i dun wanna trix u of ur monies. esp, those dance moves. woo wee. whiskey tango foxtrot. so catch it if u've got the time. =) eh..so glad xb and cheryl could join us. hmm, come to think of it. cheryl is a PSEUDO BRUDDER NOW. KEEKLES. WELCOME TO DA CLUB. HAHAHA. sian lar. no one to play gb with now. i shall go try out Praetorians. Looks kinda l337. keke. 
     

        
</post>

<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
      sian. life is so darn boring now. =\
     

        
</post>

<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
        Heart of Gold    urlLink   What is Your Heart REALLY Made of?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    keke. heart of gold. lol. =D
     

        
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
      hurhur. many pple asked me who that girl was. well, all i've gotta say is, U'VE BEEN TRIXXED. TRIXXED BY DA TRIXMASTA. :D HURHURHUR. yar lar. there's no other girl in my life now anyhow. all my time is like spent on gb and stuff. how to buaya. not like someone lar. hmm, how bout B _ N ? fill in the blank with a suitable vowel. =) eh yeah today was a great day. nice of cheryl to tag along even tho she didn't know most of the pple, actually she knew only me in fact. lol. oh well. but i thot she was really outgoing and sporty to hang out with a group she doesn't know. mm. nice nice. hurhur before that. i was actually up to some trix. we were standing at the 2nd floor of taka, overlooking the baby fair. xb and jamie were supposed to meet us, so i called them up, and told em that we were in the baby fair and that they shud come and look for us there. HAHAHA. then frm the 2nd floor we could see jamie walking into the baby fair, surrounded by pacifiers, diapers, and baby toys. LOL. DAMN KEEKLISH. xb nearly got trixxed lar. stupid ben had to show his big balloony head. hurhur. anyway, after that we had lunch at bk at cine, then walked arnd aimlessly for a while. xb and ben juz had to give me stupid faces now and then lar. like seriously, there's nothing going on dey. doh. ya then i went home while cheryl, ben and jamie went back to sch for trng. haha. oh well. quite a fun day. i thot it was quite nice to be able to meet up with xb and shanna again. and btw, shanna looks weird in a skirt. KEEKLES. :P
     

        
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
      ahah. the bored dude has come to blog again. alv's away at trng, xb's bathing. no gb kakis. :( hmm. lets see. did nothing much today except go lot 1. turns out that NO ONE msged me. oh well. at least there's sch tmr. but no one will be going anyway. :\ hmm. so many people i know are going away. some going to other jcs, others going to poly. i'll miss em. but on the other hand, i hope the 2nd batch will be better. tho its always not the case. but i can always hope for the better. =) i was thinking this afternoon when i came home, in my quiet room, whether have i come to like this certain girl, or is she just something which i use to fill the void in my heart, or rather a substitute. i've always been serious with this kinda r/ship stuff, and i'm strongly against playing with people's feelings. hurhur. unlike some people i know. whose name COULD start with B and end with N. lol. and i dun walk around looking at girls like most guys do anyhow. but i'm not a fsking gay or something. doh. its just me i guess, and i believe that u don't have to look around to find that special someone, u'll find each other. haha..to most people i know, gb might be the most impt thing in my life now. lol. that's true. but the fact is i've got nothing better to do anyway. but i'd rather go out and socialise then stay at home the whole day (eg. today). bah. nvm. Gb time. =) btw, i'm not gonna say who's the girl. so dun ask. =P
     

        
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
      sian. boring day. went to swim and bowl at ben's condo. met alv at lot 1 to have lunch. went home and gb-ed all the way. sian leh. tmr also another same day. argh. eh. anyone who wanna go out or juz need company, drop me an sms. i'm so fsking bored. =\ k lar. sounds like i'm prostituting myself. whatever. 
     

        
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>


           
      keekles. thanks to those who asked me how i was today in sch. altho they knew i was faking sick. but oh well. keke. kinda boring. juz played gb. gonna go off soon. lol hope everyone's taking care of themselves. kinda easy to fall sick now. and cheryl, rilak one korner and i hope u're enjoying ur camp. =)
     

        
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>


           
      keke. nv blogged for such a l0ng tyme. syan. din go to sch for 3 out of the 5 days this week. i pwned pee jay see. :D
     

        
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>


           
      keke. bored. anyways, here's a l337 foto which jy sent me. look who's in it. LLOLOLOOLOOL   
     

        
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>


           
      hmm. same old boring day. guess i still have some work left to do. =\ -shrugs-
     

        
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>


           
      lol good friday wasn't very good after all. did nothing much. bought a pair of l337 goggles tho. some jap brand which has degree so that i can finally see under water. hurhur. sigh. bored.
     

        
</post>

<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Oh. The Angst. :D btw, happy birthday alv. didn't give u a prezzie or anything. maybe tonite i treat u haojian. hurhur. essenceofhao4u? KEKEKEKE
     

        
</post>

<date>07,April,2004</date>
<post>


           
      lol. Has anyone ever wondered what does the word "friend" actually means? to most people, it might mean people whom u treasure, people whom u like to hang out with, etc. in pri schs, the kids even have best friends and such. i used to be like that too. until today when i was sitting in my room thinking, what actually does the word "friend" stand for? to me, its just names of people which i remember so that i can smile at them and call out their name. nothing more. something that u put at the back of ur head once u smile and greet them. how fake are sayings like "a true friend never walks out on you", or whatsoever. the thing is, how do u define true friend? to one person, u might be their "true friend", but on the other hand, u might not be "their" "true friend". its just a matter of perspective. so in other words, the saying cant be correct. perhaps to some people, once they find more entertaining friends, they leave their "old" friends behind, thus contradicting the phrase "friends forever". whoever came up with that seriously takes the whole thing too lightly. in fact, there's no such thing as friends forever. its just a phrase to relieve the so-called pain and suffering when people part. that's it. and if u take my definition of "friend" just being a name to remember, then "friends forever" is legit. because its no problem to remember a name for life. ultimately, u cant depend on ur friends. that's what i've learnt. i''m not biased or anything, but i think its better to depend on urself rather than to seek help frm ur "friends". -shrugs- how ridiculous this god damned world is. i'm so glad i'm in it. to hell with social skills.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>


           
      lol. Had pe two days in a row today. How fun is that. Did circuit yesterday, and lan sai 9 rounds today. Woo whee. 9 rounds in 14 mins. Kekeke. And I realized its extremely irritating to wear a XXL pe shirt to run. Stupid sleeves. Lol I wore it to loh tuan summore. Looked like a karung guni man. Anyways, met alv there, then Cheryl came later. Had the usual tok c0ck ala mat jokes session with the bing. Wanted to buy my billab0ng shirt. But argh dunno why I didnt buy. Juz didnt feel like it I guess. Nvm I shall buy it on thurs or fri. keke. Then I shall wear it with board shorts and look like a true blue hip hop surfer dude. HAHA. Lol today I zhupped canoeing trials. They told me there was a mat who did 3 pull ups, but only 8 push ups. And I mean eight. EIGHT NIAAAA. Actually can tell lar. He looks seriously scrawny. Even pinky can pwn him tombaleh. Plus with her pink shoes as her l337 weapons, the mat WILL be pwned TOMBALEH-LEH. DOUBLE PWNED. DOUBLE BREWED. DOUBLE h4XED. K. dunno wad shit Im saying but Im typing this in Microsoft word now. And that explains "the bing", cos its supposed to be iced milk tea. Yeah juz as my name is  the jin yu . Lol. Hurhur trix trix. My mum thinks I'm doing gp essay now.  Keke. Too bad she didn't see the amount of red and green underlines. Hahez. Wtf I am seriously crapping. Oh well, I'm going swimming tmr alone. And guess what regent sec is having their sports meet at the sports complex tmr. That means it will be damn crowded. Darn. Hmm, can anyone sponsor me monies? I wanna buy a pair of jeans. I juz realized I dun have any longs in my wardrobe. Hurhur. I really envy gunbound biatch lor. Everyday juz go work, slack arnd and earn lotsa monies. Asdfasdfsdfsdafsdfasdf. Bored. =( my sms is like under-used can. No one smses me. Except for 11124. go figure. Nvm. I shall apply to wacky sms. Hahez. The gals are so kewt and h0t. lol damn I better stop now. This is serious crap. Im juz writing whatever comes to my mind. Anyway, out of boredom, I trixxed scott. Hence, I shall now name it "SCOTT THE TRIXXED." Keke. Heres a l337 pictar for u all. :D   
     

        
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>


           
      hmm. i juz realised i spouted a whole shit load of crap. -shrugs- well, off to sleep now. its late. =)
     

        
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>


           
      hmm. hardly have any time to blog nowadays. but oh well. here i am. to get straight to the point, i'm confused. confused as a mat finding a korner in a circle, confused as an indian looking at himself in the mirror in a dark room. that's right. i'm confused. not about what i'm thinking, but what i should do. its so much like deja vu. and finally i know how she felt last time. because the decision to make on what to do, no matter what, will change everything. its just like telling ur buddy u like her, and all of a sudden, the two of you feel awkward and break off. its just so delicate, the human emotion. i've not felt like this for a few months, its the same feeling i felt almost 1 yr ago, but after being through a relationship before, i can't help but feel a sense of dread. a sense of what might happen if this all goes wrong. i told myself, not to have anymore r/ship committments, mainly because its stressful and i've got no more confidence in this sorta thing. but much as the rational mind works the body, the heart works on its own. and much as i try not to get involved in anything, i still fail to do so. to many people, i'm a gunbound freak. but however, its a sort of means with which i run from reality. ben keeps telling me so and so likes me, that, i don't know, but i do know that as much as i wanna run away, all i want is someone to be here with me. its not that i'm desperate, but who wouldn't want anyone to love? and that's why i'm back to the beginning. i'm confused abt what i should do. if i make the wrong move, i lose a good friend. even if i make the correct move, i really do not think that i would want any committments now. to put it bluntly, i'm afraid i will not be able to keep them. besides, i'm not even sure how she feels. maybe its best to keep it this way, for now.   
     

        
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>


           
      lol. today i took some l337 quiz and i was some golden retriever. and one of the traits that i have, is "being able to withstand incredible emotional pain, but still able to stay committed.". hmm, wonder if that's true. oh well.
     

        
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      haha. life's bland for me nowadays. been gaming most of my time away. talknig to cheryl and jiahui online now. cheryl's telling me abt her sch and friends, jiahui that noob is tinkering with her ipod. heh. ben's getting along better with huiwen now. glad to know that he's feeling better since last saturday. glad to know that after god knows how long he's been trixxing, he's finally found the special someone. heh. and that feeling is way different frm being with other people. i still wanna see if u can still kao pei me abt being too loyal. haha its damn funny when he says this to me. "eh fysh, dun trix huiwen leh. plspls. i beg yuo." HAHAHA. wtf? i'll show u what she said nex tyme lar. u'll laugh. whahha. hm, hols are here. tyme to get my jeans. AT LONG LAST. 
     

        
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      ben's feeling fucked up now. and that's the feeling which i know. i've been there, done that and in fact been through more than him in this aspect. but as much as i know he wanna give up and throw everything away, he cant help it but just hold on. and then sometimes, i think to myself.   You don't love a person because he makes you laugh. You don't love a person because he's handsome. You don't love a person because he's Mr. Popular. You don't love a person because he messsages you "I love you" everynight. Rather,  You love him because You know that he loves you  As much as you love him.  And that's all that matters. 
     

        
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      lol. firstly, i've gotta comment on the narrow minded-ness of people nowadays. u ask someone for the email of another person, and they assume u wanna buaya her, jio her, trix her. whatever. wtf does asking for someone's number/contact = to flirting? that is unless u're that kind lar. but if u're doing it out of sincerity, and just really wanna make new friends. i dun see anything wrong. lol not only that. she refused to give me the email, plus she commented abt one whole shit load of crap. fuck off lah. i dun need u to give me ur crap. stupid acsian shit. pls lar if i'm the kind who goes arnd asking for people's numbers, i wont be me. fucking hell u ask arnd lar. this is the first fucking time i'm asking for someone else's email. and that's because 1. she stays in the choa chu kang area, 2. i see her every morning in my mum's car on my way to school, 3. i've seen her arnd even before she came into pjc, and lastly, i juz wanna fucking make more friends cos pjc is one big fucked up graveyard. plus i've always been devoted to the one person. u've got a problem with that? sue me. "cos the best is fucking yet to be". ah well. i cant be bothered now anyway. i've been asking arnd, which is so not me. makes me seem like i'm so desperate, which i'm not. i'll just take things one step at a time. dun wanna seem like some desperate fool. 
     

        
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      lol. i juz realised that my classmate knows c****. keekles. that makes it one step easier for me to know her. benita hasnt replied my msg yet. gah so slow. sian lar. there's lantiu physics test tmr. oh yeah. this morning there was this lantiu indian kid who ran in between me and ben for no fucking reason. of cos i kaobei-ed. and it went like this.  Me: Simi lanjiao? Nigga: what lanjiao? dun think i dunno wad lanjiao means. Me: yeah that's you. so fuck off. =) and stupid nigga juz ran off. keekles. PWNED. wanted to type an essay on what i thought abt christianity. but oh well. shant. keekles to u alv.
     

        
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      haha. maths sucked. and so will physics and chem. :) MASS COMMIE FOR ME. FUX j00 NOOBS. 
     

        
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Hmm, i was wondering what my life lacked. And i realised it was adventure. so many months of not canoeing, and i've almost forgotten the feeling of canoeing thru choppy waters with the possiblity of capsizing any second. The thrill, the excitement, was what i joined canoeing for in the 1st place. but i'm outta it due to a shoulder injury. and it sucks. i'm just sitting at home doing nothing and eating a lot. just today, i ate 1 packet of beehoon for breakfast, 1 packet of prawn noodles and 1 packet of carrotcake for lunch, and 1 whole pizza plus garlic bread plus chicken drumlets. waddafuk. ok anyways. i was saying that i lacked adventure and thrills in my life. i wanna try paintball and white water rafting. i want excitement to flow thru me instead of countless physics and mathematical formulas. mm, i'm listening to Red Rain - Summer now. and i just love this phrase. "blue skies and long hot summer days, white sands and surfing in the bays." there's nothing like a warm summer day and me doing some water sports. hmm, or perhaps i can go to new zealand to stay and play with kiwis. i've always loved kiwis. my fav shirt when i was young used to be some new zealand shirt which my uncle bought back. it had a kiwi on it. uber cute.
     

        
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      hmm. i'm feeling chirpyyyyy now. had a good laugh at supper just now. that was what i needed i guess. =) dont mind my previous angst post guys. i just had to release some steam and i'm feeling better now. at least i aint sleepin at 9.30pm no more. keke. no hard feelings, but if u can read between the lines and all the swear words, u shud know what i'm trying to say yea?  oh btw. uber l337 mp3 player which xb showed me.  here's the link. KEKKEE http://www.hbe.co.kr/english/product/xdrum_mp3/mp3_xd403.htm
     

        
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
        Slytherin! You're classy to the core, favoring the traditionally finest things the world has to offer. While you may or may not be evil *wink* you certainly have the power and attitude to get what you want. You're clever as all heck, and tend to be a couple steps ahead of even the most astute Ravenclaw.     urlLink   A More Unique Hogwarts Sorting Quiz     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     

        
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      ok now i'm gonna address the irritance that has been bugging me since yesterday. if i sound offending, so be it. its all my thoughts and i dun give a flying fuck what u've gotta say. ok yesterday was ben's bdae, and we all went out to have a good time, or at least wanted to. first part of it was ok, went to the stadium, then went on to town to meet huiwen. we were still laughing and joking. went on to play pool, but halfway thru huiwen got a call from some jackass and so she went to some remote area to talk to him. i could tell something was not right, so i went to look for her. asked ben abt it, and he said "dun care lar dun care lar". so ok nvm, i went alone. waited for her to finish talking, then asked her abt it. tried to cheer her up a lil. that's all.  went back to play pool, and i thought "okay maybe everything's alright now". and went to have lunch after playing pool. as we were walking, huiwen was more or less talking to me along the way, and ben was with xb. ok perhaps that made u jealous ben, but what the fuck if u are just gonna keep to urself, dont expect her to come tagging by ur side. everyone prefers someone whom they can talk and laugh to, i'm sure she aint an exception. and there i was just trying to keep her entertained, or would u rather she stone off into the distance? perhaps if u would have joined in, things might warm up between u and her, dont u think? i'm content just to play the fucking middle man. not like i didnt leave u guys to urself. i went into DKNY to look at women's clothing. like how fucking interesting can it get? i just didnt wanna see 2 faces. one's BEN'S "MI SI PWNED" FACE, AND two's HUIWEN'S "HI IMMA GARGOYLE" face.(in case u didnt get it. its the STONED face.) ok nvm. then when we went into the food court, ben and xb happily went to "shop". so obvious they were gonna talk stuff abt me and her. well, fuck off lar. i hate people talking behind my fucking back. but its alright. i tolerated it. i figured xb might be the only one with the clean mind and of neutral standing to talk to ben. but no, when they came back, i felt so fucking like an alien, like a fucking muslim who doesnt believe in Allah. and when xb and i walked outta wisma, he said "i think u shud have a good talk with ben". well, i'm not going to. if by now u still do not understand me, i'm not going to fucking talk to u. what brothers can we be if u have no faith in me. wtf she aint gonna be my next target. pls lar if i were to be ur competitor, i'd have pwned u hands down. trust me. and i suppose u've noticed quite a number of "perhaps" in my blog post? just maybe if u had fulfilled those "perhaps", ur bdae might have been a much more enjoyable one. and here i was trying to make it more lively, but got suspected instead. u guys seriously pissed me off to the living hells, so much so i just went home, ate cup noodles and went to sleep at 9 fucking 30 pm. well ben, i only have 3 pieces of advice for u.   1. Dont be so passive about everything. she's a girl, u're the guy. make ur move. 2. The best way to get someone u like is to just be urself. what's up with all the "stop swearing within 2 weeks" shit. u cant stop swearing, everyone knows that. if she cant accept it, so be it. and jealousy will ONLY cause ur downfall. trust me. i've been there, and i've changed. 3. Dont keep on saying "I DONT CARE I DONT CARE". BECAUSE U DO. TOO MUCH. QUIT DELUDING URSELF. DO SOMETHING TODAY.  ok thats all i've gotta say. at least i've gotten everything off my chest. take it or leave it. 
     

        
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Dashboard Confessions - Vindicated  Hope dangles on a string Like slow spinning redemption Winding in and winding out The shine of it has caught my eye  And roped me in So mesmerizing, so hypnotizing I am captivated  {Chorus} I am Vindicated I am selfish I am wrong I am right I swear I'm right I swear I knew it all along  And I am flawed  But I am cleaning up so well I am seeing in me now the things you swore you saw yourself  So clear Like the diamond in your ring Cut to mirror your intentions Oversized and overwhelmed The shine of which has caught my eye  And rendered me  So isoloated, so motivated I am certain now that  {Chorus}  So turn Up the corners of your lips Part them and feel my finger tips Trace the moment, fall forever Defense is paper thin Just one touch and I'd be in Too deep now to ever swim against the current So let me slip away (3x) So let me slip against the current So let me slip away (4x)  {Chorus}  Slight hope It dangles on a string Like slow spinning redemption... 
     

        
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      for some reason i woke up at 4.35am. so decided to use the comp. my mind is like so full of thoughts now. so full that its overflowing. how irritating. i shall go for a jog now. perhaps it will open my mind up to other stuffs. =) 
     

        
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      hmm. 12.20 am. and i'm feeling nostalgic again. whenever i look down frm my block, i see an empty park, an isolated playground, a long canal, and a sparse highway. and i cant help but think abt everything that has happened to me thru out the 17 yrs of my life. the people i've met, the stuff i've been through, everything just surfaces at this point of time. hmm, right now, i'd like to climb up some really high place, lie down and look at the night sky and just ponder. huiwen asked me this outta nowhere "is it possible to stay devoted to a person forever?" i dont think anyone knows the answer. its just as impossible to answer as "is it possible to love a person forever?" so much paradoxes, so much ironies in life. yet day by day we ask ourselves the same question over and over again. girls like to ask emselves if relationships will work out. they contemplate day and night abt stuff which is like totally irrelevant to the entire issue. the thing is, how would u know if u dont give it a try? i'm not trying to be sexist or whatsoever. but that's whats happening to most of the guy friends arnd me now. and its irritating to keep on discovering that its the same problem thats bugging them all. kinda funny that its now the guys who get pwned by girls. i wonder why. 
     

        
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      fried 6 pwns j00.   urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      oreo 4 u again  urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      alv teh si n00b  urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      haojian after ritual  urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      haojian before ritual  urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      oreo4u  urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
          F     Flirtatious       I     Intelligent       S     Serious       H     Humorous       Name / Username:       urlLink Name Acronym Generator  From  urlLink Go-Quiz.com   REALLY MEH. since when was i flirtatious. =\
     

        
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I SEE RED RAINING DOWN ON ME AS FAR AS THE EYE CAN SEE I SEE RED RAINING DOWN.  ON MY KNEES RED RESCUED ME NOW I CAN FLYYYYYY lIKE A BIRD IN THE SKY THERE"S NO MOUNTAIN  THAT I CANNOT CLIMB  whoo. the red rain concert i went to yesterday was seriously uber tuber ruber good! RED RAIN ROX j00. KEKEKE.
     

        
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      AFTER : HAY. I LOOK SO DIFFERENT AND NISE, DONT I? KEKEKE.   urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      BEFORE : this is a uber fugly pictar of me =(  urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      and yes, lastly, ben the n00b. and guess what? he's the vice presisdent of the "huiwen SI N00B CLUB"! oh u already knew? guess it isnt much of a suprise then. only ben's suprised. just look at him. *GASPS* KEKEKE. 1X HOH SEI FOR U BEN. AHAHHAHA ps: CLICK ON THE PICTURE FOR A VERY HOH SEI VERSION. KEKEKKE   urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink    KEKEKE.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink    KEKEKE. 1X RALPH LAUREN SHIRT FOR YUO. &nbsp; urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      HAHAHA. THIS SI THE ULTIMATE TRIXXOR. KEKEKEKKE. 4X HOH SEI FOR ALL OF U. well, actually its just extreme boredom.  Disclaimer : this was just done for fun. no religious blasphemy, no comtemplated ridicule. in short, PLs dun pwn me. kthnxbey. KEKEKE
     

        
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink    KEKE. lASTLY, A KEEKLISH GIRL AT DA BEACH. APPARENTLY, SHE HAS LONG EARS TO KEEP HERSELF COOl, L337 GLASSES TO POSE, AND A SUNBURNT NOSE. OH PLUS A MOUSTACHE TOO! &nbsp; urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink    HAHAHA. DISNEY4U. KEKEKE. THE MINNIE MOUSE WHICH SAYS "HAY!" KEKE. HOW CUTE. :P&nbsp; urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink    OK. THIS SI THE GYPSY OF TEH FUTURE. SOME HOW. GYPSIES NOW HAVE UBER l337 PURPLE TURBANS AND FANGS. PLUS THEY"RE ISLAMIC TOO. KEKEKEKE&nbsp; urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink    KEKE. HAS ANYONE WONDERED WHO WAS THE MASTERMIND BEHIND THE "BAND" PLAYING AT LOH TUAN? WELL, ALV IS. KEKEKEKEKE. *tOSSES 10 CENTS*&nbsp; urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      we were both 16 and it felt so right. sleepin all day, stayin up all night. says: CUT CUT CUT we were both 16 and it felt so right. sleepin all day, stayin up all night. says: CUT we were both 16 and it felt so right. sleepin all day, stayin up all night. says: CUT OUR WRISTS we were both 16 and it felt so right. sleepin all day, stayin up all night. says: SLASH OUR VEINS we were both 16 and it felt so right. sleepin all day, stayin up all night. says: LET OUR BLOOD FLOW we were both 16 and it felt so right. sleepin all day, stayin up all night. says: AND WE ALL SHOUT HOORAY c h e r -                                  *unexpected, what yu did to myy heart. =) says: HOORAY! c h e r -                                  *unexpected, what yu did to myy heart. =) says: ahaha c h e r -                                  *unexpected, what yu did to myy heart. =) says: oh my c h e r -                                  *unexpected, what yu did to myy heart. =) says: u si n00b c h e r -                                  *unexpected, what yu did to myy heart. =) says: u're actually learnin frm chief n00b 
     

        
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      hmm..just woke up. had some really weird dream of me getting pwned. by what, i forgot. gah. less than 2wks left for the hols. time seriously flies past damn quickly when u're sitting at home doing nothing. =( 
     

        
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      hahez 2 all. today was a si quite okay day. bummed arnd in the morning, then went to town in the afternoob. kekeke. so glad to see xb again. but i'm not gay. oh and ben joined us too. keke. 2x hoh sei. nothing much, juz walked around, and played a lil pool, then headed to loh tuan for dinner. mm, i tried the grilled whitefysh. not bad lar, but kinda bland. oh and saw kai kiat too. haha that clown still looks as goofy as ever. saw quite a couple of chinese high people also. but didnt know them well. so yeah. been noticing quite a few people falling sick lately, here's a shout out to u all to drink more water and get more rest yeah? pls dont bei1 bei1 too much. hurhur. in case u're wondering, bei1 bei1 = mug. literally, and yes its a pun too. kekeke. 
     

        
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      today, was another utterly boring day. i've not really seriously started revision yet. gotta start it nex wk or sumthing. dun wanna get triple Fs. lol. and while i was rotting at home, miss huiwen went to the beach, then went to a bar, then went for dinner. so much so she didnt bother replying smses. :P hmm, gonna watch some movies, and they're The Punisher, and spiderman 2? tho sequels arent really as nice as the original. keke. getting quite sick of maksim's classical music. Rock music still rox yuo. :)
     

        
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Broken - Seether ft. Amy Lee  I wanted you to know that I love the way you laugh I wanna hold you high and steal your pain away I keep your photograph not knowing it serves me well I wanna hold you high and steal your pain   Because I'm broken when I am lonesome and I dont feel right when you go away  You go away You dont feel me...anymore  The worst is over now and we can breathe again I wanna hold you high and steal my pain away Theres so much left to learn and no one left to fight I wanna hold you high and steal your pain   Because I'm broken when I am open and I dont feel right I am strong enough  Because I am broken when I am lonesome and I dont feel right when you go away  Because I'm broken when I am open and I dont feel right now I am strong enough  Because I'm broken when I am lonesome and i dont feel right when you go away  Because I'm broken when I am lonesome and I dont feel right when you go away  You go away You dont feel me...anymore  This Song rox yuo. in case u're wondering, its the OST frm The Punisher. keke. imma gonna watch it. violence galoreee :D
     

        
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      hmm, went out to town with huiwen and her friend today. was kinda bored at first cos they had to walk arnd looking for girly stuffs like happy house pins and pens, ankle socks, and hair clips. nearly fell asleep walking. hurhur. anyways, huiwen's friend left for her class chalet at 3 plus, so hw and i went to paragon to have xiao long baos. hurhur. she's so noob can. she never ate em b4. k lar i was a n00b last tyme also. kekeke. walked arnd a lil after eating. kekeke. at least i wasnt so bored after that. hurhur. then went to mambo to meet alv and the tr0ll. went home. tired. :)
     

        
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink     What Color is Your Brain?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    At work or in school: I like to be with people, sharing with them, inspiring them, and helping them. I work and learn best when I can take into consideration people and the human element. I flourish in an atmosphere of cooperation. With friends: I always look for perfect love. I am very romantic, and I enjoy doing thoughtful things for others. I am affectionate, supportive and a good listener. With family: I like to be happy and loving. I am very sensitive to rejection from my family and to family conflicts. I really like to be well thought of and need frequent reassurance. I love intimate talks and warm feelings. 
     

        
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      KEKEKE. woke up at 8 today cos alv the si chief noob smsed me. went to kopitiam to eat laksa. then ben came over. ranted a whole shit load. then left. then alv, troll and I went to town. i bought my first pair of levi's 512s. MUAHAHAHAHA. 1x HOH SEI. plus i saw some uber l337 nautica polo tee. WAH THAT ONE DAMN HOH SEI. 2x HOH SEI FOR ME. then once i buy the nike polo tee. WAH SEH 3X HOH SEI. KEKEKEKE. yeah then walked arnd doing nothing. then back to lot1 to have dinner and played a lil of pool. end of my day. si sian. i wanna KOMBUST myself. KEKEKE. I SI TEH CHIEF NOOB.   REALLY MEHREALLY MEHREALLY MEHREALLY MEHREALLY MEHREALLY MEHREALLY MEHREALLY MEHREALLY MEHREALLY MEHREALLY MEH
     

        
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      hmm. lotsa stuff have been happening arnd me lately. especially Mr. A, who is frustrated over r/ship problems now. the overall situation was something like this. He got to know some girl in his sch thru her senior. and then started to sms each other and stuff like that, talk on the phone, and then go out on dates. they got quite close, and kinda had feelings for each other. but one day, the girl says " i've been thinking alot lately and i think we're just better off as friends." naturally, Mr A would be disappointed and depressed. If u were Mr.A, how would u react? if i were Mr.A, naturally i'd be devastated, depressed, and feeling emotionally drained. its the feeling of "after everything and all the feelings i've put in, is this what i get in return?" furthermore, i'll feel cheated and being led on. i'll wanna juz tell her to fuck off and die u stupid biatch. even when she smses, i'd feel reluctant to reply. on the contary, i'd be REALLY happy if she smsed me last time. but, can u actually do that to the one whom u have feelings for? are u able to risk it all, destroy all the bridges which the 2 of u have built thru time, with "fuck off"? i dont think so. in addition, not only will u be missing her a lot, u'll be sorta "desperate". but seriously, i dont think she's leading u on. also, i dun think she would want to see u like that too. i just think she's being rational. that she puts a lot of thought into considering. it just shows that she takes it seriously. i dont think she's taking u for granted. trust me. she still likes u. but i'm sure she has her own reasons. well, u've got 2 choices. one is to juz fuck it, or one is to wait. u decide. the 2nd outcome will be like mine. but hey, as long as u know that what u're waiting is worth waiting for, then why not? its the human emotion which makes us homo sapiens different frm animals. :)
     

        
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
         KAT *WINKS* IMMA KITTY KAT AND I DANCE DANCE DANCE AND I DANCE DANCE DANCE 
     

        
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      wtf. i screwed my own blog up. thanks to my itchy fingers and boredom. allahu akbar. KEKEKEK
     

        
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I feel so broken up  And I give up   I just want to tell you so you know  Here I go, Scream my lungs out and try to get to you  You are my only one   I let go,  There's just no one that gets me like you do  You are my only, my only one 
     

        
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      &nbsp;  SIAN LEY.  
     

        
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      boredom is eating me inside out. :\ *plops head back on chair.* 
     

        
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Everywhere i go, i keep getting shit frm Christianity. Just yesterday, i got this pamphlet that had these words on the front. "PLEASE DO NOT READ THIS". lol. wassup. christianity going into reverse psycho now? i flipped it open, read it a lil. the gist was like, if u do not do this, this will happen to u, and that people now only use God in swear words. its&nbsp;kinda like, if u do not believe in God, u will go to hell. and the way they put it is really subtle. this is what i interpreted. "Hey (reader)! God is great! God can salvage your soul, IF u believe in Him! but if u dont, its alright! just that u'll go to Hell only. :)" how fucking pseudo. some assclown gave it to me at the Orchard Mrt station. I read it in the Mrt. I swore. I got out&nbsp;at Newton. I threw it away&nbsp;with disgust. Sorry lar but i see no point in joining a religion which coerces other people to join em. Oh, did I mention&nbsp;I was Anti-Christ? Guess so. -shrugs-&nbsp; 
     

        
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      hurhurs. somehow i realised my blog is more than 1 yer old. keke. how wundarful. i just hope i can keep it going. :) 
     

        
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Someone please tell me this is not chio.   urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      20 things I like 1. White 2. My Fav music 3. Shellfysh 4. Classy girls 5. Watching cartoons 6. Gaming 7. Hanging out 8. Being Racist 9. Talking Nonsense 10. Doing gym 11. Talking to new people 12. Cursing and swearing 13. Being Anti-Christ 14. Eating really expensive stuffs 15. Star/Moon gazing 16. Bbqs/Chalets 17. Day-dream 18. Taking little walks 19. Coming up with puns, puns, and more puns.  20. Being Myself. :)  20 things i dislike: 1. Malays. 2. Indians. 3. Nigga Musik. 4. Psuedo People. 5. Whiney guys. 6. Wussies. 7. Guai Tais. 8. IMMENSELY quiet people. 9. Cold Weather. 10. Exceedingly Enthusiastic people. 11. Going to school. 12. NKF and all sorta charity shows.  13. Yam 14. Travelling around. 15. Being around people whom I dont even know. 16. Having no monies. 17. Not being able to get what i want. 18. Having committments.  19. Fucked up stuff. 20. asdfasdfasdf  ok. keke. anyways after MT day today i went to watch I,Robot with jamie, daryl, and ass-ther. gotta say that it was a Fantabulous movie la. i'll give it a rating of 8/10. everyone shud go watch it. and i simply cant wait for Aliens Vs Predator to come out. cheesebun that one is a MUST WATCH. anyway i'm bored. :\ JusTea Aloe Vera si nise. 
     

        
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      just came back frm buying paper plates and stuff for the Mt day shit tmr. tired. gonna sleep. 
     

        
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      just came on to burn a cd for shahul. so i thought i'd might as well blog a lil since i've kinda disappeared for quite a while. hurhur. anyways i'll not be coming online that often anymore till promoos are over so yeah dont miss me. and yes i am mugging now. hurhur u guys might not believe it, but just wait and see yea? :) oh and darn it i'm in charge of some lantiu booth on saturday's mt day, so drop by and visit alright? it ends at 12.30 pm&nbsp;and i'm so darn free after that. movie, anyone? :) 
     

        
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
            urlLink    border="0" alt="People like you becuase you're smart!" />     What attracts people to  you?       brought to  you by     href="http://quizilla.com">Quizilla              fuck lar. i'm at alv's house now cos i didnt fucking bring my damned  key and i cant fucking go home cos my parents went out at the last  minute. they trixxed me. cheesebun.  
     

        
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      this is the mp3 playa i'm gonna get. kekeke. nisenise. :)  urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      hmm. kinda not blogged for quite some time. been busy lately, with chaos legion and work. hurhur. sorry guys if i didnt reply ur messages on msn. i just left my comp on, as usual and went to sleep. i'm not ignoring u guys! so relax ok. lololol. just had tuition frm 8-10 oclock. gotta say that although it was kinda boring, i learnt a lot lar. i hope it'll be a stepping stone to rebuilding my motivation to study. :) anyways, gonna sleep now. and i hope i can get my creative muvo slim tmr. =D 
     

        
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      gahahaha. got this off gabriel's bloggah. it si 1x funny lo. read it. kEKEKEKKEEKKE  L0rd of teh Ringz0r  F3ll0wsh1p of teh R1ng   [At Bilbo's 111th Birthday]  Merry: "Omg, I pwn"  Pippin: "Sif, I pwn"  **Rocket goes off  Gandalf: "Pwned!"   Bilbo: "This = shiz, bai foos"  Bilbo has left the server  Frodo: "wtf!?"   [later, in Bag End]  Gandalf: "Give teh ringz0r to Frodo"  Bilbo: "Sif! It r precious!"  Gandalf: "STFU NOOB!!!"  Bilbo: "ok"  Gandalf has logged on as admin  Bilbo has been kicked from The Shire   **Later  Gandalf: "Show me teh ring, foo!"  **Gandalf rides out, does some research, comes back  Gandalf: "OMGZ, it R teh ring!"  Frodo: "wtf?"  Gandalf has logged on as admin  Frodo has been kicked from The Shire  Sam has been kicked from The Shire   [At Isengard]  Gandalf: "sup dawg, i r g4nd4lf da gr3y!"  Saruman: "Foo! U R teh noob!"  Gandalf: "wtf?!"  Saruman: "Sauron pwns joo!"  Gandalf: "Sif, I R leet"  **Sarumon beats the sh*t out of Gandalf  Saruman: "Pwned!"   [on the road to Bree]  Merry: "look foos, shrooms!"  Pippin: "Woot! Shrooms!"  Frodo: "Ph34r!"  Sam: "Shrooms!"  Frodo: "PH34R!1!1"  **black rider stops, sniffs, goes past  Frodo: "OMG, packetloss!"   [Bree, in the Inn of the Prancing Pony]  **Frodo is drinking and dancing on a table, then slips  Frodo has left the server  Frodo has connected to the server  Frodo: "OMGz, dc'd"  Aragorn: "OMG, noobz"   [at Weathertop]  Merry: "Mmm, shrooms!"  **MERRY IS BROADCASTING HIS IP ADDRESS!!!  Frodo: "Foos! Ph34r teh haxorz"   **the black riders attack  Merry: "OMG!!!"  Sam: "O.M.G!!!11"  Pippin: "plz"  Frodo has left the server  **head nazgul stabs Frodo's ghost  Frodo has connected to the server  Frodo: "wtf... hax!"  **Aragorn lraps into the fray with a flaming brand  Aragorn: "PH34r!!!!!!"  Merry: "LOLOL flamed! "   [on the road to Rivendell]  Aragorn: "ZOMG!Arwen!"  **Arwen rides up  Aragorn: "A/S/L? Wanna net secks?"  Arwen: "Sif! wtf is up with Frodo?"  Sam: "teh leet Hax0r "  Arwen: "Firewall?"   **Arwen rides off with Frodo, the nazgul give chase. Arwen crosses the ford at Rivendell.  Arwen: "PH34R!! My dad pwns urs!"  **nazgul start to cross  Arwen: "LOLOLOLO noobs!!1!"  **the ford rises up and washes the nazgul away  Warning: Connection Problems Detected  nazgul has disconnected  nazgul has disconnected  nazgul has disconnected  nazgul has disconnected  nazgul has disconnected  nazgul has disconnected  nazgul has disconnected  Arwen: "Pwnt"   [at the Council of Elrond]  Gimli: "dwarves pwn!"  Legolas: "Sif, Elves pwn!"  Boromir: "OLOLOL noobs, men pwn!"  Elrond: "STFU tards!!1!"  **Frodo puts the ring on the plinth  Gimili: "Sif ring pwns all!"  **Gimli swings his axe at it, which shatters  Elrond: "**sigh, noob"   [Frodo meets up with Bilbo]  Bilbo: "OLOL, me = 10th level thief!"  Frodo: "OMG, u r teh pwn!"  Bilbo: "Do u still have teh ringz0r?"  **Frodo shows ***** the One Ring  Bilbo: "OMG u tard, I want to TK you!"  Frodo: "sif!"  Bilbo: "ph34r my mithril"   [The Fellowship leaves Rivendell]  **Gandalf leads the fellowship through the mountains  Legolas: "ZOMG, leet gfx!"  Gimli: "I R dropping frames! FFS"  **There's an avalanche which threatens to knock them off the shelf  Gimli: "Gandalf, teh draw distance is too far!1!!1"  Gandalf: "**Sigh. Moria?"  Gimli votes to change map to Moria  Votes 4 of 4 required  Legolas: "lolol Gimli, time to upgrade!"   [The fellowship approaches the gates of Moria]  Gandalf: "FFS, its too hard! Anyone got a walkthrough?"  **The gates of Mordor open, but the Guardian attacks!  Frodo: "OMG! ph34r!"  Boromir: "GL HF"  Aragorn [broadsword] guardian  Legolas [arrow] guardian  Gandalf: "gg"   [The fellowship enters the mines of Moria]  Gimli: "OMG!!!! PWNED!"   **After travelling some time in the dark the Fellowship come to a chamber with a large well  Gandalf: "teh bookz0r has some clues!"  **Merry knocks a skeleton in armour down the well  Gandalf: "OMG! noob!"  Merry: "d'oh"  **The fellowship hears the ork drums  Boromir: "wtf?"  Aragorn: "wtf?"  Frodo: "..."  Gandalf: "Oh ffs >. **the fellowhip shores up the doors as the orks come  Boromir: "TEAMS FFS!"  Aragorn [broadsword] ork  Gimli [axe] ork  Legolas [arrow] ork  Aragorn [broadsword] ork  Aragorn [broadsword] ork  Boromir [broadsword] ork  Gimli [axe] ork  Gimli [axe] ork  ork: "OMG! h4x!"  Gimli: "pwned"!  Legolas [arrow] ork  Legolas [arrow] ork  Legolas: "lol!!"  Boromir [broadsword] ork  Gimli [axe] ork  Gimli: "Foos!"  Legolas [arrow] ork  ork: "ffs, wallhax!"  **The cavetroll enters the chambers destroying the doors  Gandalf: "Oh ffs!"  Boromir: "Omg, its teh boss!"  Aragorn: "Sif noob, we're not at teh end yet!"  **Cavetroll slams Boromir and Aragorn out of the way, and then skewers Frodo  Sam: "OMG!"  Gandalf: "OMG!"  Aragorn: "omg, pwn!"  **Legolas jumps on the cavetroll and shoots arrows down into its head  Legolas [arrow] cavetroll  Ork: "OMG! PWNED!"  Gimli: "LOLOOLOL! noobs"  **The fellowship then runs through Moria, chased the whole way by a horde of orks  Boromir: "FFS! Teams, foos!"  **A flaming shadow starts to follow them, and the orks withdraw  Aragorn: "Now THIS is teh boss!"  Gandalf: "OMG!"  **The fellowship take to long flights of stairs that are starting to crumble and fall. Orks shoot at them with arrows.  Legolas: "LOL, noobs. Chex0r this out!1!"  Legolas [arrow] ork  Legolas [arrow] ork  ork: "AIMBOT!"  ork: "turn it off!"  Legolas: "lolol!"  **The fellowship crosses a bridge, Gandalf stops to confront the balrog  Gandalf: "joo shall not pass!"  Balrog: "wtf?"  Gandalf: "JOO SHALL NOT PASS!"  Balrog: "Sif, noob"  **Gandalf strikes the bridge with his staff, cracking it and causing it to break under the Balrog's weight  Balrog: "ZOMG! PWNED!"  Frodo: "OMG! Gandalf!"  **The Balrog falls and in a last act of defiance strikes out with its whip, entangling Gandalf  Gandalf: "D'oh"  Frodo: "OMG, joo foo!"  Gandalf: "fly u foos, fly!"  **Gandalf lets go and follows the Balrog into the crevass  Gandalf has left the server  Balrog has disconnected   [After escaping Moria the fellowship finds itself in Loth Lorien]  **The fellowship rests, and in the night Frodo speaks with Galadriel  Galadriel: "For a noob, u r teh leet!"  Frodo: "Sif. I don't want teh ringz0r. Do u want teh ringz0r?"  Galadriel: "omgplz! SIF I want teh ringz0r. I have enough h4x of my own!1"   [The fellowship leaves Loth Lorien and sets out via river]  Saurman: "ph34r my army of uruk hai! Go outz0r, find teh hobbitz and pwnz0r them!"  uruk hai: "leet!"   [stopping at the banks of the river, the Fellowship sets up camp]  **Frodo goes off looking for firewood, Boromir follows and confronts him  Boromir: "Gimmie teh ringz0r so ** hax can fight teh boss!"  Frodo: "Sif, foo. Punkbuster will pwn joo!"  Boromir: "Naw, we play on non-pb servers"  Frodo: "STFU noob"  Frodo has left the server  Boromir: "wtf! FRODO! Bring teh ringz0r back, faghat!"   **A group of Uruk Hai encounter Boromir  Boromir: "OH FFS, TEAMS!!"  Uruk Hai [arrow] Boromir  Uruk Hai [arrow] Boromir  Uruk Hai [arrow] Boromir  Uruk Hai [arrow] Boromir  Uruk Hai [arrow] Boromir  Uruk Hai [arrow] Boromir  Uruk Hai [arrow] Boromir  Uruk Hai [arrow] Boromir  Boromir: "f*cking campers"  **Aragorn comes across the battle  Aragorn: "Boromir joo noob! plz!"  Uruk Hai: "Hah, pwn!"  Aragorn [broadsword] Uruk Hai  Aragorn: "I bring joo teh pwn!"  **Aragorn goes to Boromir  Boromir: "Damn lag!"  Warning: Connection problems detected  Boromir has disconnected  Aragorn: "FFS!"   [Frodo returns to the bank of the river where he gets into a boat. Sam 'sees' him]  Sam: "Frodo! plz! Invisibility h4x!"  Frodo has connected to the server  Frodo: "Sam, STFU and FOAD!"  Sam: "Sif!"  Frodo: "Oh, ffs noob!"   End. 
     

        
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      gahaha. top in class for gp with 63 marks. wtf. someone tell me wtf is wrong with this world.
     

        
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      teehee. =) 
     

        
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      saw this on someone's bloggah. "like there was this one on what love is, and it says that love stems from a very long friendship, when you know each other so well, you could complete each other's sentence before the other finishes, you know exactly what's going on in each other's minds, and that you've accepted their faults. you don't have doubts of the other person when you're really in love" how very true. my sentiments exactly.
     

        
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      hurhur. i juz came back frm having a really nise dinner. went to some thai restaurant at taman jurong. total cost was 202 bux. keke. shark's fin and lobstar was GREAT. HURHUR. one bowl of shark's fin was like 25 bux lar. yum yum. plus the lobstars were fried with butter. whee. nise nise. hehe plus my sis didnt like her share of lobstar. so i took hers. in the end i ended up eating 3 LOBSTARS. HAHAHAHAHA. YUM YUM. PWNS j00. MEIRDAS.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      this one also lor.   urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      fux j00. this fone si nise can. =(  urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Train - Ordinary  Whose eyes am I behind I dont recognize anything that I see Whose skin is this design I dont want this to be the way that you see me  I dont understand anything anymore In this world that Im tired of Is taking me right up these walls That I climb up To get to your story Its anything but ordinary  And when the world is on its knees with me its fine And when I come to the rescue I get nothing but left behind Everybody seems to be getting what they need with mine Cause your what I need so very but im anything but ordinary  Can you save me from this world of mine Before I get myself arrested with this expectation You are the one look what youve done What have you done? This is not some kind of joke Youre just a kid You werent ready for what you did  And when the world is on its knees with me its fine And when I come to the rescue I do it for you time after time Everybody seems to be getting what they need with mine Cause you what I need so very but im anything but ordinary  I think im trying to save the world from you Youve been saving me too We could just stay in and save each other  Im anything but ordinary (ordinary) Im anything but ordinary (ordinary)  hurhur. this song ROX j00. MSG ME FOR IT. MERIDAS4U. KEKEE
     

        
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      hmm. why do people always feel depressed over emotional matters? in order for a relationship to kinda materialise, its gotta start with 2 people liking each other in the 1st place. but, very often, its only either one sided, there's some other guy/guys, or both sides are confused.  i shall touch on one sided-ness first. One sided-ness happens when A likes B, but B isnt really attracted to A. so therefore its only A feeling for B, but not B feeling for A. Therefore, things get quite difficult for B, who has to put up with all the sickeningly sweet stuffs that A does for her. Not that she doesnt appreciate it, but its awkward. And naturally B would feel guilty, as she's sort of "leading" A on. B could tell A that she doesnt like him, but A would most probably say, "i will wait for u." and stuff like that. personally, i'm not sure if things would work out between A and B. but what i think is, just try to drop subtle hints to put him off, or if things get worse, just tell him its impossible. its hard not to consider his feelings when telling him the truth, but at least u will prevent him from being more depressed in the end. but as for IRRITATINGLY persistant people, just tell them, to Fuck off. =) Ok next, the problem of the other guy/guys(or girl/girls). Everyone is bound to have people whom they have loved and liked before. Some forget easily, others find it lingering within them all the time. what i think is, if the person u like is constantly thinking abt her old flame, give her some time. approach her in a different manner, try to make her laugh, and play with her. if circumstance is good, have a good talk with her. find out more abt the other guy. BUT DO NOT PROBE. find out what she likes abt the other guy, and that will give u an advantage. share her problems, and share her joy. very soon, if nothing goes wrong, tadaa. =) (ps: Jealously is ABUNDANT in this kinda situation, so one thing to master is to curb ur jealousy NO MATTER WHAT) Ok last part. the situation where both sides are confused abt each other's feelings. very often, that is just brought abt by insecurity and lack of communication. how do u like someone seriously if u dont even know what he's tryng to say? and miscommunication always ruins things. 2 people cant possibly go out on a date and smile at each other for the whole day. sure. u might like him, u might want to make an impression. but trust me, guys or girls relate better to more active or playful people. so for a start, treat him as a friend. when u find that u can talk to him EVEN WITHOUT THINKING ABT WHAT TO SAY NEXT, then u know u can take the next step. one thing to note, whoever ur partner is, he should not only be ur boy/girlfriend, he should be ur soulmate, ur bestest best friend, and someone whom u have no qualms sharing ur problems with. =) hurhur. i think maybe next time i can be 1x marriage consultant. KEKEKEKE.  (to anyone who read this: i hope this helped. :) ) 
     

        
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      lol. no prizes for guessing who this is. =) FUX J00 NOOBS  urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      HAY. today rocked. :) chem test today. and GUESS WHAT? I KNEW HOW TO DO EVERYTHING EXCEPT 2 TOPICS, OF WHICH THEY ARE REDOX AND IDEAL GASES. WHOO!! WHOO!! KEKEKEKEK asdfasdfsdfsdf   unfortunately, those 2 topics made up about 5/8 of the paper. fuck.
     

        
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      bah..i feel bad to those people who thought i was online and msged me while i was happily sleeping. really sorry man. nowadays i can only come online, or rather, materialise after 10.30 pm. hurhur. that's when my parents sleep. i'm sorry if i kinda zhaoed halfway in the middle of e conversation ok? :) oh, and dren, i miss you too..and would really like to catch up with u. so, drop me a call or msg ok? hurhur. thats about it. i still cant figure out if u're in england or spore. :\ 
     

        
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      You are Blue Monkey, who is always smiling and are extremely cheerful.  That is your selling point.  If you can keep your cheerfulness, you would be able to lead a good life.  You have a big heart and are person of broad mind.  You are also very curious, and therefore can not leave still something that you don't know.  You tend to barge into almost everything.  You are a great researcher, and want to master one thing thoroughly. You are hard worker, and have a persistence to finish what you have started no matter what.  Nevertheless, the wish to quickly make ideals come true makes you impatient, and may lead to unpredictable failures. You tend to have sharp temper and are little bit too self confident.  And if this character comes out, it could lead to resentment.  But don't try to fear failures. If you follow the road, you won't have to experience failures, and you will definitely be able to gain success. You are good at making judgment on situations.  Your strength when it comes to a showdown is fantastic. Dedication and efforts towards work is extremely strong.  You bring up results constantly.  Although you care about the others, you have a narrow range of acquaintance, and therefore may be suited as a specialist or a researcher. 
     

        
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      she wanted to watch the NDP parade live. i wish i've gotten 2 tix so that i could ask her along. 
     

        
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      This is an excerpt frm one of my msn logs. :)  Hope is the waking dream. says: for me, i'm gonna wish em the best Hope is the waking dream. says: and i think ben's sharing the same feeling Hope is the waking dream. says: if ben can go up to her and say Hope is the waking dream. says: "hey if alv can make u happy, so be it. I wish u guys the best." Hope is the waking dream. says: what will huiwen think? Hope is the waking dream. says: being magnanimous earns u respect Hope is the waking dream. says: i'm sure she will respect him for that Hope is the waking dream. says: even all the bystanders Hope is the waking dream. says: will respect ben Hope is the waking dream. says: when ben swears and rants at them Hope is the waking dream. says: he gets nothing at all Hope is the waking dream. says: people think he's just plain jealous Hope is the waking dream. says: but when he wishes them the best Hope is the waking dream. says: they cant really say anything, and would also respect him. Hope is the waking dream. says: therefore he in fact, has won something from nothing Hope is the waking dream. says: and also learnt how to let go at times. Hope is the waking dream. says: i think thats the most impt lesson people have to learn.  So there you have it. The thought of the day. Sometimes being magnanimous will let u see the light after the storm. Don't think of it as a painful experience, think of it as enlightenment. :)
     

        
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Sometimes in life, we care too much. And it spoils the broth. I guess this is what's happening now. You know, I can just imagine ben's pain and anguish, huiwen's frustration, and since alv's her bf, I think he must be feeling pretty screwed up too. Question is, how did this whole thing end up like that? Very often, the unpredictable happens. And it not only affects the three of them, but also the people around them. I happen to be connected to all three of em. And right now, i guess I can't help but feel sorry. Yet, there's this feeling which I cannot describe. When Alv told me he was together with huiwen, I felt something. Something which I could not figure out even after thinking for the correct word for several hours. The fact that I'm sort of like a brother to both Alv and Ben doesnt make things easier. Personally, I dont think its anyone's fault. And I wont side with anyone. I just think this whole event was really sudden, so I only hope it'll settle down after a while. Ben's reaction was really expected, to me at least. If his blog is his outlet, let it be. If you'd ask me, one year down the road when Ben reads that blog entry again, he'll not be swearing, but smiling to himself. This is what I do now when I look back on my previous blog entries. This is part of life. So therefore what I am trying to say is, Ben's just feeling really cheated. But I'm not saying anyone cheated him. Just the feeling. So that's why he's ranting and swearing in his blog. Well, I'd have him do that than cut himself or, would you rather he call u up and swear in ur ear at 3am in the morning? So please, cut this dude some slack. He deserves some after all he's been through. After all, we all grow from our own experiences. As for Alv and huiwen, I'd have to say that its kinda awkward for me to talk to u guys now. Alv might have noticed that I was quieter when we walked to sunshine place recently. Huiwen, hang in there if you believe alv's the one for you. You're a great girl, and I like ur personality, but sometimes you go into things too rashly and end up hurting people, so the bottomline is just care about the things which you deem important for now, and set ur priorities right. I think ur life will be better if you have something to live for. :)  Ben, i hope u'll pull urself together like a real man and be magnanimous. People will respect you. And Alv & huiwen, I wish u guys all the best, and I hope after this whole thing has settled, we can all hang out together like buddies again. Peace out. :) 
     

        
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      [01:04:43 AM] raise a glas: i ought to scold u [01:04:46 AM] raise a glas: ur not updating ur blog  hurhur. ok fine. so here i go. not been blogging for quite some time, cos i decided to put more time into my studies. :) and i did. so yup. had n'dae celebrations yesterday. i'd say i was quite bored till swong came by and sat down. at least ben and i had someone to make fun of then. hurhur. went to play pool with the guys after that. swong and daryl came along too. and yea la, some unbelieveable stuff, since Allah came down to Earth, happened at Pool factor. i shant comment. ;) read ben's blog or swong's blog for more info. i'm too embarrassed. hurhur. anyway, i'm hungry. gonna grab a bite. :)
     

        
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      while walking in lot 1, there's this poster frm breadtalk saying "You have your flaws, i have mine."  Come to think of it, I'm Flawed. You're Flawed. Everyone's Flawed. Who isn't?  But then again, Everyone's Flawed in their own unique way. The World itself is Flawed. And that is why, For Flawed people like us, The World's a perfect place for us to live in. :)
     

        
</post>


</Blog>