<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hmm, i dont even know what memorial day is... wow, im drawing a complete blank on what i did this weekend, so im just gonna assume that i sat areound playing pokemon and other video games all weekend, although i might not have. today i went to sami's and we went swimming, thats a bout it, and i went to charlie's afterwards to eat. i think thats it, if i figure out what i did before i might blog about it, maybe, maybe not, oh well im istening to yellowcard - ocean avenue, good song though they play it alot on the radio, its about to start getting old im now prolly gonna go play pokemon or harvest moon...
      
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ow, i got burnt really bad today, pressure washing windows and swimming outside just about all of today, i really should have used some sunscreen, but oh well now, anyways, i went to work at 9 again till 2, went to sami's to go swimming till 8, came home and will prolly sit here till about 11 or 12, for once, im not listening to any music(woah), im off here i guess, later
      
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ug, i havent known what day it has been all day, or yesterday really after asking many times i have come to the conclusion that it is in fact wednesday got up at 8, went to work at 8:30, pressure washed windows till 1:30, ate lunch, came home i got really sunburned today on my arms, neck, and face and that sucks. anyways, i dont really remeber what i did yesterday, cause i didnt know what day it was or is, didnt do much yesterday, went to work from like 2:30 to 5 i think, tomorrow should be a litle more eventful working from 9 to 2 then going swimming at sami's, finally a break from work and home, ahhh... i cant wait, i am really bored right now, i took out the trash outta boredom, i was gonna mow the back yard, but the phone kept me from doing so now im back to my usual routine of listening to music, downloading music and stuff, and playing solitaire(oh, and blogging), fun fun... im listening to ben folds - rockin' the suburbs, good song about being a male, middle class, and white... lol ok im outta here, well not really but oh well, later
      
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hey peoples, well, im glad schools out, i guess, didnt have to get up  that  early, i got woken up at 9:25 when i had to be at work at 10, UG, i got up, got dressed, got a pop tart and got in the car, went to the local One Stop(lol), to get a 2-liter of dew, went to work, felt really sick around 2, only worked till 5 instead of 7 because me and alan were really burnt out on assembling cabinets, came home, took a shower, went to my dad's, ate dinner, played badmitten a little, had dessert, came home, talked to sami for about 3 hours, then blogged(which is right now, hehe) really long day, well work was at least, word of advice: dont have pop tarts and mtn dew for breakfast, it'll mess you up... now i am swatting at the few bugs attracted to the bright glow of my moniter, killed about 10 of them last night, bugs suck... i guess im gonna go to sleep soon, nothing else to do really, oh well ive got nothing to do tomorrow, which is later today... woah, to late to be thinking... ok, just gonna sit around all day and talk to people probally, maybe clean up the house some, damn there are already 4 bugs on my moniter, better go before tey multiply again, btw listen to 99 red/luft balloons, preferably an english version(if you want to understand what they say), im listening to the Goldfinger version, its good, yeah, ok, im outta here and off to sleep, later.
      
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hey all, i went swimming today w/ sami and megan, learned to swim today, its kinda sad that i havent learned until now but hey, fuck it cause i can now before hand i cleaned up the house a little(woah) found some odd sort of motivation i guess now im home and ratherly bored, im listening to Saliva - Your Disease, good song,  ok well ima go do something else now, later
      
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hey ppl solataire is evil... dont play it.... i just watched The Fast and the Furious a little while ago, pretty good movie although i liked the second one better, it was on tv so it was edited and cut shorter but oh well ratherly boring day today, i didnt leave the house at all, except to play with the kittens im currently listening to Story of the Year, they are very good in my opinion i get some of my braces off on the 14th of june(yay!) i hate braces they totally and completely suck ok im done bitchin for the night, good night ppl
      
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hey people, not much anything going on today, ive been sitting inside all day because is 95 degrees outside, almost as hot as hell. for some reason im listening to The New Guy soundtrack... dont know why... i hope the summer wont be as boring as this weekend, but we'll just wait and see ok, later ppl
      
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      well, its friday night, woohoo.... school is officially over now, today was the last day although i didnt go i feel sorry for any one who did. school is over, its friday night and im sitting at home blogging, this sucks... wow, i just got invited to an AIM chatroom by a spambot, thats kinda sad. im getting tired and i really dont know how i got motivation to blog but oh well solataire keeps kicking my ass, damn game, its depressing it really is i dont even know what im gonna do this weekend, my dad wants to get his old shitty cars out of here sunday, thats good, and i might do something w/ sami and megan if we can come up with something. ok im done, later ppl
      
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      yay! my blog is back up again well mostly at least i think is template looks good, although i have no links section yet, ill get that up later, hopefully... anyways, got some stuff going on, not too awful much, school is almost out(woohoo!) this is our last week and im not going tomorrow or friday, tomorrow im going to work all day(yay.....), i got exams wed. and thurs. fun... i would advise listening to lostprophets - last summer, it is a great song. again, as i have said before, i hope to update a lot, which i might because i do a lot more than i used to, oh well feel free to comment(if you dont have a blogger account just hit the annonymous thing, just put ur name in there ok well im going now, later everyone.
      
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      test
      
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      well, we got back to PA (from NY) a little while ago, dean, yes my site is bac kup, i will link to you later. alan, i will help you out later prolly over the phone unless you got it already, sami, cable is good... lol, ill ttyl   tuesday  was awesome, we went to Hersheypark, that is now my new favorite amusement/theme park ever, there we rode roller coasters and stuff, went on my new favorite rollercoaster, the storm runner, it was just f-ing awesome   wednesday , kinda boring most of the day as we went to NY, through HEAVY traffic when we got into NY, we traveled the world's longest parking lot, aka the long island expressway, express my ass... when we got to my aunt terry's house my cousins came over, along w/ my sister, renee, that i havent seen in about 5 years, had a pretty good time though we didnt do much but eat and talk   thursday , we went bowling w/ my aunt and cousin, went to my cousin's, went to sam's club, back to my cousin's, to my other cousin's, then back to my aunt's, didnt do that much, but i did watch a few hours of MXC, the best show ever in my opinion   friday , we came back to PA from NY today, was pretty crappy because we have a rental van that SUCKS, horribly, its a 2005 Ford Freestar, sounds good but it sucks complete ass, horribly uncomfortable, anyways, my uncle called us on our way back, he is a truck driver and he told us a diff. route to go to get around traffic which was backed up for miles, we met him and got lunch, then i rode w/ him in his truck, that was really cool, we talked, and checked out the ladies for about an hour or two, lol, then we met my dad at a rest stop so i went back w/ them to come back to my grandparents house, now im back here watching tv again, i dont know what we are doing tomorrow, then we are coming home on sunday, fun...  i have been eating constantly about this whole trip and i dont know why, oh well  i guess ima go now, ill talk to you all later, maybe...  bye
      
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      well, i now know what im doing this week, tomorrow we are going to Hershey Park, that oughta kick ass, wednesday we are going to NY for a few days, we coming back to PA friday. well we dunno what happened to the van's transmission, but now we got a rental van for about a week. well im gonna go watch tv again now, later
      
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      well, we got to PA last night at 6:30, we left at 8:30, 10 hour trip, kinda boring like always, but it was alright got here, ate spaghetti, then watched tv till 5 in the morning, went to bed just because.. i wasnt really tired but anyways, the van got messed up, it started leaking transmission fluid right when we pulled it, its now at a dealer getting fixed, now that we have no car for a little while, we might not make it to NY, but hopefully we will. i think we are also going to Hershey park sometime too, that'll be fun. thats about all thats going on, ill follow up w/ more later, so later yall.
      
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm.... this weekend is not only gonna be short, but go by very quickly sunday morning im leaving to go to PA for a week, we are also gonna go to NY for a little while to, i still havent decied whether or not i want to go, i know i AM going though, hmmm... did pretty much nothing today. tomorrow i dont know what all is going on, i really want to go see sami before i leave, but i dont know if that is gonna happen as my aunt and uncle are coming here sometime tomorrow, tomorrow night im going to my dad's so we can leave tomorrow morning, probally too early for my liking, but hey, who the hell cares i guess i think i will wither be posting a lot when im gone, or not at all. probally a lot, but i dont know where ill be or if my grandparents r gonna be bitchy or not, ug well i guess im gonna go pack or whatnot... bye
      
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      wow im behind, last update was wednesday then saturday, and the sat. was jut saying my links were up i really dont remember what the hell happend from thur. thru sun. although im not worried about it at all really, yesterday, sami's mom went into surgery in the morning, so i went up to the hospital in the morning to keep her company, i stayed there till 6-ish, came home, and sat around, and went to sleep today: got up, went to the orthodontist atabout 10:30, that was good because i got my braces off my top teeth(WOOHOO!!) that is whole helluva lot better, then i went back to the hospital (sami stayed overnight w/ her mom), didnt stay very long, we all went back to her house, hung out there all day watching movies, playing playstation, and having sami and her grandma attempt to braid my leghairs... unsuccessfully..., came home about 9:30 when it rained like all the angels in heaven decided to take a piss at the same time. im now kinda bored, and kinda tired like usual, i have no clue what im gonna do tomorrow, ill find out then, sooo...., bye
      
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      i now have a links section, although the number  of links i have now is limited more will probally be added later 
      
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      well i kinda lost yesterday somehow, i guess i didnt do anything of importance, i remember helping my little sister make cookies though, i think that was all i really did all day. today i did pretty much nothing, woke up at 9 somehow, that kinda sucked, just made more hours to be bored during, i went to sami's for a couple hours this evening, there i helped plant raspberry bushes, surprisingly kinda fun..., came home, and now im here, hmm, i always end up back here... im now listening to good charlotte, their old cd, its good ok ill be back tomorrow... hopefully... later!
      
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      well, i guess not all mondays suck i just got back from ryan's and bowling, it was fun, i went with my dad, step family, and sami came too, she got me a turtle made of shells(named frank...) and a necklace from myrtle beach, yay! at ryans we had hot sauce just for the hell of it, the tabasco is much hotter than the texas pete, then omg!,our waitress came one time when we were eating the hot sauce so she brought a hot pepper sauce bottle with the peppers in it, omg they were nasty and not very hot at all then onto bowling, i bowled my all time high tonight(yay) 118, my old high was 117, lol, big improvement... i only got 2 strikes, which is alright i guess, sami got 3 plus 2 more after gutterballs but they counted as spares, i had a great time, i think everyone did, there were surprisingly no arguements between anyone, woah but cool ok anyways, im gonna go do something else now... later
      
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hmmmmm... another boring monday well for now at least im going to ryan's to eat then bowling w/ my dad and step family peoples should be pretty fun... should be. also going to get rubber to shoot at people, hehe. okwellimgonnagogetreadyandgogoodbyepeoples
      
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      did nothing most of the day friday, rearranged the room untill i went to a LAN party there we played games from 8 pm till about 5 am, fun, we also had a rubber band fight, i now know how to shoot a rubber band that will go fast, make a cool sound, and sting lan party was fun, came home about 6:30ish, went to bed and slept till 12 didnt do much today, till tonight, went to eat at Ryan's Steakhouse with alan and lizzy, then we went to walmart, there i bought max payne 2, good game now im here sitting in the dark with only the glow of my moniter(no bugs today, yay!) well thats about all, later oh yeah, go  urlLink here , its great...  
      
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      wow, ive done all of nothing since my last post, really bored... anyways, this month might be interesting, might not, on the 14th  i get some of my braces off, dont know which ones.. but some. im going to PA the week of the 20th, leaving the 20, and coming back the 27th, im going to help reshingle my grandparents roof, fun... wow, im really peeling now, and slightly tanned... ok, im going back to my usual routine of playing video games, listening to music, and occasionally talkin on the phone, bye
      
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      well today...  sami's birthday, HAPPY BIRTHDAY!!, she is 15 today.  went to the school this mornin to change my schedule, so that i will have drivers-ed this year, then i went to sami's, but no one was there, so i went inside and watched jerry springer until they got there, we watched Gone in 60 Seconds, (excellent movie, i would recommend), sat around for most of the day, megan came over about 8, we had cake and all that, then we sat around talking about a road trip we wanna go on, in a hippie van w/ flowers and stuff painted on it just to see if the cops would try to bust us for possesion, lol, we then went outside and burned sami's diary, dont really know why, but it didnt wanna burn, we tried bugspray, but it wasnt flammable, so i thought of past expierences and remembered that PAM was flammable, so we used that (although there was hardly any left) it was in one of them little fireplaces for ur porch and the top was covered so i got a bunch of smoke in my face, that sucksed but oh well,&nbsp;then i came home about 10:45ish  we closed on our new home today, WOOHOO, that is the greatest news ever for me, for i will finally get my own room, which i've never had&nbsp;before  WOOHOO  school starts next thursday, kinda cant wait for that  everyone should listen to Rehab - Sittin at a Bar, its a great song  i will also be an uncle tomorrow morning, (my brother's gf/fiancé is having a baby) they are inducing labor tomorrow at 6:30 am  well thats about all i can think of right now, although i usually remember something right after i post, but im usually too lazy to go and post again, so thats all for now  good-bye/night people!!!!   
      
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      oh, and also school starts next thursay(aug 5) as yous can see i got a new template, its all blue and well, different. hope yall like it, if not fsck off :-P later 
      
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ugh. times are rough we are getting a new double-wide sometime this week, probally, hopefully im gonna be an uncle by wednesday, for some reason thats kinda stressful samantha's b-day is tuesday, happy  early  birthday!! i got my permit , i drive around town, thats it i went to augusta today, kinda boring, at least we had air conditioning then went swimming at charlie's thats it, bye 
      
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      quite a long while too. i havent updated because i havent really done anything, wow, not since PA, well i got home that sunday, and been here since just been siting around for a while, i went to my dad's last weekend, kinda sorta celebrated ind. day, nothing special, just a bunch of people eating.... monday i went to the movies, saw white chicks, that was a very funny movie, then went to charlie's to eat sat around tue thru today, going to my dad's tomorrow night, then to eat out on sat. my b-day is on the 16th, woohoo, i can then get my permit, cant wait for that. thats all that i remeber that has any relevance to anything... i have no idea what i just said... later
      
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      *long sigh* well, my brother's baby was born on the 28th of july, its a boy more info  urlLink here  at his site, school started today, it was ok, really long, but ok we are now on block scheduling (4 90 min. classes) , which was normal for them, but last year they did traditional scheduling (7, 50 min. classes) and so did the middle school, so its new to me 90 minutes of one class at a time is boring, but oh well it works, we got our new double wide the other day, they still had to set it up though, which they are finishing right now as i type this, that'll be cool, though we still have to run our power, water, and septic lines over so we can move in, should be about a week eh, i feel kinda crappy right now and im not sure why, think i need a nap... maybe not oh well, ill try to post later, hopefully tomorrow evening, as i dont get online at school every day now( no compy class this semester) untill then... 
      
</post>


</Blog>