<Blog>


<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's open.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The shows were recorded during October - November 2003. They were captured live in a two-CD audio release:  urlLink  G3 Live: Rockin' In The Free World     urlLink     and a full feature DVD:  urlLink  G3 Live in Denver     urlLink     The audio release is comprised of 2 CD's loaded with flawless performances. Each guitarist performs his own improvised guitar soloing on the first disc. On disc two, the guitar masters team up to perform three covers:  Voodoo Child (Slight Return) ,  Little Wing  both by  Jimi Hendrix's  and  Rockin' in the Free World  by  Neil Young .  Satriani's drummer posted some  urlLink photographs  throughout the tour.  If you are a guitar soloing freak, like me, then you are gonna love this one.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Porsche, the sports cars maker, is announcing two new models in its 911 line.     Watch the exclusive images, video and more at  urlLink porsche.com .
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Sometimes I get sooo bored during that stop-and-go pattern at rush hour traffic. I gotta keep movin'.     The classic arrangement of instruments in the cabin. Where I travel everyday from home to work to home.     After all the hard work. A smooth ride at last.   
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm just posting more pictures that I shot.   The Columbus Alcazar , a 22-room palace, was built in the second decade of the 16th century. Constructed of native coral and rock, it was built on the shores of Santo Domingo's Ozama River.      The Caribbean Sea . Beware of pirates, they are watching :)   
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Is the title of the latest Satriani CD. Joe Satriani, widely regarded as one of rock's top guitarists, has just issued his 9th studio album.    urlLink     In this release he's gravitating towards more blues roots, funky blues, mid-tempo tunes, such as the wah-wah-phased title track. The album's masterpiece is the ten minutes long "Searching" track. This is one cool little record.  There are two bonus tracks: " urlLink Tumble " only on Apple's iTunes store and " urlLink Dog With Crown & Earring ", only on the  urlLink japanese release .  Every "Satch" released album makes ripples in the rock guitar community.  You can listen to  urlLink clips , or even better, get  urlLink the album .
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is a picture I took at the beach with my new camera, a  urlLink Canon PowerShot S50.  The picture was taken in Juan Dolio, Dominican Republic.   urlLink    Click image to enlarge.  For those of you who are wondering where the Dominican Republic is, it's a Caribbean island located near Puerto Rico and Cuba. Down here the whole year is hot and humid, perfect scenario to enjoy a coconut-based drink with a little umbrella straw on white sand beach.  You can take a look at my  urlLink portfolio  if you want to see more pictures.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm on the street right now, using someone else's bandwidth.  Just because I can (a la  urlLink evhead ).     I didn't ask for permission to use it -- I don't even know whom to ask.  Twelve Wireless LANs found so far, only 2 are using WEP!  Wanna try it? Here is all you'll need:    urlLink The hardware .   urlLink The software  (if you want go further get  urlLink this  and  urlLink this ). 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I know that all of you who want to be billionaires, check this  urlLink special report  at forbes.com.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've got some extra Gmail invitations.  If there are anyone out there who didn't already get one. Consider making a donation to the site. (To give, use the PayPal button on the  urlLink bottom  of the home.) You'll receive a Gmail invite as a  thank you gift. Supplies are limited.   Update : No longer available.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      More than once,  Peavey Electronics Corporation  and many  urlLink famous artists  have co-designed musical instruments. In this case, it was  urlLink Joe's turn  to create the  urlLink  Peavey JSX   &reg; guitar amplifier. Check the official site for more information on  urlLink Satriani's Gear .  This 100 Watt head was the result of extensive research and development with the guitar legend.  It was tested during the  urlLink 2003 G3 tour .
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    One cool t-shirt.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is the 4th generation of iPods. Apple has upgraded the look and capabilities to the iPod and probably one of the best changes is the new price ($100 cheaper). Read the full report at  urlLink NEWSWEEK .  
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      One interesting  urlLink new way to post  to your weblog is using your mobile phone while away from your computer.  Press play to hear my voice speaking in spanish:    urlLink   
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last Saturday I added a new Album to my big collection. The album is  urlLink  Every Day   by  The Cinematic Orchestra .    urlLink     This CD contains experimental underground English music. Experts classify this style of music as Trip-Hop. All I can say is that I love it, specially the song titled  Man With the Movie Camera . The song is a bit strange, it is jazz and punk brilliantly-blended. The guy behind this work is Jason Swinscoe who studied art at  urlLink Cardiff College . I'm a big fan of experimental genres fusions and this record sounds so natural, acoustic and paced that you hardly notice the electronic samples during some passages.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Now I think is time to start writing clearly. Recently I've got a copy of  urlLink The Elements of Style . It is a classic reference book that all conscientious writers must keep near its desk.   urlLink     Do you write e-mail? Letters? Blogs? Comments? Then you'll need this book. Read it.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>