<Blog>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Me and James have a bet going on, this is to stop boredom from kicking in during the holidays. Right now&nbsp;I can't really reveal too much until me and James have a clear set of guidelines and limits for this bet, so he can actually win.  The purpose of this blog is simple -- we use it as the main page for the whole site and report how the bet is going. It will feature commentary from both me and James as we need comedy, don't we all?  The message board shall be sorted out tomorrow as soon as I get the time, and we will begin the archiving of what we already have.  Expect all to be known tomorrow. 
     
    
</post>


<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Rawwwwwwwwwr I'm ready to go.     Got my survival kit all ready, Are You Dave Gorman?, Ten by cLOUDDEAD, journal (which is all pwettyfied) and pen to write with (as you should do).  Veeeeery excited about it all tomorrow and am thinking of writing plenty of stuff on the three hour trip there. After that I have no idea whats going to happen but I'm pretty sure we'll get straight to the boat, unpack, then have a look around Salcombe.  I'm sure Monday will be spent doing fun fun stuffs and I promise to get many pictures, as I have eight charged AA batteries with me on my trip, however I have a nagging feeling that that is not going to be enough.  I bought a new shirt today in town which apparentely looks teh secks, sooo I'll wear that quite a bit.  Now I'm going to rip cLOUDDEAD onto my computer and listen to the coolio avant garde rap fo' shizzle.  (I promise that when I return there will be a mega update with lots of stuff, including photographs which I intend to kill my webspace, extracts from my journal and re-telling of the whole adventure.)  Toodles.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Reading through yetserday's entry has made me think if I was on some sort of drug when I posted it. I had no idea why I posted it, and feel very stupid for doing so. The entry sounded so twattish and I didn't even take into consideration different people's lives which can be very different from mine.  I'm going to keep the post there, but choose to ignore it instead. I be listening to The Residents now, and probably for the next half hour or so.  Toodles.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Thought much about what I do here with my life, and how I feel about other people. What I've done to others and what I could of done to avoid doing that, it seems such a shame that I can't turn back the hands of time and just put things right. But even so, if I did do that a new consequence would commence, and the end result may be more catastrophic. I've tried not to think about it all too much as I'll end up thinking I'm worthless and, but then I said something to myself in my head that seemed so god damn simple and true as well, that I couldn't really feed bad about stuff which has happened in the past.  "Consequence is inevitable."  Yeah I know it sounds a bit like, "For every action there is a consequence" but it feels different somehow.  Now thinking about it again reminds me that of course, you should say this to yourself if you wasn't really a direct cause of something happening, so don't fret about what you could of done to stop something happening.  I'm trying not to think of anything negative at this moment of time to oppose this, but I'm sure I'll eventually find a loophole in my sentence and try and forget it.  I think for now I'll stick to the maxim, "What is in the past should stay in the past."
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Just making a little entry to let you all know I still use this thing.  Little things have been happening in the past few days, but my negligence to post them as soon as they happan has led me to forget them. How unfortunate. ¬_¬  On Sunday, I will be leaving Swindon with James and his dad to go to their boat in Salcombe. For those poor (well, hardly anyone knows where it is) in Geography, Salcombe is a coastal village/town situated in southern Devon. As really dodgy as it sounds we will be going there for five days, and doing many things. Going for hikes (I think), lazing about and just walking around the place will be the most of it.  I promise I'll take lots of photographs, and I will have a journal by the time, so do expect a big massive entry from me (thats if I bother, someone remind me) when I return.  Before I go I have various things to buy, namely a journal, pen, and some clothes. When it comes to clothes I'll buy them in the generic form (free of brands and logos and whatever, thus removing all sorts of social labels I can be given). I'll purchase Are You Dave Gorman? by Dave Gorman, as that shall be my reading companion for the holiday.  So yes, expect comedy, drama, and downright silliness. I'll update a couple of times before I leave and if you're all little good boys and girls maybe a picture of me. (Oh yes, aren't you the lucky ones?)  Toodles.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Having had a good read through the b3ta newsletter I found two links that you guys may find quite funny.   urlLink The South Wales Echo   A man ia ao proud of his local newspaper he makes a website about it. Good read.   urlLink Infinite Cat Project   Based on a theory that cats always look at other cats, even if its a picture.  Going off to bed now, toodles.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Our recent run of good weather had been put to an end today as it tipped down during lunch, much to my anger as we stopped playing a good ol' game of rugby. Backed onto our line I had no way of clearing the ball as Taj did not run behind me, as I was urging him to. The game was called off in the end as of excess rain, although continuing the game would of been fun.  Was woken up at 7:30 this morning to have a shower, however I didn't creep out of my bed until 7:45 (oooooooh such a rebel). A lack of Head & Shoulders shampoo meant "argh crappy stuff" that made my hair smell badly of strawberry. I did not like this, and had to put up with the smell of strawberry running through my hair until the rain cleansed it out at lunch.  Studied the Holocaust and Nazi propaganda in history and I managed to write a heck of a lot during the lesson, no one really had anything interesting to say so I just got on with my work.  Assembly was called off because of year 7 exams I think, but nevertheless it was called off and we went to tutor where I managed to eat a subtle amount of food.  In DT I managed to actually draw the outline for our woodwork projects, and I'm pretty sure I'm feeling ok today. Break managed to pass with nothing actually happening, and as I write this I do remember me and James discussing Eurovision as I was singing a part from the Ukraine entry, le woo for cheesy music contests.  Got sent out of Citizenship for being sarcastic and chatty, and put on a 'last warning', later to be warned again for eating sandwiches in class. I like my tutor, I think he can be funny at times, but I just have this feeling hes losing his, erm, how you say it, 'cool'. Heh, now I sound like an idiot. Michael told me he had Mr Tate for Science as Mr Maher was planning to give pupils in our class detentions on Monday. Of course, as usual, I misheard this and began to make poor one-liners.   "Mr T teahces you Science?! I pity the foo' that messes with sulphuric acid!"   Michael laughed though, so I suppose we have hope here in Swindon...  In French Katie made me wear her sunglasses and as I put them on, she took a picture of me on her camera phone. I only saw the picture at the end of the lesson and looked the foo' (oh yes, Mr T styley). I couldn't stop her from showing it to other people though, so I guess people laughed at it. Hell, it made them smile, thats good right?  At lunch James was a bit angry as Mr Runham had totally ignored him for twenty minutes in his Maths lesson when he needed an explanation to a question. The end result is as follows:     Tis a mad James, but if you look a little closer, you'll notice he's very organised, hes even remembered to update his blog! He'll have to give me the link some time so I can pimp his up.  In yesterday's entry I forgot to include some photos I had taken, so I take it upon myself to add these here now.     This was taken in Drama (so maybe it was a picture from Wednesday then :P) and is a shot of Dee trying to maul her fingers to death. Having the flash off caused one hand to not be blurred and another clutching a pen to be very blurred. I kind of liked the way it turned out, so I guess thats why its here.     This is a wall. +2 points for observation. I edited the colours very quickly in Photoshop otherwise this would have been a very dull black & white photo of a wall... Erm, I guess its still a dull picture of a wall anyway, but at least its in a good colour.     I guess I'm adding this picture for the sake of it. Its not really good at all, however I do believe that the high resolution copy of this picture looks way much better.  Going back to our lunchtime shenanigans now. *End cheesy transmission music*  The weather to begin with was very nice, good warm temperature, shining very brightly. Didn't do or say much, but at least it was good weather.     There isn't much point to this picture, but you can see that it is bright in that picture, and this was taken about twenty minutes before the rain really kicked in. I was playing rugby with James, Taj, Devon (haha), Jack and Joe for a while. I had already screwed up once, but to save face, I just blame Taj for not being behind me so I could pass to him. Rain had started to spit slightly but we still went on regardless of this, and then we had to call the game off because it really did start to rain then. I did taken an enjoyment to watching people run madly across the field to get shelter.     Look raaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaain! *ahem*  Bell went and I went into James' music room for a little while. Just before I left I looked across the room trying to find something. I had only just realised that I had lost my boot bag. Without thinking I found myself continually saying "Bugger, bugger, bugger, bugger, bugger" right in front of Mr Sizeland. By now the class had found it hilarious, and I guess I did too, after all I was making a complete fool of myself. Mr Sizeland told me to go look for it and I quickly pounced off to my French class where I did indeed find my boot bag.  Went past James' music room again on the way to PE, knocked on the window, did a little celebratory dance whilst everyone laughed (again), and I could hear Sian shouting "Bugger, bugger, bugger!". The things I do to entertain people I tell thee...  High jump in PE, avoided it a bit, then got into it. In the competition I only got through to the second round, but went out of that after I think my shirt came into contact with the line. In the end Bobby won with a height of 165cm if I remember correctly.  With that done, my school day had finished and I went off home. But before I go any further, why not have a picture of some leaves?     Yes, didn't do much after school. Spoke to Rebecca and other people on MSN, watched The Lenny Heny Show and ate apple and raspberry pie.  Have to run into town tomorrow to buy myself a new book to use as journal when I am unable to get onto the internet and post something here, so maybe you'll read something more interesting in the near future. Today is firday, so the b3ta newsletter should be released. I'm off now, toodles.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So far the game has gone well for us, Sammy Parkin scored in the 81st minute and brought us to 1-0 (1-1 on aggregate). We're going to extra time and I have a bad feeling we're going to end up with a penalty shootout. I'm staying rather confident that Swindon can go through.  EDIT - Just as I posted this Rory Fallon scored for Swindon. 2-1 on aggregate to the reds! Going up!  EDIT2 - Brighton scored with ten seconds to go ... I have a bad feeling about this.  EDIT3 - Bad feeling was correct, Brighton managed to win in the penalty shootout 4-3. Swindon will not go to the playoff final now and their season has finished. :( Lets just hope I do have a good day on Saturday, I'm hoping Millwall beat Manchester United.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I must really get myself into a routine of waking up early and sorting things out around the house. Looking around me I can see a hell of a mess in my room, from my chair I can spy some Belgian chocolates which were bestowed upon me as a present on Christmas Day. I'm unsure whether to eat these or not now, I'm not sure if they'll taste horrid, and I'm going to feel guilty as I would waste them otherwise. If anyone knows what I can do with them then answers on the back of a postcard please.  Woke up at 8am again today, leaving me little time to get myself ready and leg it out of the house. Much to my annoyance, the gate that allows entrance to New College was locked  again , so after furiously muttering 'naughty sweary shit' under my breath, I walked around the building, thus making me a good five minutes late to school.  Maths really for me won the 'whaaaaa?' award for the day, or we could say the fortnight. After some really easy work in the past two weeks, we were given bitches of questions and work to do, and to add more insult to the injury, I had only woken up an hour before and was being watched by Mr Runham.   "Right Kev, what's 4 cubed?" *cogs in brain currently not running ... pause ... dirt becomes untrapped in cogs* "64 sir."   Finding myself rather pleased to be out of the lesson when the bell went, I rushed off to my tutorial lesson, only to spend ten minutes of it outside my tutor class talking to Rebecca and Jessica. Finally went into my tutor class, to have my digital camers inspected by Mr Maher, whilst I ate a cucumber and tomato sandwich. Yes, I know Rebecca, please don't go on about sandwiches.  The next lesson was Art, one that I always dread on a Thursday and daydream of getting out. Take three objects and draw them, and the background. Do outline for this lesson, and then next lesson work on getting one and a half sections complete, and on the third week complete it.  I know I'm definitely not an arty person when it comes to me and a pencil, especially observational drawings. I find no satisfaction in drawing an old violin, jug and a purple cup. Oh wait, Rebecca doesn't like that purple cup, lets change it for a doll! Heh, I can't draw, and changing the cup for a doll made it all the worse, I protested.   "But I don't like that doll, change it please!"  I claimed, hoping that out of Rebecca's heart she'll agree and choose something simple to replace it.  "No, I want to draw it,"  she replied rather menacingly, and that was it really. I gave up all protest and just put up with it and drew what I could.  By the end of the lesson all I managed to draw was half the violin and a wonky jug, nevermind the doll, I wasn't going to bother with that for a while.  Scurrying quickly out of my art classroom I took the usual journey of going down the stairs and heading for the far playground where I usually spend my break. Unfortunately I couldn't remember anything interesting from break, just making sure that I remembered how to breathe and digest food.  After break I left to go to my DT lesson, in which I did nothing ... again. Its starting to annoy me that I do nothing in my DT lesson, after all teachers are paid to teach students, and not for us to just waste their time. The discussions during DT had varied a lot, from penis piercings to well, boyfriends and girlfriends; something that I lack excess knowledge of. I shut up for most of the lesson and as soon as the bell went, walked to my english lesson.  On the way to my english lesson a year 9, who is probsbly less educated than a braindead goldfish did something so stupid that she could of seriously hurt someone. She waited behind a door of a busy corridor, and when someone went to open the door, viciously kicked it sending the door straight into the person's face. Now, I am not making a rant out of this just because the two people it happened to happen to be my best friend and my friend, but because of the fact that in year 7 we have a brittle-boned student who is barely 4 feet tall. The corridor was full at the time, so he wouldn't of been noticable at all. Had he been there, and he had been knocked back by someone who was knocked back or hit in the face by the door itself, he would have been seriously injured. I considered hurling abuse to the person who did this, but I decided not to in the end as I felt it would of added more fuel to the fire and I would just be stooping down to their level.  I didn't do much work in my english lesson, until the last fifteen minutes where I quickly noted down an opening paragraph to a short story I may write in the near future. Rebecca said to me that it was 'all pwetty', so I explained to her that this is only how it will seem, but once read will change your opinion ... slightly.  Lunch past quickly as well to my disappointment, so I have nothing to say about it. I went off to Science quickly and remembered that I took no pictures during the break, bugger.  Science had continued its trend of being dull and boring, no matter what experiments or 'exciting things' we do. Brushing up on how to use a microscope didn't exactly interest me, so I just watched as Rebecca plucked hairs from Tricia's head, although in turn I did get hairs pulled from mine.  Refused to go home without a hug from Rebecca, and in the end, managed to get two. Muahahaha.  The New College gate was still locked, so once again I had to go the long way to get home, which caused me to arrive home about ten minutes later than usual.  The day after school has not been very interesting for me, I must of spent so far about fifteen minutes decided what to write and not what to write here, was thinking of avoiding the rant about the door incident, and then felt it had to be included.  I know this is a pretty long entry so far, but I'm going to give you guys a little treat, have some links that I've found in the past week.   urlLink Hey Hey 16K   I'm jumping on this bandwagon a bit too late here, its been around for about two weeks now and I've only just decided to blog it. Hey Hey 16K is a song composed by DJ Hibbett and animated by B3ta's very own Rob Manuel. The song is about the consoles before 16K had become popular. Oh how I wish I could play Jetpac...   urlLink La Haine - £15 On Play   I've heard very good words about this french film, so this will have to be one of my next purchases. To save myself some time, I'll put up its description from Play.com, and I'll have you know that the guy who directed this also directed Gothika.   La Haine is packed with sharp street humour, intense action and brutally brilliant camera work.   Police viciously beat a 16-year-old housing estate kid they are questioning, leaving him almost dead. Responding to violence, teenagers from the estate turn their home into a 24 hour war zone. Among the people blinded by hate are Said, Vinz and Hubert, youths who survive on petty crime and dealing dope. In the intensely volatile environment, the teenagers find a chrome-plated Smith & Wesson 44 that a plain-clothes cop has lost. If killing a cop with his own gun doesn't express their rage then what will?   The French cabinet commissioned a special screening of this tragic story on its release, to see the problems of the angry French underclass on the streets of Paris.   "A brutally brilliant masterpiece of 90s cinema" - NME    urlLink Andy Kaufman Returns   The author of this blog is supposedly Andy Kaufman. He claims to be the real deal, the man himself. For one of his entries he posted a press release in which it states that he has taken DNA tests and had his fingerprints checked, all pointing that this is indeed the legend Andy Kaufman.  There are still those suspicious of all this, but if Andy Kaufman did fake his death, then why has he announced it on blogspot?  Keep an eye on this one guys.   urlLink Insaniquarium Game   A link that has been lurking around my favorites for a long time now, its time to dig this one up from the dead. Concept is simple. Keep fish fed, make them grow, collect coins, destroy aliens. Strangely addictive.   urlLink Arnie's Pizza Shop   Matt send me this link some time ago, and I found it hilariously funny for some reason.   "I'm not here now, I'm out killing pepperoni!"   That will have to be all for now, until something else of interest happens to me. One more thing to do though, I'll have to pimp Rebecca's blog to hell. She is at  urlLink prettyh8-machine , and will probably have something more interesting to say than I do.  I'm off now to do things, toodles!
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This entry really is just a follow up from the last post. I've made myself a profile so others can find me. I was a bit reluctant at first to let other people whom I do not know see my blog, as this is the first time I've done so since I think in the autumn of 2003. I might add a picture to my profile, that is if I do conjure up the bravery to do so.  I've deleted all the entries before the last one as I feel they sounded a tad bit dull to be honest, I think most of them followed the pattern of, "I'm so bored, there is nothing to do" when I know well that I didn't even try to find or do something interesting atfer complaining about it.  To make this entry feel worthwhile, I'll leave you with two pictures that I took during my school day yesterday...        Toodles.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Nein? Changes are good when you think about them. Everyone changes a lot in there lives, and I think changes usually take place when new ideas circulate around one's head for a long time.  For a while I've been urging myself to go out and buy a decent book with plenty of pages to use for a journal. After I bought a book for the sole use of writing ideas for songs, I felt compelled to write varied ideas in there, slowly falling away from my music and lyrics, and probably heading towards a journal. I've managed to fight off this resistance, but I don't want to give in (as I know I will soon), so I've decided to go and buy myself a journal as soon as possible.  I'm considering changing this blog around as well, adding a proper description to go with a title change (the Hollow Wishes, feels quite, hollow if you ask me), and if you're the lucky ones I may update this often enough, although that itself is a hard task, I do not maintain an interesting life as others so brillantly do.  This was a short post, but was only supposed to let you know I am still alive and breathing, and that I plan to do some more in the future.  Toodles.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The past week has gone by quickly and I'm rather happy to have it finished with so it can be forgotten. Hopefully I won't have to feel how I did in the past week for a long while, because lets face it, life doesn't last forever.  So with those thoughts in mind, I have achieved nothing over the past weekend. That is correct, I've been playing Championship Manager again, and you've only got those little monkeys at  urlLink SIGames  to blame. With my nerves of steel, determination and lust for caffeine, I managed to push Montrose into the Scottish Premier League, which I'm not sure whether to be ashamed or proud of.  Obtained  urlLink Fruity Loops  and  urlLink Cubase , have started using Fruity Loops, however a lack of music editing knowledge, I've only been able to create a standard rock rthymn on drums, which may be impressive depending on what you do with it. I'll give Cubase a go later, not sure whether to expect something even more mind-boggling than Fruity Loops or something more easier to understand.  I haven't been searching around the interweb recently for any new websites of interest, but I can bring you to the attention of the new blogs at  urlLink Weebl & Bob .  One website was brought to my head just as I typed the previous paragraph, it is a web comic, and I think its nicely done. If you have some free time, check out  urlLink Phish-D . I'm unsure whether the site is up at this moment in time, but do check it out if you can.  I suppose in the future I should update this blog with something just remotely interesting, and I hope to do so tomorrow. Perhaps I should take my camera into school again and see what creativity urges me to do . . . (creativity?)  Toodles.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      On Monday, just as I was about to leave for school, four lovely little packages arrived from Play.com, and much to my delight, they were the cds I had ordered the Thursday before. First package ripped to shreds that I remember had to be  urlLink The Flaming Lips'  album 'Hear It Is'. This was followed by my cries of glee as I opened my second package,  urlLink Boards Of Canada's  great album 'Geogaddi'. Having looked at their website just now I recommend you take a visit, very nice Flash stuff in there.  Third package turned out to be  urlLink The Zuton's  'Who Killed The Zutons?'. which had to be my most awaited album of all four. And to top it off, Keane's (whose web address escapes my mind right now) 'Hopes And Fears'.  Still waiting for my U2 album to arrive, and even now, at time of posting this, has not arrived.  The Zutons totally blow away all the opposition in this album, having plenty of tracks that I already know the lyics to, and have shown to others. Next comes Boards Of Canada, which people I give a taster of, they do not like, which then I guess confirms that they are lunatics (oh yes, loonies).  Keane do have a good album, its fairly consistent and has some amazing tracks, and the first bar in 'Somewhere Only We Know' is powerful and gears you up straight from the very start.  The Flaming Lips' 'Hear It Is' is definitely not their best album, but still has great tracks. 'With You' is a song so lyrically simple and built up well with a crescendo that its hard to hate, its the Lips as they are, even if this was released in 1986. 'Unplugged' is a prime example of their punk sound, but most I could pick out during the first listen was the expletive 'shit', as what seemed to me, quite random. The rest of the record is great, and 'Summertime Blues' as a punk cover is explosive and lovely finish to the record.  The school week has been uneventful and dull, proving that school really is just not interesting anymore. During Monday's tutor period I visited Becci to organise an appointment with Connexions, and I was told that she would try and contact her and I was then given an information card. My thoughts then convinced me that I wasn't going to get an appointment and should just try and forget everything.  However I did get an appointment, I bumped into Becci on Tuesday and hse informed me that I were to have a meeting with the advisor at Connexions today. I was told to expect a slip taking me away from one of my lessons today, so that was that I thought, I had a meeting today.  Then I remembered.  "Oh crap, I have Ecology study at Lawns Woods in Science today. Lesson four. No doubt I'll get called for then, and I won't be there to go, I bet she does."  And my suspicions were correct, when I went to the office to check, I was informed that I was called for at lesson four and I replied that I was away on ecology study.  Damn.  Back I went to Becci, who told me that the Connexions person has gone for lunch and may come back, but may not. So after lunch I waited at the office for five minutes with Jessica, then gave up on all hope that she had returned.  Wednesday I was given a note to say that I had a meeting with Connexions on Thursday at 9am, so that was good. The rest of the day really flew by and I can't renember much anyway.  The meeting with Connexions was a bit tense at times . . . There were a lot of awkward silences where I couldn't think of what to say, and unsure of whether I should say some things. First we discussed careers, and I managed to find out a bit more about journalism and music, which was good. After about half an hour of discussing careers, I was given a little card and on there it listed many things that I may have wished to talk about. Briefly spoke about health, which moved on to how much I sleep, and this led to being asked if I felt a little depressed. I brushed it off as hormones, as when you think about it, it really is, and that was the end of the discussion, although I was advised to go see the school nurse. I thanked the person there and went to tutor as usual.  Nothing had happened until Friday, which was my mentoring meeting at school. I do not see the point in them, you go to the school for ten minutes to discuss whats going well for you and whats not going well for you, then you leave and have the day off. I'm not complaining, but it does seem a little silly if you ask me.  With the day off, I went into town with Matt, at the very early time of 9am (I consider this early as I am a lazy child), most shops were closed as expected, but we killed sometime then headed off to check out deals on XBoxs. In the end Matt went for a bundle offer that Game had, £150 for an XBox, extra controller, and two games of his choice, providing that they cost under £40. With a tenner left, he gave it to me on the one condition that I continue to work well in school, and I promised too, so trip to HMV!  Picked up 'Led Zeppelin IV' and 'Hit To Death In The Future Head' by The Flaming Lips, in a buy one get one free offer, came to £11 in the end. I was pleased I decided to bring my own measly balance of £3 with me, as it turned out to be life-saving, I had to get my hands on Led Zeppelin IV or I would cry!  Walked to Matt's after, and played Project Gotham Racing for a while, was fun, I managed to do over 100mph in a Volkswagen, and I tell you now, you haven't lived until you've driven a Volkwagen at over 100mph! Or maybe not, but there you go, thats me. Landmines on Splinter Cell: Pandora Tomorrow are funny. Matt decided the only way to get over them must be by jumping, how wrong he was. The screen was shrouded from the mine explosion and a little, "pfffft" could be heard. Both of us burst into fits of laughter, and then got past the first batch of mines. We continued walking along and all of a sudden, the screen became shrouded again and a little, "pfffft" could be heard. There was silence for a second, and then we erupted into laughter once more. I have no idea, but at the time it just seemed hilarious.  I left at about 1:15pm to see Jess, and stayed there for a while. Nothing really happened, except for watching Jess be a little clumsy around the kitchen. Had to leave at 2 because her mum might return, and Jess wasn't allowed any visitors whilst her mum was out, so I left, went to Tesco's and bought some Dr Pepper.  Knocked for Rebecca but she wasn't in, (I was told later on MSN that she was in, but opened the door and I had gone) and I began walking home. Looking at my watch, it told me that it was 2:30pm, I thought about what I could do. I could go back to my school and offer a helping hand, although the mentoring meetings would end pretty soon, and I wouldn't reach there until about 2:45pm anyway. Then I thought, what about my old school? Doesn't school finish there at 3pm? I could go there and say hi to the teacher that I knew. Going along with this plan I walked towards my old school, aware that I had plenty of time.  I passed my old school at 2:45 thinking I could see my nan, and so I did. As I walked past the school I could confirm that they were in school, as children were doing PE outside. I arrived at my nan, who seemed surprised and pleased to see me, and also told me that school finished at 3:15 there, not 3:00 as I previously thought. This gave me some time to relax, so I had a drink and spoke to my nan for a while.  My old school seems very small to me now, and it seems that a lot of teachers have left now, leaving only Mrs Ash, Mr Morris and Mrs Harris the familiar faces that I remember. I spoke to Mrs Ash first, being my teacher for my last two years of junior school. She recognised me instantly, which is a little different considering others took a while to recognise me. I offered to help them around the school for their last three days, and waited in the reception to talk to Mrs Harris.  The school is still the same in my opinion, it seems smaller to me seeing as I do go to a secondary school, but I still see a lot of work that my year made around the school. Most of it was the abstract paintings that have been scattered across the hall, and some leaves all put together to resemble a tree, was supposed to show that the school is united, I'm pretty sure thats what it meant. I do believe they have better equipment for theatrical productions now, even though the hall is short of space for a proper stage, they've still got a good PA system and lights, which I consider excellent for a primary school.  After talking to Mrs Harris I went home and found out that I was bought a new mobile phone! Woo yay! If I remember, its an NEC e313 on 3 pay as you go. Its all spiffy and has a camera, which makes a vast improvement from my previous phone, so I was happy. My only fault in it is that it has the length of my TV remote control, but seeing as I can fit my CD Player in my pocket, I'm sure I could get it in my pcoket with ease. Still can't remember my phone number, and I haven't jotted it down somewhere either so I have to get that done.  Using my phone I downloaded the video to XFM's alternative England Euro 2004 anthem, 'Born In England'. I have to say that the song will probably sell better than 'Altogether Now' as it follows the traits of many England anthems. The song is patriotic all the way through and I guess thats what makes a football anthem sell, even though I would like to see 'Altogether Now' sell more.  The weekend managed to pass by uneventfully, and I got bored to a point where I began to write the blog entry that you happen to be reading right now, except for that I got bored of that, saved a draft and continued it on Tuesday (the day I'm writing it now).  By Monday my U2 album still hadn't arrived, but unfortunately not a thing could be done about it because it wasn't 14 days since the order, so I just hoped it would arrive on Tuesday.  It still hadn't arrived.  I did get two nice e-mails through my inbox though. One said that my order for 'Beautiful Freak' by The Eels had been despatched now that it came into stock, and another saying that they had despatched 'War' by U2. War was the CD I had been waiting for. So as it seems, the CD that I had been waiting for over a week now, hadn't even been despatched yet. I felt a bit angry, they did send me an e-mail over a week ago saying they did despatch it, but this one had told me the same.  This brings the blog up-to-date for now, sorry its been so long without an entry, I just guess I've been lazy. I promise I'll get the pictures from Salcombe up too, thats one job I've been avoiding due to about 100 shots ruined by rain on lens, so I need to edit it all out before I can do anything.  Ciao.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Got back from Salcombe at about two in the afternoon, the time I spent there was brilliant, and I had plenty of fun, even though it did rain in buckets on monday.  I now have two new books, Tolstoy's 'Anna Karenina' and Dickens' 'Tale Of Two Cities'. I've finished 'Are You Dave Gorman?' and it was amazing, he also made an appearance on They Think Its All Over on friday too, but I missed it and only saw some parts of its repeat saturday night. Damn.  At the moment I just feel like crap, can't put it in any other way, just crap. I honestly have no idea whats going on, I just feel really angry at myself at most times and thinking about a lot of things, which just makes me feel even worse. I can't stop it either, and its really getting to me.  I've got problems nearly everywhere right now, home, outside, school, internet, I can't really enjoy myself without thinking of things.  I'm going to get an appointment with Connexions who are very conveniently still at my school, until then I can just hope that things can't get any worse. People may think I'm throwing a hissy-fit, but even though I would post anything here, I'm not going to go into detail about whats going on right now. All I can is that it hurts like hell.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Bought a new cd,  urlLink Radiohead's  'My Iron Lung' EP. Listened to it about three times, its brilliant stuff. One of the better purchases I've made in a while. Recommend it to anyone, currently on sale in HMV or £6, so get it whilst its cheap.   Was given £10 from my mum and nan today, which confused me but I'm not really complaining, so its a journey into town tomorrow to spend it on more cds.   Started a new blog, as the basis of a bet with James, which you can find  urlLink here.    Check that out, bookmark it, and come back soon for updates.   Short entry I know, but I haven't much interesting to say, so I'm saving you random rabble.   Ciao.   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Fourth entry of the day, smashing.  &nbsp;  Been playing about with Photoshop, looking at photos and seeing what I can make of them.  &nbsp;  In the past two days I've developed a series of pictures that I'll be working to extend in the next few days, quite possibly with sepia shots. Following that idea I may base photos on one colour and work from there, and stop limiting myself to grayscale.  &nbsp;  Feel free to look at what I've already done, they're linked and at 1260x1024, I didn't want to go any smaller for some reason, this probably being that 1260x1024 is my screen resolution.  &nbsp;   urlLink "Fall Over"    urlLink "STFU World"    urlLink "Maracas"    urlLink "Wasted" &nbsp;  Apologies to those on 56k, these may take a while to load. &nbsp; Enjoy, toodles.   
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Looking back at my blog this morning, I noticed that this day marked 2 months of successful blogging. Never before have I kept a blog and actually regularly updated it this long. So, me being very smug and pleased with myself, I've decided to make a third entry of the day.  &nbsp; I didn't manage to sleep until 3am, so to make up for it I slept until 1:30pm. Showered quickly, logged onto MSN and spoke to Devon and Stephen for a while whist waiting for James to come online. Once he did, a meet-up was arranged and I left the house ten minutes later. &nbsp; Met James at 3:10pm, we were both five minutes late as it seems. Made our way up the hill and had a chat, then waited for Stephen and Devon to arrive. &nbsp; 3:35pm, Stephen and Devon still hadn't arrived and boredom had begun to settle in. Loaded batteries into camera and took a picture of where we were waiting. Yes, I know its not exactly the most exciting thing to do when you're bored, but still it kept me busy seeing as my camera takes a while to load. &nbsp;   &nbsp; Luckily Stephen and Devon arrived a few minutes later, just in time before I really did get bored. This saved me from taking pictures of my foot, as you do. &nbsp; We arsed around in Lawns Wood for a&nbsp;while before going to Co-Op to get something to drink, then came back to Lawns Wood. I felt things were going to get a bit dull again, so I scraped through my mind for ideas, until finally one cropped up: &nbsp;  "Hey guys! Lets play a game of Hide and Seek!"    &nbsp; Then what followed could only be described as fun, even though tiring and slightly childish. Four teenagers running around Lawns Wood hiding from each other is always fun, because, lets face it, theres nothing better to do in Swindon. &nbsp; Saw Michael, Simon and Ben and let them join the game. They didn't do very well though, with me and Devon working as a team we were unbeatable. (Of course, there was no cheating involved). &nbsp; Rode down the hill on Ben's bike thinking to myself, "Wheeeeeeeee!" and then the long ride back up the hill again. Well, I gave up on that one and just walked the bike up. &nbsp; By 6pm Devon and James had left, and Michael, Simon and Ben went off somewhere else. Feeling hungry, me and Stephen decided to go and get something to eat from Co-op. The only problem was that we still had a Co-Op bag with us, containing seven party-sized Milky Ways and an empty bottle of Pepsi. &nbsp; Our only solution was to hide the Milky Ways in Lawns Wood, in a location only we knew. We looked around, and deciding not to hide&nbsp;them&nbsp;under a tree, we hid them in a hole in a wall instead. We resolved that should we leave them for an hour or two, then they would be safe and not found. Hell, we could have even left them there overnight and picked them up the next day, seeing as we were all going to meet again. &nbsp; It would not be so. &nbsp; Having bought some crisps, a chocolate bar and a drink each, for the lovely price of £2.97, we went to the Town Gardens to take some pictures and relax for a while, the earlier events of Hide and Seek had tired us out after all. &nbsp; Looked at the aviary for a while, took some pictures and then walked along the park. &nbsp;         &nbsp; Weeee budgies! &nbsp; The park itself is very nice, very peaceful despite those who breaks the rules of the grounds, playing ball games and being generally loud.                            &nbsp; Whilst walking we found a squirrel, its true.    &nbsp; We tried to get closer, but the little critter ran as soon as he saw me with my camera. I blame the camera. Ugly thing.    &nbsp; So at 7:50pm after finishing taking pictures, we decided to head home after a long-ish day. As we got to Lawns Wood we remembered the Milky Ways, and set off to get them. In the distance we could see an old lady with a dog, led by a wall, and pulling out a shopping bag. Getting closer we could see that she was examining it, pulling something out, putting it back in and then walking off with the bag. Two seconds later, me and Stephen were in hysterics. &nbsp; The old lady had found our Milky Ways and had off with them. We thought it was bad for us to even leave chocolate in Lawns Wood and come back for it later, let alone an old lady to look around, find them, and take them for ourself. &nbsp; Part of us was in hysterics at the thief, and another part of us was feeling robbed, and lets face it, we were. &nbsp; We had lost seven Milky Ways, these were going to be used the next day as food, and now we would have to get some more food for tomorrow. &nbsp; We finally went home after confirming that the old lady did indeed thieve our chocolate and rested. &nbsp; This brings an end to todays' events, and now my fingers are hurting from typing too much. &nbsp; Will update some more soon, ciao. 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        &nbsp;  "Raaaawrgh! I am a Chocobo! I demand that you give me three golden eggs, a spatula, and a subscription to Ostriches Monthly. If you do not meet these demands, I shall be forced to peck you on the head with my sharp green beak. If you are to harm me, I'm sure my dozen or so other friends will be here to hurt you. Skin us alive and with our feathers make a little rainbow thingy."    &nbsp; Conclusive proof Swindon really has lost it.  (Or me perhaps.)  
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Oh yes, school is finally over and done with. I shan't be returning until 2nd September, which means I have six weeks of wonderful spare time.     Strangely though, it feels weird this year after breaking from school. A huge part of me feels glad that I've finished, giving me the chance to take a break from actually doing some work, and now being able to wander around Swindon.     In other ways though, I do miss school somehow this year. School was really the only way for me to regularly see my friends without having to make up excuses not to make it to meet-ups or whatever. Not only that, but I did find some of the work set to me fun and challenging too.     I've decided to keep in contact with my tutor during the holidays, so I shall be sending him an e-mail on Monday to see how things are, and hopefully I'll get a reply soon after.     Saturday was fun. After waking up late, I still managed to meet James in town, along with Devon, Stephen and his friend Amy. Little did I know that in town the Swindon Festival was taking place, so I was surprised that as I passed the Millennium Clock, creatures that resembled Chocobo's (in many colours) were creeping about. Afraid, I quickly found James and the others in time to be rescued, before any of them got near me! :)    (I shall include a picture of the Chocobo-like creature in the next entry)    I met Rach in town, as I was about to go to Virgin Megastore, had a little chat, then set off to purchase my fiftieth (:o) cd. For £7, I grabbed the  urlLink Red Hot Chili Peppers'  - 'Blood Sugar Sex Magik'. I've listened to it many times now and its a brilliant album, the best track on it obviously being 'Under The Bridge'.    So, me and the others walked around town for a while, passing the brass band on the main stage of the festival, and then walked off to some place which I didn't know of. James decided to get out his bag of glucose and eat a mouthful of it -- in front of a packed restaurant. The result, a large amount of glucose settling under his nose whilst people watch on in wonder. I think it goes without saying that we quickly rushed to the alley so that he could wipe it off.    After that, it was off to Lawns Wood for a good two hours or so, just messing about and calling Devon, "Emo Boy". James ate a whole lot of glucose and felt very sick, and soon after,  was  sick.    Me and James went on covert operations and snuck behind Stephen to pelt him with a banana, but before we could I screwed up the mission by being spot by Stephen. We still hit him with the banana though.    At 4:55pm we went to Co-Op (yay) to buy some food and drink. I bought two 500ml bottles of Pepsi for 81p (bargain) and left the shop. Remembered I was going to need a bag I re-entered the shop, went to take a bag, and dropped all the bags on the floor, thus making me the idiot.    Went home about 5:20pm, mainly because I was supposed to be home twenty minutes earlier. As I walked down the hill I could hear the cries of, "EMO BOY!" directed at me, so I gave James the swift finger and carried on walking. Woo.    Whilst walking down Upham Road I noticed two girls further down the road. Remembering I was wearing my Foo Fighters hoody, and the fact that it was quite hot that day, I knew that I was about to be called a goth. I was quite wrong, as one of the two girls happened to be Maria, so I had a quick chat before heading home.    Got home, parents weren't in yet. Yay.    The rest of the day carries on being uneventful, and then after getting back from my Nan's house, I head off to the land of Nod.    Sunday was boring, I didn't leave the house. More importantly, I didn't get dressed until after 3 in the afternoon. \o/ Lazy bonus score!    Hopefully I'm going out later today, as long as I get some rest now, as its 2am and I am le tired. Jams set me the challenge of taking one good photo of him over the summer holidays, so bored as I was, I went through my photo collection and found two pictures of Jams, and edited them. Of course they won't qualify for the challenge but I shall be asking Jams if I can put them up on here with his permission.    Oh how I love writing updates in the wee early hours of the morning.    Ciao. 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Random Fact #23 -- My desk is filled with so much crap.  Proof I hear you ask? Read on my friend . . .  Well I have the proof, and the proof is terrifying! I need no proof to prove that this proof is by far some of the most horrific and stunningly real proof I've ever given.     Dun dun DUUUUUUUUUUUUN!  Look, a plate, a pile of CD's, biscuits even! Not even 'The Hobbit' escapes the woodenness of the desk! Oh, and a bowl! Can't forget the bowl! With a spoon! Yes, the bowl has a spoon with it! Who would have thought of that? Me? Surely not, for my IQ is lower than that of a braindead goldfish.     I have plenty of paperclippery things. This is useful, for holding things up and stuff . . . I've never used them though, but they're still paperclippery. Don't forget the coppers, I may need them in the case of an emergency, like scraping 23p in one penny coins so that I can get a nice £1 coin.     Even Rebecca's sheepy lies in the depths of the desk, and I fished it from behind the Bowl Of Cereal Scrummyness so it can sit upon the Book of Hobbitness.     More sheep, with off-orange glowage action!     Raffle tickets are seen occasionally lying about the desk, however I shall be returning them to the School of Churchfields tomorrow for the grand finale of all raffle draws! Weeeehehehehehe!     One thing on this desk does feel right at home however. As you can see, I do indeed have a pink pile of post-it notes, and a yellow one too but thats not really in the picture. Post-It notes are vital for the survival of a Kevvie, and play a major part in his life. As you can see:        So, I think this proves that my desk is indeed a great big tip of junk, that will sooner or later, need sorting out. Not only has that been proved, but it also proves that I a} have no life, and b) need to get out more.  I thank you and bid you goodnight.  Kevvie (Teh Wizzard/Annoying/Eejit/Sexxeh) -- delete as applicable xXx
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm finding it hard to motivate myself, and I'd say its been difficult for the past month or so now. I've neglected many things, namely doing work at school and updating this blog, which I need to do more often. I want to get out of this pattern as soon as possible, I finish school on Friday and I don't want to be facing six weeks of achieving nothing and being lazy in general.  I'm thinking of getting my forum up again, although it wouldn't really work due to lack of members, as it always does. Not only that, but I'd prefer to do something that keeps me out of the house as well. This wouldn't really effect my amount of blogging considering that could be done at night or through the medium of (dun dun duuuun) e-mail.  I would love to go take more photographs over the holidays but even photography has faded away from my to-do list in the past two months. Its not that I don't like photography anymore -- its just that Swindon is a dull and boring town, and there are very few sites which would look good.  I don't really want to see many people during the holiday -- only four or five people I'd rather see. I suppose they know who they are, mainly because I tell them everything on my mind which frequently doesn't make it onto this blog.  So yeah, motivation, I need it, and preferably in abundance. I'm fed up of lazing around the house and doing nothing. Suggestions left in the comments section or an e-mail sent to poor_posture@[REMOVE THIS PART]hotmail.com would be appreciated.  Hell, if you want me to do something stupid or funny then go ahead and suggest it, I wouldn't mind doing it. In fact, I'll do it unless it has something to do with me and a large amount of pain.  Toodles.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I finished my last Art lesson . . . Ever  \o/  (Proper update later today or tomorrow)
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm happy.  I have someone who truly does brighten up my life, keep me sane, and still be so amazing at the same time. This person is all I'll need.  I love you. 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yup, I lie, so heh.  Yes, thats it, heh.  Anyway, the reason I decided not to go with my plan of posting about nearly everything since Saturday is that it would take too long, and not only that, but quite frankly, it was not interesting.  To sum it up though, this is what happened:-  Saturday: I get no sleep on this day, meet James fairly early-ish, and beat my record for staying up as long as possible. It now stands at approximately 30 hours. This however, has its downside, my uncle thinks I'm a weirdo. But I pwn at Halo, even when I'm nearly asleep, oh yes.  Sunday: I wake up at 4pm after having big sleep (finally), and nothing happens.  Monday: Fall asleep at about 6am. Wake up at 4pm. I play Euro 2004. End.  Tuesday: Fall asleep at around the same time as Monday. Wake up at 10am thanks to alarm clock. Go back to sleep. Wake up at 12:30pm, James is on the phone and I'm supposed to meet him. I tell him I'll meet him in an hour, I fall asleep again. Cue 1:45pm, a call from a rather annoyed James as I tell him to come to my house. We go to town, get absolutely drenched, thanks to the 'la la la, sunny . . . AAAAARGH FUCKING THUNDERSTORM!'. Go to a barbeque later.  Wednesday: omgomgomgomg fall asleep even later than ever, but not losing all my sleep. Wake up and play Euro 2004 for a while, get dressed, find the 'Stop Wars' t-shirt I want and order it. (OK, how really fucking spooky is this? As I type about the Stop Wars shirt, 'Run' by Snow Patrol comes on. How incredibly creepy! Incase you didn't know, Gary is wearing the shirt I've ordered in the 'Spitting Games' video, except mine is navy blue.)  Thursday: Emerge from bed at 7am because aaaaargh I give up trying to sleep! Grrr! Meeting James at ten.  As you might gather, I'm rather annoyed at my inability to sleep, and am now considering hitting myself over the head with several large objects before I go to bed tonight. However, for tonight though this will not be a problem as I'll fall asleep fast enough due to a complete lack of sleep today.  Thats how it works.  Its strange too, I could get two hours of sleep and still not feel tired and go to bed at about 12am, as normal. When no sleep comes into it though, by 7pm I feel faint and dizzy, and thus fall asleep ANYWHERE (hence the uncle thinking I'm weird) pretty soon after.  I'm not going to bother with any sleeping pills or anything, I'm just going to hope that this all ends pretty soon, because its starting to get to me. One plus side though, is that I'm up and now able to meet James on time! \o/  Also, in other news, today being the 5th August, this means that Fairford is two weeks away. Woo and yay, for total boredom! Houpla, for I will have nothing to do for five days, along with no internet, limited camera-age and music, and most probably no credit whatsoever!  As you can tell, I'm just brimming with excitement . . . Maybe not.  Seeing as its 9:32am now I really should be rounding off this post and getting ready to meet James, not sure what I'll do though. I'm thinking of writing some short stories when I won't have internet access in two weeks time, so I may post them on here for your viewing pleasure/pain, thats if I ever do write them. I seem to write enough anyway.  Byeeeeee. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I am here, and this post really is to let you know that I am still alive, and breathing, and still being a bloody mess spending my time in a bloody mess of a room. Am I going to clean it? No! Why? I just don't know!  Anyway, sorry for bringing you boredom and nothing interesting to say, after all I've promised two people an update. Whats that I hear you ask? Two people? Unbelievable, but true, two people now read my blog and demand updates, what is the world coming to eh?  So, I'm going to go to sleep, (thats if I ever get sleep, considering the situation right now) and I will fill you all in about everything in the morning. I can tell you one thing now, that the entry will be called, "Stalking, Lazing, Thunderstorms and Barbeques".  Toodles. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>