<Blog>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      COOL!!  I personally thought the Concert Companion was remarkable.  I would love to attend a symphony concert but am reluctant because my wife has very little music background and would not enjoy a long performance of Beethoven's 9th.  I, on the other hand, would.  The concert companion would allow her (and me too for that matter) to access information regarding the orchestra, the piece of music, and other important information to make her feel engaged in the performance.  I can see this opening up a whole new audience to the symphony orchestra.  The other gadgets were neat too.  It is yet to be seen if they will "catch on" and become standards in the U.S.  I thought the toilet was a little much.  I mean, come on, who needs a remote to raise the seat and/or flush the toilet?  I can certainly see the need for a cell phone that helps eliminate background noise.  I often see people in the airport talking on the phone with one finger crammed in their ear, cell phone smashed against the other, and the grimaced face of "What did you just say?!"  It would bring a whole new meaning to the phrase, "Can you hear me now?".  BC
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I enjoyed this article.  I guess because under each rule of good technology, it provided a real-world example.  Like rule number 3 - Good technology is always connected, it talks about fire alarms....they are always connected!  It also provided examples of things that have become so popular because of their advances...like the telephone.  It is simple to use, does not require any "start up", and is readily available for a cheap price.  It does what we want it to do and we don't have to wait to use it after someone else (well, sometimes we do).  I think good technology is also adaptable.  I have added to and used different products with my computer at home.  I have added a scanner, webcam, digital camera, CD burner, and tons of software.  My computer has adapted with me as my needs have changed.  That's what makes it good technology.  It also has done everything I have asked it to do.  It falls under several of the good rules of technology.  These 9 rules are a good guide to purchasing and improving technology at home or at school.  They can be a valuable resource when starting the process of purchasing new technology.  BC
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      As I read through the article, Teaching in the wireless cloud, I thought about what emerging technology means for me as a classroom teacher.  I can see the benefits of using wireless connections in the classroom for research, discussion, and interaction.  I think it can be a powerful educational tool....so long as its used in an appropriate manner and is monitored.  Students already use cell phones to text message their friends in class.  Cell phones are just the beginning.  As students begin to get deeper and deeper into technology, schools will continually have to adpat.  They will have to learn to use technology to their advantage.  I think college and universities are a wonderful place to use wireless technology in the classroom...I think use of these technologies in the public school classroom are a long way away.  The resources (technology and financial) are limited in public school education.  In order to acheive such an undertaking, a teacher would have to receive a grant in order to fund and provide for such a project.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I guess this article is about the future of librarian interaction.  Instant messaging has become a standard in the Internet community.  It is fascinating that IM has created its own language for communicating.  This new form of communication has obviously created a new outlet for expression.  Here, a library patron happens across a librarian.  He asks a question for curiosity and a discussion begins.  The discussion continues until the patron has a book set aside for him at the library.  Just like asking questions in person, just of the Internet.  I do see a problem with IM for schools.  That is the ability to communicate with friends via text messaging or IM.  We already have to watch cell phones VERY closely so that students will not text message each other.  If they are caught with their cell phone out or in the "on" position, it is taken away and has to be retrieved from the office.  As technology grows and changes, schools will continue to adapt to those changes.  BC
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      As I read through the article, I thought about my own school.  How difficult would it be to re-create such a website for Russellville High School?  Do we have the technology and the expertise?  I don't see why not.  With the help of EAST Lab, I am sure that our school could develop a user-friendly, community based website for students, teachers, and community members to access and make the school a real part of the community.  I browsed through some of the Beacon school website and was impressed by the professional quality and ease of access.  Many clubs and sports were linked as well as individuals "homepages".  I thought about what a wonderful resource this would be for the community.  For example, let's say a family is about to move to Russellville.  They could access the school's page and explore the school system they are about to enter.  I current district and school webpages are underdeveloped, hard to "explore", and do not make the community feel a part of the school.  We have simply not stuck to a vision of a plan.  We have grasped at the air to try and integrate the Internet into the school community.  I think with a clear vision and a dedication to make it a reality, a project similar to this would be possible for Russellville High School.  BC
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      How do I get into the printer ink business?!  Talk about a gold mine (no pun intended)!  As I read through the article, I couldn't help but get a little steamed.  My printer ALWAYS runs out of ink at the most inconvenient times.  Right when that big report is due or right when you have finally gotten the data EXACTLY like you want it....boom.  No ink!  Then to think I have to go out and spend 28 dollars to replace the stupid thing.  Not to mention that I have bought the wrong cartridges before because of one little letter on the code (ex. 45A as opposed to 45).  I can't believe that people pay more for ink cartridges than they do printers!  It's almost better to go buy a new printer everytime you need ink.  It sure might be cheaper.  As I think about printer ink companies, it makes me think of brick manufacturers.  There are only 2 brick companies in the United States.  If you want bricks, you pay for them and have to wait 6 months to get them.  If ink companies continue to monopolize the industry, we will soon be on a waiting list at the local Staples to purchase printer ink!  BC
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I think facial recognition software is a good idea.  If nothing else, to have a database of parents who check there kids in and out.  I know in our school, it is hard to know each and every student, and who his/her parents are.  I think this would be a valuable asset in schools.  We currently do not have photo ID badges for students.  HS faculty members have them for security/alarm purposes.  Students do not have them for any reason.  These IDs could be used for lunch cards, hall passes, identification in the community, etc.  I do not see a violation of any rights or personal liberties by establishing a database of parent and student photographs.  Those that did not wish to participate in such a program could sign a waiver releasing the school from liability of allowing students to check out with the wrong people.  BC
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I can't believe that the United States only has 39 percent of its school computers hooked up to the Internet.  Knowing that almost all of our computers at school are networked and Internet capable, I guess I feel sorry for those schools that do not have their school computers wired for the Internet.  Technology use around the globe has exploded and will continue to grow.  It will also bring us closer as a global community.  I find it interesting that other countries are starting to "catch up" to the U.S. in technology use and computer ratios.  We should take a closer look into continuing the push for technology integration in the United States education system.  The problem exists that states are responsible for education.  I think we will continue to see national legislation about education and the use of technology.  Education is a continually changing field and educators must be willing to change with the times.  Those changing times include the integration and use of technology in the classroom.  Teachers must be willing to commit to educating the next generation of Americans to be successful in their careers.  That committment will mean stretching the envelope and teaching new things in new ways.  BC  Additional Comments 6-14:  I looked at the charts for technology use by state.  I was pleased to see that Arkansas did NOT rank near the bottom in an education category!  As I looked at the Use of Technology statistics, I was impressed that AR 4th graders had one of the highest percentages of computer use once or more a week....BUT I then saw that that use was mainly drill and practice.  Drill and practice is good, but does not allow students all the benefits of using computers in the classroom.  I was suprised that more states do not require technology training for veteran teachers.  Only a handful, of which AR is a part, require such training.  Very interesting information from these charts.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      WOW! How do you respond to something that big?  I personally wouldn't want anyone to use my computer for a "shared power" project.  I understand the importance of having shared power between computers.  It allows people to perform astronomical amounts of computation with the power of many computers together.  The idea of helping sort radio signals from outer space with my computer is insane.  I would not want anyone to put software on my computer, use it freely without me having any knowledge about what was going on.  I don't think that anytime in the near future we will have "roaming computational tribes".  The idea of a group of people sharing computer power to perform major computations is far-fetched for an individual like me.  I don't believe that teachers will be sitting around the lounge sharing laptop power to compute radio signals from outer space.  BC
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I think digital cameras will replace SLR film cameras in the public market.  I do think "regular" cameras will remain in the photo world for photographers.  As technology advances and becomes easier, faster, and more user-friendly, more and more people will catch on and begin to use digital cameras.  I personally enjoy my digital camera.  I am on my second one.  My first was cutting edge at the time because it had a place to put a floppy disk right into the camera.  It was fairly expensive and was a 1.5 megapixel camera (which, at the time, was about as good as you could find on the mainstream market).  Now, my camera holds an SD card (much smaller and more memory) and is 5 megapixels.  All this for about half the price!  I will continue to use digital cameras (both still and video) for personal and school use.  They are a vital tool in the educational process.  For me, digital video has superior sound quality and allows us to evaluate performances through video and audio.  It also allows us to put together a collaboration project of the year featuring video and audio elements from throughout the year.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Often times if you are helping someone use a computer, they are already in an uncomfortable position.  If you spout off computer lingo, you can only confuse them further and cause them more stress!  If you help them through it slowly and basically, you are much more likely to succeed in the task and with that person.  It is beneficial to be honest...like the article stated, if you don't know, say you don't know.  If you are guessing, say something like, let's try this.  I have often guessed on how to do things and said, no, that's not the way to do it, let me try something else.  I will just keep poking around until it works or I get frustrated enough to start over.  So remember when you are working with someone who needs help.....  be positive, respectful and walk them slowly through the process.  Don't rush them because they are probably already a little apprehensive.  BC
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The age of computer based testing is already here.  I personally took some of my Praxis exams on the computer.  It provided immediate feedback and was simple to use and complete.  This was on the math section of course.  Essay questions, however, are a little different.  Computers can check spelling, grammar, and layout easily.  The content and flow of ideas is a little more subjective.  I see the benefits of computer based grading - rapid return in results, accuracy of spelling and grammar, speed of test administration and cost efficiency of materials.  However, nothing replaces the need for human grading.  There will always be a need for huan testing.  Someone has to run the computers!  BC
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I took a look at a few of the fine arts field trips.  COOL!  I wish I had this resource when I taught a fine arts class.  I could have let my students explore and learn the things I was teaching.  Instead, I had to dream up ways to teach them.  I think I will email this link to a friend of mine for her use.  These tools make taking a "trip" outside the classroom a little easier.  It is a MASSIVE undertaking to take a field trip.  The planning, the paperwork, the approval, the forms, the discipline, etc.....I could go on for a while.  These virtual tours allow students similar experiences right at their fingertips as opposed to getting on a bus and traveling somewhere.  Besides, some of these tours take you to places that might otherwise be unaccessible.  BC
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The teachers that allowed students to view this video should be held accountable for their actions.  Their actions show a lack of educational control of resources, lack of moral judgement, and lack of ethical rational.  These teachers showed a lack of educational leadership in the classroom by either not screeing the materials prior to using, or by giving students free reign of computer use.  It is also a huge ethical and moral judgement to show this particular video.  If a teacher felt it was ethical to show this video, a process of approval should have been followed.  As a teacher, I am outraged that educators would show such a disregard for their moral and ethical responsibility to students.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Recall the last difficult problem that you had to solve. Did you solve it alone, or did you solicit the help of others? What did you learn from solving that problem? Can that learning be used again?   I like to listen to others.  I do, however, like to make my own decision.  For example, I had to make a career choice earlier this year.  I had an opportunity to take a job at RHS instead of staying at my current position at RJHS.  I asked advice from family, friends, co-workers, etc.  I took all of their advice and put it together to help me make my decision.  I knew this would be a choice I would have to live with for the next 15 to 20 years so it weighed heavy on my mind for nearly a week.  It is stressful to have to carry a large burden for a long period of time.  What did I learn from that??  That your gut reaction is almost always correct.  Can I use that again...sure.  As long as I am rational about my decisions and make clear and just choices, I can use my gut reaction to be an indicator to me in the future.  BC
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Some educators argue that we learn much more from our failures than from our successes. Why? They believe that we should put students in situations where their hypotheses or predictions fail. Can you think of a situation in which you learned a lot from a mistake?  Not so much a mistake but a failure.  In music, students are often put into situations where they don't succeed as well as they had hoped.  It is these "failures" that make us challenge ourselves to greater success.  For example, when I was an 8th grade music student, I tried out for All-Region band.  There were 93 trumpets that tried out that year.  After the tryouts, I placed 80 out of 93 (NOT TOO GOOD!!).  I would consider that a failure...I did then and I still do.  After that, I learned what I could do to increase my chances for success.  I started taking private lessons, began to practice more, and prepared myself better for the next year.  The next year's tryouts came and 112 trumpets tried out and I placed 1st out of 112.  I would consider that a success....did then and still do.  So, I learned from a failure and turned it into a positive learning experience for me.  I have seen it in my own students as well...success can come from failure.  BC
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Can you think of an activity that makes you dumber, not smarter? Do you learn anything from that activity?   No.  Acticities are a way to continually expand your mind.  Even if the knowledge base is in place, the activity has been taught before, students have shown mastery, actually participating in the activity should just "reinforce" the learning.  Making the transition from short term to long term memory.  How many times as a kid did I put the same puzzle together...50, 100, 1000 times?  It wasn't that I was learning something "new" each time I did the puzzle, I was just transferring knowledge and expanding my thinking each time I did the puzzle.  Maybe the 1,156th time I did the puzzle I wanted to put the pieces together by size or maybe by color.  Who knows what I was thinking.....that's just it...I was thinking.  So learning is constantly going on no matter what the activity.  BC
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      WOW!  I had no idea that teachers, students, and administrators had so many standards in technology.  I knew we were supposed to be receiving 6 hours of technology training each year, but is that truly sufficient to meet these high standards?  I doubt it.  For example, teachers being able to "demonstrate introductory knowledge, skills, and understanding of concepts related to technology" is a tough task for some experienced teachers.  They need adequate hands-on training to be able to acheive these standards.  If our school district wants us to succeed as teachers, they will provide us the apporpriate and adequate training that is needed in order to acheive these standards.  Currently, technology in-service is scratching the surface of the introductory skill level.  Our in-services typically consist of 6 or 7 short 45 minute sessions on a particularly BASIC topic of technology.  I can only learn about how to hook up multimedia equipment so many times.  Personally, I am not afforded the opportunity to grow in my technology training at our district in-services.  They are basic and in need of overhauling.  Maybe that's where I can grow - by developing more adequate training for young teachers that need something to "push" the envelope a little.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The question is will you take your personal PC to school.  My answer is no.  I already use my school computer and home computer in conjunction with each other by emailing documents home and to school.  I also have a school laptop that I can take home if necessary.  This portability allows me to "work on the go" and be productive on those bus trips and during commercials of my favorite TV show.  Will students start taking personal computers to school.  The answer is two fold.  Yes, students will start taking PCs to school for personal use.  The problem lies within the use of the computer.  For example, palm pilots are currently not allowed in most schools because of the inappropriate uses that have occurred with them such as changing tv channels and beaming messages.  The same problem lies in the use of PCs in school.  They could be used for personal entertainment such as games, web sufing, or other "fun" stuff.  Some schools have set up a system where the school checks out laptop computers to students to use for educational use.  They can set up these computers to be "game free" and be more educationally sound.  I think the PC will be integrated more and more into the classroom as technology advances and teachers receive more training.  I believe that we are still some years away from the student carrying his/her personal computer to school.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Question #2  What is your theory of learning? From your perspective, how do people learn?    My theory of learning....  I believe all students can learn.  No matter how large or small the concept or task, students can learn.  The nature of humans is to learn...through touch, sight, hearing, smelling, etc.  It is our job as teachers to tap into the particular avenue of learning that is best suited for our students.  How do people learn??  All people learn differently.  It is my belief that no one person learns the same way.  We may share similar styles of learning and similar preferences for learning, but the actual learning process is completely individual.  As a teacher, it is my responsibility to make sure that I provide my students with numerous avenues of learning.  By incoporating different teaching methods, I can address particular learning styles which can aide in the learning process.  I then have to determine if my students have completed the learning process by evaluating them.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      My niece will be 4 years old this month. She too already knows how to work a VCR and DVD player. In fact, Papa (my father-in-law) was trying to help her get Sleeping Beauty started on the DVD player and he couldn't figure out how to get it started. My niece (independent that she is) said, "Here, Papa, let me do it." As a young adult and with plans for children someday, I wonder where technology will be when my children become school age. Will all computers be small, portable, and fast? My hope is that I can stay on the cutting edge as long as possible before I too become obsolete.  
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Technology is constantly trying to become smaller, more user friendly, and faster. If a student has a choice between a large textbook and a CD-ROM, GREAT!! It is important to make students feel involved in learning. By providing them with an option in their learning, they are taking ownership in their learning. The problem that I have seen arise in integrating technology is providing adequate resources for those students that do not have access to technology outside of the school walls. Those students have to be provided the same opportunities as those students that have access to technology at home. I would like to see integration of technology INCREASE within our educational system.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      test
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Welcome!  I hope what you find here is useful and informative.  Brad
     
    
</post>


</Blog>