<Blog>

<date>11,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      "Art washes from the soul the dust of everyday life."     - Pablo Picasso 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      "Be kind, for everyone you meet is fighting a great battle."     - Philo of Alexandria
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      "The great mission in life has nothing to do with any struggle between classes, races, nations or ideologies, but is rather a personal quest to enlarge the soul, liberate the spirit and light up the brain."     - Tom Robbins
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      "Consistency is the last refuge of the unimaginative."     - Oscar Wilde
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      "If we, citizens, do not support our artists, then we sacrifice our imagination on the altar of crude reality and we end up believing in nothing and having worthless dreams."     - Yann Martel
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      "Without art, the crudeness of reality would make the world unbearable."     - George Bernard Shaw
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      "Creativity is allowing yourself to make mistakes.  Art is knowing which ones to keep."     -Scott Adams
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      "Every child is an artist.  The problem is how to remain an artist once we grow up."     - Pablo Picasso
     

    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Last week I attended the Alternative Press Conference in San Francisco.  I met many great cartoonists and I'd like to share some of their work with you.    Kris Dreesen -  urlLink www.girlthrow.com   Paige Braddock -  urlLink www.janesworldcomics.com   Carol Lay -  urlLink www.waylay.com   Gina Kamentsky -  urlLink www.t-gina.com   Wayne Chan -  urlLink www.turtlecomics.com   Raina Telgemeier -  urlLink www.goRaina.com   Jeremy Lambros -  urlLink www.abusecartoons.com   Ellen Forney -  urlLink www.ellenforney.com    and also check out:   Manual Comics -  urlLink www.manualcomics.com   The Cartoon Art Museum -  urlLink www.cartoonart.org   Friends of LuLu -  urlLink www.friends-lulu.org   
     

    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "I prefer drawing to talking.  Drawing is faster, and allows less room for lies."  - Le Corbusier
     

    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       This weekend I participated in the first (and hopefully annual) Art for Charity Days at the Cornelia Arts Building in Chicago.  Special thanks to  urlLink Jason Messinger  for organizing such a great show and being so supportive about my work.  20% of my proceeds will benefit  urlLink Lambda Legal .  The best part of the weekend was meeting fellow artists, enjoying their work and stories.  Check out this great work!   urlLink Jeanette Bezazian    urlLink Brian Justice   urlLink Michael Bonfiglio     urlLink Michael T. Prichard  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's time for a professional to step in. The website is currently under re-construction.  Look for a new, improved site sometime this summer.   In the meantime, listen to  urlLink Air America Radio .
     

    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just back from NY.  Spent Saturday at The Whitney Biennial.  Check out  urlLink this related site.         
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I should be a better blogger.  When I'm up in the middle of the night I really enjoy finding people's blogs to read.  And it's even better if they are funny, smart, insightful.  I like to think that now and then I'm any one of those things, but I realize my blog is totally lame.  What are the elements of a good blog?  First and foremost for me as a reader, there's the balance of self-understanding without self-absorption.  That's key.  And being able to tell a story helps.  Having a story to tell helps even more.  Most of us don't think we have stories to tell but we do.    What are blogs generally about?  Just whatever is on people's minds at the time of writing, I suppose.  For me that would be: politics, how to finish a home remodeling, surviving my chronic upper respiratory tract infections, making art, and selling things on the internet.  Oh and my goldfish who just won't die.    This ties in with this week's cartoon of the week so it's fitting story to tell here.  I'm currently going through a nightmare pet situation again.    Here's the deal: we have this goldfish named Boomer that we got shortly after moving into this house three years ago.  He has grown  at least twice his original size.  His old home was an Eclipse three gallon tank with filter and BioWheel, which is supposed to maintain a healthy bacterial balance in the tank.  But he outgrew that.  This fish has at least tripled in size.  So we got him the six gallon version of the same tank.  He's thriving in that, now four times his original size.  I even painted a custom backdrop to make him feel even more special. (If fish can feel special.)  At five times his original size, he's pretty happy.  (You see where this fish story is going, eh?)  So then we have the perfectly good three gallon Eclipse tank free for a new occupant. We thought it would be fun to give to our friend Pat who could use a pet.  After cleaning it out thoroughly, I filled it and added a fish from Chicago Aquarium.  He died overnight.  I asked them what it could have been and they said, "ammonia."  A no brainer apparently, but I didn't get it.  I had put ammonia lock in the water - how could it have happened overnight?  Doesn't ammonia need a while to build up?  So I decided they were wrong, their fish was sickly.    I cleaned out the tank again and went to Petcare.  Got a little orange goldfish who would later be named 'Ade' because I got her the day Adriana was killed on The Sopranos.  After a few days in the tank, she started getting brown spots all over her.  According to some pamphlet on goldfish care it's hemorrhagic bacterial septicemia.  Great.  My fish is bleeding from the inside out. She didn't eat for the first week we had her.  I can't imagine how she survived.  No eating, no poop, just bleeding into her fins for a full week.    I decide the tank must be the problem and I put her in an old-fashioned biowheel-free goldfish bowl, exchanging 50% of the water every day.  I threw away the Eclipse 3.  She got a little better.  She started eating.  She was doing well.  Believing her on the mend and thinking she deserved another chance at BioWheel living, I went out and got her an Eclipse Profile three gallon tank of her very own.  I carefully set up the tank, let it run for an entire weekend so it would be all ready.  I took no shortcuts.  When we got home from our weekend away, I put her in the new tank and within 24 hours she starting dying again, swimming on her side, acting like the ammonia had gone to her head, divebombing the bottom of her tank.    All this time, Cindy will walk up to her perfectly healthy seven-times-his-original-size Boomer and feed him in his happy little tank, almost mocking my sickly, splotchy, now crazed little fish.    Ade is back in her old fashioned goldfish bowl now, back to 50% water changes every day.   She's not swimming on her side anymore, but she's not eating again.  And now I have an Eclipse Profile 3 drying out downstairs.  Cindy actually verbalized the thought I wouldn't let myself speak: I'd love to put another fish in there just to see what happens...  I'm picturing tanks on every countertop with fish in various stages of demise.  Goldfish hospice.  I don't think we're zoned for that. 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Lincoln Square Chamber of Commerce Guide and Directory is about to come out with my piece on the cover.   urlLink See the article online .
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Life has been pretty hectic with my two favorite people having monumental birthdays on the same date this year, but the celebrations were worth every second of effort.     During the mayhem, I've tried to keep on top of my work, and I'm proud to announce I've delivered two commissions, been interviewed and photographed by the Chicago Tribune and done a Cartoon of the Week every week except one. (I got busted by friends for re-running an old cartoon that week.)     I do realize that blogging, general accounting and making new architectural caricatures have suffered but I'm catching up quickly. Yesterday I went downtown and took some great pictures for future pieces. The best part of going downtown was that I had a Zek sighting! For those of you not in the know, Pam Zekman is a legendary Chicago watchdog journalist. She's one of my all-time personal heroes. I've even invented a slogan that she doesn't use: "If you're life is a wreck, call the Zek." We watch the pathetically painful Channel Two News every night just hoping to catch one of her always entertaining segments. Whether she's chasing a mob boss down an alley with an outstretched microphone and screaming, "Why aren't you working? The city is paying you right now!" or having a door slammed in her face by the head of a predatory lending firm ("You Channel Two news? You Channel Two News?? Get out of here Channel Two News!!") she's the toughest broad in the Midwest BAR NONE. I love that woman. And I got to see her on the street yesterday. Too cool.     Ade the fish still carries on with her humdrum existence. I've decided she's just a low-tech fish. She refuses the great advances in the fish-keeping industry in favor of a clean water only existence. Whatever. As long as she gets healthy enough to be passed to her rightful owner. At which point I know I'll go down in the basement, see that new Eclipse Hexagon tank lying empty and run out to the fish store for a new occupant, starting this whole ugly cycle anew.     If you don't know what I'm referring to in that last paragraph, the story is in an earlier blog entry. But a now-scarred friend points out that I must warn you: THE LAST BLOG ENTRY REVEALS A MAJOR PLOT DEVELOPMENT IN THE SOPRANOS 2004 SEASON. If you are waiting for the season reruns or DVD release, and don't want to know what evil fate awaits a certain female character, DO NOT READ ON!     Do send your best wishes to Studs Terkel, though. He apparently took a spill over the weekend and is recovering at an undisclosed location. All the best, Studs!      
     

    
</post>


</Blog>