<Blog>

<date>05,May,1999</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday morning, my Little Bug, 4 years old, was sitting on the couch watching Sesame Street. There was a cute song about birthdays and wishes coming true. Bug wrinkled up his nose and said, very loudly, "That's not true! Wishes don't come true!"  My heart broke. I looked at him and told him when I found out that I was pregnant with him that I wished for the sweetest boy in the world and my wish came true - I had him!  He scowled and said, "Well they don't come true for me!"  "What did you ask for?"  "On my birthday, I wished for a million dollars - and I didn't get it! So there, wishes don't come true!"
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,1999</date>
<post>

	 
      Both my boys seem to take after their father, they happen to be quite laid back about things and seem to take a lot of stuff in stride.  Bear once put 2+2 together and figured out that if we have a Mother Earth, then there must be a Father Sun! He is very smart. He has also figured out that the occult store we go to is for mommy's beliefs. Both boys had a blast yesterday when we found a 'new' Botanica in town that had a great selection of herbs. The whole time they were so well behaved but had to know what everything was and what it did. Even the shopkeeper was impressed with their behavior! (Hope it stays good!)  When we first moved here, we knew no one and wanted the kids to make friends, so I decided that I would enroll them at a Sunday school. But every time I started to, I would get a nauseous feeling and not do it. I am very glad I never signed them up. Around here, there are a lot of Sunday schools that are preaching hellfire and brimstone to children as young as 3. I have even heard of a church that was preaching the 'thou shall not suffer a witch to live' to preschoolers. Chilled me to the bone. And now, they might put the 10 Commandments up in our schools.  Bear is almost 7 now and knows that mommy's goddess is different than the Christians. He also knows that we do not discuss private matters, etc., to others without mommy and daddy's permission.  Sometimes I think it is hard to have a 'normal' life. I meditate on that a lot. Peace, harmony and understanding...
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,1999</date>
<post>

	 
      A RL Wiccan friend was over with her children and her daughter (7) asked my son (6) if I was a witch since her mommy was one and I had a black cat and candles too. Little Bear just made a puzzled face and said that he didn't know. When we talked about it later, I said that what I believed in is called by many different names. My younger son (almost 5) was the one who seemed got upset saying that if someone said I was a good witch he wouldn't mind but he would be upset if they said I was a bad witch. We then had to go over the witches aren't bad, people just think they are - like chicken liver - LOL. It made me feel guilty - I didn't lie, but you could say it was a lie by omission.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,1999</date>
<post>

	 
      I have been on a diet for about two months now. Inspired by our dear Morigainne, I am on the Atkins (or Eades) High Protein, No Carb diet. DISCLAIMER: NO diet is ever easy. They all take tremendous work and will power and have a potential to really screw up your life while you are trying to improve it.  Even though I have bought a brand new scale, the weight loss is not showing in significant numbers. BUT, I have gone down 2 pant sizes and people who do not see me every day and have no idea about the diet are complimenting me on it. Even hubby, whose duty is to cheer me on, seems very insistent that I have lost a lot.  So, I decided to reward myself. Food was out (*taco bell* sob) so I went to Wally World and bought myself a pair of jeans. But that really wasn't good enough. I HAD to buy them since the others were falling down and getting very awkward to wear. And a necessity in my book is not a reward. Barbies were out - I can have one anytime.  I wanted something different, something special...  So I decided to color my hair red.  My 2 boys wanted in on it - they wanted me to color my hair carrot orange - thank the goddess I talked them out of it. So we picked a dark cherry shade. It took 2 bottles of the coloring and about 1 1/2 hours (the bathroom now looks like a blood bath), but it is done and I must admit it looks great. Not screaming red, but a lovely auburn with a touch of burgundy. Not enough for someone to go "Oh, you died your hair (smirk)" but just enough to get "Oh, you died your hair! (happy face).  So, back to the diet and the long hard tedium of no potatoes or rice or beans or pasta or bread... But, I am sticking to it because, damn it, I am worth it.  So, I wonder what I shall plan for my next reward???
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,1999</date>
<post>

	 
      On living with intolerance…   Well, unfortunately the most hateful, intolerant of witches would be my inlaws and my father - all born-again with a vengeance.  But, since I have been around on the net, I have met more and more Wiccans/Pagans in Jacksonville, Florida (where I live) and believe it or not, it has prompted me to organize a Pagan Picnic at one of our treasured beaches. I have done that mainly because everyone I meet is a solitary (except for the occasional CUUPS member) and wants to get together and meet others. Until me, no one has done it as far as anyone knows.  I came out of the broom closet to my mother, who is happy as long as I am. I am slowly coming out in real life.  BUT, I will not flaunt it because that is just not me. I also will try not to advertise around my husband's coworkers due to the fact that he is now acting Manager of his store, working for the promotion (please goddess!) and I do not want to jeopardize his career.  I also will be careful around my sons' classmates, etc., this year for similar reasons. But, as I am planning on becoming active in the PTA, I see no reason to completely hide myself. If my 'inner witch' pops out, I will not shove her back in!  I feel as if I am slowly emerging from a cocoon. I am not changing, me as myself is still intact, but it is like a veil on the world is thinning and I can see so much more clearly now...
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,1999</date>
<post>

	 
      I am a big supporter of cross-gender toys. All little girls should have trucks and blocks and all boys should have dolls and stuffed animals.  In fact, when my second son was born, we gave Bear a baby doll for him to parent. So, every time I fed my baby, he fed his, etc. He named it Baby Geordi after his favorite character on Star Trek The Next Generation. (Yes, he was only 21 months, but he knew the character and would shout Geordi when he saw him. The funny thing was that the baby doll was white, so maybe it is true that babies are 'colorblind'!)  Well, back to the thread. I collect Barbies and that has been part of our life for a long time. Both boys have been asking for their own for the longest time. So, a couple of weeks ago, I broke down and bought them one Barbie and one Ken (and some clothes), thinking that they would share and trade, etc. Well, right off the bat, Bear claimed Barbie and Bug claimed Ken.  They have played with them every single day, dressing and undressing, making beds for them with teenybeanie babies as pillows and bandannas as blankets. They hug them and kiss them and constantly tell me how much they love them.  They know that if I ever catch any 'abuse', the dolls will disappear into my collection, never to be seen again. So they are very careful with them, always holding on tight when they fly them threw the air and always making them the innocent victim that gets saved in the nick of time by Spiderman and the other superheroes.  When I presented the Barbies to my sons, my dear hubby just gave a big sigh and whispered, "If they turn out funny, you are going to have some explaining to do." Then he winked.  What a guy! Most of my friend's husbands would literally give birth to a cow before they would ever let their macho sons touch a girly toy.  I love my family...
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,1999</date>
<post>

	 
      Little Bear was making a Family Book by cutting up some paper and stapling together. He then traced his hand, his brother's, and then mine. (Dad was at work). I told him it was a good idea - always praise craftiness!!  Next thing, from the dining room behind me came his voice...  "Would you please concentrate Cosmo? I am a professional and have trained long and hard to do this."  I turn around and Bug (his younger brother) had Cosmo, my black cat, pinned down spread eagle on the dining room table as Bear traced around his paw with a pencil.  "What are you doing?" I asked.  "Well, Cosmo is part of the family, isn't he?"  I had to agree - and reassure the cat that it was over...
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,1999</date>
<post>

	 
      Many years ago, before I got married, I dated a marine, "DC". He was a Chihuahua-type of person, short, thin, cute, sweet and very jittery. He was stationed in the Carolinas and I lived in SW Florida, and he would commute back and forth on 3 day weekends.  One trip, I was out of town. When I came back, I discovered that DC had answered an ad in the paper regarding these Naturists who would do their thing on the Peace River. Somehow, he got up enough guts to meet with them at their outing. He said it was fun, but awkward (duh..) and brought me some of their literature, including a calendar w/pictures. I said eeuuww, and tossed the stuff aside after looking at it (what do you expect?). Incident forgotten.  We had fun together, but the break up was kind of awkward. I really do not remember much, but it didn't bother me.  Skip ahead two years, I met Sharky (my hubby) and we were together a year, then married. He was a 'biker' but his club was not the Hell's Angels sort, they were all family men and women who just happened to love leather and Harleys. We all had a great time together.  After a while, we drifted away from the bike club. Soon, we moved into a house, I was going through some old boxes and ran across DC's stuff he left me (a tee shirt and some photos). Under it, was the naturist literature. I picked it up and called Sharky over for a laugh. I was telling him the story and he was smiling as he was looking at the calendar. All of a sudden he turned gray (under his tan). "Oh. My. God." was all he could get out.  I took the calendar from him, and there in all their naked glory was half his motorcycle club. Bert and his son Ernie, privates flapping in the breeze as they dove together. Cookie and Elmo floating in the river, their buoys drifting in the current.  Now, Sharky and I know that there is nothing wrong with nudity, but there are some things a man does not want to know about his friends and that definitely was one...  It still brings a smile to my face!
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,1999</date>
<post>

	 
      My mother is a wonderful woman, my bestest friend in the whole world. She and my bonus dad had moved away for two years and it was very dark and bleak not to have her here. She has finally come back home and I am happy. She can spend time with my boys, her only grandchildren, and me. Even though she is in St. Augustine with my grandparents, I know that she is barely an hour away if I need her. That is the most comforting feeling in the world.  I have wanted to tell her about my religion for so long and was very scared. Mainly because a beloved relative of ours is/was mentally ill and would profess that they were a witch and believed in Satan and was a born-again Christian all at the same time in one package. I just didn't want my mother to think I was having mental problems.  A few days or so after she moved back home, she spied my pentagram under my shirt and wanted to know what it was. In typical fashion she jokingly asked if I was a druid or a Satanist. I said no, Wiccan, and she said want to be or are and I said am and she just smiled nicely. That was the end of the conversation.  Well, today, I called her to see if she would baby-sit on the day of the Picnic I am planning and she wanted to know about it so I told her. We had such a wonderful conversation about it. She wanted to know what Wicca was and I gave her a brief definition and she understood what I mean.  Then, over the course of the morning, she called me back 2 different times to tell me other things. She shared feelings she has had about the Earth and how much she loved it (that I already knew but this conversation was different) and that one of her missions in life is to pick up garbage. She goes nowhere without a plastic bag in her purse or pocket or car to pick up litter. It is sort of her way to pay the Earth homage.  She has always been a pagan type of person and would fit right in - she just does not seem to be aware of it. She is a bird woman who has had wild birds land on her and eat out of her hand and has always had a birdfeeder wherever she has lived. When we left our home in New England and migrated south, she cried the whole way down because she did not know if the person who bought our house would put food out for the birds and keep the birdbath unfrozen in the dead of winter.  She also reminded me of the reason not to tell my father. I had been lulled into complacency with our relationship, being nice and all, but she reminded me of how vindictive and underhanded he can be (i.e., just because someone is a born-again Christian does not mean they are nice and loving) and how he had treated our relative (mentioned above) because of the things that relative had said in their illness. I shudder to think of how his response would be to me. I am grateful to my mother for that. In other words, I was getting comfortable with myself being open, but I still cannot let down my guard.  So we are back to where we were. My mother and I, best friends taking care of each other. I am so happy that I can share myself with her, it makes the hiding from others less painful.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,August,1999</date>
<post>

	 
      Today, I went on a few errands to pay bills (ick). My last stop was at the Jacksonville Electric Authority (JEA) to pay my electric and water bill (duh).  I lucked out when I got there and not only got a parking space right by the front door, I also had a quarter for the meter. No lines, no waiting!!!  I walked up to the first available teller, a giant toad of a woman. I smiled and told her I was here to pay my bill. I handed over the bill and started to write the check.  She looks at me, grunts and says "Heard of Locks of Love?"  Startled, I looked up and said "What?"  "Locks of Love, they make wigs for little cancer babies."  Confused now, I said "Yes, I saw them on TV a few weeks ago."  Not even looking at me, she said "You should've called them. Ain't fair that you have all that hair and some babies have none."  I felt like a cow. Big and stupid (and hairy) with my mouth hanging open. I didn't know what to say. I handed her my check and (I think) muttered something like "Maybe one day" and quickly left with my receipt.  I made it to my car, sat down and cried like a baby. I know, very hormonal, but all things considered, that was the absolutely last thing on this green earth that I expected someone to say to me. Looking back, I can think of all sorts of comebacks and witty retorts, but then? Of course not.  I love my hair and enjoy it. When my husband cut his hair off, years ago, we called all over the county (down south) to find a charity to donate it to since his hair was long and dark and straight - never been permed or colored - perfect. There was none and he would not let me keep it. What a waste. When we saw the news item about the "Locks of Love" I told him that if I ever cut my hair it would be donated for a charity like that (even if I pass away, so it would not be wasted). But that is personal, not for public scrutiny.  I know the utility teller was probably just a spiteful old woman and probably enjoyed hurting me. I know that she is probably like that because someone hurt her at one time, but no matter what, she will get it back karmically in the end.  But, come on... What is worth hurting a complete stranger?
     
    
</post>

<date>30,September,1999</date>
<post>

	 
      Well - it finally happened... Bug came out of the closet in Kindergarten.  It seems yesterday, on the playground, that my darling 5 year old Leo asked his best friend if he believed in Jesus. Of course, his best friend replied "Yes, do you?"  Bug said "No" to which his friend informed him that if he didn't believe in Jesus he would burn in hell.  His friend repeated that twice before asking Bug what he did believe in. Bug's answer (thank the Goddess) was "Mother Nature" just the way I wanted.  I decided to speak to Bug's teacher this morning before school just to make sure that there was no problem or confusion that would arise from that.  I have been blessed by the Goddess with the gift of this woman. Mrs. R was Bear's teacher last year and Bug's this year. This woman should be a saint - nothing fazes her. She listened to my tale (I was very nervous) and had nothing but love and sympathy in her expression.  I explained that we teach the boys that religion is a private matter, not to be casually discussed with others. I also explained that while Bear had been approached on occasion last year by other students curious to know why he didn't attend Sunday School, he in fact was a little older and more savvy than his younger brother and would just duck out of the conversation.  I also explained that I was Wiccan and although I was not in the 'broom closet' and I was not ashamed, and didn't want the boys to be either, I wanted them to be cautious.  She understood everything. I trust her. I feel so much better now!
     
    
</post>

<date>24,September,1999</date>
<post>

	 
      We have been wanting a dog for a long time and keep running into people giving away 'free' puppies. Don't get me wrong, a puppy is a wonderful, incredible creature. But an awful lot of work and stress. So, Sharky and I decided to get a slightly older dog.  I went to the local Animal Care and Control facility just to "LOOK" - LOL - and guess what? Found exactly what we were looking for.  There were exactly 20 'adults' up for adoption. I instantly weeded out all the males (Sharky wanted a female). I then eliminated all the leaping, screaming, howling, snarling ones.  That left one little girl, standing up on her hind legs, quietly, sadly looking at me. I put my fingers in her cage and she licked them, then rubbed her face on them.  I took the slip leash they gave me and took her out. Pandemonium ensued among the other dogs and she started to shake. I took her on the dog run, around the corner, behind a wall. When they didn't see us anymore, they quieted down.  I sat on the ground and she crawled into my lap. She comes up to a little over my knee and weighs about 35 pounds, but she fit. All she wanted me to do was to hold her and twiddle her ears. She almost fell asleep in my arms.  I found out from the front office that she was 6-8 months old and they thought she was a lab mix (I see no lab, but some Shepard). She also was a stray, picked up by an Animal Control Officer on the streets.  Well, I left, talked to Sharky, then went to Wal-Mart and got a collar, leash, and some dog food, then went back and got her.  She has a hard time on a leash, wants to belly crawl everywhere, sniffing everything. Loved the car ride home and sat in the back seat with Bug wonderfully.  A name is very important. I named her Gabrielle after the character on Xena. A woman who is loyal and loving and trustworthy. Just the way I want my dog!  We discovered at home, that if she was a stray, it hadn't been for very long. She knows the commands sit and shake, and lie down some of the time. She is housebroken.  How are Cosmo and Butters handling it? ROFL...  Gabrielle is terrified of cats. One look from Cosmo has her cowering in the corner.  She will eventually get used to my little tyrants - but in the meantime, I would rather have her scared than aggressive. (I was all set to take her back the minute she tried to hurt them.)  I have high hopes for this little girl, she shows so much promise and is so loving - and will be loved in return.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,September,1999</date>
<post>

	 
      What a relief!   Today, Little Bug, who is in kindergarten, came home all excited.  Animals were brought into the cafetorium for all the children and their teachers to marvel at. There was a python, a bearded lizard, a box turtle, a corn snake, a sugar glider, an alligator, and many others that Bug just couldn't recall!  He even got to pet a de-scented skunk named "Stinkerbell".  I asked him, "Were the animals from the zoo?"  "No," he replied, "a vegetarian brought them."
     
    
</post>

<date>14,November,1999</date>
<post>

	 
      DISCLAIMER: I LOVE my children - both of them.  For two days now, Bear has been running a bit of a fever and has not been feeling good at all. So, he is sleeping a lot and laying on the couch watching some videos.  Meanwhile, Bug is being the biggest jerk of all time. He is hitting and punching his brother, the dog, and one cat. He is being obnoxious and just a plain ass. I don't know how else to describe it. I mean he woke his brother up at 5:30 am by punching him repeatedly!  Now, I know the obvious response, that he is jealous of the attention his brother is getting. I have been working my tail off to compensate for that. Bug gets to pick the video, he has spent time with me on the computer, he got a special snack. I don't know what else to do.  I am NOT neglecting him. I am not ignoring him. But I cannot spend all day with him attached to my hip - he is five years old, not five months. (BTW, while I am typing this, he is in the bathroom.)  I just cannot understand my children sometimes. The dog I understand. The cats I understand. But a small person that I gave birth to, just confounds me.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,November,1999</date>
<post>

	 
      Bear’s Night Terrors  This morning, I went into the boys' bedroom to wake up Bear (Bug was already up). I found Bear in the bottom bunk (he sleeps in the top one), sitting up, literally freaking out. He was waving his arms in front of his face crying "The room is trashed" over and over.  I sat on the bed and held him in my arms and tried to comfort him. He was still asleep. Then he started saying incoherent things about the monster. I called for Sharky who came in and tried to help me comfort Bear.  It took a while but Bear finally woke up, shaken and still upset. He had dreamed of a monster coming into the room and destroying everything.  Now I have heard of night terrors - strange dreams that occur primarily with young boys. Bear has had a few odd ones, but only as a very small toddler, where he would wake up in the middle of the night screaming his head off for no apparent reason - not crying mind you, but screaming in terror. He would always be fast asleep when it occurred and like this morning, would take a while to wake up.  (14th) Well, it happened again last night. I went over some friends house for a little bit (they had a little birthday party for me) and Bear had another episode while I was gone.  Sharky said that this one lasted almost 15 minutes before Bear could be calmed down enough to sleep again. Even then, he just laid on the couch with his dad until he fell asleep.  This has really gotten Sharky upset - never has experienced this before (neither have I).  We had thought that this might have been tied in with his fever, yet during the episode last night, he wasn't feverish at all.  (16th) Bear is doing better. Night before last, he had another one. Woke me up as he barreled down the bunk and came flying into our bedroom screaming "I had a bad dream" over and over.  He really responds to touch. I pulled him into bed between Sharky and I and practically laid on him - sort of like bundling a baby? He calmed down almost immediately and was able to speak about it in an almost rational manner.  The dream was that he walked to school on his own and a monster (body of a cat, head of a bird with razor sharp teeth like a shark) ripped him to pieces.  As he talked about it, I could see the light come into his eyes as he realized the dream was about his fear of walking to school on his own. When he stated that, I agreed and assured him that we wouldn't do that until he was a lot older.  We impressed upon him that his 'guardian angels' could help him battle bad dreams. Also, because he is a huge fan, that he could always carry Poke'mon balls with him and capture the monster if need be.  He actually slept all the way through last night.  (17th) He has done very good - no dreams last night. No fever either. I really am starting to thing those went hand in hand. Never did before, but now that he's getting older...
     
    
</post>

<date>02,November,1999</date>
<post>

	 
      All of you who know me, know I have a difficult relationship with my Sharky's Italian mother. I have actually scored brownie points with her and am quite proud of it!  She sent birthday presents to our boys (one late, the other early) which they loved greatly and an early birthday present for her son. Since mine is coming up soon, she asked what I wanted and also ideas for the boys on Christmas.  I learned long ago, if you want a decent present from someone, when they ask you what you want, tell them! You can always tailor it to their budget, etc., but it almost guarantees you to get what you want.  So, I wrote her a very nice letter, thanking her for the boys presents and Sharky's and gave her some suggestions for their Christmas presents. Then, I told her about the doll I wanted and even included a picture in the letter so she can see which one it was.  Well, I read the letter over and over and the more I did, the more unhappy I became with it. Then, I remembered some freeware Sharky found for me over the internet. It's called AltaVista BabbleFish and is supposed to translate websites and blocks of writing into different languages.  Well, I cut and pasted the letter into the BabbleFish and ended up with an Italian language letter to her. I signed it and mailed it off. (Hell, I can't read Italian too well so I kept my fingers crossed.)  I received a call from my mother in law last night - thrilled to death. It seems that in the 35+ years she has been here no one has written a letter in Italian to her (with the exception of relatives in Italy of course). She was so touched that I made the effort.  Of course, she did have to point out the grammatical errors (simple ones) until I reminded her that it was a computer program and wasn't perfect. ROFL  Oh well. I feel a bit better now.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,December,1999</date>
<post>

	 
       Last night, at about 7:25, our yellow and green parakeet, Ariel, passed away. Ariel was never in the best of health, but I think she had a stroke. She was fine up until about 6:45 when I found her on the bottom of the cage unable to move a wing and a leg. (We found her in the wild at my uncle's house, so are unsure of how old she was.)  We still have Duncan (Ariel's 'boyfriend') but he spent all last night on the bottom of the cage. I think he was mourning since he never does that. When she passed, I was standing right by her and Duncan sang the saddest song - it was very intricate and beautiful and I know he knew she died. I have never seen/heard anything like that before.  We had the boys come in and say goodbye to her body and talked about how she is gone now to the Summerlands and might come back someday. My sweetheart Sharky got all bundled up and buried her in the little pet cemetery we have in the back yard (holds a stray cat and two squirrels that were murdered by cars in front of our house). I know she was just a little parakeet, but she brought a lot of happiness to our lives.  We still have Gabrielle (10 months) a dog, Cosmo (1 year) a cat, and my precious Butterscotch (14+ years) a cat who we realize may not last out the year.  I have had pets pass before, but as I said, it was the kids' first and just a tough reminder that things you love don't last forever.  The most ironic things, in our family - pet happenings occur on holidays. Butterscotch was found on Thanksgiving, Cosmo on Sharky's birthday. My Crystle (cat) was born on the day I miscarried my daughter in 1985. My Tigger (cat) was given to me on New Years and passed away on our wedding night. Ariel was found on Easter and passed on Christmas...
     
    
</post>

<date>23,December,1999</date>
<post>

	 
      Crazy Baby or Crazy Mommy???  LOL  During my past two pregnancies, I never had a problem in the car. It would appear to me that the boys would just go to sleep if I drove somewhere.  This little peanut is a whole 'nother ballgame... S/he always wakes up during a drive and decides to head south. Once there, gets into a sideways position and starts to push or kick with both hands and feet out towards my sides.  At first, I thought it was the seatbelt. Obviously for safety and legal reasons I have to wear one, but it is recommended that the belt be placed UNDER the tummy. Well, I haven't gained that much weight and so tucking it under is hard to do. I have finally figured out that if I pull up my shirt and tuck it around the belt, the belt stays put. But the baby still goes crazy.  Is it the vibrations or the motion? I don't know. All I know is that it does hurt (especially when the bladder becomes the punching bag).  Then, yesterday, all of us met my mother in St. Augustine for a little 'tourist' walkabout and lunch. After lunch, Sharky looked at me and did a double take. He said I looked like I doubled in size. That crazy baby of mine decided that as long as we were up and walking that s/he was going to crawl UP as far as s/he could go. Thrilled my mom though, she could actually feel a head or a rump making a point right under my ribcage.  Of course, once we got into the car for the drive home... Back s/he goes again!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>21,December,1999</date>
<post>

	 
      First off, I must tell you that Bear, 7 years old, is a big Britney Spears fan. He loves her music and likes to watch her when she is on t.v. About a month ago, we were in K-Mart and saw all of the Britney Spears dolls. He went nuts! He showed them to me and asked if I liked them. I said Yes, of course, because they are pretty dolls and do look a lot like her.  The other day I discovered that he was telling people that he is getting her for me for my Christmas/Yule present and that if he couldn't he KNEW Santa would. After the third time I heard that story, I started to feel guilty. As much as I would like to have that doll, he wanted to get her more for me than I did!  So, Sharky and I decided yesterday that we would find the doll, buy her, then he and the boys would 'secretly' wrap her up as my present. I had to go with them to find her because Sharky, being the manly man he is, would have a major problem in the pink aisle finding the exact doll I wanted.  So, we went to K-Mart. Guess what? Absolutely NONE left at all. We crossed town (1/2 hour drive) and went to K-Mart #2. They had one left - in an outfit I hated. So, as a last resort, Sharky suggested Toys R Us (another 1/2 hour drive). So, again, through all the insane holiday shoppers crowding the roads, we made it with our sanity somewhat intact.  First glance down the non-Barbie aisle turned up the giant headed Japanese singing Britney doll (gag). A little digging turned up a handful of regular Britney dolls in a different hideous outfit. By that time I was truly depressed. Finally, I tossed my head back and was about to utter a moan, when... WAY up on the shelf above my head was a stack of about 10 dolls. Praise the Goddess for tall husbands. He pulled them down and voila! The exact doll I wanted in the exact outfit. By this time, the boys were a bit confused so I told Bear that I just wanted to show Daddy the doll I wanted. Bear said that was a very good idea. (hahaha)  So, the boys and their dad toured the more masculine toy aisles while I quickly purchased Britney and stashed her in the trunk.  So here is the dilemma... Should I feel guilty for going through all of this for MY present? It is kind of bizarre you know. In all honesty, I didn't expend this much energy on the boys' presents because I already knew what I was going to get them.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,December,1999</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes, here it is, another rant - this one about little Bear, 7 years old.  My husband and I are trying to raise a non-violent son who is still a man.  It is HARD!!!!!!!  There are a couple of punks in his class that do asinine things to him. I caught one, K, pushing Bear around after school. Why? Because Bear looked over his shoulder. The teachers on duty did nothing. I told Bear that if I ever saw that happen again, I would tell the teacher. I then told him to just stay away from K.  Then there is M. Bear has a theory that M is gay. Why? Because M is a 7 year old boy that insists on kissing all of the other little boys in class. He also likes to jump on other boys on the playground and pinch/punch until they cry. I told Bear to tell the teacher. Good news, the teacher is very aware of M and sends a lot of notes home to his parent(s). Like that did any good. I told Bear that I doubted he knew if he was really gay and that M was just doing it for attention.  Then there is L, M's best friend, who begs for food in the cafeteria and when Bear gives him something (because he feels sorry for him), L destroys the food. I have convinced Bear to stay the hell away from them.  Then there is J who slaps Bear upside the head almost every morning with his backpack. Why? Who knows.  OK, face it - I am sick of this shit. My answer every single time is to tell Bear to stay away from these bullies. He does. When I do see the teacher, she says she has it under control.  How old should a kid be before he physically stands up for himself? I don't want Bear to be a bully or to fight, but is there a limit to this?  My biggest concern is that it is typical of school fights that if someone defends them self, they get blamed/punished also. I DON'T want that.  I also don't want my son to grow up and run away from every fight either.  My husband is torn between telling Bear to knock the shit out of the next kid that hits him and siding with me on the no-violence. So far, the no-violence is winning.  But for how long???
     
    
</post>

<date>30,January,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday, I got sick and had to lay down and I fell asleep.  I dreamt that I was hanging up old fashioned women's nightgowns - lacy, pretty ones. I held one up to my face and smelt it. It smelled like old roses and lavender. I looked up and saw my grandmother. Not old, but young, 30ish, standing straight and tall, with her reddish hair in a 1940s style. She was wearing a beautiful nightgown and standing in a doorway. I was surprised to see her. She gave me a sad, sweet smile, turned away and walked into her bedroom.  Needless to say, I cried most of yesterday.  This morning, I got a call from my mother. Grandpa woke up at 4 this morning, like always, and brought Grandma a drink. She asked for the light on. He sat on the side of her bed and held her hand and they talked. About 6 a.m., she turned her head away and went to sleep - and passed away.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,January,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      I have been suffering from carpal tunnel syndrome (where the arteries swell, cutting off circulation in the wrists and hands). It only happens in the wee hours of the morning, waking me up to intense pain. It starts of being annoying and easy to 'wake up' then as time progresses it gets more intense until it no longer 'wakes up'. This morning it became so bad that it felt like someone was driving a nail through my wrist (sorry for the analogy but it's true).  I cannot feel with my fingers (my hand feels like it's asleep) and I cannot move them properly or even close my hand gently. And now it takes longer and longer to wake up.  I have had this before, in other pregnancies, but this is the absolute worst.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,January,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      Cravings…  Besides the usual Taco Bell pangs, I have been craving some things I haven't eaten in DECADES!  1) Howard Johnson Toastees. Little square corn muffins you popped in a toaster. Couldn't find one for weeks - that's because I was looking in the frozen breakfast aisle. Wrong – Winn-Dixie puts them in the dessert aisle instead. Doesn't make sense to me... Had one for breakfast with a little bit of butter, yummy! Just what the baby wanted!  2) Chef Boyardee or Franco American (?) Macaroni and Cheese. Yes, the long noodly pale yellow stuff in a can. (Stop groaning!) I LOVED that stuff as a kid. Can't find it anywhere and cannot for the life of me remember which one made it so I can write/call and ask. Can someone help me???
     
    
</post>

<date>05,January,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      So many sad things have been happening all around, it is nice sometimes to take a step back and be happy about something.  This is very silly - sorry - but Taco Bell has brought back the enchirito for a limited time. I haven't had one in 10 years! *Happy Dance*
     
    
</post>

<date>23,February,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      Just wanted to let y'all know that little Petunia has dropped - and I am not kidding. :-)  {It is a very weird feeling to have something as large as a baby's head in your pelvis. Bear started to drop but backed up so I never experienced this before.}  I go back to the doctor on Friday morning and will let everyone know if anything has changed...  Just keep your fingers crossed. I DON'T want to spend my 8th anniversary in labor - not to mention, Leap Day would be an odd birthday to have.  I just have this odd feeling that I may not make it to April 2nd (my due date)...
     
    
</post>

<date>01,February,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      Don't Die at Home in St. John's County, Florida  My mother didn't want to tell me this, but she had no one else to rant to - not to mention I kept asking her when the interment of Grandmother's ashes would be so my husband and my sons could be there with me.  On Sunday, my grandmother passed away at 6:00 a.m. My Grandfather called my mother, her brother, and the nurse. My mom washed my grandmother and dressed her nicely. The nurse called the funeral home, and because it is county policy when there is a death at home, it was reported to the Sheriff's Department.  Guess what? The Sheriff's Department shows up like Storm troopers and literally forced their way into my grandmother's bedroom. They treated everyone like it was a crime scene. They poked their noses in and around the house, looking and prying. They insisted on examining my grandmother's body. They spoke to the nurse and the doctor on the phone, so they knew she had terminal cancer and was released with permission to die, but it's policy that they examine the body anyway. My mother even found a strange Goth dressed teenage looking girl wandering around the house. She was a "trainee" who was there to watch the proceedings.  They forced everyone, my mother & step dad, my uncle & aunt, and my grandfather to write out long statements detailing every single thing done. Luckily, my aunt took my grandfather's dictation so he didn't have to do it himself. The sheriff's officer wanted everything in detail, from what she ate to what she said to every single movement my grandfather made. Just like a crime scene. They wouldn't even let a family member stay in the bedroom with my grandmother's body.  They were rude, bossy, and rough with absolutely not one lick of compassion. It wasn't until my mother completely lost it and started screaming that she was calling a lawyer that they attempted to act decently.  Because of county policy, my grandmother's body is now in storage awaiting the paperwork to be completed. There has to be a sheriff's report written. There has to be a report from the doctor and the medical examiner. Not to mention a whole bunch of others. Then, the body will be released to the funeral home to be cremated. The funeral parlor doesn't expect to get the body until the end of the week.  The only good note, was the funeral parlor was the people who came and got my grandmother's body. Mother said they were very kind and gentle with the family, in fact, even remembered my grandparents from a year or so ago when they bought the "condos" (vault) for their ashes.  My mother is now compiling a list of people she will be writing to. Who's on it? A short list would be the Sheriff, the Council on Aging, the Newspaper (both there and in Jax), all the way up to the Governor.  We know that my grandmother had passed and it was truly just her shell. She could suffer no indignities. But it was my family that suffered - my 89 year old grandfather who had been married to her for 62+ years, my 58 year old mother who had taken such good care of my grandmother so she could pass peacefully and with as much dignity as she could, my uncle and his wife who just needed to be there for support and let's not forget my step-dad who tried to keep everyone calm in this messy situation.  So, my advice to you is: If you love your family and you want to die at home, find out what the county policies are and prepare them first before they have to go through this...
     
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      Greetings all!  I am glad to see that the postings continued while I was gone - I had a good time this morning reading them. I still haven't gotten through all of them, but I shall! LOL Then, I have to tackle some other forums... I won't be bored for a while!  To end the suspense, my precious Petunia is doing fine. For those who wonder, her real name is Rhiannon but I shall continue calling her my Precious Petunia until she objects to it. :-)  We were released from the hospital late Friday night. We haven't done really anything at all - Petunia is jaundiced so we have a home health nurse who stops by every day to take a blood sample to check on her bilirubin levels. She sleeps night and day on a light bed that fits inside her bassinet. This is NOTHING like those monstrous light tables found in hospital nurseries where the baby has to be naked and blindfolded - this looks like a copy machine with a soft mylar top where the baby lies (not unlike a hammock). She wears a paper outfit on it that looks somewhat like a cradleboard that a western NA child would wear (sorry, lack of better description) but is loose, and she is velcroed onto the light bed. I will post a picture when I get them developed. Her levels went up on Saturday but have come very slowly down and she has finally stopped losing weight. Things are starting to look very, very good.  We had an incredible adventure but I am glad it is finally all over now.  Thank you all for the kind wishes and comments.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,March,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes - Little Petunia is showing up bright and early Tuesday morning - our appointment is for 5:00 a.m. (EDT) and I go into the operating room at 7:30 a.m.  So we are expecting her to arrive before 8.  At least I get 3-4 good days of hospital bed rest before coming home - a little pampering doesn't hurt! LOL
     
    
</post>

<date>16,March,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I just got a call from my doctor and while one test came back fine, the other came back well, not so fine (protein in urine abnormally high).  So, tomorrow morning I go back to the doctor for a pre-op exam, etc., and if everything is fine tomorrow (and they don't take her then), there is a good chance I will have a c-section on Monday or Tuesday morning.  I am happy and very disappointed and scared. But, trying to stay calm so my blood pressure doesn't rise too bad.  A little prayer would definately be appreciated. :-)  11:57 UPDATE: Just got a call from the Doc's office, ~unless~ something happens between now and then, my c-section is scheduled for 7:30 Tuesday morning (March 21st).
     
    
</post>

<date>14,March,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      My mother came over on Sunday and brought a ton of baby stuff that she has either bought new or found at consignment shops (she has better ones where she lives). It was fun looking at all the PINK things she bought!  Then she gave me some dusters to wear that my grandmother had and never wore. They are so comfortable it is almost unbelievable!  Want to know what a duster is?  ROFLMAO  It's a polite word for a MUU-MUU! And I don't care! For the first time in my life I am actually happy to be wearing a muu-muu... Is it old age or senility? Who knows. All I know is that I am very comfortable.  ((Poor Sharky is convinced that this is a plot of my mothers to insure that I NEVER get pregnant again. I mean, these are muu-muus in all the prerequisite colors and patterns.))
     
    
</post>

<date>10,March,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes, everyone. I am still here and still waiting. The good news is that baby Petunia is fine and dandy, and I get to wait some more. I go back on Friday for another test/checkup and another decision on when it will happen.  The doc said they will NOT let me go past my due date (April 2nd) and are pretty sure they will not let me go past 39 weeks (I am 37). So, rest assured that Petunia will make her grand entrance sometime within the next two weeks. *sigh*
     
    
</post>

<date>10,March,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      The good news:  Little Petunia is fine, heartbeat good, measures right on age and (according to ultrasound) weighs approximately 6 pounds, 14 ounces (give or take 10%) and her amniotic fluid is right on the mark.  The bad news:  I am borderline preeclampsic (pregnancy induced hypertension or toxemia). I am on bedrest. I take a 24 hour urine and blood test on Monday morning and have another NonStress Test with Petunia on Tuesday.  On Tuesday, the doc will reevaluate me and decide if I can (a) wait another 2 or 3 days or (b) have the baby then and there.  My options? Induced labor or c-section.  Damn. I actually thought I would be able to do it this time...
     
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      Sharkdance says:  Greetings all,  I just wanted to take a moment to thank everyone for their kindness and well wishes to Topaz and I.  She has gone thru a lot with this pregnancy and the friends she has made here have helped make things a little more bearable for us both.  Well, as you all know, Petunia has made her arrival and I for one could not be more proud of being her father.  I would especially like to thank Mori for coming down to help "keep things semi normal" in a time of complete chaos. Topaz and I think you are the best!  I have included a few photos of "the crew" for all of you to enjoy as a token of my appreciation.  Just wait until this little girl realizes how many people around the world were waiting and watching and praying for her safe arrival.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      Grandma died on January 30th. I had thought that by now I had shed all the tears that I could.  Today, I received a card in the mail from Grandpa with a check for the baby - to buy a gift for her. He signed his name and Grandma's - just like always.  The tears just started to flow again as I held my baby - the one I had hoped so hard that my Grandma could see...  I know that wherever she is, she knows Petunia is alive and healthy - perhaps even watching out over her as her angel.  In the hospital, every time I shortened Rhiannon into Rhia, it came out Rita - my Grandmother's name - so though we didn't plan on it, the baby's nickname is Rita (RitaRhiannon - say it!). When we call her that she smiles a happy toothless smile.  I just am hoping that one day I can think about Grandma without the tears flowing like the first day she passed...
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      OK, this isn't original - while in CVWS, I saw the post on how sometimes people just don't feel witchy.  What I would like to know, is what gives you that tingle - what is something you do, or something that happens that gives you that "I'm glad I'm a witch!" feeling?  Me?  Not to be boring or anything :-) but lately, when I nurse my baby and I am holding her in my arms, loving her, is when I feel so incredibly powerful - I so feel the Goddess in me that sometimes it's almost unimaginable...
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      Everyone knows that pregnant women crave things to eat...  But, have you ever craved anything AFTER you had the baby?  I am becoming more and more obsessed with onions. I eat them at practically every meal on just about everything. I HAVE to have ONIONS! I have always liked them, but this is getting odd.  Sharky thinks I am probably lacking something - but what do onions have? Vitamin C? I really don't know...
     
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      I finally did it! And, I am so proud too!  On Sunday, we all had a hankerin' for some BBQ. So, we fed the baby first (as usual) breast, then an extra bottle (just in case) and headed out to our favorite BBQ joint. It was about 3:30 p.m. - after the church crowd and before the dinner rush so it only had perhaps 5 tables full.  Sharky asked for a booth because Petunia was in her infant carrier and it's easy to sit her at a booth (won't fit in a chair). Well, they don't really have booths, but against one wall there is a booth-like seat that runs the length of the wall and has table and chairs pushed up to it.  Well, we ordered the AYCE rib special (yummy!) and dug in. Half-way through, guess what?  Yep, you got it. Petunia started crying. Not loud or annoying mind you, more like a kitten mewing. But we couldn't get her to stop. When she started rooting on me, we got it. Even though she had just ate until almost bursting, she was hungry AGAIN!  We had no bottle with us.  So, I took the booth seat facing the rest of the restaurant (chair was way too uncomfortable), balanced Petunia in my arms, opened my shirt, tossed a blanky over my shoulder, and VOILA! breastfed quiet baby.  That was officially the very first time I breastfed my baby in public (cars in parking lots don't count!).  I am very proud of myself. :-)  A few minutes after I started feeding her, the waitress came up with our check - Sharky got all tensed up thinking she was trying to rush us out because I was nursing the baby. Turns out she was just letting us know that another waitress would be taking care of us because her shift had ended. She even made a little joke - something along the lines of when you go to a restaurant, everyone wants to eat. The other waitress was nice too - not ignoring me, but not paying too much attention either.  I guess I wouldn't be so nervous about it if it were a common sight. But in all honesty, I can only think of two occasions where I have seen a breastfeeding mother in public - the S. African mom who sat next to me in a mall about 7 1/2 years ago (and she was nervous about American attitudes toward breastfeeding) and a casual acquaintance in a restaurant about 11 years ago (and we had to sit in the very back in a dimly lit booth because she was afraid of getting kicked out).  Won't it be nice one day to have this such a "normal" sight that you wouldn't even have to think about it?
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2000</date>
<post>

	 
       I was sitting in my living room this evening, breastfeeding Petunia, when I noticed flashing lights coming in through the front window.  When I had finished feeding her, I placed her in the bassinet and stepped onto the front porch.  There are 3 cop cars, one civilian car, a guy handcuffed sitting on the curb, a cop searching his car, and a bunch of other cops standing around looking important.  And lo and behold what sight should my wondering eyes perceive???  A cameraman and boom man from the t.v. show COPS.  How FREAKING humiliating is that? In my own little urban neighborhood!  All I can do is to thank the Goddess that the car is across the street, instead of directly in front of my house...
     
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      As I mentioned in another thread, Sharky and I have been discussing past lives due to some odd things we have noticed with Petunia.  When Petunia was only like 2 days old, I was holding her in my arms in bed and talking to her. She was awake but not focused or anything. I was just rambling on about nothing in particular, then called her "My little Princess." At the instant I said princess, she focused her eyes and furled her brow at me - staring at me so intently I knew she understood what I said. The moment passed and her eyes unfocused again. She has continued to have moments like that since, always at different words and we haven't found a pattern to them except they are all used in the English language. It is so obvious that she ~knows~ what the word means - she recognizes them. [Bear and Bug never did that, although Bear did "recognize" me when they handed him to me for the first time - he had that very serious look of "it's YOU!" on his little face - quite startling.]  One of the good things about being a parent multiple times, is that you already can interpret a baby's cries. You know the one for hunger, for a messy nappy, for tummy ache, and for general fussiness among many others. There is also a specific cry for fear but you usually do not hear that from a newborn.  I have basically decided that Petunia has abandonment issues. She can be happy as a clam, but if you put her down and step away sometimes she will go absolutely berserk and scream in terror. It happens sometimes when she is asleep and we put her in her bassinet and she wakes up and cannot see me or Sharky. Now mind you, this isn't the usual baby cries - this really is fear/terror.  We tried to figure out why - it cannot be from the nursery in the hospital or while she was on the bili-bed because they are too distant - not to mention she was never left alone. Heck, she is never left alone now, but I do have to go potty sometimes you know.  All I can think of is that prior to "now" something happened to her in a past life (probably the most recent one) that has left her with the fear of being left alone.  We handle it easy - when she shrieks, we pick her up and hold her tight until she calms down. It isn't spoiling, a child needs to be around 6 months before they understand the cause and effect and are able to manipulate their parents. Petunia is only 6 weeks.  I have heard theories that babies recently reincarnated have their memories as babies but lose them as they grow older, retaining only "deja vu'" type memories. Not to mention, most cases of "proving" reincarnation involved very young children who were able to verbally communicate at a very young age.  Well - what does anyone else think of this? (and yes, I know that I sound weird, but as Sharky says, we are normal, everyone else is weird...hehehe)
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      This just pissed me off and I need to vent...  Had to take Bear to the new doctor today for a physical, new rxs, etc. Sharky couldn't get off work, so I had take all three kids.  Not too bad, I can handle it - but, it's raining. Bigass thunderstorms, etc. Can't complain - need the rain. But why right then?  So, all of us, completely soaking wet and dripping (can't carry an umbrella and baby at same time), enter the waiting room. Kids watch video while I balance baby on shoulder and fill out forms.  Finished, I brought them to the front desk and as I turn around, I realized that precious Petunia just spit up all over me and my red shirt. Nice white chunks. From my left cheek to my left breast - all over. Nice and smeary. (Of course, she didn't get any on herself.)  Big deal, right? No problem. I cleaned it up as best as I could with tissues. Unfortunately, my red shirt now has funky stains all over. Hey, I'm a mom, I can handle it!  As I go to sit down again, the only other parent in the room, a father in his 30s, who witnessed the whole thing, walked to the front desk with his child and said to the receptionist, "You'd think ~some~ people would take pride in their appearance."  AAARRRGGGHHH  Who the **** does he think he is? What, his brat never puked? He never got caught in a rainstorm without an umbrella? I'd like to see Mr. YuppyPerfect try to handle 3 kids in a rainstorm!  AAARRRGGGHHH  *phew*  I feel better now. Thank you for listening!
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      My precious Petunia can see faeries and angels...  She will sit, staring into space and start smiling and laughing at something that we just cannot see. If we move her, she will try her hardest to get back to her original position. The point where she is staring at is always at about the same place a human face would be - if standing or sitting.  My mom thinks it's my grandmother...  As for the faeries... On quite a few occasions, I was holding her in my arms, she was sitting up (with my assistance of course!) and she looked on top of my head and just started cackling! It was the funniest thing she had ever seen. Where I sit, there is nothing behind me but a beige wall. Sometimes, sitting in her swing, she will twist around and smile and laugh at a spot above the t.v. where, again, nothing is.  Bear and Bug were puzzled until I told them that she was seeing faeries - they asked why they couldn't see them. I told them it was because they were her faeries! :-)  Sad - they have forgotten the days when they saw faeries too. I have wonderful memories of a chubby Bear and then Bug, running around a sunspot in our living room, laughing as they tried to catch the "faewies"...
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      Major Guiliani declared today "Kathie Lee Gifford Day" in New York City to commemorate her final broadcast with "Live with Regis and Kathie Lee".  Well Crap. I missed it all. *TC goes off and pouts in the corner*
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      Adios Little Buddy… They announced on the news today that Taco Bell has changed their ad company and there will be no more Taco Bell Chihuahua...  *sniff*
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      “Mom?  What’s a period?”  "It's a punctuation mark at the end of a sentence that signifies that the sentence has ended. It looks like a dot."  "No, mom, a period - like something happening to somebody!"  Well, hey! That really was the last thing on my mind that my son would ask about. How did he hear about periods? A tampon commercial on the telly. (I don't hide it from him, but I haven't had one in a year, thanks to pregnancy and breastfeeding.)  So, I just gave him the basics. Women grow a lining of blood in their uterus once a month to help in case they have a baby. If they don't get pregnant, their body sheds it - ergo, the mouserugs in the cupboard. (Or mommy diapers as he called them once! LOL)  His reply?  "Oh, ok."  *phew*  We decided long ago, not to pull punches when it comes to explaining things. I HATED as a child being told, "I'll tell you when you get older" - if I can answer the question, I will - to the best of my abilities.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      How’s Petunia?  She's doing good! Getting photos developed this week.  Not rolling over - she cannot stand being on her stomach...  Finally smiling, laughing, blowing bubbles and getting very good at aiming her hands and feet (instead of just swinging wildly). Getting harder to eat and hold her - LOL!  And her neck control is great - still does the snake bobbing thing a little, but she's getting stronger and stronger!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      A little while ago, my sons called me to our front window.  There, lying on my porch, was a tiny, scrawny, scabby black kitten.  I opened the door and stepped out, but the kitten ran into the neighbor's yard (perhaps 20 feet or so) and talked to me.  The kitten was hungry and tired but wasn't ready to accept my help.  What if it was ready for help? What could I do? Poor Butterscotch is so old that she has a hard time walking sometimes - and she puts up with enough guff from Cosmo and Gabby (dog) - she couldn't handle a kitten again. I vowed to her the other night when I was feeding Petunia and Butterscotch wanted to snuggle on the couch - it took her 3 times, falling and stumbling to get up there - that I would make sure her final bit of life is as comfortable as I can make it.  I know there are so many more "important" things on this earth - but it still breaks my heart when I can't help just one little kitten.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2000</date>
<post>

	 
       Roll Over Petunia!   Yep!  As you can tell by the title, my Precious Petunia Blossom rolled over! Ok, she still has an arm trapped under her and she's trying to figure out how to extricate it...  But she did it! Yahoo!
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      Crap-a-mundo...  I learned some very important lessons this morning during the making of the infamous poke'ball cake:  If you want to make the color RED then use paste/gel food coloring - not the liquid stuff.  DON'T use buttercreme icing - it's not white - it's ecru.  If you end up with Barbie Pink - DON'T add blue - it turns a lovely shade of lavender.  So, if you couldn't see this coming - Bug has a lavender and white poke'ball cake...  One good thing - Martha was right! Line the cake platter with parchment strips and you won't get icing everywhere! You just gently pull strips out when done and VOILA' - clean platter!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      Since Petunia was born, I think she has slept through the night a grand total of 5 times. Yes, it's hard on me, but I am getting used to it.  Last night, she got hungry at 10 p.m. so I fed her and she went to sleep. Then she woke up at 1 a.m. So I fed her again and she went back to sleep. Then she woke up at 4 a.m. Yep, fed her again. This time, she didn't want to go back to sleep.  Now, don't get me wrong. She isn't the screaming crying type of baby - but she does make little fussy noises and I can't sleep through it.  I was too tired to sit out in the living room with her, as usual, so I took my pillow and laid down at the foot of the bed next to her bassinet. I placed my hand on her tummy and she quieted down. But, that position hurt my arm so I moved. Started fussing again. In goes the arm. Quiet. Pain, moved arm out. Fussing again.  Finally, I crooked my left arm under my head and just draped my left hand into the bassinet without touching her.  Miracle! She quieted down. I guess she just wanted to know I was there - and by seeing my hand - that was all she needed.  Then, as I was finally dozing off to sleep, a little hand clasped my thumb ... and I heard a little sigh.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      My precious little Bug is turning 6 this Friday (Aug. 4th). I can't believe it!  I will be making a birthday cake for him - a poke'ball cake. I am making a vanilla cake w/vanilla icing, baking it (2 layers) in a round cake pan. Then, I will color the top half red, bottom half white with the black doohickey thing in the middle - just like a poke'ball! I am going to get a couple of plastic poke'mon and decorate the top of the cake with it, along with a #6 candle.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,September,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      I had to run to the grocery store this afternoon and when I was walking back to my car, a pickup truck passed me and parked. In it's rear window was a sunscreen with the 'famous' saying "Lose Weight Now - Ask Me How!"  I didn't pay much attention until the driver got out of the truck and walked toward me. She was my height (5'2") but probably weighed about 80 pounds. I have no idea how she could drive much less walk, she was so emaciated - she just tottered on her feet and wobbled like she was going to collapse.  Now granted, I have no idea how she got to be in such terrible shape - whether it was anorexia or disease - but seriously folks, what weight loss company wants someone looking like that to sell their product??? 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,September,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday, we had lousy weather, so I loaded Petunia up in the car to go pick the boys up from school. As I was buckling her up in the baby seat in back, I started to panic that I was going to lock her and the keys in the car.   So, I checked for my keys, found them, then resumed buckling up. It hit me again. And again. Over and over. I kept hanging onto my keys and trying to buckle her in while I am panicking. My breath got short, I started to sweat, and was crying. It took almost 10 minutes for what should have taken 1 minute.  Luckily, it didn't bother Petunia a bit and once I got in the car and started it, it went away. What a relief.   I drove down the block and around the corner - and there was a giant hook and ladder fire truck almost blocking the road. The firemen were running back and forth and there were women screaming and crying, pulling at their hair.  I had to slow down to a crawl to get through the mess and was able to flag a fireman down to ask what had happened. A woman had locked her infant in the car with the keys and the firemen were having difficulty opening the car. Luckily, they were able to get it open and the baby out - suffering a bit from heatstroke, but otherwise ok.   I have come to the conclusion that my panic attack must have been from somehow picking up on what was going on a few blocks away (psychically or empathically???). I didn't hear a siren or anything - their house is no where within view of mine so there is no way I could have known what was going on.  I have prided myself for being able to block things like this - but it looks like I'll have to go back and start working on it again... :-)
     
    
</post>

<date>31,October,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      My Step Mom just called to let us know that they will arrive here in town tomorrow afternoon and that they would call us to let us know about dinner plans.  Silly me said "Are you all excited about seeing Billy?"  Step Mom: "Billy who?"  Me: "Billy Graham of course, aren't you seeing him while you are here?"  SM (in a VERY icy tone): "No, of course not."  Me (shocked): "I'm sorry, I just assumed that since you were here you'd be going."  SM: "No, we wouldn't do that. Your dad just has vacation time now."  So, the verdict is in. Benny Hinn culties don't do Graham... ROFLMAO
     
    
</post>

<date>26,October,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      Sweet Taters and carrots … ... turn baby poop orange.  Ahhh, the wonders of new food!
     
    
</post>

<date>13,October,2000</date>
<post>

	 
       North vs. South - Living in the land of Sunshine and almost perpetual Summer, I forget my kids do not share the same life experiences I had at their age.     Today, watching ZOOM on PBS, the boys were laughing at the kids on the show who were telling jokes.    "What does a car wear when it gets cold?" "A car-digan!"    Bug says, "What's a cardigan?" I replied, "A heavy knit sweater."    Then, thinking I'm some sort of cool mom, "I have a better answer! A car wears a muffler when it gets cold!"    Bear looked at me and said, "Mom, a muffler keeps a car quiet. You can't wear it. It's a piece of the car!"    I just sat quietly and realized that there is a whole world of experiences that I have taken for granted that my kids do not know of. Snow. Snowmen. Snow angels. Eating snowflakes. Wearing one piece snowsuits that made me look like a starfish. Splashing through slush in my red rubber boots.  Wow... 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,November,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      Please, if you have a moment, say a little prayer for Butterscotch, my 15 year old kitty.  Had to take her to the Vet's today - she has a UTI and a 'fever' (her temp is below normal) and they have her on mild antibiotics. She also has a heart murmur and hyper-thyroidism - all relatively 'normal' for an old cat.  If the UTI doesn't clear up and/or gets worse, I don't plan on taking any measures to extend her life. I love her dearly but I just can't put her through tests and other traumatizing things that probably will not work.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,December,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      We went to TRU to pick out my present - Sharky wanted to get me a doll, but couldn't decide on exactly which one, so we all went this afternoon.  Christmas is over, right? So what the heck is with all the attitudes???  I lost count of how many times I or my cart, or my kids, were pushed aside by OTHER MOTHERS dragging their little brats across the store!  EXCUSE THE @#$% OUT OF ME! I have NEVER pushed anyone aside so my kid can go look at a freaking toy. Never, never, never!!!  I just don't get it.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,December,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      The kids and I went to Wal-Mart very early this morning to avoid the crowds and take advantage of the marking down of xmas stuff.  I was really looking for one of those "porcelain" tree-topper angels to take the head/hands out and use the outfit for a Barbie. Alas, there were none left the right size.  I then spied some santas and thought perhaps there was an angel or two in the pile. Sorting through, I realized that these Santas were really neat. There was one or two traditional Coca-Cola looking ones but the rest were white or gold or maroon.  Then, to what do my wandering eyes (and hands) appear? The PERFECT Santa!  He's 12 inches tall wearing a brown "wool" coat with brown faux fur trim, and a rope belt. He's carrying on one arm rustic looking twig/rope snowshoes and an evergreen sprig with tiny pine cones and on the other is like a large felt mitten which I may remove (too countryish for me). The coat falls below his knees and he has on plastic boots (oh well) with faux fur trimmed maroon felt pants. On his head is a faux fur trimmed long floppy hat (matching the coat) with a bell on the end. He has a 'real' beard that is wavy, not curly white. His face is sweet and gentle, NOT jolly, and is made from a plastic that looks/feels like porcelain.  And the biggest thrill? He was $12.96, marked down to $9! LOL  Can you tell I'm thrilled?  BTW, when I was showing him to the boys, Bear said he looked like the Greenman in winter!
     
    
</post>

<date>21,December,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      Bear just told me he asked Santa to get a present for his Dad. When I asked him what, he told me that he wanted Santa to get a motorcycle for his Dad because it was too expensive for us to buy - like $130 dollars.  I wish. :-)
     
    
</post>

<date>18,December,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      Today, my Papa turns 90 years old. I called him today to wish him a Happy Birthday. He was quite chipper and looking forward to Christmas.  He and some other friends at the trailer park where he lives are having a potluck Christmas dinner.  I think it's fantastic - he hasn't associated with friends in years.  But honestly, all I keep thinking is that in 2 weeks, for the first time in his life, he will be older than my Grandma. This will be his first Christmas without her since WWII.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,December,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      My Christmas Tradition  Written by ADC (a.k.a. Bear - 2nd Grade) and typed here by Mommy - who also corrected the spelling but that's it.  My family doesn't really celebrate Christmas but we celebrate Yule. It is a holiday that the Pagans celebrated before the Christians took it and called it Christmas. Many people say that Jesus is born in December but my mom told me Jesus was born in a different month but for some reason some one told every body that Jesus was born in December. What is a Pagan? A Pagan is a person that doesn't believe in God, Jesus or the Devil they believe in the Goddess. On Yule we always decorate a tree and we give presents. My whole family celebrates Yule. Yule is a special holiday to my family. Also we celebrate the Winter Solstice its also special to my family. My family is Pagan. That's why we celebrate Yule and the Winter Solstice. That's my tradition.  Bear got to stand up in front of the whole class and read his story.  He is very proud of it.  And I am very proud of him too.  I've told him many times that he doesn't have to talk about our religion if he feels uncomfortable - he told me he didn't mind.  The teacher even told him that he didn't have to sing the Christian Christmas Carols at the Nursing Home yesterday but I told him he could do whatever he wanted to - as long as it was his choice.  He was happy about that and went ahead and sang the carols.    Last week, during Library, the Librarian mentioned the Winter Solstice (because it's her birthday) and Bear volunteered the fact that his family celebrates it.  She took that opportunity to tell the other kids about what a great nation it was that we can have any religion we want to.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,December,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      Today, my cat, Cosmo, knocked a box of genealogy papers off my desk onto the floor. As I was picking them up, I ran across the funeral program of my paternal Grandmother who died in the late '80s. I read it again, tears welling up in my eyes. I had only met her once (she lived with my relatives in Australia) but we had a wonderful 'pen-pal' relationship.  She was a Salvationist - a religion I know very little of. On the program, instead of stating that she died, it read:  "Promoted to Glory"  It seems that is a term they use when one of their officers passes over.  I think it's lovely. :-)
     
    
</post>

<date>08,December,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      A little while ago, I received this email gem in my box from some relatives. They NEVER send me any personal email, just some Spam once in a blue moon.  Subject: FW: Cancer (DO NOT DELETE) - You must forward!!!!!!]]  Hi, my name is Amy Bruce. I am 7 years old, and I have severe lung cancer from second hand smoke. I also have a large tumor in my brain, from repeated beatings. The doctors say I will die soon if this isn't fixed, and my family can't pay the bills. The Make A Wish Foundation, has agreed to donate 7 cents for every name on this list.  For those of you who send this along, I thank you so much, but for those who don't send it, what goes around comes around. Have a Heart, please send this.  It took me around 30 seconds to research this and fire off a reply:  From the Make-a-wish Foundation's website:  This Internet-based chain letter claims that a 7-year-old girl named Amy Bruce, who is suffering from a brain tumor and lung cancer, will receive 7 cents from the Make-A-Wish Foundation each time her letter is forwarded via e-mail.  This request is false, and the Foundation has contacted the originator’s Internet service provider to pursue the matter.  So, annoying relatives aside, did you all notice the statement in bold in the original email?  Yes, I understand that people want to help others, especially when it comes to children. But to THREATEN someone who doesn't want to forward email Spam?  THE NERVE! Hmmmph. :-)
     
    
</post>

<date>07,December,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      Little things that make me happy - Rocking Petunia to sleep, then putting her down and discovering a little ear print on my arm...
     
    
</post>

<date>07,December,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      Nothing upsets me more than during the Holiday season than to be around nasty, ill-tempered, arseholes. In other words, HOLIDAY SHOPPERS!  How do you handle them?  I have to admit to having a bit of a sarcastic mouth in real life. I have actually confronted nasty hateful people with comments like: "Well, Merry Christmas to you too" But, my all-time favorite is: "Great way to celebrate the birth of YOUR savior!"  I've NEVER had a comeback to the last one. It just leaves them standing there with their mouths hanging open...
     
    
</post>

<date>22,January,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      When I picked the boys up at my Mom's yesterday, as usual, she gives me a bag of goodies - magazines, etc. - that she picks up for me.  In the bag, was a nice little plastic box for crafts, etc. On the label of the box it's called "Shiny Box" and has a picture of the box being used as a sewing kit, a cassette tape holder, and ... a box to store candles, matches and LOTS of incense.  hehehehehehe
     
    
</post>

<date>19,January,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      I don’t know why.  That is the answer that Bug has been giving every time he gets into trouble (at home and school). "I don't know why"  It's driving me batty. He knows he can talk to me about everything - and has! But now, he's on thin ice at school. He gets a behaviour report sent home every day (instead of every week like the other kids) because he calls the other kids names, pushes and shoves.  The WORST happened last week. In quiet story time, the kids are broken up into groups. Completely out of the blue, Bug states that "black people are bad". Can we say the shit hit the roof? The teacher is "horrified" and I am flabbergasted. The teacher had to counsel all the other children who were "traumatized" by Bug's racial statement. The only thing I can think of that would cause that statement is that there is a little black boy in the class (he was in Bear's class last year and failed) that continually picks on Bug all the time and gets his friends (also black) to pick on him too. I've brought it up to the teacher and she says that she is aware of it.  The teacher has asked him why he made the statement and his father and I have asked him, and all he will say is "I don't know why."  I keep telling him that just because someone is bad doesn't mean everyone is bad - there are good cops and bad cops, good moms and bad moms, and good black people and bad black people. Just because you have a problem with one doesn't mean all the others are bad too. He's not a racist little boy - one of his best friends in kindergarten was black. I have NEVER heard Bug made a racial comment before. We don't and we try hard NOT to use stereotypical comments.  We live in an extremely mixed racial environment and the school is very mixed. I want my children to grow up in this environment because that is the way the rest of the world is. They have to learn to deal with it early on.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,January,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      This morning, Bear decided to tell me about a movie they watched in class yesterday.  "It was about two camels and a donkey. The camels didn't like the donkey and kept telling him "Get away asshole!" Then all the kids laughed and the teacher had to stop the movie and tell us that "Asshole" is another name for donkey."  Believe me, it was VERY HARD to keep a straight face while trying to explain to him the difference between ass and asshole...
     
    
</post>

<date>05,February,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      The Diaper Rash from Hell.   I am not kidding. Poor Petunia had the diaper rash from hell. Two whole months. Red, itchy, skin as thin as tissue paper. No yeast infection, just raw skin.  We tried EVERYTHING. Bathed her in oatmeal every diaper change. Every diaper rash medicine known to man. Changed diaper brands (Bear was allergic to Pampers as a baby, the blue lining irritated his skin).  Nothing worked. Until... I changed baby wipes.  Turns out, Petunia has a reaction to Huggies Non-allergy, Sensitive Skin w/Aloe.  I switched to the generic Wal-mart White Cloud brand and she has had happy pink skin ever since.  Who'd a thunk that something that was hypo-allergenic was irritating?
     
    
</post>

<date>02,March,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      How stupid do they think we are?  I just saw an ad for "Sears Super Saturday Sale" starting at 5:00 p.m. Friday...
     
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      We have Petunia in a walker now and she has learned to love standing up - it scared her before - now, with the "support" that is all she wants to do. She can move back a bit and forward if she tries hard, but I picked this walker out because it's quite hard to move (safer to me).
     
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      My heart is breaking...  ...and I don't know what to do.  My mom is doing a lot better. She got out of the hospital on Saturday with a ton of meds and still got us all together for Easter. I helped as best I could to keep her stress level down and we all ended up having a great time.  BUT, now, my father-in-law, the man my husband loves most in this world is dying from emphysema.  Yesterday morning, I first got a hysterical call from Auntie V, telling me that Jim was dying and would be dead in a few hours. After a few minutes she changed the story to a few days. I called Sharky at work to tell him to call his dad - and reminded/warned him that Auntie V exaggerates most of the time.  Then, I get a call from Della (Jim's wife) telling me that yes, Jim was in the hospital on and off all weekend, but was NOT dying and if he were, SHE would be the one to call us, not an Auntie. So I called Sharky back and told him - much to his relief. Jim was fine, having problems breathing, but had a doctor appointment tomorrow (today).  THEN, I got a call in the afternoon from Piza, Sharky's sister, telling us that he WAS dying. After I explained everything, she started yelling at me accusing me of not caring. Turns out, she had just got off the phone with Della and they were walking out the door to take Jim back to the emergency room at a hospital over an hour away - the local hospitals can't help him anymore. (Like I was supposed to have known that? He sent us an email letting us know, but I received it almost an hour after her call.)  Everything has just gotten worse. I am unfeeling and uncaring because I *gasp* am praying that he will be getting better and not believing that he is dying. I am also mean because I'm not letting Sharky abandon his job and his family to go running up there (his sister and his brother didn't either, but they are better than us). On top of it all, the brother had the balls to tell Sharky that he (Sharky) may not be able to take time off now, but he better after Dad dies. (HUH??? Why is it so important to drop everything to go see a dead body?)  I am so thankful that we had (on and off) three weeks with his dad - Sharky got to spend a lot of time with him and the kids got to too.  We can't afford a plane ticket and we only have the one car. I want Sharky to go up there and see his dad but we can't.  And I am turning out to be the bad guy in all of this.  I understand why the sister and brother have short fuses, but they are quite well off financially compared to us and yet I don't think it's fair for them to demand that Sharky be the one to go up there.  It's hell - we live in NFlorida - and dad is in Michigan. That's a good 24+ hour ride (with no potty breaks). I do want to clarify - it's not that I am not LETTING Sharky go, he can't go. Even if he could leave work - gas=money... But to them, I am nothing but a shrew who won't hock everything she owns...  Do I tell the boys that grandpa is sick? I mean, they know he's sick, but do I tell them he is dying sick? I don't know what to do.  I'm just sitting here waiting for the phone to ring...  I lost my grandmother last year - she was the first person close to me that died. I've had friends and family that died, but it was always far away - nothing close. The pain was excruciating to lose someone so close - grandma was like a mom to me.  I will say something to the boys after school. I don't want to scare them, but I do want them to be prepared. Hopefully, I can follow it up with good news about Grandpa getting better.  The thing is, their hateful comments doesn't really hurt me directly anymore - I've had going on 10 years to get used to it. But it still hurts Sharky when they are mean to him, and that hurts me - that I can't stop his pain. :-(  Update! (FINALLY!)  Dad Jim is doing great. The hospital has his emphysema under control and is balancing all the meds, etc., to make sure he has everything proper. He told Sharky that he really thought he was going to die yesterday.  He also told Sharky how proud he was of me for keeping my cool and attempting to keep everyone else calm and civil. :-)  I feel so much better now. The kids have finished their get-well cards and will put them in the mail tomorrow.  Thank you all for your thoughts and prayers and just listening to me ramble. Sometimes that is all one needs.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,April,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Just a little prayer please for my mom and best friend, Robin, who will turn 60 on the Summer Solstice.  She just called me from the doctor's office - they are admitting her to the hospital this morning for tests and possibly admittance for a few days. Her blood pressure is up, her cholesterol is up, her heart is enlarged - showing signs of congestive heart failure, and she has been suffering from mini-strokes.  She called me from her room (on her cell phone! gasp - had to bitch her out for that one) to let me know where she is. They have her on telemetry machines and are scheduling the tests. The doctors say that it will be a couple of days.  She had to have the doctor call and talk to Dad (step dad) - he was going berserk and couldn't work. He has to stay at work because his job doesn't give time off and they need the pay right now. Mom thought it was silly for him to be with her anyway right now - it would just make him more upset - which would upset her - etc., etc.  My best friend's MIL went through almost the exact same thing last year, and came out with flying colors (and 20 pills a day), so I do feel better. And knowing I have friends praying helps more than you realize.  I've been talking to Grandma for the past few hours, begging her to stay with my mom. The last time I saw her before she died, she told me that I had the best mom in the world and that she (Grandma) wished she could have been like Robin. I pray that Grandma is with her right now, holding her, and making sure she will be alright.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,April,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Bug will be the featured artist for his grade next week at the 1st Annual Art Exhibit and Ice Cream Social at the Elementary school. We are so proud of him.  When he came home with the notice, the first thing I said was, let's tell Grandma Rita! (She had always wanted to be an artist and was even accepted to an art school, but in 1928, it wasn't an "appropriate" thing for a young lady to do. So, she went to nursing school instead.) And then I remembered, I can't call her.  And then today, both boys came home with prizes for winning a short story contest for St. Patrick's Day (leprechaun stories) - in the little packs were 2 real coins from Ireland, some gold chocolate coins, a shamrock key chain, and a really neat green and white shamrock whirligig. Silly me, I asked the boys if we could save the whirligig and give it to Grandma Rita when we saw her this Sunday at Easter.  And then I started crying. You know, it's been a year and 3 months since she died and it still feels like a stab wound when I realize she's not here physically anymore. I feel her a lot sometimes and it makes me happy - and then times like this happen and I can't feel her.  It makes the boys sad to see me crying and I don't want to upset them - but I don't want to hide it and make it seem like it's something to be ashamed of.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      What do you wish for? No, it doesn't have to be to hit the lotto or peace on earth.  Something more tangible, mundane, and possibly within reach...  I wish for one day, just one day, where the kids don't fight and I don't have to yell and no one gets mad and I get a nice big breakfast made without any problems and without my help.  Ooops, I guess that is a couple of wishes, huh? :-)
     
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      I just wanted to let you all know that Bear, my 8 year old second grader, has won the photography portion of the County Division PTA Art Contest - and has qualified for the State contest...
     
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Baby sweat smells good. :-)
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm ashamed that this took me so long to do. I am no longer the Queen of Complaints - I need to reclaim my crown. :-) Seriously folks, I cried when I wrote this. The grocery store description is tame to the reality. Please, no corrections - it's already been sent and I can't get it back.  *************  I was in your store on Sunday, May 27th, at 11:00 a.m. and, as usual, was disgusted by what I found. The front door's glass was broken, garbage littered the foyer, and produce and dead bugs were all over the floor of the produce section. Ceiling tiles are spotty brown and warped, some not completely attached looking like they will fall down any minute. The rest of the store was in equally shabby condition.  I am dismayed by the fact that your corporation allows this store to remain in such filthy conditions. You have poured money into the nearby Normandy Blvd. store twice - once to build the new Winn-Dixie Marketplace, the second to remodel that same brand new store. Why couldn't you have left that store as is and used the remodeling money to fix the McDuff store?  I have shopped at this particular store since my family and I moved into the neighborhood in 1998. I have continued to shop there due to its close proximity to our house. When I have friends or relatives visit, I do not take them to the McDuff store, I drive the extra miles and take them to the Normandy store. Yes, I am embarrassed and ashamed by the conditions of the McDuff store - my neighborhood store.  By you leaving that store in deplorable conditions, you are telling us, the residents of the neighborhood that we are not worth a clean store.  I constantly hear rumours that the McDuff store will be closing. Please, DO NOT close the store! There are too many residents of that neighborhood that rely on its closeness - they cannot afford to drive all over town to shop. There are many elderly residents who physically cannot drive the distance to another store.  Please, explain why our store cannot be clean and modern like the Normandy store. Please let me know why nothing has been done to repair the store.  I have tried to speak to the Manager about the conditions of the store, but I have never seen him and when I ask for him, I am told that he is always somewhere else and cannot be bothered.  My husband and I have grown up in Florida and have shopped at Winn-Dixies our whole lives. We have never, ever seen a store this filthy, this in need of repair in our lives.  Follow-up – June 1st - I received an email letter this morning:  Thank you for your comments. We apologize for the problem. Your email has been forwarded to our Division Office to check this out and respond to you.  We appreciate your patronage and know we must earn the privilege of serving your supermarket shopping needs in the future.  Director of Public Relations  When I arrived home from picking the boys up from school at noon, there was a message on my answering machine from the Manager of the McDuff Winn-Dixie asking for me to return his call. Of course, when I called back, he was at lunch, so I left a return message.  Second Follow-up (June 5th) Well, I called him at lunchtime and am pleased with the results.  Heck, he was thrilled that I sent an email to corporate - it validated HIS complaints to them!  Turns out, he was transferred from the nice Normandy store to the dirty McDuff store - as he said, "I don't know if this was a promotion or demotion." The old manager was fired.  In the past two weeks that he's held this job, 8 employees have been hauled out in handcuffs, the front door glass has been replaced twice, he's in the process of repairing the ceiling tiles and trying to convince the employees to get rid of their negative attitude and take some pride in the store and their work. He thinks it's working - sales has been up $20 grand since he got there. He says he's there 6-7 days a week trying to get the store up to decent standards.  He also told me why the Normandy store has been remodeled. Turns out, that is the biggest money making store in the area and Corporate uses it for a test store. They remodel it every so often and try new things out before it is sent on to the rest of the country. (Winn Dixie HQ is only a few miles down the road from here, near downtown.)  Well, I am satisfied for now. It won't be a brand new store ever but all I want is nice and clean.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      I just realized that there is the most perfect picture happening at this moment and no one to take it with a camera. :-(  As I am sitting here, Petunia is in her high chair next to me. I have a computer in front of me. She has her Little Tykes Laptop on her high chair tray. I'm typing. She's pushing buttons.  LOL!
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      My baby, my Bear, left this morning with his 2nd grade class to Orlando on a field trip to one of the attractions.  This is the first time he's been away from me so far.  When the bus left at 6 a.m. this morning, I burst into tears. I didn't let him see though.  Please send safe happy thoughts - (I am a nervous wreck) - that Bear and his class have a wonderful SAFE time and all get home safely.  6:40 p.m. Thank you all.  Bear is home, safe and sound, brown as a bunny and as full of energy as one too!  This whole experience made me think. How in the world do mothers cope who's children are going off to war? *sigh*
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night, I had to go to Wal-greens to pick up some "feminine protection". There were a good 20 people in line at the front register and no one at the Pharmacy, so I went there to buy it.  The girl (20-ish), rang up the order and was bagging it when she sort of zoned out, staring at the package. Completely out of habit she asked:  "Do you have any questions for the pharmacist on the use of this product?"  I said, "No, after over 20 years, I think I know how to use a maxi-pad."  She blinked, did a double take, and then "OHMYGOD I am so sorry!" and laughed.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      You know, if it wasn't for all the conveniences of society that I have grown to love, I could be a hermit very easily.  Sharky changed jobs last November - got a bigger, better one. :-) We waited the 3 months until he qualified for insurance, then filled out all the paperwork. Then, they lost it a few times, he had to fight on the phone, yada yada yada, and FINALLY, 2 weeks ago, I got our insurance cards in the mail. So, I immediately made an appointment for Petunia's 12-month well baby - (she turned a year 21 Mar).  Now, when I filled out the paperwork, her doctor was listed in the insurance book AND I even called them to verify that they were a member. When I made the appointment, I again verified that they were a member.  So, Petunia and I got all dressed up this morning to see the doctor. I walked in the doctor's office this morning, signed the sheet, put my insurance card in the waiting box like always, turned aside, then heard "WAIT!"  I turned around, just to have the receptionist bitch SHOVE my insurance card in my face saying "We don't carry Humana."  So, I politely told her that I had verified numerous times that they do.  "Oh NO, we don't take Humana HMO, we only take Humana PPO."  When I asked what the difference was, she sneered and said, "We don't take the low end HMO, we only take the PREMIUM PPO." And she made the word PREMIUM much louder.  I stupidly said again that I didn't understand, and she said "If you don't understand..." laughed, and said "NEXT!"  And I was pushed aside by mom with a snotty nosed brat. So, I struggled with my purse and the diaper bag and Petunia, got the insurance card back in my wallet, and when I turned around, there was a waiting room full of parents sniggering at me.  I just walked out.  I just hate people sometimes.  The good news, I fixed out the problem. The lady at Humana apologized for the mix-up (they knew that the doctor wasn't the right type but he ended up on the card anyway) and we were able to find another good pediatrician in the neighbourhood (0.8 miles away) and got Petunia an appointment on the 30th of this month.  I still hate people right now.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm fixing dinner and Petunia was hungry - so I sat her in her highchair and gave her a cup of milk and a small handful of Cheerios.  She had to have her two best friends, Cassie and Ord (Dragon Tales) with her too.  I just looked over and she's FEEDING THEM CHEERIOS!!!!!  Isn't that just the CUTEST??? LOL
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Today we were in Kmart picking up dog food, etc., and the boys asked to walk through the toy section. Of course I said yes because I wanted to scope out the Barbie section. LOL  Then, the inevitable - "I want _____." "Can I have _____?" I had to explain that there is a birthday coming up, and we will be shopping for school clothes this Saturday and NO I am not buying any toys and since they were out of money, they couldn't either. Well, the whining commenced, and soon stopped - turning into scowls, watery eyes and dirty looks.  Oh well, like that is new? LOL  So, we get to the checkout. Behind me is a mother with four kids, all about the same age as my three with one in the middle.  They were animals. Fighting, crying, grabbing candy and opening it, stuffing things in their pockets, climbing on the counter, climbing on the racks, knocking things over, etc. The mother couldn't control them. "Bobby don't do that." "Suzy, get down from there." And the kids completely ignored her. The only way I can truly describe it is that it looked like a shark feeding frenzy.  I had to grab my stuff to keep the beasts away from it all. I turned around and there are my three - Petunia buckled in the seat, flanked on either side by a boy - all three with frozen looks of horror in their eyes.  I paid for the stuff, put it in my cart, and as we were walking out, BOTH BOYS at once said:  "Mommy, I'm sorry about whining, that wasn't nice." "We don't want to be like those kids, that was embarrassing."  In front of everyone, I grabbed them, hugged them, and told them that they were the greatest.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      The Cat Who Came for Thanksgiving by K. St. John  I know you have heard of the famous book, The Cat Who Came for Christmas, by Cleveland Armory. Let me tell you of another cat, one who came for Thanksgiving.  Once, there was a Mommy and a Daddy and two little boys named Bear and Bug. They had just moved into a little rental house while waiting for their dream home, a little brick bungalow, to be finished.  On Thanksgiving Day 1997, Mommy discovered a little orange and beige cat living under their house. She was hungry and sick. Mommy named the cat Butterscotch.  Mommy and Daddy asked the neighbors if they knew whom Butterscotch belonged to. Her story was very sad. She had lived in the house next door with a very old, sick lady and many, many other cats and dogs. One day, the lady’s home health nurse abandoned her. The police and paramedics had to rescue the lady and take her to a nursing home. Someone, thinking they were being kind, let all the cats and dogs out side instead of calling the animal shelter. They all disappeared, except for Butterscotch, who moved under the house next door. She lived, all alone, scrounging for food for a whole year.  Mommy took her to the vet who told her that Butterscotch might not live long. She was an old, tired great, great grandma kitty who had been very neglected. Butterscotch was about 12 years old, which can be old for a cat. She was blind in one eye and was missing all her molars and most of her bottom teeth. One of her canines was broken. It was hard for her to eat hard food, but she gummed it like a champ.  Mommy and Daddy talked it over and decided to give Butterscotch a loving home until it was her time to pass over the Rainbow Bridge.  Bear and Bug were happy. They finally had a cat of their own!  Butterscotch was confused. She was happy to have a warm, safe home and lots of food and water, but what were these little boys? They wanted to play. She wanted to sleep. They wanted to pet her. She wanted to be left alone. Soon, after a cat smack or two, they learned to be extra gentle and nice to the old cat. Soon, Butterscotch loved them and trusted them enough to let them hold her and love her like they wanted.  Butterscotch was a funny cat. Her old mommy used to feed all the cats on the dining room table, out of plates and bowls. Her new mommy had a hard time convincing Butterscotch that it was better to eat on the floor. Butterscotch loved to snuggle and as soon as Daddy would get home from work, she would run to the couch and snuggle up with Daddy and the big brown blanket. Most of the time, it was Butterscotch who ended up with the blanket and Daddy snuggling with her. When Butterscotch wanted love, she would sit next to a person and tap them on the arm with her paw, letting them know she was there and needed affection.  Soon, the family and Butterscotch moved into their bungalow. Butterscotch was very happy – lots of room to run, hide, and play in. She acted a lot younger than her age.  A year later, Mommy found a tiny black kitten in the gutter. He was hungry and had been eating out of people’s garbage cans. She fell in love with him and brought him home. Bear and Bug were excited! A new kitty! They named him Cosmo.  Butterscotch was not happy. Who was this annoying little pest who was trying to nurse on her? She was too old to deal with babies. She would smack little Cosmo when he’d come near her.  Cosmo loved her. He would chase her around the house and try to kiss her. Pretty soon, he tried to love her too much and Mommy had to take him to the vet and have him altered before he’d hurt old Butterscotch with his ‘loving’.  After that, other than a brief frisky occasion, Butterscotch came to love Cosmo. He was warm and was a great snuggler. He’d groom her and wash her for hours. And, once in a while, if she felt like it, she’d groom him back.  Life was good in the little brick bungalow. Even the addition of a dog and a new human baby wasn’t very much stress for Butterscotch. She knew she was loved and she would always be taken care of. Never again would she have to worry about being cold or hungry or alone.  Three and a half years passed. Butterscotch became sick. Her kidneys no longer worked like they were supposed to and her back legs could no longer support her body.  Mommy and Daddy were very sad – they had to tell Bear and Bug it was time to say goodbye. Bear and Bug were broken hearted – she was their first kitty love. They thought life was very unfair. Butterscotch was a very important part of their life. They fed and watered her every day, faithfully. They learned to scoop the litter box and to hold her gently when Mommy trimmed her nails. Butterscotch had given Bear the dream to one day become a veterinarian.  Butterscotch passed over peacefully this morning (6 July 2001) with the help of a loving veterinarian, surrounded by the little boys who loved her so much.  When you read this, don’t feel sorry for us. We were blessed with her love and don’t regret a thing. But instead, please do us a favor. Find your loved one – be they furry or feathered or scaly or flesh – and tell them you love them. Life is too short not to.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      My ancient grandma kitty, Butterscotch, is failing. She's 15 or 16 years old.  She is incredibly thin and frail, all skin and bones, and hasn't eaten in days. She has drunk some water. She hasn't pooped in days - I know because she can no longer climb into the litter box but there is no droppings anywhere, but her hind legs and tail have urine on them. She can barely walk without falling.  I don't want her to suffer anymore. This is a very undignified way to go for a cat. :-(  I will be calling the vet when they open.  Please pray that they will help me and not give me a hard time about not wanting to prolong her life. I don't want her to die, but it is her time - I know it is.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Today, Bear goes back in to retake the gifted test at 1 p.m. EST. He took it before in kindergarten and missed acceptance in the program by a couple of points. Ironically, the part he did the worst on (puzzles) is one of his greater strengths.  Bug, on the other hand, aced it. Which, of course, made Bear feel even worse inside - though he does put on a brave front and brags about his very smart little brother.  It's hard. We keep telling him to do his best because that is what really counts - and even if he doesn't pass, he'll still be kept in the Edge program (like a junior gifted class).  I just don't want to see his spirit crushed by all of this...
     
    
</post>

<date>26,August,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      We have the anniversary video of The Many Adventures of Winnie the Pooh - the original movie that started it all.  You know, I can't make it through the first five minutes without crying.  And I have no idea.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,August,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      After the *umpteenth* visit to www.snopes.com  to debunk yet another email urban legend a kind relative had sent me, I clicked on the email at the bottom of the page and just sent Barbara Mikkelson a quick note saying, "I just wanted to drop you all a line and say "Thank You!" for the great service you provide all of us on the internet."  This morning, I got a reply in my email box: "*blush* Thanks for taking the time to write me such a nice note -- the encouragement is greatly appreciated. - Barbara"  When was the last time you thanked someone? :-)
     
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      This morning, waiting in very heavy traffic at a light, I spied an incredibly gorgeous man.  He was a surveyor and was wearing Bermuda-length blue jean shorts, and an orange safety vest - no shirt. He looked a lot like a very young Tom Selleck - from the Magnum PI days, remember? *drool*  He turned and looked at me and smiled. I smiled back.  He waved. I waved back.  He BLEW ME A KISS! I lost my nerve, smiled and looked away, blushing like mad, but still watching out of the corner of my eye.  Then, he made the motion of writing my phone number down. I blushed, smiled and shook my head no.  Then, he started walking over to me. I made sure the windows were rolled up and the doors were locked.  THEN, as my heart beat 90 miles a minute, he walked PAST MY CAR to the monster truck sitting along side of me and was given a piece of paper by the MAN INSIDE THE TRUCK!  I just about died of embarrassment. *sigh*
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Yep, she's getting to be a big girl now. Last night, she slept in her crib, in her room, for the very first time - at 16 1/2 months old.  We waited until she was asleep, put her in there and we slept alone - with the baby monitor turned up high enough so I could hear her snore.  Damn, that was hard.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,September,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      I've been lurking around in other forums and freaked out a bit in Kathi's ExWitch forum.  Someone started a thread about what to do with all their magickal stuff when they go from Wiccan (etc.) to Christian. It was all "destroy it" or "throw it away".  NONONONONONONO!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  Reduce, Reuse, Recycle!  Makes me want to get a post office box for people to mail all their unwanted, unneeded magickal stuff to so I could clean it and donate it to poor pagans who need it.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,September,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      I keep fluctuating between two major emotions or thought processes:  (1) When will this sorrow fade enough for life to go back to normal?  and  (2) When will this over-patriotism fade enough for life to go back to normal?  I know this may sound heartless (it isn't meant to), but the pain of the tragedy versus this sudden onslaught of patriotism is like being in the middle of a giant tug of war. If I'm not grieving, I'm celebrating.  I don't care for this. I don't know how to mesh these two emotions together so I'm not tugged back and forth.  Has anyone else experienced this? Or am I just nuts? :-)
     
    
</post>

<date>20,September,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Is this email I received this morning tasteless or am I just ultra sensitive?  From: Paradigm Wireless Sent: Thursday, September 20, 2001 4:50 AM To: ******@************* Subject: Emergencies call for cell phones, and now they are free.  It's Time To Get Together.  It's never been more important or more affordable to bring your friends and family together.  In times like these you've got to stay connected with your friends and family. They need you on call, and you need to be able to reach them.  Today, cell phones are the only way to go.   
     
    
</post>

<date>13,September,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      I watched the news last night - American mosques shot up, death threats, bomb threats to any Arab, no matter how American they are.  A restaurant is closed now because the owner is terrified - she's received bomb threats and death threats. Her family is Syrian/Pakistani and has been in this country for over 60 years! Shit, my dad didn't even come here until 1963! They are more American than I am.  I live in a city FULL of Arab-Americans. An Arab convenient store owner was shot and killed two years ago in a robbery and practically 1/2 the city showed up to pay respects because he was a good, kind, decent man. We're just to forget that because of the nationalities of some coward assholes?  Every pagan list I am on is begging and pleading for us to remain calm and not attack the Arabs. Yeah, right. Like the people who will do that are on those lists. Hah.  I'm sorry.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,September,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Prayers...  For all the victims of the terrorist attacks on the WTO.  And the Pentagon.  And all four of the hijacked planes.  And their friends, family and loved ones.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,September,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Stupid N*gger – A Rant  Are you shocked by the title of this thread? Upset? Horrified?  Well, guess what? I feel like that every freaking day of the week.  It's bad enough that every day after school, I am surrounded by little boys and girls calling each other "n*gger" and other almost as vulgar words, this morning I walk outside to my porch and catch my xian next door neighbour attempting to beat the shit out of her six year old son, chasing him around the yard, screaming "Stupid N*gger" at the top of her lungs. (She never did catch him.)  This is the same woman who blasts xian music all the time and who can be heard evangelizing at the television set in the mornings. I'm pretty sure if we asked WWJD, he wouldn't call his own child a n*gger.  Do you know what I am scared of the most? That my children will start saying it.  I've explained to them over and over that the word is NOT appropriate to say. But I have no idea what to tell them when they ask me why the other kids say it. Their friends say it. The good kids say it. The bullies say it. Now they are hearing parents are saying it.  It's different than other dirty words. I've only heard a few kids saying things like f*ck, etc. But I swear every single kid who walks our way after school says n*gger. It's not a bad word to them. It's so ingrained into their language I don't think most of them even realize they are saying it.  And I am scared that it's contagious.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,September,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Sagwa, The Siamese Chinese Cat  They have just started showing Sagwa on PBS here the other day.  I LOVE IT!  http://pbskids.org/sagwa/  The boys love it and Petunia couldn't stop yelling "CAT" and pointing to the TV.  Sagwa is a Chinese Siamese cat who lives with her cat family (mom, dad, brother, sister) and her human family, the Magistrate, his wife (who he's always calling things like "Peach Blossom), and their 3 daughters.  It's written by Amy Tan and the artwork is simple, but lovely.  It's about time there was a good, positive cat cartoon on television!
     
    
</post>

<date>30,October,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      My kids went Trick or Treating at the Zoo's Spooktacular this evening, and in the bags of candy they got, they received boxes of Kellogg's Cinnamon Crispix Cereal and Ragu's Pasta Express.  No lie.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,October,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      You know, to me, a fussy baby is one thing. Yes, I'm not a saint and have shed a few tears over a baby fussing, but it was always easy to understand - a baby can't communicate.  BUT a toddler can, up to a point - and Petunia isn't a baby anymore.  She was so freaking fussy yesterday. Nothing made her happy. NOTHING. Everything I did was WRONG in her eyes.  I finally broke down, put her in the car and she fell asleep in minutes. Drove around for a while, came home, and lay on the couch with her sleeping.  Well, I don't have the car today. I'm praying that today isn't a repeat of yesterday.  Don't worry, I would never hit her. I just don't want to spend today crying. :-(
     
    
</post>

<date>23,October,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Getting rid of stuff - It's hard.  I'm finally parting with the baby swing and bassinette that we've been dragging around for years and years. We don't need them, can't use them (Petunia's too big), but considering we've been hanging on to them for so long...  Always hung on to them because we "knew" we'd need them again - but no more babies in this house. Oooops, there go those hormones again. :-/  I don't feel right selling them, so I put out a note on the local pagan list to see if anyone needed them.  Within 30 minutes, I heard of an emergency c-section (baby boy) last week of a local pagan woman who is in financial trouble. So, looks like they will be going to a new home.  The baby clothes that I'm not keeping are going to a young man who has partial custody of his girl.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,October,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      I'll be gone most of the afternoon today to go to my doll club meeting.  Every year, we have a small toy drive for Yule/Christmas. Instead of giving toys to Toys for Tots, etc. (which everyone does), we give to a battered women's shelter.  This year, a member is donating 50 dolls (in various conditions) and today we are all bringing in clothes, etc., to fix the dolls up and dress them. (Next month, we will be bringing in boy toys and Mom gifts too.)  I'm really looking forward to this. Instead of just buying a toy, we will be handling them and filling them with love and happiness for these little girls. *sniff*
     
    
</post>

<date>12,October,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Day #2 – Binky free?  Well, almost.  Night before last, we lost Petunia's daytime binky. So, when she woke up yesterday morning, we said goodbye to the nighttime binky, left it in the crib, and came out of the room. She went ALL DAY without a binky, until she got cranky around 8 pm, her bedtime. We gave her the nighttime binky and she went to bed.  Again, this morning, said goodbye and came out here. She's been without it for 8 hours.  I have my fingers and toes crossed that we won't be having a problem...
     
    
</post>

<date>01,October,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      As most of you remember, I am NOT a big fan of our school's PTA. (For a refresher, the year before last I went to my first meeting - just to hear a PTA bigwig make a snide remark that she was glad no "neighbourhood" parents showed up. She believes that my 'hood is a poor black 'hood and filled with worthless parents and they (PTA) do not need their help. I was pregnant and over emotional so I didn't speak up. :-( No one called, no one asked, and no one contacted me for any of the projects even though I volunteered. So last year, I didn't even bother to join.)  Well, this year, they sent the application home for us to fill out and send back with our $4.50 dues for the year. I decided to be a bigger person than last year (LOL), and filled out the form.  On the bottom, it asked if you were a Grandparent and if you were a "Community Leader", both with a Y (yes) and an N (no) next to it.  That really pissed me off. Why? Because I feel that just because I am a housewife doesn't make me an unimportant person in society.  So, I circled Y and wrote "Aren't we ALL community leaders?" and sent it in.  I received my PTA card today, and on the envelope someone wrote "Yes, we ALL are community leaders!" with a giant smiley face.  I think someone got my point. :-)
     
    
</post>

<date>21,November,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      If Poke'mon are so smart, why aren't they making the humans battle?
     
    
</post>

<date>09,November,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Everyday I walk my kids to and from school and every day we are confronted by a gang of rude nasty little boys. They insist on playing football in the street as they are walking home. That would not normally bother me, except they end up in people's yards and trash their bushes, plants and trees. The other day, two of the boys were in my neighbour's bushes and the other one was up in the tree - so I stepped outside and asked them nicely to move along and play around their own home.  One of the boys (4th or 5th grader) turned to me and said "F*** off bitch, this is city property." I informed him that my neighbour's plants were private property and was laughed at and called more names. Today, as they threw the ball at my children, and me another little boy turned to me and told me his mother was going to kick my ass.  I don't know their names or where they live (other than somewhere down my street) and of course, they won't tell me. I'm waiting for the principal to call me back because I don't know what to do about this.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,November,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      The closest body of water to me is the St. Johns River. It flows (or meanders) from Central Florida north, through Jacksonville, then makes a turn right to flow into the Atlantic Ocean. I use it in spells at times because it flows "home" to me. It's a cleansing river.  I live a few blocks from it. I cannot see it from my home, but I can feel it. I believe I draw a lot of energy from water. I was once very far from it, in Nebraska, and I suffered an awful headache - that only abated when friends took me fishing on a manmade lake. It may not have been "natural" but it was of the Mother in my heart and for that bit of time, my head did not hurt. I've always felt bad because it was a beautiful state - but not a place I could live.  I posted this today because of something that happened this morning. It was a very stressful time - my daughter had some vaccinations and was very, very fussy, and I am worried about many family problems - the worst of which is that the doctor thinks my mother might have cancer and she had the tests this morning but won't find out the results until later. I was in my car and I started crying - the next thing I knew, I had ended up in my parked car, right next to the St. Johns River.  Because of the floodwall, I couldn't touch her (the river) but I felt the warm soothing waves wash over my soul and for a while, I felt at peace.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,November,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      My passenger side windshield wiper isn't working. So, this morning at work, Sharky takes a look at it and discovers it's a bad bushing that should only cost a couple of bucks at the most.  Guess what? It's a Saturn exclusive bushing. No one else makes or sells it.  Saturn won't sell just the gdmf bushing. They will only sell the ENTIRE ASSEMBLY which costs about $137.00.  Saturns are too new and in too good shape to be found in junkyards...  AARRGGHH!!!!!!!!!!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>17,December,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday, we went to my mom's to visit. (She's doing well btw.)  My Grandpa came over and told me there was a dresser he wanted to give to the boys and wanted me to help measure it. So I walked down to his place (just a couple of doors down).  As I climbed the steps to walk inside I had a terrible panic attack - my heart felt like it was being squeezed in a vice and I couldn't breathe. I realized that instant that I hadn't been inside their trailer since two weeks before Grandma died in January 2000.  It was a horrid feeling, of fear and dread, and terror, and anxiety, and sadness, and remorse, etc., etc.  I didn't feel my Grandma's spirit there - although I do feel it a lot at home and with my mom and Petunia.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      I’ve sent the men hunting …  ...for a Tree that is.  I thought it would be good father/sons bonding time to let them go out and hunt us down a Yule tree while I get the living room set up for it.  So why the heck am I on the computer? EEK - bad Topaz, bad. *smacks self on wrist*
     
    
</post>

<date>08,December,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I know I've mentioned before that we have never told my in-laws (Sharky's fundy xian dad and step mom) about our religious beliefs. When they came to visit, I did put some stuff away, turned some stuff around, but gee whiz, there's so much crap in my house (just ask Mori) that I forgot stuff everywhere...  Well, I set up that prayer circle and sent the link to them. I never heard back, so I didn't know if they got it or not.  Well, they told Sharky in chat last night that they had tried to sign up for Belief.net so they could add their prayers but weren't able to. (I had a lot of people tell me that they couldn't sign up.)  Then it hit me. ROFLMAO There's a lot of "stuff" there...  So, between my "Once upon a time, God was a Woman" bumper sticker, my pentacle bumper sticker, my pentacle around my neck that my daughter loves to whip out and chew on, the tarot cards I had laying out when they were visiting, my strange collection of suns/moons/stars that are everywhere, and now all my friends with stars on belief.net ...  Well, since they haven't said anything, I'm assuming that they are turning a blind eye to it all...
     
    
</post>

<date>07,December,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Today, as I was picking up my boys from school, Bear's 3rd grade teacher came outside to ask me a question. She told me that she wanted to know about how we celebrate holidays so she wouldn't offend us - she told me that Bear said that we celebrated Yule instead of Christmas.  I informed her that we celebrated Yule the same way most people celebrated Christmas, except we weren't Christians and we don't worship Jesus Christ. She then asked about things like using holiday stickers on his papers or attending the class holiday party and I told her that I had no problem with it at all. I also told her what I had told his 2nd grade teacher when asked about him singing Christmas Carols during a field trip to a nursing home - that he was his own person and was allowed to make his own decisions about things like that and it was fine with me whatever his choice may be.  After she had thanked me and left, I asked Bear what happened. (He didn't hear our conversation.) He told me that she asked ALL the class how they celebrated the holidays (not xmas, but HOLIDAYS). The first two hands that shot up were his and a little girl. (The little girl celebrates Eid (Id Al-Fitr), the day that follows the month of Ramadan - occurring this year on December 16th. It is a feast celebration, with houses decorated special and presents exchanged.)  Then Bear stood up and announced that his family celebrated Yule not Christmas and that it was the same as Christmas, except we didn't worship Jesus Christ (LOL almost word for word what I said!) but he worshipped his God and Goddess instead.  He then told me later that one of his friends asked "Do you worship our God?" (meaning the xian one) and Bear replied, (and I quote) "I said that I don't believe in your god, but I believe in my God and Goddess and my friend smiled and says that it's ok, he still likes me."  I am very happy with this school. My boys have been attending this school (a Gifted Magnet) for 4 years now - and I have only had a problem with one teacher. (That was Bear's first grade teacher who gave a candy bar to the kid who told her the true meaning of Easter. Bear didn't tell me about it until after the fact because he said that since I had just given birth to his sister, he didn't want to upset me.) His kindergarten AND second grade teacher have known about his/our religious beliefs and have always been very accepting of it. In fact, during Christmas of last year, his teacher went out of her way to change her card to me to read "Mother Nature" instead of God in the greeting.  My youngest son, Bug, is in 2nd grade and is a Leo (a born ham) but does not want any confrontation about religion. He was verbally attacked in kindergarten by a young girl threatening him with damnation and hellfire if he didn't accept Jesus into his life. When I informed the teacher, that was quickly brought to a halt and it never happened again. Unfortunately, since he has told me that he believes that his religion is a private thing and he doesn't want to speak of it to strangers. But that's fine too - it's his choice.  Bear, my Scorpio, is the one that will lead. He's told me time and time again that if someone doesn't want to be friends with him because of his beliefs, then he doesn't want to be friends with them. Pretty good for a 9 year old.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,December,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      I would like to thank everyone for his or her kind thoughts and prayers. I just spoke to my step dad and Mom is in the recovery room now. Her cancer was localized and they were able to remove all of it. She will be in a lot of pain, but she will be healthy once more.  See? There are such things as "Yule" miracles! :-)  BTW, I lit the Angel candle (the one Bug found at Kmart that is cradling the bird (Robin) to her breast) at 12 noon when she went into surgery, but I extinguished it at 3 pm because (1) it was out of wax and (2) I had to get the boys from school. Guess what? She was rolled out of surgery at 3 pm. I guess it was the perfect candle after all...
     
    
</post>

<date>13,January,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      OK, I'm bored. But I just saw something that made me laugh so hard, I have to share.  It's winter (yeah, right) and most of the leaves here are down - and my next-door neighbour did a hatchet job on a lot of plants in her back yard. So, for the first time since we moved in 4 years ago, I can see the garage apartment in the yard behind her house from my back steps.  So, I'm standing on the steps, marveling at the blue, blue sky, trying not to watch the dog do her thing, when a motion catches my eye.  I look over and see a woman standing on the porch of the aforementioned garage apartment. She's heavyset, strawberry blonde, in sort of a nurse’s shirt/jacket thing.  She lights up a cigarette. Not just any cigarette, but one of those super long ones in a cigarette holder! You know, like Cruella de Vil.  Then, she starts shaking an aerosol can, lifts up her shirt and starts spraying on underarm deodorant! (OK, I'm assuming it's deodorant - I hope it is at least. hehehe)  I had to cover my mouth to prevent myself from laughing out loud. I call Gabby and once we are inside, I just lost it.  Maybe you just had to be there, but between the long cig holder and the spray deodorant - it was way too comedic.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,January,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Yep, it happened again and I was infuriated. I've almost gotten over it now *gasp* maybe I'm starting to get used to it? :-P  I was a block from the school, pushing the stroller, when I stopped at a cross walk to let some cars pass so I can cross the street. There's a car behind me and as I cross, he pulls up behind me, rolls down his window and yells:  "You need to donate that hair. There are too many bald kids out there who need it."  I can't get confrontational - I've got my baby with me - so I just give one of those idiotic smiles and nod my head. (Well, thank Goddess it wasn't like last time where the pregnancy hormones made me burst into tears and run away...)  Where the hell do people get off saying things like that?  Day late and a dollar short, but I've finally come up with a comeback:  "Hey, got an extra kidney? I've heard there are a lot of people dying for one!"
     
    
</post>

<date>02,January,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       (From the old Lawrence Welk show)   Good night, Good night, until we meet again, Adios, Au Revoir, Auf Wiedersehen 'til then. And though it's always sweet sorrow to part You'll know you'll always remain in my heart.  Good night, sleep tight and pleasant dreams to you. Here's a wish and a prayer That every dream comes true. And now 'til we, meet again, Adios, Dobranoc, Auf Wiedersehen. Goodnight!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>08,February,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      OK, I know this one's a silly one, but it bugs the heck out of me!  On a list, a girl writes in and asks about something historical. Most people reply with decent sources (books, etc.).  THEN, one woman (a high priestess of course) writes in, says the complete opposite of everyone else and justifies it because "I WAS THERE! I lived in the 15th century and I KNOW how witches lived and everyone else is wrong because they weren't there!" and then went on to claim a whole bunch of other things too.  After having a good laugh over it, I looked back and realized that this wasn't the first time she's done it and it's not the first time that I've seen this happen on different lists with different "witches".  Now, I believe in reincarnation and I do believe that some people either retain some memory or can recall some things - but isn't it presumptuous and a wee bit crazy to be claiming to be an expert on things that you "experienced" in another lifetime?
     
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Grocery Shopping is a pain in the butt ... especially when you have a wedgie.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,April,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      I was about to fix lunch for Petunia and I when I had this urge to go look outside.  Why?  I don't know.  A little voice just said "Hey, go look outside!"  Well, I stood at my door and looked around, and spied a dove lying near my steps.  I put my shoes on and went outside.  It was a male mourning dove, in his full breeding glory - almost bright pink plumage around his neck and head and gorgeous iridescent patches on his cheeks.  There were no wounds anywhere and just a tiny trickle of red blood on his beak.  I didn't know what to do, so I went inside and got some newspaper and my trowel to pick him up with and wrapped him up carefully and said a prayer for him to go to the Goddess that she was waiting for him to join her.   I called Miss Ivy (next door) but she wasn't home, so I called Sharky.  He said I could either put him in the garbage can or keep him until he got home and he would bury him.  So, I found a brown paper grocery bag and put Little Dove wrapped up inside and put him safely on the porch.  I couldn't leave him there for the stray animals to get to even though I know its just nature.  I am so sad right now.  I know doves look alike, but I can't help thinking he was one of my "regular" buddies that visit us on our porch.  Why else would it look like he was trying to get up here?
     
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Bragging rights…  Yeah, yeah, bear with me...  BOTH of my boys had a piece of artwork chosen for the annual school Art Exhibit and Ice Cream Social tonight at 7 p.m.  I am so excited!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>22,April,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      IMO slumlords are worse than lawyers.  Gerry the pig owns the "house" next to us - the ones with the tiny kids who like to vandalize our home.  He first rented it to a bunch of sleaze bag women with kids and rotating boyfriends.  Then, for about 3 years the vandal kids have been living there.  Well, Sharky busted his butt on Saturday building a fence on the front property line - and used a string to mark off down the side.  We spent most of Saturday night and Sunday yelling at the little urchins to keep off the fence and the string.  At one point Sunday, to get their "revenge" they started bouncing the basketball off the side of our house and when Sharky told their parents, the kids started screaming that he was lying.  Lovely, huh?  Well today, Gabby started snarling and barking at something on the porch.  Well, it was Gerry the Slumlord.  No, he never bothered to knock, he decided to stand at my storm door and try to look in.  Pig.  He informed me that the string was a foot over onto his property line and wanted to know if we got the place surveyed.  I told him No, we had the fence marked off from corner to corner where the survey markers were.  He told me that we were wrong and he's going to get the place surveyed in the next two days to stop us from "stealing" his property.  Well, get this folks.  The property is no more than 4 foot wide at the most - from the wall of my house to their DRIVEWAY.  The total amount of property they own on our side is about 2 inches of dirt.  Yep, that's what he's afraid of us stealing.  Now I am scared that he's going to get some crooked schmuck of a surveyor to fix it so we end up losing our property.  We don't have the money to get it done ourselves.  :-(  He doesn't do a damn thing about the garbage all over their property, or their abused dog, or the fact that every plant/tree in their yard is almost dead or shit all over is destroyed.  I HATE SLUMLORDS.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      AAAAAAAARRRRRRRRRGGGGGGGGGGGGHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  *breathe breathe breathe*  Picked up the kids from school today. Halfway home, Bear turns to me and says "I found a note in my desk today and you are going to be upset." "What is it?" He replied, "I don't know, I was too upset to read it."  Here's the letter:  Dear ______, Please become a christan. All you have to do is say this prayer. Dear Jesus, Please come into my heart and live with me forever. Amen. And if you want to be forgiven Just say this. Dear Jesus, please forgive me for all my sins and make me clean. Amen Please become a christan. If you don't you will go to Hell but if you are a christan you will go to Heaven the paradice. from a classmate P.S don't ask everyon in the class. I don't want you to find out.  I called the teacher as soon as I got home.  She was upset and wanted me to send it in with Bear tomorrow morning.  No way.  I'm going down there in person and I am NOT letting her keep this letter.  She can make a copy of it.  I don' t want this to "disappear".   (BTW, I know for a fact that Bear didn't do this himself because, frankly, his handwriting stinks and this child's writing is almost perfect for a 3rd grader.)
     
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Bug came home today with a music sheet - one-line songs with xylophone numbers to play. One of the songs was "Jesus Loves Me." (Yes, I have a call into the principal's office about it, but I won't hear from her until tomorrow.)  We sat down and had a heart to heart talk.  While Bear says he doesn't care if his friends know about his religion, Bug told me when people ask he just ignores them.  When I asked why, he told me that he's afraid they would hate him. So he only tells people he knows can keep a secret.  Goddess I feel like crap right now.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,April,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi, my name is Topaz and my mother is an eBay addict - and she's NOT even on the 'NET!!!  Well, I told my mom that we've been going to the flea market to buy veggies (they're cheaper and fresher than the store) every Sunday.  She told me to keep my eyes open for a little blue Pyrex bowl.  She had a mixing/nesting set that she bought in 1962 and years ago, broke the smallest one.  They are hard to find and antique dealers want way too much money for a complete set - which she doesn't want, she just wants the missing bowl.  So, I said, "Hey, I'll look on eBay."  In about 20 seconds I found one dirt-cheap and made a bid.  She got so excited, she wanted me to check on a missing glass.  Found it.  Then on some perfume bottles that she was missing one of.  Found it.  And more.  And more.  And ...  Finally I had to scream "STOP! Mom, let's just do this one at a time, ok?  Let's get the bowl first and then LATER we'll bid on the others."  For the first time ever, THANK GODDESS my mom doesn't have Internet connection or she would have just blown a wad of money...  hehehe
     
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Corny Confession Time:  This coming weekend will be the third straight weekend off that Sharky has had since starting his new job.  Can you believe that I still get teary when I think about it?  *sniff*  Must be hormones...
     
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Obscenity on my computer?   Yeah, I fell for it.  I should have known better.  I went to http://www.contentwatch.com/ and took their free audit.  Guess what? 1,035 files containing "questionable content" ALL in two sections of my computer.  Which ones you ask?  Well, obviously my Grimoire wears a big red flag - and so does my Fashion Doll folder.  Book of Shadows and Barbie - signs of evilness, lewd and lasciviousness behavior, and lack of morals.  I'm a bad, bad girl.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      We didn't think we were going to be able to send the boys to Art Camp at their school this summer (like last year) but my mom helped us out so we could send them.  Listen to this:  Back to the Future - Travel through time to experience Art of the different Eras.      * Sculpt like the Ancient Greeks     * Create Abstract Art from the Modern Era     * Weave a Basket like the Colonials     * Tile like the Romans     * Make Paper like the Ancient Egyptians     * Create Tessellation Art from the year 2020     * And More!  Gee, don't you wish you could go?  I do!  LOL
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night, Sharky and I watched the movie K-PAX with Kevin Spacey (good movie, btw).  We were all snuggled up on the couch with Cosmo on my lap with the lights out.  Well, not to give out any spoilers in case you haven't seen the movie yet, but there's a part where a bunch of people in a mental hospital all jump up and start yelling.  Just at that moment in the movie, I noticed out of the corner of my eye something flicker.  Then hop.  Then jump.  Coming ever closer to me.  It then leaped from the floor onto Cosmo who squealed and ran.  Then it jumped on me and I jumped up and started yelling.  Then Sharky jumped up and started yelling.  It was a palmetto bug - about 3 inches long with wings - hence, the 'jumping'.  Well, after Sharky killed it, we had to pause the movie because we realized at that moment that the 2 of us were yelling and jumping just like the people in the movie and we just couldn't stop laughing.  A bizarre moment, to say the least.  :-)
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Have you ever rain danced?  You know, danced/charmed for rain?  We need rain here in NE Florida very bad.  Some areas are already on a burn advisory.  A few days ago, Sharky and I were discussing how bad we need the rain and he asked me if I was going to do a rain dance.  I told him that the only way I'd do it is if I lay on the floor naked (representing Mother Earth) and he danced over me naked (representing the Thunder God) and sprinkled me with Brita water.  He thought I was serious.  *snort* We didn't do it.  So, today the sky got grey and I was excited - RAIN!  It started at 2:50 p.m. and sprinkled lightly until 3:10.  Exactly as I left the house, walked up the road, got the boys and walked home - ending as we walked up to the porch and the front door.  Hardly any at all.  We didn't even get wet - just really, really damp.  Petunia was royally p'od by it all.  She loves the rain.  She sat up in her stroller, head back, arms outstretched crying "More Rain sky!  More Rain!!!"
     
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      WASABI  !!!  Pay no attention to me, I just LOVE saying that word...
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      No, this isn't really a rant.  My stomach is aching and rumbly (not in a good way) because in less than 30 minutes, the 3 kiddos and me are walking back up to school for its Annual Pig Roast.  No, no actual oinkers will be there.  The school was built in 1911 and one of the oldest traditions was to have a giant pig skewered over a bbq as a fundraiser.  Well, you don't do things like that anymore, so a local chef volunteers to roast pork and they make big bbq pig sandwiches instead.  I'm not complaining about the food because it's always been good.  It's the fact that Sharky has a meeting tonight and can't go with us.  Not a big deal, right?   *sigh*  I'm so freaking lonely.  I don't know any of the freaking parents up there to say any more than "Hi, how are you?"  And most just nod their heads and keep walking.  OK, I'm fat, but I don't think I'm ugly, and I do think I'm rather intelligent, but I am quiet.  I really think it all comes down to is the fact that most of the other parents do not live there - they all live in wealthier neighbourhoods and their kids won our school from the magnet lotto.  And they all know I live here, just a few blocks away.   They all get together at these things in their little cliques and giggle and laugh and I swear it's like a HS event sometimes.  Who's more childish - the elementary kid or the parent?  But the boys want to go, they always enjoy functions like this.  So, I'm going to take a deep breath and smile and say hi and try to keep my chin up and not let them know it bothers me. 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Dinner with Bear  This evening was just me and Bear. Petunia was asleep in bed, Bug's at his Grandma's and Sharky had run over to a friend's house to help him with a computer problem.  I was fixing Bear and I a burrito to snack on during a PBS documentary on Tigers. He kept running into the kitchen to update me on what was going on.  Then, he came in to tell me that two tigers were mating. How did he know? They were biting each other on the neck. So, I told him, you know that's part of mating - but they don't have babies that way, right?  "Of course Mom," he said, "I know that." "Well," says I, "how do they mate?"  "I have no idea."  "Bear? They mate like humans."  "I didn't know that."  *lightbulb* "Bear, do you know how humans have babies?" "Well Mom, I know it has something to do with sperm and eggs..."  "Would you like me to explain it to you?" I asked.  "No, not right now."  "Why not?"  "Because mating isn't appropriate dinner conversation." he said in all seriousness.  "How about after dinner?"  "Sure Mom, that sounds great."  Hmmm, is this my son or what? ROFLMAO!
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Memories of a Waterfall  I need to get this out now, before I forget - so please, forgive me if this is disjointed.  I believe in reincarnation and I have had glimpses of my past lives - nothing ever clear enough to accurately pin down, but enough to convince me.  Sometimes they are actual memories - sometimes they are just feelings, like deja vu - and sometimes they are just sensed.  Today was a definite sense - a sensation if you will.  Petunia was in bed, Bear, Bug, Cosmo, and Gabby cuddled on the couch watching tv.  Sharky was finalizing my computer and I decided to take a shower.  Unfortunately, even though it was 8:00 p.m., the neighbours were outside playing basketball - my bathroom window is IN the shower so I could hear everything.  :-(   So, to remedy it, Sharky brought me my portable cd player and a candle and I turned the lights off and got in the shower, listening to one of my favourite cds, The Renaissance Album (1998, Windam Hill).  I turned it up loud to drown out the game - and it worked.  The fading light outside and the flickering candle shining through the clear & ferned shower curtain helped me to just 'fade out' so to speak.  Now, I love hot water showers, the hotter the better - and I lucked out this time and our water heater was working it's best for once.  I washed my hair, conditioned, washed myself and then started rinsing my hair.  I really wasn't thinking of anything other than just enjoying the hot, hot water.  After the conditioner was rinsed out I decided to turn the cold water on to give my hair a final rinse.  I turned the cold all the way on, and the hot off and felt the gradual turn from hot to warm to cold to ice.  As the icy water started on the top of my head, running through my hair, down my back, and so forth, I suddenly was hit with a memory of a memory.  When I was 17, I spent a few weeks with my grandmother's sister (great-aunt) in Ipswich, MA.  One weekend, my aunt (mom's sister) had her girlfriend pick me up and bring me to stay with her in her home in New Hampshire.   Auntie let me have the run of her property and told me I could go to the creek as long as I was careful.  So, the next morning, I got up early and went to it (a long hike) to sit on the rocks and just be with nature.  I knew it was the last time I'd have a chance to do that since in a few months I was going to bootcamp.  So, I hiked across the pasture, evading the goats who were determined to butt me (pun intended), the geese who I feared, and the chickens who ran everywhere.  I knew if I got to the trees and just walked straight, I'd find the creek - and I did.  The creek ran gently downhill and rippled and rumbled and flowed and dripped in places.  The rocks in the bed were every shade of brown imaginable - some teeny fishies scattered, but nothing bigger than my pinky.  The water was as clear as glass, tasted like crystal, and sparkled like diamonds.  As I was walking along, I slipped a couple of times, getting my shoes and calves wet.  This was July, but the water felt like ice and the air wasn't much warmer.  All of a sudden, I had this tremendous urge to completely submerge myself in this flowing, liquid ice.  I walked downstream until I found this large rock that was nestled against larger ones, forming a small waterfall.  I sat down, dug my heels into the gravel and leaned back so the water would run around my head and over me.  As soon as I leaned back, I had a flash of "this is wrong, I should be standing".  I then remembered standing on a rock feeling the most icy water cascading on me and over me.  I was standing nude, feeling the water and the almost ice crystals in it, biting and stinging - not hurting - a wonderful clean, cleansing feeling - almost like ice cold light pouring over me.  I remember feeling that in my hair and ears and eyes, numbing me, but not burning, and making me feel so alive from the inside out and back again.  Then, I came to, sitting back on the rocks, in a daze, wondering where I was, how did I get there in my memory, how to get back to that waterfall and then, how to explain to my auntie why I was all of a sudden chilled to the bone and shivering like crazy.  I climbed out of the water and staggered back.  Auntie obviously knew something because the old griffin-footed cast-iron tub was already full of water and bubbles to warm me back up.  Strangely, I kept the memory of enjoying the icy creek, but the waterfall memory escaped me until this very evening in the shower when I felt it once again.  I have had many nice hot showers followed by cold ones over the years, but this is the first time I've recalled those two moments.  I don't know where or when that waterfall memory occurred, but I do know for a fact that it wasn't this lifetime.  It was so clear and sharp, that standing in my tiny tub feeling those icy water droplets come down made me feel as if I could put my hands out and touch that other place and time, like only if I could step forward, I could grasp it in my hands and be there once again.  And then, a little voice: "Good night Mommy."  And, BAM, I was back in my shower.  I said goodnight back, turned the water off and called for my bathrobe.  I had to write this and share it with you all - why?  I don't know, but the strong urge is there....
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      My ears, Yep, I've got two.  hehehe  I had my ears pierced the first time when I was eleven and the second time when I was 16.  Later on, when I was about 23, in a creative right of passage for myself, I got a 3rd hole pierced in my left ear.  Because of the way my ears are constructed, it nicked the cartilage and took over 6 months to heal.  When I had Bear, and then Bug, I had to take out my earrings in the hospital and then put them back in when I got home - didn't have a problem.  But, when I had Petunia, it was almost a month before I put my earrings back in - guess what?  My third hole had closed up and I couldn't put one in.  Then, I lost an earring in hole #2 and so I took those out and they started to close.  For Valentine's Day, Sharky bought me a 24k earring set of three graduated hoops for my ears.   The first ones went in fine.  The second ones took a bit of forcing.  OUCH!  No go for the third one.  :-(  Well, guess what?  Sharky's Father's Day present to me was to get my ears pierced!  LOL  The left was re-pierced and the right pierced for the first time.  OUCH!  hehehe  I feel so silly.  Must be from all those holes in my head.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Potty Training has Commenced...   And wow, is it hard. LOL  We bought a potty and started Petunia on it on June 9th. Here we are, 10 days later and there is no improvement.  Every day, we wake her up, strip her, and put her on the pot. The rest of the day is spent taking her in there every hour. Yes, whoever takes her in there (me or Sharky) goes with her.   Nothing. Not a drip, not a dribble. And yet, she knows when her diaper (or pull-up) is wet and tells us. She just hasn't figured out that she needs to tell us BEFORE she goes.  *huge sigh* It was so easy with the boys...
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Urchin #2 just came over telling me that my sons stole his ball and took it into our yard - which is a blatant lie since the intense heat and my sons' allergies have kept them inside this summer.  I told him that we did NOT steal his ball and if he had a problem, he was to have his parents talk to me.  So, what happens?  Mr. Nasty comes over and tells me that he just wanted to retrieve the ball from our yard since we do not allow them to climb our fence.  I told him that Urchin #2 said we stole it and he of course denied his "son" saying that.  I said "No problem, always ask first since our dog bites."  He said thanks and left.  What upsets and scares me is that when Mr. Nasty came over, he didn't knock - my dog's barking is what alerted me.  He tried to OPEN the screen door!  What kind of person would just walk into someone else's house unannounced?  Especially since they cannot stand us?  Our glass storm door has darkish glass, but one can tell the cream-coloured door behind it is open or closed - even if they cannot really see into the house.  Private - 4:27 PM
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      A Bathing Suit Funny  We got up early this morning to get packages ready for my trip to the Post Office - I then checked and discovered *ack* the PO doesn't open until 9!   Well, Sharky, my hubby, decided to take one of the boys with him to Wal-Mart to get some CD sleeves to mail to a friend of his.  As he was leaving, he asked me if I needed anything from the store.   Since I'm hosting the Barbie club meeting today and I would like to have another doll in a bathing suit for display.  So, I told him, if he saw a nice one, to pick up a bathing suit for me.   He stopped and gave me this look of almost-horror and sort of stuttered a bit.  I asked him what the matter was (he's never had a problem buying a doll before and has bought me lots of dolls, outfits and other similar things in the past).  He blushed and said "I don't know what size you wear."  Silly me forgot to tell him that I was talking about a BARBIE bathing suit, not a human one!  hehehe  You know how us old married folk get, I just assumed he knew what I was talking about.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Nine days ago, Sharky and the boys were in the back yard. The boys got into a weed fight and both broke out into a rash. Bug's rash was gone in 2 days. Bear STILL has his.  Oatmeal baths everyday, calamine lotion, Gold Bond lotion, Benadryl - nothing...  BUT, on Saturday - our insurance information arrived at last! hurrah!  So, first thing tomorrow morning, we've got an appointment with the doctor.  Of course, I HATE having our first appointment a sick one, instead of a healthy "get to know you" kind, but, oh well...
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      My Naughty Mommy  My maternal uncle's wife has been spamming me lately with religious email. I've just deleted them.  Well, I finally got sick of seeing them, so I told my mom who informed me that Auntie Pam has become a Pentacostal holy roller type. OMGs. I didn't see that coming. Mom said it's been gradual and she and sDad have been watching the holy roller rolling down hill. hehehe  So, Mom told me to write her and tell her NOT to send me any more. I told Mom that I have been wanting to but haven't wanted to start any family hoopla. (My maternal family is SO freaking blind to my religious choice - only Mom and sDad have 'recognized' it.)  Mom told me that I shouldn't worry about that, I should stand up for my rights. (Yes, then I broke it to her that I was the Acting President for the NEFlorida Pagan Alliance. ROFL)  I told her I was worried about Grandpa who will be 92 in December.  She told me "Tough Cookies" and that Grandpa doesn't believe in anything and neither did her sister or my Uncle K who is married to Auntie Pam.  She kept pushing and pushing, so I wrote the most polite note I could (and no, I didn't use any of the words she suggested I use LOL):  Dear Pam,  I would like to thank you for thinking of me enough to send emails. But to be honest, since I am not Christian, I am not interested in the Christian emails that you have been sending. Please don't think I am offended, but rhetoric such as this is wasted on me.  I would love to hear how everyone is doing - and cannot wait to see you all again. (The kids) send hugs and kisses.  Love, K
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Mr. and Mrs. Nasty got into an argument this morning in their driveway over who gets to use their car early this morning - really early - 2:30 a.m. to be exact.  Yes, they were arguing loudly - yelling at some points - right outside my bedroom window.  Wasn't that nice of them?  Private - 6:21 AM
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Today, around 3:00 p.m., we arrived home from the grocery store in a rainstorm.  As my boys got the groceries out of the trunk and carried them to the porch, I got my baby out of her car seat.  The screaming from the Nastys' front yard was deafening - even above the pouring rain, thunder and lightning.  Nasty Boyfriend was on their porch with assorted children while his friend stood in the rain.  Both were screaming at each other.  All I could discern between the "Fuck You Nigga" and "I'll kill you Nigga" was something about stealing money and missing drugs.  The friend eventually walked away still yelling that he was going to kill him.  I rushed the kids into the house as fast as I could and got the groceries in.  Luckily the storm got worse and they were driven inside.  About an hour and a half later, I looked outside and saw Big and Little Urchin picking garbage that had washed down the street in the gutter streams and flinging it at their "friends".  Private - 5:56 PM 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      8 July 02 0757, Just spoke of Officer Carr at the Cedar Hills Police Substation.  She said that there is no time limit for residences in regards to noise disturbances.  It can be 9 am or 9 pm and if the noise outside is disturbing you in your home you can lodge a complaint with the police. 	 Private - 7:56 AM   Put my daughter to bed last night around 8:30 and she couldn't sleep.  Why?  Because of the basketball game in the Nastys' driveway which is next to her bedroom window.  She was up until around 11 before she could fall asleep.  Sharky and I went to bed soon after her and laid there wide awake as they had their very noisy party.  We didn't fall asleep until around 1:30 a.m. this morning.  I could hear snippets of their conversation as they walked around their driveway - coming close to our bedroom window.  Mrs. Nasty, obviously for our benefit, gave a HUGE speech to her friends about "their GOD given right to do whatever they want to do whenever they want to do it and GOD will protect them and allow them to do whatever they want whenever they want" yada yada yada.  These people are evil.  Seriously.  They were relatively quiet on Friday and Saturday nights, but had to throw a wild party on Sunday night?  Believe me, this was NO bible study.  How can they afford that house?  I know they rent it - where does the money come from?  She doesn't work.  He doesn't have a job.  The boyfriend lazes around all day and smokes pot.  But they own 3 cars, a big screen rental tv, satellite cable for their tv, etc.  They are either on public assistance or deal drugs - or both.  All I know is that my husband busts his ass to keep me and our children fed, clothed, and housed and we don't have anything like they do.  We can't afford 3 cars and rental furniture/appliances and cable - not to mention throwing parties for our friends every week.  	 Private - 7:31 AM 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Our New Car! Yes, we have a brand new car! OK, brand new to us.  Wait, I can hear many of you asking - how can you afford a new car? Well, we can't. BUT, it was a horrid strain being a one car family when Sharky works on the other side of town. We were always worried about what would happen if I needed it and he had it. I couldn't go to the store until he got home - sometimes running out late at night or super early in the morning (before 6:30 am). I was even caught once walking the kids home in a sudden downpour that turned into mini-flash-flood a few blocks away earlier this year.  Well, Sharky worked with a guy who was buying a new/used truck. He wanted $800 for his old one and offered it to us. Sharky told him, thanks for thinking of us, but no thanks - we don't have the cash. The guy lowered it a few weeks later to $500. Again, thanks/no thanks - we'd have to make payments, don't have that kind of cash.  Well, Friday, Sharky called me and told me to have the kids ready at 6:00 p.m. because he had to pick us up and go back to work - he just bought a truck. Yeah, you know me - dollar signs flying away in my head and stomach at that moment and yes, a brief moment of panic.  When we got to work, he told me the selling price. $100. Yep, no lie. Now, this is no new truck. This isn't even a used truck. It's a beat up 1984 Dodge Ram Pickup (full sized monster), in need of a power steering pump (about $40), painted primer black - an ugly bitch of a truck according to my dearest hubby.  The kids were strangely horrified by it. Bear: "Look, you can see through the bottom!" (a few rust holes) Bug: "I'm afraid to wash it, it might fall apart!" (No, not kidding, he really said that.)  We can afford tags/insurance/etc., because I've got one payment left on my car. (Pray to Goddess that she doesn't take a dump - I can't lose MY car...)  BUT, the most important thing, THE TRUCK RUNS GREAT.  *happy not-nekkid-wearing-muumuu pagan dance*  On a side note, a friend of ours who lives a few blocks away saw the truck on Saturday and offered Sharky $500 cash NOW for it and he turned it down. Then, he raised it to $700, and we turned it down. Why? Because you can't get a piece of shit that RUNS around here for less than $1000. Hard to believe, but true - in a land full of cars, they don't run cheap. *sigh*
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Nasty Boyfriend and friends sat on their front porch today, smoking pot.  Lovely.  I'm afraid to call the police.  Why?  Because I am afraid that they will retaliate.  Other neighbours are frightened of them - if they weren't, they'd be complaining too.  I want them to move away.  I want them to find a place they like better and want to leave and forget all about us and NOT encourage their friends to rent the house... 	 Private - 1:35 PM 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I guess I slept ok, except for the nightmares, which were to be expected.  We went to bed after 11 and of course, as soon as all our lights were out and our heads hit the pillow, the fireworks started again.  *sigh*  It quieted down a little after midnight - and I was awoken at 4:30 by someone setting them off AGAIN in front of the Nastys' house.  Give me a break!  What a bunch of freaks!  Private - 8:03 AM 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      No longer a virgin...  Yep folks, you've read it correctly.  I am no longer a virgin - a Starbuck's virgin that is.  Our coffee pot committed suicide last year. I stopped drinking coffee and Sharky switched to instant. We refuse to buy a new coffee maker until we can get the one we want (a mount under-the-counter model).  Well, I went into the new Publix this morning to take advantage of some great food sales and spied someone walking around with a Starbucks coffee cup - the coffee shop across the lot was open!  After I loaded the groceries into my car, I walked over and bought Sharky a Grande Caramel Machiatto. OMGs was it delicious and EXPENSIVE! *swoons*  But, hey - it's a holiday, right? *wink*
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, the time has come now for my most hated night of the year - 4th of July - where every Tom, Dick and Jethro come out of the closet to celebrate the birth of their nation by blowing up a small piece of it.  Thank Goddess it rained.  In fact, it soaked us pretty good.  It's now quarter after 8 and the popping of firecrackers and small caliber pistors has resumed again.  At least everything should be wet enough to prevent fires.  *fingers crossed*  Will we get any sleep?  We'll find out in a bit.  It wouldn't be so bad except Sharky has to work in the morning...  Private - 8:16 PM   Stayed up a bit late last night, hoping the idiots would get bored with shooting off the firecrackers.  When it appeared to have ended, we got into bed and soon dozed off.  *BOOM*  As soon as our heads hit the pillow we jumped up to the sound of cheap firecrackers going off in front of our house.  Luckily, they must have ran out because after 20 minutes or so, they stopped and went inside.  *sigh*  I hope tonight is quiet...  Private - 11:01 AM 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      It's 9:12 pm and I'm dreading this evening.  You know, fireworks, and other things.  There has been a child blowing a whistle for almost 2 hours straight now.  I hope they run out of air before bedtime - or at least get bored with it.  *sigh*  Private - 9:10 PM   Well, it was relatively quiet last night.  I heard some screaming and yelling over at the Nasty's house, but it wasn't enough to keep me awake.  Yesterday, though, was a strange occurrance.  Two men were riding bikes -  one was in the street, riding in circles, the other was riding on the sidewalk with a large television on his handlebars.   I don't know what happened, but Mr. Nasty flies out of his house, yelling and screaming at TV guy, threatening to "beat his ass".  Lovely, huh?   The two bike guys slowly rode off, laughing, and yelling back invitations for Mr. Nasty to come beat their ass.  Private - 10:31 AM 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Good Morning!  Or I hope it was good for you.  Sharky and I slept awful.  Went to bed at 9:00 pm last night to the sounds of our neighbours having a 'get-together' in their front yard and driveway.  There were many kids playing basketball in their driveway which borders my home's bedrooms.  Well, I tried to tune them out and as soon as I started to get sleepy, a whole bunch of firecrackers went off in the street in front.  Mrs. Nasty (the mother) started screaming "Call 911, Call 911".  So, I got up and told Sharky.  He went outside and they were just sitting on their stoop and dancing in the street (no music).  He came back in and we went to bed.  Just started to doze off again when, a toddler shrieked "AAAAEEEEEIIIIIIIII" right under our bedroom window.  So, Sharky got up, put his bathrobe on, and went outside.  It was 10:30 p.m.  He tried the nice approach.  "Could you please keep it down so we can sleep?"   Didn't work.  Mr. Nasty started screaming that he wasn't going to keep his kids locked away in the house just so we can sleep.  He doesn't give a shit about us, his kids can do whatever they want to.  He was having a family gathering and was sick and tired of Sharky coming out and bitching at him about every thing.  If they wanted to play basketball in the middle of the night they could.  *sigh*  Then, as usual, Mrs. Nasty pushed him away and started being all nicey-nicey that there was nothing to worry about, she apologized and promised to keep them away from our bedroom.  Then there was a comment that I couldn't hear and I heard Sharky say, "Keep Your God out of this" and all hell broke loose with Mrs. Nasty, in a preacher's voice, yelling things like "It's OUR God and if you don't have GOD and JESUS you don't have LOVE and without GOD and JESUS'S LOVE you don't have NOTHING..."   On and on and on, so Sharky came inside.  They went inside too but the damage to our sleep was done.  ***  So, to bring you up to date, since I've just started this weblog:  We are home-owners, they are renters - our homes are almost identical, which means they have 3 bedrooms and 1 bath just like ours.  In their home is supposedly a married couple, Mr. & Mrs. Nasty, their boyfriend, their 2 elementary school age kids (Lil Urchin and Big Urchin), various friends who come, live a while, and go and a neglected dog who howls night and day because it's hungry and wants to be loved.  They smoke pot - on their porch, in their cars in the driveway, and in their house with their children inside.  Two weeks ago, I was walking past and they opened a door - looked like something out of Cheech & Chong - a giant cloud of pot smoke with a toddler walking in the middle of it.  Very sad.  The Two Urchins are abused, neglected, liars, bullies and vandals.  They've broken our waterpipe, our fence, tried to break our a/c unit by climbing over our fence and jumping up and down on it.  They've killed all but one of my rosebushes.   Sharky had to get at them this weekend because one of the family friends was screaming and taunting our dog when Gabby went out to go to the bathroom.  It was the first time we've ever seen our dog go ballistic like that.  It took everything Sharky had to hang on to her and keep her from going over the fence after the kid.  A few months ago, Mr. Nasty made veiled comments regarding their moving soon.  No sign of it.  I cannot wait for them to leave.  	 Private - 8:40 AM 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      My husband called a little while ago to tell me to clean the area in front of my antique desk. We've been sorting clothes there to figure out what fits, what doesn't, what goes to Goodwill, etc.  When I asked why, he told me he's got a new desk that came from his boss's office.  Me: "What are we going to do with it?" Sharky: "I don't know."  "Can I put Barbies on it?" "What?" "Can I put Barbies on it?" "What?" "You know, dolls. Scenes. Clothes. Dolls." "Uh, can we talk about this later?" "No. Can I put Barbies on it?" "Alright, if you insist. You can put Barbies on it." "OK, I'll clean up the area."  *snicker* Yeah. Just let him try to explain that conversation to the guys at work. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      There's a note on the Nasty's door from their landlord telling them that if they continue moving, he will sue them for August's rent.   I'm thinking about calling him and telling him that they aren't sleeping there, but their friends are still...
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      OMGs, they are STILL moving.  Their house is the same size as ours, 3 bd and 1 br.  How in the world can they have that much stuff?  They moved stuff again last night and they are here now, putting MORE bags and lamps, etc. into their car.  That house must be like a clown car, small on the outside, able to fit tons on the inside.  I walked past them as I was coming home from taking my kids to school and when Mrs. Nasty looked at me, I smiled and said "Hi".  She sort of smiled back, but her husband turned away and muttered something I couldn't understand.  Oh well... 	 Private - 8:11 AM
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Can you believe they are STILL moving?  On Saturday, they tossed a couch out and a particle board shelf and bags of garbage and other things I can't identify and finally took their basketball hoop down.  They were back there on Sunday moving more things.  They kept me up Saturday night and last night - no talking this time but those moving noises of pulling, pushing, dragging, dropping of unknown objects.  This morning, walking past their house taking my kids to school, I noticed that their front door was open.  When I came back, it still was - and both of their boyfriends walked out getting dressed.  Obviously there is still something to guard there if they are having people sleep over.  Private - 9:42 AM
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      They still are not completely moved but are not living there - and yet they show up every night around midnight to remove more things.  The basketball hoop and porch furniture are still around.  Yesterday, someone broke into the house.  I don't know who did, but they took the front screen down and jimmied open the front window and didn't replace the screen when they left.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Praise be - I think my dreams are coming true.  The beds left the house next door today.  We saw car after car full of clothes leave this afternoon and groceries left early this morning.  The only thing we are concerned about is possible retaliation from them or their friends.  We have absolutely nothing to do with their moving, but who knows what those wackos think?  Private - 10:51 PM 	  I went to bed last night at 10:30 and stayed awake until 3:00 a.m. thanks to the Nastys.  They were moving - I think.  Hard to tell from the noise.  They had a large vehicle with a sliding door (a van perhaps) that kept slamming back and forth outside my window.  Mr. & Mrs. Nasty kept getting into arguments that progressively got louder as the night (or early morning) went on.  Their children, the Urchins, were outside my bedroom window and in my front yard blowing whistles and fighting the whole time.  Why in the world were they moving in the middle of the night?  To skip out on their lease perhaps?  They still aren't done moving - their most precious possession, the basketball hoop stand - is still in the driveway.  At least they took their dog.  *sigh*  Private - 8:02 AM 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Are they moving?  Yesterday we saw the Nasty family loading boxes up in their cars, over and over.  Then, finally, a couch.  The littlest Urchin (around 7 yo) ran loose, all alone, with a giant set of keys.   There's still a car in the driveway, garbage and toys in the driveway and back yard and porch furniture.  Can TPTB have heard our prayers?  Private - 2:43 PM 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      This morning, while walking the boys to school, I heard a man's voice coming from a house that's vacant and for rent.  I looked over and saw the front door cracked and a hand.  We kept on walking.  On the way back, I casually glanced open, the front window's curtains were up and there was a crumpled beercan on the sill.  The house didn't have any furniture in it, but tied to the back porch was a bicycle that I recognized as belonging to a homeless (?) guy whom I've seen crashing at vacant houses in the past.  So, when I got home, I looked up the house on the Property Appraiser's site on the 'net and found out who owned it.  I tried to find her phone number but couldn't, so I called the police.  The woman who took my call didn't seem to take me too seriously.  I mean I didn't see the guy, just his hands and told her I thought he was black but wasn't sure when she asked what colour he was but I did make sure to tell her that his hands could have been black because he might have been wearing gloves.  So, I went back on the net and finally found the owner's phone number and left her a message.  She called back almost immediately and was shocked to find out that someone broke into her rental house.  I advised her to check it out asap because I wasn't sure if the cops were actually going to check it out or not.  About 30 minutes later, the police called me to tell me that they were there at the house and the man they apprehended said he was the owner!  I told the cop that the man was lying.  The cop burst into laughter.  ???  So I gave him the name of the owner and her phone number and told him that I found the information on the Property Appraiser's site.  Twenty minutes later, the owner called back and thanked and thanked and thanked me.  The man was arrested for breaking and entering AND it turns out, he's wanted by the police for previous breaking and enterings!   So, the lesson of the day is, sometimes being a nosy bitch pays off.  ROFLMAO
     
    
</post>

<date>06,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      07/25/02 289 08/01/02 275 08/08/02 270 08/15/02 264 08/22/02 261 08/29/02 253 09/05/02 253 09/12/02 248 09/19/02 243 09/26/02 241 10/03/02 245 10/10/02 239 10/17/02 239 10/24/02 239 10/31/02 237 11/07/02 235 11/14/02 233 11/21/02 232 11/28/02 235 12/05/02 234
     
    
</post>

<date>17,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm tired.  I just made my husband a pickled bologna sandwich for work.  LOL  The stupid things look like hotdogs on steriods so I put it in a hotdog bun with mustard.  Let's see if he notices...  *snort*
     
    
</post>

<date>28,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Binky free?  Petunia has slept two whole nights on her own, without the binky. (It's lost somewhere in her room and we haven't found it.) She hasn't asked for it and we haven't said it's name.  *fingers crossed*
     
    
</post>

<date>08,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      It's been showering here off and on all day - cold and relatively dreary.  The only real sign of life are the magenta seeds blossoming on my maples, waiting to take flight upon their maturity.   I have a very large tree in my back yard that sheds leave 365 days a year and because of the weather, we've neglected raking the leaves up, so they are about 6 inches deep.  It's hard to justify raking them anyhow because our yard was so neglected by previous owners over the years that any bit of fertilizer helps.  *smile*   The laundry room faces the tree and I often look out as I'm hanging or folding laundry at the birds and squirrels who pass by.  All of a sudden, out of the corner of my eye, I spied a movement.  I turned to look out the window and noticed that the fallen leaves were jumping, sailing and spinning through the air up from the ground.  I rubbed my eyes and looked again.  What in the world could it be?   I carefully moved the hanging clothes and stepped closer.  There in my back yard were 30 - 40 robins on the ground, picking up the leaves and flinging them into the air over and over again until they uncovered a bare spot of earth.  Then they would scratch a bit and pull out something wriggling and eat it.  There were large robins and small ones.  Fat ones and skinny ones.  All flinging leaves in a manic dance of dinner.   I softly called my husband and then my children, one at a time, to come to the window and witness this hilarious, yet solemn all-you-can-eat buffet.  I wished I could have grabbed a video camera and caught it on tape, but I didn't dare open the back door and interrupt their mealtime.   We weren't the only audience they had.  The grackles were swooping down trying to join them, but the frenzy was too much for them to handle.  The blue jays racously cawed over head, in joy and jealousy of the bounty below.  The robins ignored the other birds, continuing to fling, hop, toss, and eat to their hearts content.   My heart soars - spring has sprung in Jacksonville Florida. 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      How big of a reader are you?  I used to read everything and anything I got my hands on.  Even after kids and the internet, I still found time to read.  But now, my reading is limited to on the toilet (sorry!), waiting in the car, etc.  I realized this the other day and looked to see the reason why my reading has slacked off so much.  Hmm, I think it's Petunia.  Every waking moment with her I'm doing something.  Playing, housework, reading to HER, etc.  I've tried to read, but I can't concentrate if I have to watch her.  I tried reading at night after she went to bed and I can sometimes.  But it's really the only time I have alone with my husband and sometimes we just like to sit and talk.  Or even just sit and be quiet.  (Although we do have fun sitting in the same room messaging each other.  It's kinda warped but fun.  *giggle*)
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday, as Bug and I were waiting for Rene to open up the Stray Cat house for us, another woman showed up with towel in her arms wrapped around a kitten that can fit in your hand.  Saturday night, as she was eating dinner, her Corgis out back started barking and howling.  She went outside to investigate and found, under her porch, a Manx kitten.  She fed him sugar water and bathed him (he was covered in fleas) and brought him to the SCH first thing in the morning.  (She couldn't keep him because she's a nurse on a 12 hour schedule.)  The odd thing is, she's been catching a litter of Manx kittens and bringing them into the SCH and has been trying to catch the mother.  This kitten is about 2 months younger than the other ones, so isn't from the same litter.  The kitten was all alone under the porch and she has no idea how he got there.     When Rene showed up, she called every volunteer she had and no one could take him, since he had to be fed every 3 hours for at least the first week.  The SCH doesn't have the staff to do it since they are stretched themselves.  So I said I'd do it.  Rene gave me a weeks supply of stuff, Bug and I fed him and put him in a carrier, then carried him around with us as we did our chores.  We left a little early to get him home and feed him.   Sharky was upset because we really cannot handle another animal at the moment, but he knows me.  I had promised no more animals, but this really was an emergency.  We aren't going to keep him, but will be his foster family until he is strong and old enough to enter the kitten room at the SCH.  He's on vitamins because he was anemic from the fleas but has been given Advantage, and we've only seen dead fleas on him since.   Rene figures he is about 3 weeks old because his eyes are open and he is sort of walking (more like staggering) but his milk teeth are just barely nubs and his ears are still curled over.  He's black or brown, with white whiskers and a white chin & chest, and four little white slippers on his feet. Oh, and no tail.  :-)   This has been an incredible experience.  I've never been around baby kittens before - mine were like 3 or 4 months or adult when I got them.  I feed him kitten milk (like powdered baby formula mixed with warm water) with a syringe and have to gentle stroke his privates to make him tinkle when he's done eating.  He had his first bowel movements this morning and wow, was I a proud mommy! LOL  He's living in his carrier (huge) with a blanky, a small pillow and a toy lion, donated by my kids.  He walks slowly around, takes a nap, walks some more, sleeps, etc.  At night, his carrier stays in our room.   I wanted to give him a nice male Scottish name and thought about it all night, between feedings.  Malcolm came to me this morning and it fits him quite nicely.      
     
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Woke up this morning to a wonderful grey rainy sky.  Wish it could have stayed that way, but it blew over.  *sigh*  We need more rain.  Still.  You know, for a rainy state, we sure haven't had much.  Sharky's doing the errand thing this morning.  Took Bear with him for some one on one time.  Bug's 10th birthday is next week.  He wants a chocolate cake with chocolate icing (LOL) and bugs.  I'm thinking some gummy worms would be fun.  Maybe a big version of the dirt cake (pudding and oreos)?  Might be kinda fun.  Don't have the money for a big birthday, especially with school right around the corner.  If Mom doesn't get him a GI Joe, I will.  Probably one of the Power Team Elites from Big Lots.  He really likes them. 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Juggling bills, what a major pain in the tuckus.  One day, I hope we get to the stage where we don't have to worry (much) about money.  *sigh*  My MIL promised us some money as a gift to buy the boys school clothes, but it hasn't arrived.  This Sunday is the end of Florida's tax free week too.  I asked my dad if he could help us out and he didn't answer me.   Oh well, not surprised there.  It's a shame, 90% of his income goes right to the church.  Glad to know that he's buying himself a nice seat up there in heaven... 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *sigh*    Sharky blew a hose in the truck yesterday.  Since all the hoses are probably 30+ years old, he says there's a chance that if he replaces the blown one, the rest will go, one by one - so might as well replace all of them.  I really wanted us to work on the house this weekend.    There's a little black & white cat living on our front porch.  It's quite the talker and probably has ear mites.  It's very scrawny.  I feel terrible for it, but we can't have another animal.  I had a talk with it today and told it that it was ok to kill the rats to eat, but to make sure it actually eats the rat and not just leave it torn apart in the back yard for my children to see.  I hope it understands.  No bird or squirrel killing allowed.    Bug is watching me type.  He thinks it's very cool that I can type without watching my fingers.  I'm not that fast, about 40 wpm, but he thinks I'm fast as lightning.  He'd get a big kick out of a real typer! LOL  
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bug had a bit of a traumatic moment yesterday morning.  He took Gabby out and found what he called "a squirrel ripped in half".  He came into the house shaking and crying.  We had to have the "circle of life" talk again and I reminded him that there are stray cats around and sometimes we might see something like this.  When Sharky got home, he checked it out and said that it was a small rat (and it really wasn't that bad).  I think Bug felt a bit better.  Sharky gave it a quick burial behind the garage.    My Bug, you'd never know it by his actions, but he is such a sensitive child.  Death upsets him more than he lets on.  A few years ago, we found a dead lizard in the house and he insisted upon giving it a burial in the front yard.   The lizard has been joined by a frog that died on our porch and a dove that died in our front yard.  (The backyard burials, behind the garage, are for road kill, etc., and that's Sharky's job.)    Bug is so much like me sometimes, and yet so different...  
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm totally disgusted with my picture taking.    I couldn't figure it out.  I used to be such a great photographer.  Finally dawned on me.  Landscapes.  I am a fantastic photographer with b&w landscapes.  Dolls just are a failure of mine.  Excuse my whining.  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just NOW, in the mail today, received Bear's school supply list for 6th grade.  School starts August 9th.  OMGS, pass me the smelling salts.  (My mom is helping us out shopping for all the stuff, so I'm taking a small break right now before transcribing the list on the computer and emailing it to her.)  The amount of stuff he needs (that is REQUIRED) is unbelievable.  OK, I admit I should have expected this, he was accepted into a magnet gifted school, but hey - I know I'm an taco short of a Mexican lunch plate special.  I'm trying NOT to panic right now.  Seriously...
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Sunday we went to Walmart, we saw the preggo crack whore hooker at the corner and I called the cops on her using my cellphone.  We haven't seen her since.    Both Sharky and I pray that she is getting help.  Just because I don't want her in my neighbourhood or near my kids doesn't mean I don't wish her well.  She needs help, before she ends up dead.  And don't forget the baby.  That poor child doesn't deserve that life.  No child does.  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Mom and I went to NY to see Nuni.  We ended up in a strange shack place where the mentally handicapped people slept in bunk beds.  Nuni was not surprised to see us.  You could hardly see where her front teeth were gone.  I unpacked my suitcase and it was full of baby stuff, so I decided to Freecycle it.  I found some Barbies there and decided to keep them.  I was watching a soap opera and there was a murder mystery on it.  It wasn't a cliffhanger, the mystery was dropped, unsolved and the plot went on.   I was upset that they didn't solve it so I decided to find out who did it.  I wrote endlessly on a pad of paper, trying to chart it down.  Mom and I and all three of the kids went to Disney World.  She paid $13 for me to star in a soap opera there.  Unfortunately, we couldn't find where to do it. Since I didn't want my picture taken as a clown or anything, we decided to walk around.  We saw a supersonic jet take off and decided to go on that ride.    After waiting a while, we got in, followed a maze to a turnstile.  Then Petunia had to go to the bathroom, so I took her.  When we got back, everyone was in the ride already.  The lady who worked there almost didn't let us back in, but decided to anyway.  We went in and were able to sit with Mom and the boys.  We watched the film and the seats shook.  I was bored.  Then, when it was over, everone was to get up and walk into the next room.  My mom and my sons wouldn't wake up at all, they had fallen asleep watching the movie.  I was terrified.  I spoke to a cop standing outside who said it was normal, they would wake up on their own and I was to watch out for teenagers taking hallucenigenic cough drops.  My mom and sons woke up, I thanked the cop, and we walked through the door.  It was a tiny hall with doors.  We chose the first door and it was a replica of Willy Wonka's Chocolate factory.  The kids could walk around and make their own treat.  We walked around and looked.  Petunia wanted to eat some, but I said No, especially after all those other kids had touched the candy.  As we were leaving, the assistant guide held the door for us and had a large candy cane whistle flute in his hand that he had stolen from the lab.  The next door led us to the all-you-can-eat buffet outside.  We were one of the last so table choices were slim.  I chose one closest to the shade.  As we sat down, I wondered how we were to go get our food.  I found out that if I sang, the table (and chairs) danced (with us in them) over to the buffet.  So, I started singing.  It was hard and uncomfortable.   After a while, I found out that if I stuck my arms out and made swimming motions, it went faster.  At the buffet, I loaded our plates up with cheeseburgers that were on white bread instead of hamburger buns.  I had to make sure I had enough for all of us.  As I went down the buffet, still in the dancing table and chairs set, I saw that the other food trays were all empty or had scrapings on the bottom.  The one that held the fried onions for the hamburgers had maggots crawling in it.  There was no other food.  I went to the end, to get the drinks, and asked for the guy in charge.  I told him about the maggots and he reported it.  I asked when the new food was going to be brought out, and he said "What new food?"   
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, first thing first, I'm ok. Meds are fine, skin spots are just moles (ick, but relieved), and Doc Tom wants to help me lose weight.  He's a good doc, a DO (which I prefer over MDs), and he listens. He rx'd an appetite suppressant which is affordable, and should work with me without having any bad side effects. We discussed diet and he understands my hesitation regarding the mostly protein diets (kids and sheer high price of meats). We talked about different ways of getting around it.  He found out I was a Marine, so he shared his military experience with me. Long story short, he enlisted in the Army's Special Forces WWII at 17, spent 3 mos. in a German POW camp (had great diet jokes from that experience), battlefield promotion to 2ndLT, went to West Point, then became a doctor, served in Korea, was a field surgeon in Vietnam, got out when HIV hit the military and has been a civilian ever since. (Told you I liked the guy. LOL)  The weird thing, is that I had NO idea he was former military and I had NO idea he was THAT old! Saturday, Sunday, and Monday, Sharky and I watched movies regarding WWII and had very long, drawn out detailed discussions about many things - most of which happened to pop up in Doc Tom's conversation.  I'm taking this all as a good sign. Can't get my rx filled until Friday, but will start trying to eat appropriately until then...
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've got my doctor appointment today.  Meeting Mom in a little bit and transferring all the kidlets to her.  She gets to take them to the mall.   After my appointment, I'm meeting them at the mall and we'll probably grab lunch at the food court.  I think there's a Taco Bell there.    I hope this appointment goes well, I'm quite nervous.  I have to see him about my weight and talk to him about some skin spots I have that are scaring me.  Everyone in my maternal family has had a brush in with skin cancer and considering all the burns I had as a child, I wouldn't be surprised if I get it.  I don't want it.  I do hope he decides to remove them anyway, just in case.    When Sharky had his operation, the doctor removed a mole and biopsied it, just in case.  Luckily it wasn't anything but the standard run-of-the-mill variety and I breathed a huge sigh of relief.  Bad enough he had that damn tumour, you know.  *sigh*    The doc told me last time I saw him that he was more than willing to talk to me about my weight.  He said he had some ideas and options for me.  I am praying he will help me.  I need help.  My knee is still hurting me, it would have gotten better by now if I hadn't been heavy.    *double sigh*  
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmm, this might be a bit harder than I thought.    From Jax to Syr, a round trip ticket for spring is about $235 for one adult.  Damn...  We've also got to save for car and cheap hotel too.    Gotta start a lot of positive visualization for this to work out.  
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Next year, Mom is going to go visit Nuni up in NY state.  I've decided that I'm going to go with her.  I can't let her do this alone.  Going to have to start saving some money up and making plans.  I told Mom that if she chooses a date, then it will help us - help Sharky get time off, and for us to find as cheap deals as possible.  I've got a few doll friends up in that area, so I will definitely plan on trying to meet them for lunch or something.  Couldn't go all the way up there and not see them! LOL  
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Nightmares last night.  Living in an area where a xian religious fanatic had taken over.  Most of the dream is now jumbled up and hard to piece out, but we had to sit on bleachers, listening to the preaching, droning on and on.  The head fanatic's ultimate plan was to break everyone's spirit by splitting up their families.  That scared me most of all...   
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Damn, I really wanted to go to that stupid reunion.  I keep trying to convince myself, but it's not working.  I missed the 10th because I was pregnant and due any minute - there was no way I could have gone.  I couldn't go this time because we just didn't have the money to do it.  Even if we did, it would have been a very selfish thing to do.  I wouldn't have wanted to go by myself - there are so many things to do and see in SWFL and I would have loved to have Sharky and the kids with me.  
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A friend just forwarded pictures of our 20th high school reunion which I didn't attend.    Who the hell are all those old people?  I didn't recognize any of them, I barely recognized one or two of the names.    I am sort of glad I didn't go.  I would have felt very lost there...  
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sharky and Bear came back from the grocers.  Sharky says that I taught Bear well, he's a very good, thrifty shopper.  I'm very proud of him...  
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I dreamt that I had a fourth child last night, a baby boy named Alexander.  He had very dark skin and dark laughing eyes, looking more like Sharky than our other kids.  We were in England and I was pregnant.  We were walking through the streets, window shopping when I felt contractions.  We all piled into the tiny compact car to go to the hospital.  Poor Sharky, never having driven in England before, got confused and lost on a roundabout.  We stopped for directions at a coffee shop that was also having a children's show filmed inside.  Luckily, the owners took pity on us and assisted (somehow) all of us and we ended up in the hospital.  My dream skipped over the birth and went from contractions straight to baby.  I remember being horribly disappointed at first, with another son, I already had two and had planned on having another daughter, but once I laid eyes on the baby boy (and chose a name), I fell in love with him.  BTW, he was named after a dear friend of ours in the dream, Lex Luthor.   
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Drove the boys to karate this evening.  Wow, is it hazy out.  Yucky, smoggy looking clouds hanging very low downtown, covering the tops of buildings.  Very low level clouds are scooting by fast, but the dirty ones seem to be just stuck here.    My sunflowers are drooping horribly.  Too much water?  Too hot?  Who knows...    On the other hand, my chives are doing fabulous!  I've got tons of purple flower stalks shooting up everywhere.  I have GOT to weed out there soon.  Hopefully I'll have a good morning tomorrow and be able to get that done.  
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Petunia loves to wash her hands.  That is a good thing.     Problem is, if there isn't a towel handy to wipe her hands with, she goes and finds a cat and dries her hands on them.  
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I can't wait for this week to be over with.  Yes, I know it's Friday, but *sigh* the end isn't coming fast enough.    Do you know what I want?  I want to spend time with my husband alone.  Not alone after the kids go to bed or alone at night.  I just want to be ALONE with him and no one else around.  It's not about sex, it's just about BEING with someone.  I don't know how else to describe it.    ***    I have to make a list of things to-do.  We have literally 1000s of things that need to be done around here but we just don't have the old "get up and go" to do it.  
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I don't remember much, just bits and pieces.  I was back in highschool and had two male teenage friends.  We were going to be the new "Harry Potter" team.  One of the guys had longer hair than me, the other was a Cuban boat refugee.  We had lunch in the cafeteria - I had fried catfish, they had salads.  Back in the classroom, the teacher kept taking off, leaving the class alone.  We'd go for walks in the garden outback and sneak in before anyone realized we were missing.  The three of us decided to raise some money by gambling and went to a Japanese garden and took a walk on the docks...   
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's hot in here.  When Bear complained, I realized that it wasn't just me sweating (I thought it was hormones) so I checked the thermometer.  83°F.  Ouch.  So, I turned off the air and went outside and pushed the reset button, came back in and turned it back on.  A few minutes later, the fan started up.  It's been an hour and a half and it's dropped down to 81°F but I'm concerned that something is wrong.  It might be working fine and the house is just too hot to cool down quickly.  *fingers crossed*  Thank the Gods we have good fans in here.  I don't know what I'd do without them.     How am I feeling?  Like crud, thank you.  Very lethargic, sweaty, and just plain old oogily.  Kids have tried to take care of me, at least they aren't fighting.  They really are good kids, especially when they aren't being selfish and 100% concerned with themselves.  
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I wasn't able to wake up this morning.   I was up all night long, not from Petunia crawling into bed with us, but because I was sick.  Sharky woke me up with coffee and my monitor spazzed on me, so I sat on the couch to drink it (instead of at my desk as usual).  Well, I drank most of it, put it down on the table and closed my eyes.      In a space of what felt like 5 minutes, Sharky said goodbye, kids asked me if I wanted some toast, and Bear kissed me and said he was worried.  It wasn't 5 minutes, it was 45.  I forced myself to get up, get a cold soda and wake up.    All I took was Midol yesterday, so that couldn't have been it.  I don't like to take rx pain meds because I can never wake up from them, just like this morning.  But Midol is OTC stuff and contains stimulants, besides the pain relief, etc.  *sigh*  I just took some more, hope it kicks in soon.  My periods seem to be getting worse as I get older...  
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Geeze, I feel like crap today.  If it doesn't hurt, it aches.  The stuff that doesn't ache is sore.  The parts that aren't sore are throbbing.  I'm about to throw in the towel, just lay down on the floor and cry.  But that would hurt, so I won't do it.  I used to be able to do the old "mind over matter" thing and not care, but hell, I can't do it anymore.  Must be pre-pre-menopause or some such rot.  *sigh*    ***    Sharky's got a friend who has a Barbie collection stashed in his closet that he's considering getting rid of.  I sure hope he thinks of me first.  LOL  I don't know what all he's got or in what shape, but considering how tiny my vintage collection is, I'll consider taking about anything - no matter how bad of shape it's in.    I somehow like it better that way too.  My brunette s/l Midge that I won off of eBay a couple of years ago was in decent shape, but dirty and had messy hair.  It gave me immense pleasure to clean her up and to restyle her hair back to the way it was.  I think I enjoyed that more than if she had been a minty perfect doll.    I've even thought - if I won the lottery, would I buy perfect dolls?  Yeah, probably one or two.  But I would enjoy the imperfect ones more, the heavily loved ones better and make them (almost) perfect again...  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Boy, it doesn't take a dream expert to figure this one out.      We were sitting in the living room and a moving van pulled up outside and a bunch of people got off and started moving furniture off and placing it in our driveway.  We stepped outside to see what was going on.  The furniture was all used, some dirty and some broken.  We asked where it came from, but the movers wouldn't speak to us.  I started examining the stuff and realized it all came from my mother-in-law in Miami.  The reason some of the stuff was broken and dirty was because it was placed in storage right after Hurricane Andrew.  There were a lot of antiques (broken and dirty of course) and stuff that I recognized.  We started making plans on what to do with all the stuff.  The movers finally finished and left.  As we were looking around, we discovered that the movers obviously used some of the stuff on the trip here.  For example, there was a small freezer (on wheels? LOL) that had ice in it, to hold sodas.  Our neighbours stopped by to watch what was going on.  One of them, an American Indian, told us that he saw the moving van stop at a McDonalds and unload a Cigar Store Indian.  When we said we wished that was ours, he got all offended.  Sharky had to hug him to let him know we didn't mean to offend him.  My grandfather came by to help with all the stuff.  We found a large antique entertainment center and managed to get it into the house.  When you cranked up the entertainment center, panels (where the tv would go today) would rotate, showing all sorts of antique and vintage stuff.  I got all excited when I saw one of the panels had Barbie stuff.  In fact, it had original Barbies actually attached to the panel, but a simple wire.  I looked on the back of the panel and discovered that I could just snip them off.  I was so overjoyed, I started to sob.  I decided to leave them on the panel for now, it was safer.  I then started to assemble the floor maze part of the entertainment center.  It was kinda like the old game Mouse Trap, but different.  I don't even know how to describe it.  My grandfather was sitting on the floor with me, helping.  The kids were playing with all the other furniture that was still outside.   
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My precious urchins were glued to their Gameboys all day today and when I made them put the things away to help me around the house before dinner, all hell breaks loose. Major adrenaline rush and hysteria ensued.  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was proud of my blog until I started looking around at other ones.  Wow, there are some incredibly talented writers who actually stick to a theme out there!    Oh well, this is more of a diary blog (diablog?) and I never meant this to be anything more serious than that.  LOL  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I really am enjoying this new WYSIWYG editor!        A big  Thank You  to TPTB at Blogger!!!  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Cheese.  I love cheese.  I would probably die if I couldn't eat it.  Seriously.    The best cheese in the world is Dubliner, made by  urlLink KerryGold .     I first heard of KerryGold when I tried their swiss cheese years ago.  Amazingly smooth and nutty flavour, and always consistent with quality and taste.       The cheese is very affordable for the quality, and so is their butter, but we try and only buy it for special occasions so we don't tire of it.  One year, I even bought a little of all their products for my mom at Yule/Christmas.  She loved it as much as I did.   
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Plus Clothing.  Hmm, plus cost?  Yep.  Plus ugly material?  Yep.  Plus annoyances?  LOL Yep, that too.    W*M sucks when it comes to Plus sized clothing for women.  There is so much ugly 70s style polyester, it's almost a fire-hazard to walk thru the racks.  Oh yeah, what 30-something woman wants to wear things that her grandma wore in a nursing home?  Big ole flowered muumuus and shirts that look like a nurse would wear on the job.    And bras?  If it ain't padded with an underwire, W*M doesn't carry it.  Eeeuuuwww and Ouch.    Sounds silly, but shopping for clothes there makes me depressed.  Sharky found beautiful embroidered t-shirts that only went to size 14.  We found the plus equivalent and while the same brand and style, the embroidery was almost 2nd rate and a lot less detailed.  Why?      Why do these clothing manufacturers think that overweight women want to be dowdy and ugly?    The few "hip" fashions they did have couldn't have fit me even if I wanted them to.  I'm 5'2", these were styled for Amazons averaging 6 foot tall.  So, I could buy the outfit and save money, but spend a small fortune on a tailor to get it to fit.    *sigh*  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We gave up our W*M boycott and went there on Sunday, dropped a wad of cash.  :-(  No, I'm not proud of it, quite embarassed to say the least.    We had to buy the boys underwear and socks, and frankly, W*M is the cheapest place around for quality stuff.    I also needed a new pair of jeans.  After I tried them on in the dressing room, I bent over to tie my shoelaces and my right kneecap went the wrong way and "popped".  Felt very weird.  Two days later, it's still stiff and complaining a bit, and hard to pull on pants.  Every time I convince myself that I don't feel old, something stupid like this happens.  *rolls eyes*    Oh, and Auntie Flo came to visit today.  She is such a major pain in the back.  Small of the back to be specific, right where the kidneys are.  Couldn't find any Tylenol, but did have some Advil Liqui-gels that I received as a free sample.  They seem to be working for right now.    I'm supposed to go grocery shopping today, but the way my back is right now, I really don't want to get behind the wheel, much less tote 3 obnoxious kids with me through a grocery store...  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Let's see if I can recall this...      I was back in the service last night.   My old office had moved, no longer in it's prestigious location, but in the middle of the building in a crappy old room.  R was still there, as well as M, who had remarried her husband and had adopted a 5 yo boy from Nigeria.  She showed me pictures of him, he was cute with huge amber coloured eyes.  My old desk was there, but I had to clean it.  I was amazed at the food left in it.  Tons of breakfast sandwiches from Krystal, still hot and fresh after all these years, along with square burgers from Wendy's.   There was also lots of paperwork, but by the time I had cleaned it, there was no paperwork that had any meaning.  I threw a lot of stuff out.  LOL There was a new short Asian guy in the office, but he was very annoying and was fired for upsetting and pinching people.  I kept wanting to go buy a soda from the BMS downstairs and M kept giving me directions to get there, but I never went.   M and I made plans to eat in the cafeteria for lunch - not the new fancy cafeteria from a previous dream, but the real old one.  A football game with different platoons broken down by colour (red, blue, etc.) was "premiered" in our office for our viewing pleasure.   Some of the people wore costumes to play football.  There were snowmen on the white team and people painted like Aborigines on another team.  Afterwards, R gave us betting tickets to choose which team we liked and we could win a prize in the drawing.   
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sharky's fave website right now?   urlLink www.wilwheaton.net   Yep,  that   urlLink Wil Wheaton .  Turns out he's pretty cool and is a major Linux nut...  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We had an awesome weekend.  Sharky earned a bonus so we not only were able to buy the kids some school clothes and some much needed jeans for me, we were able to have a nice dinner out at Carrabba's.  We wouldn't have normally picked that restaurant because it's so expensive, but he was given a gift certificate for it so we went.  Man oh man was it good.  I'm glad it IS expensive or we'd probably eat there all the time! LOL  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just got a letter from Darnell Cookman Middle School advising us of the changes to the School Board dress code.  No obscene shirts.  No short shorts or skirts.  No dog collars or spiked jewelry.  No mohawks.  Well, darn it, there goes my son's wardrobe.  Not.  ROFL  I'm sorry, but it's hard to picture 11 year old kids dressed like that...
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went to bed early and I'm still tired.  I had a really weird, wonderful dream that I won't even begin to try and describe.  I'll just keep it to myself and enjoy it until it completely dissolves...  The club meeting is today, so I've got to find some alone time to get ready.  It's hard to take a shower when there are kids running around everywhere.  Sharky was supposed to fix his friend's computer today, but there isn't any time.  He and Bug are picking up concrete blocks this morning for our garden and then I'm going to try and send Sharky to the store with ALL the kids so I can have a free moment.  Kinda sad, isn't it?  That I have to plan and scheme just to be able to take a shower in peace?  Yeah, I can take one after everyone's gone to bed or before everyone wakes up, but then it's not enjoyable, you know?
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The boys finished cleaning their room just in time to go to karate.  Hallefreakinglujah.  I don't want to go through this again...
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I deleted my main Delphi account today, the one I've had for over 5 years.  I am sad, but it was hacked into twice and someone changed the password.  I had to, there was no other way.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If you love something, hug it. If it wants to get away, hug it until it squeals. - Princess Petunia Blossom the Cat Squeezer
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hard to wake up this morning.  Not just me either, Bear woke up in a foul mood again.  Lovely.  He's only 11 and I swear, he's already in puberty.  I've read that puberty starts years before you start seeing physical signs of it.  I'm not ready to be a mother of a teenager.  *whine*  Yes, pass the cheese please.  ***  My chives are growing back, YEAH!  We've had so much rain lately that it seems to have accelerated their recovery.  Now, I just have to keep the grass far enough away from them so people will notice that my chives are NOT grass.  LOL  Oh, and not let my neighbour mow the front strip again.  *sigh*  The sunflowers are looking nice, but the tallest one is still only like 3 feet tall.  Not even close to the 10-12 feet the seed packet promised.  hehehe
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I bring fresh showers for the thirsting flowers, From the seas and the streams; I bear light shade for the leaves when laid In their noonday dreams. From my wings are shaken the dews that waken The sweet buds every one, When rocked to rest on their mother's breast, As she dances about the sun. I wield the flail of the lashing hail, And whiten the green plains under, And then again I dissolve it in rain, And laugh as I pass in thunder.  Author: Percy Bysshe Shelley Source: The Cloud
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think I finally figured out the Mozilla Thunderbird calendar.  Took me enough time.  Now, I hope I don't lose the darn thing.  Have to see what I can do to make sure it doesn't happen again...
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Baby Bear, on Sesame Street, talks babyish with a strong lisp.  I swear, I just heard him say "Shit".
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Stupid video card is dying.  We've got a spare one around here somewhere and will swap them this weekend.  Sharky has school today and was psyched this morning about it.  I'm glad.  Shows his bosses think highly of him since they keep sending him.  I made him take my cell phone with him because there is no way for me to reach him at school (not like I'd try) but it's out in the "boonies" and if something happened to the truck, I want him to be able to call me.   My dream:  I wrapped a bunch of "Fathers Day" gifts to two gay friends of mine and then, by phone, invited them over to open them.  They weren't fathers, but I thought it would be fun.  The gifts were Poke'mon toys.  Before they were to arrive, I walked down through my dream neighbourhood to the front gates and saw two Barbies sitting in the trash waiting to be picked up.  I passed by them and then decided that I would take them home.  A neighbour lady wearing a Sailor Moon outfit struck up a conversation with me, telling me she thought about me when she saw the dolls in the garbage.  She and her boyfriend followed me home and sat in the living room while I fixed a bottle for the baby.  My gay friends had called and left messages on the answering machine, but when I picked up the phone, it was Sharky's secretary telling me he had just left to come home.  I gave the baby the bottle and then I gave one of my sons a plate of macaroni and cheese, which he promptly put to his mouth and tried to eat like a person drinking soup out of a bowl.  I got mad at him for getting mac & cheese in the yellow shag carpeting, but the Sailor Moon lady and her boyfriend said I shouldn't get upset, no one would notice.  Sharky came home then.    I had some free time this morning, so I took a short bath.  Malcolm sat with me the whole time.  Unusual for him, since he usually runs the other way when he sees water in the tub. LOL  He'd stand up and give me a kiss on the shoulder and he looked so concerned about me sitting there, I couldn't help but laugh.  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, the boys are being punished.  The deal was, clean your room and you can go to karate class tonight.  They had all day, but didn't really start until 15 minutes ago.  Sorry, Charlie, no can do.  Shoving everything in a giant pile in the corner and behind the closet door is not cleaning.  Tomorrow, all of us (me and the kids) are going into the room and sorting through everything.  Keep, throw away, give away, donate, etc. piles will be made.  Everything else will have a home.  IF it is not done by Friday, they will be taken out of karate.  What else can I do?  I don't want to take them out of class, but how else can I punish them?  I'm out of options...
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Like my new "portrait"?  It's a free Japanese site that makes these pictures.  It's a lot of fun once you get the hang of it.   http://illustmaker.abi-station.com/index_en.shtml                 Left to right, Topaz, Bear, Bug, Petunia, and Sharky
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My three angels have mutated into a slacker, a drama queen, and a spoiled brat.  What did I do wrong?  I'm so tired of this.  I hate summer vacation.  There is NO logical reason anymore for it existing.  I cannot afford summer camp or day camp.  The boys did attend a two week camp a couple of weeks ago and it was very nice.  They had a blast and my life was normal again for a short period.  They need year-round school.  I'm not joking...
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I listen to the 80s station on the radio and my kids say they enjoy the music.  Today, driving home from the store, "Heat of the Moment" by Asia was playing.  As I was singing along, I heard some different lyrics from the back seat.  Bug was singing "...it was the Year of the Mongoose..." instead of "...it was the heat of the moment..."  Wow.  Now that phrase is stuck in my head.  LOL
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am getting way too old to stay up late.  It was after 11:30 pm last night when I went to bed and now I feel like I never got any sleep at all.  I have to go to the copy place and run off the newsletter, then stuff them in the envelopes and hit the post office to mail them.  If I get it done this a.m. then the club members should get it tomorrow "guaranteed".    After that, the kids and I have to hit the grocery store and pick up some eats so we don't waste away to nothing.  ROFL    What else do I have to do?  Let's see.  Get the kids to clean their rooms and cut their hair.  I think that's it.    Hmm, lack of sleep is making it hard to remember...
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We had a great time at C's house.  She treated us to lunch at El Potro's and the boys ate their weight at the Mexican buffet.  (You think I'm kidding, don't you? LOL)  The food, as always, was very fresh, tasted delicious, with a very "homemade" touch to it - even at the buffet! LOL  I was heartbroken to see that they painted over the charming murals on the walls though.  They were idyllic country and village scenes, painted in faux arches over the tables.  Very sweet and charming and not the usual "Mexican restaurant" motif.  Well, they painted the walls orange and yellow streaked in a zigzag sponge fashion.  Yuck.  Very unattractive.  Afterwards, we went back to her house where the kids splashed around for a while in the pool (almost an hour) until the darkening skies and distant thunder chased us back inside.  C is my best friend and probably the most generous woman I know.  Her mom, Miss B, got the boys about 6 practically new Star Wars shirts she picked up somewhere (Miss B is the queen of garage sales.  It bothers me because I want to repay them for their kindness and generousity but I never know what to do...  I'll think of something...
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today is going to be a good day.    The kids and I are going over to their Fairy Goddessmother's house to play.  C's got a big blow up pool for them to play in, cable tv, and tons of toys, etc.  Even if she didn't, my sons practically worship the ground she walks on and all she has to do is smile and they obey her every command.  LOL  (Hey, it's a good thing...)  She wants to take us out to lunch today, so we'll probably pick El Potro again.  It's inexpensive, delicious, and vegetarian friendly (C's a veghead).  (No, it's not the same as Taco Bell LOL, probably healthier.)  I've got to get the club's newsletter printed out & ready for mailing and since BOTH my printers are on the blink, I'm taking the disk over to C's house to print it out.  If I can, I'll get it copied and mailed out this afternoon or this evening.  *fingers crossed*
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am not happy.  Vice didn't call me back.  I know, they are probably busy, but they should at least have a secretary or something.  So, I called the non-emergency police number again.  The man who answered told me to call my Zone Station.  She (secretary?) told me to call Vice and gave me another number.  That was a wrong number and the recording gave me a new number.  That number worked but was just a mailbox with no id.  I don't feel safe leaving my number so I pushed "0" for the operator when prompted, and the recording said that wasn't a valid response.  I called back again and spoke to an officer at this time.  I was told that making a report is ok, but what I really need to do is to call the cops (non-emergency number) every single time I see the prostitutes. She said even if I'm in the car, I can call them on my cell phone and report the prostitutes.  I guess the more reports made this way, the more the cops can do?  I really want to talk to someone in that department though and make them aware of how bad it's getting.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm burnt out on the old family tree.  I've worked (almost) non-stop on my sDad's and I gotta stop.  I close my eyes and the names are burned into my eyelids.  Ack.  Luckily, there are many stumpy branches to work on.  hehehe
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think the truck is fixed.  *fingers crossed*  Having one vehicle for all of us isn't a good thing, believe me.  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Do we fix the truck or park it?  That was the question asked of me about 20 minutes after I woke up this morning.  I could barely open my eyes.  Heck, I could barely feel the keyboard as I was trying to type my dream.  LOL  Since I'm using this blog as my diary/dream journal, I have got to get the stuff out of my head before I forget.  I know that my family considers me bizarre - that I am able to type coherently as soon as I wake up but cannot form a complete sentence without a mug and a half of coffee.  We decided to fix the truck.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Man oh man was that a bizarre dream...    We went on vacation to Maine and stayed at a rickety old bed & breakfast.  Sharky and I stayed in one room, the kids in another, and my mom and sdad in a third.  The rest of the b&b was deserted.  There was a huge storm and Sharky and I tried to watch it through a window.  It was pretty intense.  The next morning, the hostess of the b&b told us we could walk through the door next to the window and when I did, I wasn't outside, I was in a ballroom that was falling apart with a parial roof and walls.  We had watched the storm in another room. LOL  I continued through that back door and found myself in a garden.  I walked around and other people appeared.  The b&b owner took us on a tour of the garden and when I admired a tree, picked seeds off the tree and placed them on my plate.  The girl next to me took all the large seeds and left me the small ones.  I told her that wasn't fair and we traded back so we each had some small and some large seeds.  I then went to a concert with that (new) friend.  Afterwards, she and I went to a music store.  As we were leaving, I saw a table covered with music sheets, etc.  I decided to sit down and go through the Elton John boxes to try and find a present for Sharky.  As I was going through all the tons of stuff, not finding what I want, a 16 yo boy friend (of my friend) sat down with us to chat.  Well, when we couldn't find anything I liked, we straightened up the table and went to leave, and as a joke, I gave the boy a quick kiss to "remember me" by.  My friend was past her curfew, so I took her home and explained to her mom that I was sorry, I didn't realize the time.  The mom didn't have a problem with it.  Then, a process server came up and handed me papers that the teenage boy sent me.  He was emancipating himself from his parents and his school and demanding that I marry him.  "He loved me."  I was shocked and horrified.  I told Sharky who thought it was hilarious.  I then went and performed at the fashion show like nothing was wrong.  I walked up and down the catwalk and saw that the boy was watching me in the audience.  I went backstage to the computer monitor who was in charge of the fashion show and demanded that the computer take care of the problem.  It asked for my cd which I gave it.  I was then told to go to the dressing room and change clothes.  The dressing room was a mirror panel (with other contestents in the room) and I had to think about what outfit I wanted to wear to change into and I would appear to be dressed in those clothes.  I ended up wearing a blue muumuu, an orange wig with curlers and pink fuzzy slippers.  I went to the park to meet the boy and his lawyer and sat at the bench.  I grew tired of all the legal talk, even after the lawyer showed me papers that the boy could "afford" me, and told them there was no way I was leaving my husband for some kid I kissed as a joke.  The kid was heartbroken.  Sharky laughed throughout the whole thing.   
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Man, is it hot out there.  97F.  No wonder poor SaturnMarie is having such a hard time of it, poor old gal.  She's such a faithful car too.  Hmm, gotta do some mental updates here.  Vice squad didn't return my call from yesterday.  Going to try again Monday.  Couldn't get the BS site to cooperate to figure out if I can save money.  Will try again Monday.  Need to weed around front stones on Saturday or it's going to really look like ruins out there. LOL
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bug is a smartass.  Seriously.  Don't get me wrong, I love a good sense of humour, but he pushes the limits every time.    He can be the most loving caring child and in the next breath say the most horrid thing to get attention.  I guess that's normal for a middle child and a Leo?  *sigh*
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ugh.  Stomach Ache, due to overindulgence of Taco Bell beans.  Oh well, it's one of my only vices.  I have very few you know.  *evil laughter*  Speaking of vices... Got Cali Guy Blaine today, wow, is he a vinyl hottie!  Best sculpt in a long time.  Kudos Mattel!  Now, if you could have only gone a bit lighter in the hair products!  Poor dude's hair is harder than his torso, and that says a lot.  Gonna have to wash it out.  Clothing is fab, especially like the khakis and mesh shirt.    I should have bought the Happy Family Grandparents, but I couldn't pass up Blaine and just didn't have the moolah for all.  Drooled a while in the GI Joe aisle.  Man, those Medal of Honor Joes are awesome.  I saw the Pharmacist's Mate - the details are incredible.  They have his name (Franklin Pierce?) and his story on the back of how he deserved the MoH (corpsman with 4th MarDiv in Iwo Jima).  Definite Hero.  Saw the Navaho Code Talker again.  Still $29.99.  I want to get him for Sharky - he speaks 7 different phrases, in Navajo and in English, and is really cool.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Taco Bell...  I can't live without it.  'Nuff said.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hate IE?  Try Firefox (formerly Firebird).  I've been using it for over a year now and love it.  It's open source, free cost, free of many bugs and can be customized rather easily.  It will import your IE fave bookmarks so you don't lose anything when you switch over.  I can't recommend it highly enough...   urlLink www.mozilla.org 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bellsouth is ssslllooowww...  I'm trying to pay my BS bill and see if I can bundle some services together to save some money, but the website is unbelievably slow.  Get with the 21st century people!  They are a great ISP and only have a snafu once a year or so *knock on wood* but geeze, you would never know that from their website.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sharky's back in a lot of pain again.    It turns out, he's never really been out of pain.  The headaches have returned.  And I'm upset, of course.  We are going to have to get him an appointment with the specialist again.    This is breaking my heart.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Broad & W State Street at 8 am  UNBELIEVABLE!  I swear, it was a camp of homeless men!  Right in the middle of downtown Jax!  It looked like they just put out a fire and were all sitting around with their little paper bags & bottles.  WTF is up with that?  I hope to hell that it wasn't what it looked like, but geeze, what else could it have been?
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night was a major snafu.  Luckily, it all worked out.  To make a long story short, Sharky and I got our wires crossed and I went to go get him from work.  The truck is still not fixed, but *fingers crossed* it will be today.  I have to drive him to work this morning.  Morning traffic, barf...    It's all jumbled up and hard to recall.  Was on the set of a mermaid movie being filmed, starring Lucy Lawless as an alien mermaid with dreadlocks.  Swam with her and a merman in a pond and then crawled out to find out the full moon in the sky was actually the earth and it was being blown up. Went on a bike(?) ride with a friend and looked at some houses I admired.  Helped a family in one house hide from someone who was searching for money hidden inside.  Made the parents play dead under some mattresses while the kids hid in the attic crawlspace.    
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bear is a lot better now.  *huge sigh of relief*  Lots of hot tea (decaf) with honey, plenty of water, and meds when he needs it.    I don't know about the truck.  Sharky's going to drive it home and call me before he leaves.  If he's not home within 30 minutes, I have to go looking for him.  Damn, I sure hope it's nothing serious or expensive.  :-/  It's overcast and raining out and Bug & Petunia are chomping at the bit.  They're bored with kids shows and Nintendo and have too much energy to be cooped up with us.  What can I do?  Send them out to get struck by lightning, hit by a car or traumatized by the local crack whore?  Oh yeah, speaking of which, I'm freaking sick and tired of that damn bitch hanging around my house.  I'm waiting from a call back from the city vice squad to have a talk with them.  Sharky caught her last Sunday hiding in our driveway behind our truck!  When he told her to get out of our yard, she started twitching, itching, swearing and freaking - but she did leave.  Every day since, I've seen her out in front of our house, walking up and down the sidewalk.    This is our forever home, not some rental shack.  Damn it, I have rights too - the right not to be scared and terrorized by drug dealers, addicts, prostitutes, and johns.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Doc has been postponed.  Yep, rescheduled for 2 more weeks.  Just can't do it today, not with a broken down truck and a sick kid, who, btw, is doing better.  *phew*
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When it rains, it pours.  I've been saying a lot of that lately. :-(  Sharky called.  The truck cut out 3 times on the way to work.  Cut out meaning the damn thing just turned itself off.  The first time was on the bridge.  Yeah, that's a good thing.  NOT.  Man oh man, we cannot afford this!  ***  I gave Bear a plain saline treatment on the nebulizer first.  He could barely speak so I wanted his airway to open up a bit before I gave him his medicine.  After like 30 seconds breathing the saline mist, he had a good cough and opened right up.  He took his Albuterol and now is a lot better.  Damn, I was really hoping he was growing out of this.  Yes, his attacks have been farther apart and lessening in severity, but still.  :-(  He's been complaining of a stuffy nose, so it's got to be the pollen in the air again.  I fixed him a fried egg and toast (no milk!) and after he digests a bit, I'm going to give him a cup of hot tea to drink.  That should help a bit. 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Great.  Bear just woke up, hardly able to breathe.  Looks like another asthma attack.  :-(
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I feel hungover this morning.  I didn't drink anything, I think it's the pollen.  I sure dreamt like I had been drinking:    I dreamed my mother and I were walking my oldest son, Bear, to school.  We had to cross a sidewalk with construction equipment and workers on both sides, who were tearing up the area.  It wasn't until after we (and others) had crossed that they yelled at us and told us we weren't allowed to cross and had to go out of our way to come back. At school, I met with a secretary to get an appointment with a lawyer.  Turns out that part of my paycheck was supposed to go to a fund to buy stock in McDonald's, but it wasn't.  She said my appointment would be on Friday.  I crossed the courtyard to go to my apartment and tell my husband, but I ran into a guy who was a security guard at the hospital on Sundays.  He invited me to a birthday party for his son who was turning 4 that day.  So, I went inside, got my daughter and we went to the party.  (Turns out the school in my dream was also the hospital, just across the courtyard from my apartment.) He had a clown (ick) at the party and a band from Africa that played classical English music.  He told us all about how he was a house husband while his wife worked and he kept his job as a security guard on Sundays to prove he still was the man in the family.  Rosie O'Donnell showed up and brought a present for his kid. My daughter and I went back to our apartment where my husband was cooking dinner.  We were all going to watch Star Trek while we ate.  Rosie knocked on my sliding glass door and asked if she could talk to me.  I apologized to Sharky for the intrusion and stepped out.  She wanted to sit on the bench and talk.  I asked her if she wanted to sit on the more private benches by the lake down the hill, but she wanted to stay where we were because we could listen to the African band play.  She told me she wanted to be my boyfriend.  I said I was sorry, but I was already married and loved my husband.  She then pointed to a paper flyer taped to my sliding glass door advertising singles night at the local Baptist church.  I said I allowed the part-time security guy to post it but was going to take it down soon. The benches were crowded with women, coming and going in the mall (also part of the school/hospital/apartment complex).  Rosie finally stood up, gave me a tearful kiss on the cheek and said goodbye.  I walked into the apartment and shut the sliding glass door.  My kids were still watching Star Trek and my husband was dishing up salad.  It was after 11 o'clock at night.  I apologized for the lateness and he just shrugged and asked what was up.   I told him it had been a long and busy day...   
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Guess what's stuck in my head?  The goodbye song from the Lawrence Welk show.     Good night, sleep tight, and pleasant dreams to you...   That's one heck of an ear worm, let me tell you.  *rolls eyes*  It just sprang into my head a little while ago while saying goodnight to the boys.  Yes, I started singing it outloud too.  I'm a real annoying mom.  *giggles*
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Who's parents?  I've been on a major ancestry kick, doing the old family tree, and even though there are some major brick walls (and a lot of relatives overseas), I've made some awesome progress.  Just talked to Mommy Dearest and she told me that sDad's office is having a "Family Feast" on Friday.  Each employee is to bring a traditional dish from their family's heritage.  Well, sDad thought he was Welsh - after a bit of research, I think he's German. LOL  But it's ok, Mom's going to cook up a lamb stew or some such for him.  Back on subject, I've decided to add sDad to the family tree (he IS married to my mom LOL) and I'm going to do what I can to track his family back for him.  His parents are long deceased and two out of his three siblings are also gone.  The third doesn't speak to him because of her husband or something.  (No, not getting involved here. LOL)   I thought it might be fun to go back a ways for him so he can have a bit of contact with his family.  Also, if he ever gets back in touch with his kids, he can have some info to pass on to them.  Nope, not looking for any brownie points here, just love the guy.  :-)
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Painted fish today.  Keychains, little wooden ones that my mom gave us.  Not real fish.  That would be yucky and would smell.  LOL  We did good, no accidents.  Petunia pretty much has orange streaks all over her, but she's washable.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Good Morning.  Or is it?  Guess it depends upon your POV.  I woke up from a dream of having an affair with a man who wasn't my husband. (Duh, I did say affair, didn't I? LOL)      We were in a hotel room and he had made numbers out of giant kitchen sponges and was making them magically float in the air.  It made me happy, I don't know why.  I then found out I was pregnant and my husband and I decided that since we couldn't afford another child, we would give it to the guy I was having an affair with.  Of course, when the kid was born, it wasn't the same race as any of us, but no one questioned that.  Throughout the whole dream, I was so happy.    I told Sharky about it when I came out to have my coffee and he thought it was funny and tried to tease me.  That bothered me.  I'm not sure why, maybe because I am rarely that happy in dreams?  ***  I'm still rather depressed about the internet.  The joy I found in it before is gone.  I still have an overwhelming desire to chat about dolls, but as for religion?  Not right now.  I feel like I'm in a cocoon and it's getting close to the time I break out and spread my wings.  I know I will go back to the Grove, but I've got to crawl out first.  It all started with my ISP cancelling my DSL by accident.  I had pangs of withdrawal at first, and then a strange calmness came over me.  After it was all set back to normal, my video card started giving me trouble.  It's still not fixed, but unlike past times when I've been cut off from the 'net, I have no panic about it.    Maybe it's not depression.  Maybe it's a well-needed vacation.  Maybe it's both.  No, there is definite depression involved - at the very root of it all.  I know that I've upset many friends, but only one came looking for me.  I don't know if I should be concerned or relieved about that.  That has added to the depression somewhat.  I'm looking forward to my doctor visit tomorrow.  ***  My very first blog (and the last for almost a year) was about Malcolm MacManx, my precious boy.  He's grown into quite a ball of love and fluff.  He's a medium hair cat, with fur not velvety and short and not long and luxurious.  It's medium and silky and spreads like a skirt around his bottom when he sits.  One of his nicknames is Fluffer Butter.  Think about it. LOL  Gabrielle, my (spayed) dog, wanted to be his mummy so bad when he was tiny.  After he grew big enough to run free in the house, she would catch him, pin him down, and groom him with her teeth.  Yes, the first time it happened, I thought my heart stopped.  It wasn't violent, she nibbles him with her front teeth, like a child eating corn on the cob.  For a while, she completely chewed off his fur ruff around his neck.  She's relaxed on it somewhat, so his fur has grown back and he's back to looking like my Foxy Baby.  Yes, another nickname.  Every morning, Sharky wakes up first and starts the coffee.  He then comes in and wakes me up so I can have my cup.  That is, if Malcolm doesn't get me first.  He'll come in and jump on the bed, purring and marching with his front paws (aka "making biscuits").  Hence the nickname, Coffee Cat.  My cat Cosmo has finally forgiven me for bringing him home.  Took him almost 6 months, but he's grown used to Malcolm, his "little brother".  
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lasagna is giving me a headache.  I'm cooking a frozen lasagna that my Grandfather gave me.  The hot cardboard smell is nauseating but strangely appetizing because it's mixed with the smell of freshly cooked vegetable lasagna.  My husband just called, he's on his way home.  He's late but it doesn't matter.  The lasagna won't be done for another 20 minutes.  He'll be home by then.  All Petunia wants to do is play Barbies with me.  I'm too tired to, but I still help her dress Princess Dancenflex in her exercise gear.  Boy, is it hard slipping those pants up those all vinyl legs.    Petunia has gotten into the habit of playing Barbies with Sharky before dinner every night.  It's a fun little ritual they two of them have.  I love it.  How many dads do you know that will play Barbies with their little girl?  My dad didn't.  His dad didn't.  It's not "manly".  *rolls eyes*    I love my husband, he's the greatest dad in the world.  Now, if only he'll get home before the cardboard lasagna fumes overwhelm me.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My neighbour slaughtered my plants yesterday.  I was hanging a windchime on my porch when he came out and introduced himself as "Cornpone".  He pointed to the right-of-way that needed trimming and asked if I'd like him to mow it when he mowed his yard.  Of course I said yes.  Duh.  Well, I didn't realize it until it was too late that he took a weedwacker after he mowed the strip, and hacked my Allium and Mexican Heather that bordered my fence down to the ground.  I guess he thought they were weeds.  Weeds with beautiful purple flowers.  *sniff*  I'm heartbroken.  I didn't want to confront him, I mean he did think he was doing something nice for me.  Sharky says that they should come back if we water them well.  So, everynight, I'll be going out there with a hose and praying to the Yard Goddess that they resurrect.  At least my sunflowers are safe since they had a small wire fence bordering them.  Yeah, my "Mammoth Sunflowers" that barely made it to 2 feet.  LOL  Oh well, they're still pretty even if they are kinda munchkin like.  BTW, what is up with "Cornpone"?  I guess it's a nickname?  Maybe not.  After working on our family tree and seeing the truly bizarre names people (our flesh and blood!) give their kids, well, I shouldn't be surprised anymore.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Fun thing to do with money...  Try it, I dare you...
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Saying goodbye is a hard thing, you know?  We are trying to simplify our lives and declutter while we are doing it. It's hard, it really is. LOL As we find things, we try to evaluate it as to sentimental or financial value, practicality, and why we still have it. (Barbies are not included in this. LOL)  Some stuff might be sold, some might be  urlLink Freecycled , other stuff is given to charity, and some just gets chucked in the garbage.  I have (had?) many collections. Do I need them all? Do I enjoy them all still? Not really, most are just taking up space.  My coin collection is staying. Way too many happy childhood memories and it takes up very little space. Some of my childhood collections (MA dolls, Breyer Horses, Disney figurines) are still packed away, tucked in the back of a closet in a space not used. I can't deal with figuring out what to do with those right now.  My model car kits are gone now. Sharky fished those out of the attic this morning and took them to work, to "auction" them off to some co-workers. He said they went beserk when they saw what I had, in unopened boxes. He called me and asked what I wanted for them - I said "Barbies, vintage and mod, and lots of clothing." "Uh, what about cash?" "Cash is good too, so are TRU gift cards." LOL (There is a TRU down the street from where they work. LOL)  When he brought the subject up last night, I wanted to scream "NO, they're MINE!" But geeze, the kits have been packed away for over 12 years. When would I ever put them together? I guess I had been saving them for the boys, but they've never shown any interest in them. I did make Sharky promise that if any are left over, bring home and don't throw them away. Maybe I can sell them on eBay or something.  I went through the boxes before he left. Amazing, the memories, plans and dreams that came back when I saw them again. They really didn't disappear, just changed slightly and upscaled (pun!). Instead of the 1/24 scale VW garage that I wanted to build then, well, I want to build a 1/6 scale Harley garage now.  Sounds like this 37 year old still has a bit of growing up to do. LOL
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My "exercise" began yesterday.   I have to drive Bear, his shuttle spot at the HS is 1.11 miles away and I do not have time or the energy to walk him.  I walk Bug to school, 3 blocks there and 3 blocks back.  I then walk to pick him up.  Grand total of 12 blocks a day.  When I am able to do that without wanting to pass out or have my legs go numb, I will walk (all of us) up to pick Bear up at the afternoon bus stop.   That's a total of 6 blocks (3 there, 3 back).  When I get used to that, I can add in a block or two coming home in the morning and afternoon to stretch it out.  I have my bellydancing tape that I've never watched.  Today at 9:30, Petunia and I will put it in the VCR and take a gander.  I know she'll enjoy it.  I tried Tae Bo with the boys, but they wouldn't stop laughing.  Maybe someday... 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The kids fought all morning, and to think, they wanted to stay up until 10:00 p.m. to watch "Last Comic Standing".  (Thank Gods I didn't let them, the comedy was quite blue last night.)  Last year, their bedtime was 8:00 p.m. and we'd let them read until 9:00 p.m.  This year, we are letting them stay up until 9:00 p.m. - but I think we'll go back and implement the reading in the room for the 8-9 o'clock hour since they are so bad about reading.  *sigh*   Sorry, got off track.  I thought they were in a bad mood because of lack of sleep, but I don't know.   Dropped Bear off at the shuttle stop and he just walks away from the area and goes to the Security Guard.  Turns out, he asked him if the DC shuttle had been by yet.  Of course it hadn't.  The shuttle area was full of kids.  I called him back to the car to tell him I meant don't miss your AFTERNOON bus.  *rolls eyes*  OMGs, he has got to grow up!  I don't know what to do.  I keep giving him responsibilities and he just doesn't do it.  Where am I going wrong??? 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Every morning everyone wakes up in a bad mood.  I'm so tired of that.  I don't know what to do.  If I'm cheerful, hoping it will rub off, it just pisses them off even more.  My gods, is this what puberty is going to be like??? 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bus snafus, part two.  Five minutes before we were supposed to leave to pick up Bear from his bus stop, my cell phone rings.  It's Bear - he's missed his bus.  He doesn't know how it happened, but I'm sure that it's due to his not paying attention.  Maybe school day 3 will be better?  I got a lot done today, sewing-wise.  I sewed on all four of the boys' karate uniform patches.  Boy was that hard.  Yes, I'm serious, those patches were thick and my sewing skills are sadly neglected.  But, I took my time and they turned out well.  Not perfect, but well. LOL 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm trying to revamp our family website and having a hard time doing it.  Why do they make things so complicated?  *sigh* 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Second day of School.  Kids are back to their nutty selves, but at least Bear's drop off situation was better this morning.  I reworked the route so I come out at a traffic light 1/2 a block from his shuttle spot, so all I have to do is go around a corner, pull to the curb and drop him off.   The pick up yesterday afternoon was a nightmare.  We got there 10 minutes early.   3:50 p.m. came and went and no bus.  By 4:10 I was panicking.  Took 3 calls to the middle school before I got a human willing to talk to me about the buses.  Their response?  To put me on the phone with a cop at the school.  LOL  Luckily she was great and very understanding.  She said that 500 parents decided to drive their kids to and from school on the first day and the buses were backed up.  School started 30 minutes late and they still had kids waiting for a bus an hour after school ended!  She checked and Bear wasn't one of them.  Over 20 buses passed me on the corner during that time and he finally pulled up at 4:25.   Both Bear and Bug missed breakfast in the morning.  Bear, because the bus arrived so late in the morning, and Bug, because the elementary school cafeteria fed the PTA workers instead of the kids.  Yes, I am very pissed about that.  If I had known, I would have fed my kids first.  This morning, I fixed them have toast, just in case, but there shouldn't be a problem. 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just got back from dropping Bear off.  Took 3 passes in front of the high school before I found where his shuttle to the middle school picks up the kids.  Took everything I had not to burst into tears in front of him - and kept it in pretty good on the way home.  Guess I was spoiled by having my kids attend an elementary school 3 blocks from home for 6 years (K-5th grade).   Now, I will sit here and try not to vomit until it's time to pick him up.  I pray he will find the bus home safely and know when he's at his stop.  *sigh* 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today is the first day of school here in NE Florida.  So, please excuse me if I seem flighty.  LOL  We've been up and ready since 5:30ish this morning and just sitting and waiting to go.  (I had the kids get everything they needed together last night.)  OMGS, my son is in MIDDLE SCHOOL!  I think I'm going to throw up. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We've done a ton of laundry and the boys are getting ready to take their showers.  I looked out the front window and saw a dead cat in the road.  I told Sharky, who without being asked, went and got the shovel.  He dug a hole in our little "cemetary" in the back yard where we bury the roadkill from in front of our house.  The cat looked dark  coloured, so I called my neighbour to see if it was her cat, but she wasn't home.  Sharky took the shovel to the street and flipped it over.  I was standing on the front porch and saw that it wasn't a cat, it was a large black bird.  My heart almost stopped because my friend Lori had been talking about the dead crows in her neighbourhood (in LA) and West Nile Virus.  Sharky flipped it over again.  It wasn't a crow.  It wasn't a cat.  It was someone's hair weave.  He scooped it up in the shovel and tossed it in the garbage can and went and refilled the hole in the back yard.  I am so grateful that my neighbour wasn't home.  LOL 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tomorrow is the first day of school for the boys.  Why then, do I feel like it's my first day of school? LOL  We went to the zoo this morning, bright and early.  We had a wonderful time and walked farther than I thought my knee could go.  
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This morning, Sharky took Petunia to McD's to have breakfast and play on the playground - a father-daughter date.  She had a blast.  I wished they had gone someplace better (like a diner) but they don't have playgrounds.  LOL  The boys and I went to the thrift store.  We got there at 10 minutes to 9 am to beat the crowd and guess what?  There were already like 15 people there before us!  By the time 9 rolled around, there were almost 50 people in line.  Saturday must be the biggest day since they aren't open on Sundays.  We had a blast.  Found like-new shoes for Bear, like-new boots for Bug, belts, blue jean shorts, and lots of shirts for both.  We found in their sizes, two brand new (still had tags) Arizona denim shirts from JC Penney, marked down for $3.  Those are great for cool days when a jacket or a sweatshirt would be too much.  The two best buys was a gorgeous bronze coloured 100% silk shirt and a dark green shirt with Celtic knot work, both in Bug's size.  He's thrilled.  I know a lot of people (like my  MIL) frown on thrift store clothes for kids, but geeze, it would be obscene not to shop there when we are on such a tight budget. 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bug's orientation went well.  We're old hats at that school (this is our 7th year there) so we know where everyone and thing is.  A few changes, not much.  He has Mrs. TW this year - but she's pregnant and due any day - and he will have a substitute, Mrs. R, for the  next 12-16 weeks.  Mrs. R looks like she's right out of college (LOL) but the classroom was neat, organized, and all ready to go for Monday morning.  None of the other 5th grade classrooms were ready.  LOL  Bear's orientation yesterday was confusing.  The teachers weren't very organized, it was a madhouse.  The school is huge (compared to our tiny elementary school) and there are lockers and homerooms, etc.   After orientation today, we drove to  urlLink Chamblin Book Mine  and picked up two more books on Bear's reading list.  I bought Petunia two Barbie picture books and Bear picked out the first two Dinotopia books.  I'd much rather him read something with substance, but hey, it's better than not reading at all, right?  Chamblin's is a pretty awesome place.  Tons of books, shelves go from floor to ceiling and the aisles are like a maze.  Everytime we go there, we get lost.  That's not a bad thing.  LOL 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Does your dog have their own website?  Mine does! LOL  A friend shared this link and it's a cute, free site.  Here's my Gabby's page:  urlLink http://www.dogster.com/?55306 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We've got Bug's 5th grade orientation coming up in a little bit.  I am still trying to recover from Bear's yesterday.  *sigh* 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bear has orientation for middle school today.  Sharky's coming home early so we can all go.  Bear is so excited about it.  He's still reading book number 2 - out of the four he was supposed to read before school started.  Lazy boy.  He read "Prince and the Pauper" and now he's reading "Black Beauty".  I've bugged him all summer about reading and he won't do it.  Geeze, how can you force a kid to read?  Give him a book and lock him in a room?  Yeah, I can imagine it - he'd cry, throw a tantrum, and then go to sleep - never even opening the book.  *sigh*  The kid has a very high iq but hates to read.  My Gods, MY SON hates to read.  My child!  I just don't get it... 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We had Bug's birthday party last night.  I made a dirt cake (chocolate cake, chocolate icing, crushed oreos, chocolate pudding and gummi worms) and he LOVED it!  My Aunt gave him a book on how to draw Disney's "A Bug's Life", Mom gave him a GI Joe named Duke, a book on how to draw marine creatures, a radio, and a book on how they made the movie  Jurassic Park .  We gave him a book on shark attacks (LOL), a Power Team Elite "Joe", and Petunia gave him a small bucket of plastic dinosaurs.  At karate, they made him run the gauntlet.  He made it all the way through without anyone making contact, and smart ass that he is, decided to run a second time.  That time he tripped, fell and got punched good.  LOL  He wanted our Tex-Mex food for dinner last night, but we didn't have time.  We will fix it today so we will have plenty of time to enjoy it. 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The New Serenity Prayer   (Author unknown)    Grant me the serenity to accept the things I cannot change,   The courage to change the things I cannot accept,   And the wisdom to hide the bodies of those people   I had to kill today because they pissed me off. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Had a rude awakening this a.m.  Sharky asked me to get up and make coffee since all we had were instant coffee samples (ran out of 'real' coffee).  I went to the toilet and sat down (hey, I did just wake up) and Cosmo came running in, 90 mph.  Guess what was in front of him?  Yep, a 3 inch  urlLink palmetto bug .  Cosmo chased him right into the bathroom and under the door, where the bug took a left and went behind the sink.  Lovely.  Oh well, at least it didn't run over my feet.   We always have a palmetto bug or two after a good rain.  Sharky thinks they come in the house to die.  My cats are happy to oblige.  BTW, instant coffee is horrid. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's Bug's 10th birthday today.  Bear has already started his shit this morning.  He woke up, happy, and as soon as his father left for work, he turned into a hateful ass.  Won't help with breakfast, called his brother names, said no one loved him, yada yada yada.  I'm so sick of it.  He can't be nice to his brother for one freaking day?  It's Bug's birthday for crying out loud.  My mom is taking the kids and I to  urlLink Sweet Tomatoes  for Bug's birthday and will be giving him presents, along with all the school supplies she managed to buy.  But does that make Bear happy?  Nnnooooo...   The funny thing, if you separate the boys, they are miserable.  If you put them together, they hate each other.  I'm SO glad they will be in separate schools this year.  I think it will really help them a lot. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just another weird thing I found when I searched my name on the internet...   urlLink http://www.christel.co.uk/catalogue/topazcat.htm   Stockings.  Who'd a thunk? 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    One of my beautiful roses before they all died.  One day, I hope to try and grow some more.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>


</Blog>