<Blog>

<date>31,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      That was the worst day of my life.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Achoo: You're Dead   I just learned that when you sneeze, your entire body shuts down. Even your brain. It's like temporary death. Yes this is true and I'll talk to you since you probably won't believe me... It's a good thing for conversation. I just had a really cool conversation about it with a really smart person I know.. I just had to post this :P Goodnight! ^_^
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Inclement Times   Overall I'm just really confused now... I have felt the need to update my blog since I havn't for a while. And since my computer is being really odd right now I'll just keep typing if it freezes. Before I bore you with my confusion, I'll let you know whats been going on the past few ...time periods. I went to my cabin, that was really cool. I didn't get to swim =( it rained a bit I think... I can't remember really. Oh my back started to twinge... Hold on while I sit back in my chair.   ::Moments later!:: Wow my back feels better now! ::Just then!:: Oh sheesh I just realized my toasies are cold ::Suddenly!:: Socks....upstairs! ::Finally:: My toes are saved once again!  Now that I've made my life a living comic book I can continue... Yea I know that was lame and you shouldn't laugh at it, you will probably just be like ::tisk tisk:: donnie is weird :P. Well good I don't want anyone to think anything BUT that. Seriously... I could care less. So now I will tell you what I did recently... I went to my cabin (the Butts' were there, and I know you two are going to read this at some time.. And I also know you seem to like to be mentioned in my stuff :D so here ya go). Went to cousins (Last time seeing an aunt uncle and cousin for a looonng while :-/). Went to Soccer party (I played goalie, it was cool). The party was the best of those three... Since I am deep into a couple of conversations I don't feel like elaborating on those too much. So anyway let me see what I can type...Oh ya my sister Christy wants to be mentioned too, although I can't see why... She likes to snoop into my profile once or twice a...minute :P. Why do I feel like a need a shower now ;-). Anycow, I had something grand to type, but now I don't feel like remembering what it was. So you should all go to www.16yearoldreflections.blogspot.com for my good friend John's blog... He is really an awesome person, and it brings me down to think I'll be missing his presence when I move (Hey good thing is that you can still talk to me on the phone for 2 hours about religion! Oh no I'm not being sarcastic... I loved doing that it was fun). So lately I've been listening to the following bands: Evanescence, Sum 41, Godsmack, R.Kelly, U2, Jack Johnson, Usher, and Elvis... Some of those won't make sense, because they just are in some soccer clips that I've seen. So when I hear them, I picture the moves that are being pulled during that video.. I love soccer more then I ever loved hockey or baseball for the 6 year period that I played them.. But I'm afraid it won't be so fun anymore when I don't have to usual crew to play with... Maybe the Vegas people will be mean, not friendly, or really really good and I can't even compete.. I'll see what I can do, eh? I want to learn to draw. Teach me in like 5 minutes Mike. (Oh my I hope he doesn't read that he'll kill me) Hey look Mike, it's Legolas! o.o So bored! Someone IM me at toxictree6 and tell me what to type. I'll type something after that! End blog =/  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Cottenwood's Metamorphosis   Sit down children, we now hear a story about a young girl who went astray. No one quite knows how, but this girl happens to be in honors classes. Yes my friends, -honor- classes. So the story begins during the last week of school. If memory serves me right (Yes I did go into mental shock after this and lost some of the memory) it goes something like this:  So, as was already aformentioned, this all took place during the last week of school. Or was it the last month? I'm sorry, but I am currently in therapy to block this memory out of my head. The last month of school however, was very warm and it was like any typical Las Vegas summer. So we are all sitting in Communications class, and apparently some people were not paying much attention. A girl, who shall remain nameless (Oh whatever, for your own safety, her name was Kenna) cranes her neck and peers out the large glass window. Meanwhile a gust wind outside is bringing cottenwood seeds up through the air as if thermals of hot wind are causing them to be airborn. Now, Kenna is looking out and sees small white things flying through the air in a quite uniform way. And what have we been taught since we were small children to associate white objects in the air as? Snow! So, loud enough so it sounds like she is broadcasting to the whole class, Kenna exclaims "Oh my god it's snowing outside! Look everyone!" I almost fall out of my chair in shock as I am thinking "No. It's Cottenwood. Sit down before I stab you." So someone says something similar to that. The only thing she has to say is "No I'm serious! Look!" And I slide out of my chair shaking my head noticing that several other people looked outside and considered believing her.  You Americans worry about your bank's being robbed... Beware! The unintelligent people  are  out there!
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I FIXED IT!!!!  :STICKS HIS TOUNGUE OUT AT BLOG:  Evil evil blog when will you learn you can't beat a HUMAN
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Oh my god I wrecked my Blog! I went to Settings, format and turned the line break thingy off.. if i change it back it automattically changes itself when i leave that tab.... help me =(
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Oh my god I wrecked my Blog! I went to Settings, Formatting, and turned Convert Line Breaks off (NO I DON'T KNOW WHY) and now if I go to YES and save, the secong I leave that page it automatically puts it back to NO. Help me =(
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       The Story of Two Kids   Scott wants to have a piece on him... A Blog if you will.. There once was a guy named Scott, He thought to himself "I'm such a snot." Then one day he heard, "Boy you're not a turd!" So he drove to Iowa and got  (his girl)  This will probably only make sense to him... and here's my 45 second poem about how I feel being bipolar and all:  When you're happy youre on cloud nine, When you're sad you're walking a very thin line of depression and sorrow, but it'll be gone by tomorrow! So remember when you're good you shine
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Ping Pong Blitz   So... MAYBE today Blog won't delete my post.  :D What I did today... Woke up from about 4 hours of sleep is the first mentionable thing. I don't think that is enough for a growing boy like me, but I was having too much fun talking to people (you understand, I knew you would). First thing I did was wake up at 9.00am, and then immediatly start getting ready. I then went to a soccer clinic (for goalies more specifically), and worked hard for 3 hours. Now this, although tiring, was a lot of fun. After this I continued with my schudule for the day, which said that I was going to Victor's for ping pong (WITH MY BRAND NEW CARBON BASED 2-SPEED SUPER SPIN PADDLE WITH A NICE KITTY CAT ON IT :D). So I go there and play some hardcore table tennis for about 4 hours, and also play on the computer for about 2 hours. Now if this wasn't busy enough, I had some major fun at the house. I got to drive my sister back and forth (Been waiting to do that for WEEKS) and then I finally get to sit down. So I think about posting another blog, and consider not because it might delete it. Accually, this post was about to be deleted, I could feel my computer about to shut down. Luckily, I closed some programs and am not using -less- then 100% of the CPU. So now I sit here typing about ping pong and the like... Speaking of which, this is no normal ping pong.. Nono, this is ping pong with a white guy holding the paddle like an asian and an asian holding it like a white guy. So you get a 'cultural melting pot' so to speak :D. If I had to make a list of my 5 favorite things about playing pingpong with Victor, it would go about like this (IN NO ORDER!! ::shakes fist::)  1. Crowing Roosters  2. Roberto Carlos'  3. Hiccups  4. Edges  5. Wrist flick  If this makes sense to you, have a cookie. If it doesn't, you can ask me about any of them, or just pretend like you get it so that you can have a cookie...  Me and Scott were about to call four people to see if they wanted to go to a movie (inquire if you think this is you) at Hopkins for a dollar... Identity was the name, hacking was its game (see also, hax0r). Howeeverrr, we chickened out and decided not to :D. Maybe some other night I guess. But I really want to keep my streak of 5 movies a week up =Ãž... Anyways, so what I did instead is play Monsters and Me... My five favorite things about this MMORPG (Ask if you don't know what that is) are:  1. Actions with my turtles!  3. Turtle power!  4. The Turtle Army (TA)  5. Making a huge line of turtles to overpower all the other turtles in all the land  I skipped two in case you didn't see.... I'm out of twos, if you sell me some I will reward you greatly! So what is Monsters and Me? Its a role playing game basically, and everyone gets a pet and you just fight stuff to make you and your pet a higher level. I'm quitting the year of Revelation that I played, and starting this game up (Unless I get invited to movies, there isn't anything to do at night :P). So now I sit here, level 55 with a level 67 pet (It's a turtle...no joking) wondering why me and Scott didn't set up that movie... ::eats some oranges:: . Another thing about this week (Another? What was the first? ::shrug::) is that I had soccer every. single. day. On Monday, I was the ref for two 12 year old games (Oh ya, this was in the downpour, and I slicked my hair back to be more professional :D). On Today o.o I had that goalie clinic. Tomorrow I have another practice. Thursday I have a game against St. Cloud. Friday I have an independant practice. Saturday I have another team practice... Sunday we will have John practice I hope...in the rain... Speaking of soccer in the rain, that is where my happiest moment in life came accually..  About a month ago, we had John practice. We played World Cup (A game duh :D) and I was goalie. At first I was mad because there was this HUGE puddle of mud (the object not the band) and I didn't feel like diving in it with my white shirt. Then it began to rain. Oleg got the ball about 5 meters out and I was just like 'Ok there is no way I am letting Oleg score now,' so of course I dive and fall right in the mud puddle. Luckily it started to rain harder, and I didn't care anymore. So I dove (Dove? Dived? Diven? Divededen? O_o) all over , and I was playing really really well. The satisfaction that comes from denieing people from scoring their precious goals is unbelievable :D. So, after it was all over here is what I looked like:  1. As if I had third degree burns all over my legs and arms  3. As if I wore a black shirt to practice  4. As if I wasn't a simple Anglo-Saxon anymore  5. As if my shoes where blocks of black concrete  Everytime I kicked the ball I sprayed a huge rooster of mud at everyone... they were all getting so mad that they couldn't score... That's so far the best feeling in my life.  ::hugs Blog::
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Blog's habitual deletion tendencies   This thing just lost a really long post I had on spoons, now I'm too mad to repost it. I'll try again later. Darn... I had such a good post on how spoons caused that shotgun to make me blackout... I was finally about to point the blame on someone other then myself, and it got deleted... Darn...
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Blog's deletion complex  This thing just lost a really long post I had on theater, now I'm too mad to repost it. I'll try again tomorrow
     

    
</post>

<date>22,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I felt the need to post that, no, I'm not incapable of making proper links...Blog just stinks and wont listen to me >______ 

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Move over Morse Code   Wow I was just thinking about how stupid I sound when I talk... I mean, mostly when I am around Drew. We say such stupid things, you probably wouldn't even understand a sentence. We went to Dairy Queen and they didn't understand us when we wanted a Med Blizzardo with Cooklie Dog.  :(  I Suppose something can be done about it, but it is rather funny.... So yea, posted because I was getting numorous threats >. 

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      My new AOL instant thingie is CaptainGordoIII...Haha yes...My friends made me do it :D...Toxictree was old anycow
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Leavin' On A Jetplane   Ok...I haven't been very motivated to update this thingie in a while. To tell the truth, I'm still not. But, it's really key that I post this.  I'm not moving to Las Vegas anymore :D  So yea... It's because some guy freaked out, called the deal off (ok well he just pushed it back, but because of school there was no time for this). This was AFTER my house was put up for sale. AFTER about 5 people had looked at it. AFTER we bought an apartment dealy in Vegas. AFTER we had planned on leaving in a week. Yes, this is a huge shock..  Sorry if you're mad that you didn't get rid of me. I'm like a bad itch I just don't go away ;)
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Woo all better =D
     

    
</post>

<date>30,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Music, Food, SHOCK FREE SPRAY   Ooooh man I have this spray can stuff that makes all the static go away @_@. It's soooo cool! I mean...spray it on anything. Shoes, shirts, PETS! Mwhaha oh man it's so entertaining...if only it wasnt destroying the ozone layer while doing it.. I would say no static is worth the UV rays tho, don't you? So like, I want a little counter thing on my blog, who knows how to get one? Tell me if you do. And a little guest book thing. Oh man then I could FORCE people to write in it.. So I just added a link to my..links. Emily's blog! Emily is a good friend that Scott introduced me to a while back that lives in Edina...So check out her pretty blog! :D Next is music..Right now I like some Irish singers, and indy rock. Wait...no...that's not me...Nevermind. Alex just burned me FIVE Metallica CDs. So naturally I listened to five full CDs in one sitting. All awesome. Great stuff. Parents are NOT so pleased about the selection, and when I crank it they get mad for some reason...Psht...Parents.    Soccer...So like I thought we were going to lose TERRIBLY today, but we ended up winning 6 to 1 or something like that, I lost count. I was playing forward the ENTIRE time and NEVER scored. What the heck?! Oh well, at least I had two assists and made some guy cry...I think I might have hit him a bit TOO hard   School...So IB Bio...it's just like WHAT'S GOING ON HERE. AM I JUST MISSING SOMETHING OR IS THE EASIEST THING EVER?! I see why I switched out of that class in the first place.. Oh well it fits my slacking style much better. Slacking is so...satisfying. It's like hey look at me I don't want to work and I still have a lot to show for myself :D. Well not all like that, but it is a lot of fun most of the time. Instead of freaking out and being like oh man im so screwed for this test, it's just like...whatever, what's gonna happen is gonna happen. No panic dancing....   Homecoming ... Oh stupid I had to go to school with a 100 dollar bill today...That was insane, I felt really uncomfortable..My mom made me buy a ticket for my sister too, so I had to get THREE at a time, which was just WEIRD. Anyway, it will be worth it, as long as Christy isn't all pissed at me at the dance for some reason, and starts screaming "I HATE YOU I HATE YOU" over and over. If she does I am throwing a cowbell at her and she shall be knocked unconsious, at which point she will crumple over and everyone will start dancing to techno music. I swear it will happen..   Ok I just had to leave the room because my chest started to hurt. All the sudden the center of my chest got REALLY cold for some reason..Ok people, start calling out what items you want when I die.  Bah it's 10oclock, time to go to "sleep" @_@     
     

    
</post>

<date>29,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
        Hey Donnie, long time no see you come here ::asian accent::    Ah so wow still need to start updating this thing more often...Inside joke by the way, and no one that reads this will know...Ah well oh well. So news news news...Oh ya! I'm going to homecoming dance and football game :D with a  TOTALLY  awesome person! So awesome that I shall ask out soon ::hint hint::...Well ya, soon enough huh? So ya that's pretty huge news for me, since I just normally don't do anything like this, and I had to explain it all to my parents and such, blah blah I don't really talk to them about my life much, so it was hard (but worth it for you! =P). So ya, some things might change in my life I hope, for the better I hope, and it will be cool I hope. Hope..Hope, I have always used this in my life...When my sister was dieing...I had hope. The hope didn't pull through but I had hope. I had hope throughout the whole years my parents were in a depression. I had hope when she was in the hospital still, and thereafter I have always had hope. She fuels my hope. I couldn't do it without you Ginger.. You had the one of the hardest lives I have EVER seen for your age, and I can't even fathom what you had to go through...Which makes me cry what happened...And the day it happened. I know a lot of people learned from this, as did I..Started the whole hope thing...Which is good...After that I am always going through a bipolar thing, but I still have hope.. I know I can do it...and you can help..And I'm not trying to sound sappy, or whiny, but I am tired and writing about this the best I can from the heart... I know you got to the famous people you wanted to see, and I know you are happy that you taught us all of this...And thank's to all you people (friends) that have helped me even though you didn't even know you did...You are all helping....John, Lauren, Scott S., Brian, Drew....thanks gus...and everyone else...thanks...thanks
     

    
</post>

<date>22,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
        Ding Dong the witch is dead, the wicked witch, the wicked witch   Oh wow I havn't posted in a while.. Ihave accually had quite a social life going on, which is good I guess... this weekend is the BUZZ RUN, and if you don't know what that is...too bad. Ok...it's something at my cabin, and my dad organizes a motorcycle race with like 30 people there every year... Isn't that crap? No not really...it's fun, and so many people! Too bad I can beat all the old people at racing tho... heh. Well anyways, this is a good and bad thing. It's good because it's loads of fun. It's bad because I am screwing up other plans for the weekend with other people. >.   Also, I have had a deal with my parents for so long that I would get A's in school if I didn't want to have to get a job... But now I just don't care anymore...I am going to get B's I hope and have a job. I can't stand school anymore. I can't beleive how close I was today to just standing up and walking out. I was serioulsy half way out of my seat a few times.. So why the sudden change? No it's not, I have been thinking about this for the longest time....and now I just don't care about grades. I used to aspire to get really good grades, get into a great college, and have the best job possible all for money. Now I think I will get decent grades and go to maybe some different college to study a foreign language, or art of some sort. Maybe theater director at SLP ;D. Well I just am not motivated to get good grades anymore...so hopefully I will have a lifestyle change for the better...And much more fun. Cuz that's what it's all about right? :D No need to answer that one
     

    
</post>

<date>08,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I wish I could send her the silence of dust I want to tread upon her path and say nothing Once more shall she hear silence Once more shall I remain still The end grows near For fate swings it mighty spear   :(
     

    
</post>

<date>30,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Alright. Life just took a turn for the worst. I am not cared about by anyone in my family (No, I am actually not. There is absolutly no argueing this). I have asked if my mom signed the papers to take the IB tests. And she said no, and she doesn't care. I asked if I should just not take the test, and she doesn't care. I asked if I should just drop IB, and she doesn't care. I asked if I should just drop school, and she doesn't care. I asked if I should just leave and not come back, and she doesn't care. That's what's going to happen anyway, she says. What? Yes. You are done using my stuff, so you might as while go live the responsibility free life you like. Oh.. I was under the presumption that I had a family that loved me. You are. But you just said... Ok whatever.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Oh ya and I got a kitten :P
     

    
</post>

<date>02,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Long time no post     So I really obviously havn't posted in forever, but that doesn't mean I don't think about posting on my blog when I sleep. In fact, I do think about doing it but lately I have been chained to something that has fettered my life until this point. I can now make myself do things. I don't know how. I won't ever know how. But from now on I can have the self disipline to tell myself to do something, and I will actually act upon that. My life is going really bad right now, however. I lost the friendship of Lauren somehow (not sure how I f-ed that one up so badly) that could have at least been friendship, but instead it is nothing. Oh well, so much for a successful first try. Second times a charm? Nope...there is no second time. I don't know how I know this.. Somehow I knew over the summer that I would get a chance at this whole high school relationship, but somehow it got messed up and she chose to like someone else. Perhaps my mask has not been revealed to everyone yet. Nonetheless, I shall slowly unravel the stings that cover my true being. This shall be interesting! Help me out with this people..    Off topic, I have to get a job by Saturday for some reason or I get to stop being on the computer for a while. Less computer time = more control over myself = more power to me. I am glad in some ways, but really mad in the parental logic behind all of this.    Right after Tori left offline, things went downhill. My parents started getting mad, and I wanted to pick a fight so I did. I am very fluent in arguement when I have to. So that leads to one thing, and again and again until the domino effect reaches the point where I just want to leave. I just want to grab a couple of things and walk out the door. To the north, to toronto. Maybe I can stay with her for a while? Hah.    To my friends: Lets shake things up a bit, huh? Nothing new is happening. We are all sitting here in the bowels of the machine that is society plugging through one high school lesson after another. Something new is needed...And soon. Scott, are you workin on that revolution? I hope so...I could use one right now.   What else to say...Oh ya, good Echo you guys, I read most of the paper and it was really solid compared to the others. Way to go on three articles Janelle! Excellent ones, too.                The music .    It's been keeping me alive. Seriously, I would be so pissed 100% of the day if I didn't have some music to listen to. And you need the right type of music.. Oar does the trick, and I've been obsessing myself in them. I need the energy. Just how the entirety of the band feeds off the crowd, I am able to pilfer some of that energy for myself. I would like to research why this simple beat and lyrics are evoking so much emotion from me. It's almost all positive too. I am happy with the City on Down. I am delited with About and Hour Ago. I am exstatic with That was a Crazy Game of Poker. All of them in a chain leaves me smiling all school day as I hum in the hallways. I wonder what people think of me...I start laughing and or singing at such random moments. I hope they think I'm happy...I'd like to project that image. I wish my aura made others peoples aura brighten by the slightest of shades. That would make my aura get a bit brighter. A nuclear chain reaction is sure to ensue.   Out for now, hope I made you think about me a bit Captain (not a pompous title)   
     

    
</post>

<date>02,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      ...
     

    
</post>

<date>01,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Creamed....   Played Wyzata. Though would lose bad. No lose so bad. Score 3 to 2. We no do well in first part game. Tim blow it. I joke. Tim not do so bad. We all do well. Homecoming football tomorrow. I want go. Now.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Monkeys =\   Ah....we played Cooper today in soccer (Way to not come to the game Scott, Lauren, and Emily! j/k I know you had stuff to do). And Armstrong yesterday. And the other city that starts with a W tomorrow. THREE games in a row. What's that all about? I am already injuring from today....I will probably get injured more tomorrow. The good news is that I injured 2 players on the other team in the past two games...So anyway, we are going home and me Victor and Drew are just being total freaks. We started making the noise the Jackoffasaur makes (From South Park) REALLY loudly on the bus (and during the game, haha). Then victor starts doing the monkey noise, and I start screaming as loud as I can. Everyone starts cracking up, and me and Victor are screaming the monkey noises. It was SO loud. So I'm like HOWLER monkey! and I just start screaming really loud until my lungs run out of air...Then we recruit more people on the bus and we all open our windows. Next time we see someone we ALL just to make the monkey noise and scream and stuff. Monkeys are cool. So loud...Everyone is laughing...Oh man...we kept having to shift sides of the bus to scream at people on both sides. So insane. I'm such a freak.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      First survey ever to be posted here.    1)The singular most boring question: Do you have a picture? Yes (2) Are you happy with it? Nope. (3) Are you named after anyone? =D Just a …few times. Long story. :D (5) Your screen name: which one? Captain Gordo! (6) Would you name a child of yours after you? Haha. Yes. Probably. (7) Then what would you name your children? Autumn and…Uh..ülüsü. Just kidding!   (8) If you were born a member of the opposite sex, what would your name be? Gordina. Who the hell knows?  (9) If you could switch names with a friend, who would it be? Donovan. Tons of people call me that anyway. (10) Are there any mispronunciations/typos that people do with your name constantly? YES. IT’S DONNIE NOT DONNY! >_____________ (11) Would you drop your last name if you became famous? No..nonono.  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~  BASICS  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  (12) Your gender: Male (13) Straight/gay/bi? Straight. (14) Single? I don’t know (15) Want to be? meh  (16) Your birth date: may 5  (17) Your age: 16 (18) Age you act: Depends what mood I’m in. Ranges from 2-20 I’ve been told. (19) Age you wish you were: 17 (20) Your height: 5’9”  (21) The color of your eyes: “Hazel” (wtf is that exactly..) (22) Happy with it? Yea! (23) The color of your hair: Dirty blond? (24) Happy with it? Don’t care. (25) Left/right/ambidextrous? Right (26) Your living arrangement? Mom Sister and Dad…and cat.  (27) Your family: What?? (29) What's your job: Ice Cream Jockey (30) Piercings? None (31) Tattoos? Only wish. (32) Obsessions? Music, theories, Germany. (33) Addictions? Music, theater. (35) Do you speak another language? Some German (36) Have a favorite quote? “Sometimes when something is helped, they aren’t sure anything was done at all.” Don’t know. Thought I just made that up. And “It’s not about the shoes you wear, but about the footsteps you leave behind” –John Gianoulous.  (37) Do you have a webpage? You’re lookin at it.  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  DEEP THOUGHTS about life and you in it  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  (38) Do you live in the moment? Always (39) Do you consider yourself tolerant of others? No, people make me mad (40) Do you have any secrets? Billions. Why do you think I think I am disguised?  (41) Do you hate yourself? Only sometimes (42) Do you like your handwriting? I’m working on it…but no.  (43) Do you have any bad habits? Yes. (44) What is the compliment you get most from people? I don’t really get em. (45) If a movie was made about your life, what would it be called? Dull, duller, dullest. (46) What's your biggest fear? Alone, hurting things I love. (47) Can you sing? I don’t know, someone tell ,me if I can dangit! (48) Do you ever pretend to be someone else just to look cool? Hit me if I do. (49) Are you a loner? Not so much as I used to be. (50) What are your no. 1 priorities in life? Live long, prosper, make some people happy. (51) If you were another person, would you be friends with you? I think so.. (52) Are you a daredevil? With the right people. (53) Is there anything you fear or hate about yourself? I fear other people know me more then I do. (54) Are you passive or aggressive? Depends who I’m with (55) Have you got a ? feet (56) What is your greatest strength and weakness? I think I can help people without them knowing I am doing anything sometimes, but I am a really big jerk and I don’t even know it! (57) If you could change one thing about yourself, what would it be? That I could want something, then make it happen.  (58) There are three wells, love, beauty and creativity.. This question isn’t even a question! Instead of wasting a penny I would keep it and give it to some poor kid so he could buy some baked beans and live another day! =) (59) How do you vent? Scream in my mind.  (60) Do you think you are emotionally strong? I think so, I’ve lasted through all of this, haven’t I? (61) Is there anything you regret doing/not doing in life? Yes, I let a lot of things slip through my grasps. (62) Do you think life has been good so far? Half and half. (63) What is the most important lesson you've learned from life? Don’t condemn others…And live life for yourself. (64) What do you like the most about your body? My appendix! Which doesn’t exist. Long story. (65) And least? My appendix =( (66) Do you think you are good looking? Nope.  (67) Are you confident? Oh god no!  (68) What is the fictional character you're most like? Holden Caulfield. Kidding! (69) Do people know how you feel? Do they? I don’t know. Scary.  (70) Are you perceived wrongly? Yes, for sure.  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  DO YOU...  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  (71) Smoke? no  (72) Do drugs? no  (73) Read the newspaper? no (74) Pray? Not really (75) Go to church? no  (76) Talk to strangers who IM you? Not really  (77) Sleep with stuffed animals? no (78) Take walks in the rain? no (79) Talk to people even though you hate them? yes (80) Drive? yes (81) Like to drive fast? Who’s reading this?   *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  WOULD OR HAVE YOU EVER...  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  (82) Liked your voice? kinda (83) Hurt yourself? yes  (84) Been out of the country? yes  (85) Eaten something that made other people sick? yes (86) Had sex? no  (87) Been unfaithful? yes 88) Been in love? yes (89) Done drugs? no (90) Gone skinny dipping? no (91) Had a medical emergency? yes  (92) Had a surgery? yes (93) Ran away from home? Only thought about it (94) Played strip poker? no (95) Gotten beaten up? kinda (97) Been picked on? yes  (98) Been on stage? Yes. =D (99) Been so drunk that you know you're supposed to go out on a date with someone, but you can't remember with who or when and then you faint when you look at yourself in the mirror in the morning, not to mention your breath? O.O (100) Slept outdoors? yes (101) Thought about suicide? yes (102) Pulled an all-nighter? Yes, probably 3 times a year (103) If yes, what is your record? A couple of days (104) Gone one day without food? yes (105) Talked on the phone all night? Never use the phone (106) Slept together with the opposite sex without actually having sex? no (107) Slept all day? yes (108) Killed someone? no  (109) Made out with a stranger? no (110) Had sex with a stranger? no (111) Thought you're going crazy? yes  (112) Kissed the same sex? no (113) Done anything sexual with the same sex? no  (114) Been betrayed? yes (115) Had a dream that came true? yes  (116) Broken the law? yes (117) Met a famous person? no (118) Have you ever killed an animal by accident? yes (119) On purpose? yes  145) Told a secret you swore you wouldn't tell? No. never! 146) Stolen anything? Probably not (147) Been on radio/TV.? Probably not (148) Been in a mosh-pit? no (149) Had a nervous breakdown? yes (150) Considered religious vocation? no (151) Been criticized about your sexual performance? no  (152) Bungee jumped? no  (153) Had a dream that kept coming back? yes   *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  CLOTHES and other fashion  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  (154) Shoe brand? ?? soccer stuff (155) Brand of clothing? Soccer jerseys (156) Cologne/perfume? sometimes (157) What are you normally wearing to school/work? Jeans and a jersey? (158) How about parties? Same, or shorts (159) Wear hats? yes (160) Judge other people by their clothing? Probably…only once in a fortnight (161) Wear make-up? Lol. Probably. (162) Favorite place to shop? I don’t like shopping (163) Favorite article of clothing? Bayern-Munich jersey (164) Are you trendy? Am I? (165) Would you rather wear a uniform to school? no   *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  BELIEFS  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  (166) Believe in life on other planets? yes  (167) Miracles? yes (168) Astrology? Not really (169) Magic? no (170) God? yes (171) Satan? no (172) Santa? no (173) Ghosts? yes  (174) Luck? yes  (175) Love at first sight? no  (176) Yin and Yang? Forgot what that was (177) Witches? no (178) Easter bunny? aww i wish (179) Believe it's possible to remain faithful forever? Doing my best  (180) Believe there's a pot of gold at the end of the rainbow? Moo (181) Do you wish on stars? I wish on EVERYTHING  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  DEEP THEOLOGICAL QUESTIONS  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  (182) Do you believe in the traditional view of Heaven and Hell? No (183) Do you think God has a gender? No (184) Do you think that science counteracts religion? Yes (185) Do you believe in organized religion? Yes (186) Where do you think we go when we die? Lately, I like Scott’s idea. But I don’t want to misquote it so I won’t type it.  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  AMIGOS  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  (187) Do you have any gay/lesbian friends? no (188) Who is/are your best friends? Scott, drew, Emily, Tori. (189) Who's the one person that knows most about you? I don’t know..My mom? (190) What's the best advice that anyone has ever given to you? Try. (191) Your favorite inside joke? TONS. Those are great. (192) Thing you're picked on most about? You’re good at everything, Donnie. GRRRRRRRRRR  Friends (194) Newest? I guess Emily, or Spencer. And my sisters friends. (195) Shyest? Trevor (196) Funniest? Drew (197) Sweetest? Er. I dunno. (198) Closest? See 188 (199) Weirdest? Natasha o.o weird=good. (200) Smartest? Donovan (201) Ditziest? N o  c o m m e n t .  (202) Friends you miss being close to the most? I guess Lauren. (203) Last person you talked to online? Emily (204) Who do you talk to most online? Emily, Tori, Scott. (205) Who are you on the phone with most? No one. (206) Who do you trust most? Everyone  (207) Who listens to your problems? Scott Emily Tori (208) Who do you fight most with? Scott. (209) Who's the nicest? Er, I dunno. Victor. (210) Who's the most outgoing? All my friends are lazy! Emily, I suppose. (211) Who's the best singer? I don’t get together with my friends and sing. (212) Who's on your shit-list? No one. (213) Have you ever thought of having sex with a friend? Ugh, no. (214) Who's your second family? None. (215) Do you always feel understood? no (216) Who's the loudest friend? Greg. For sure. You dink! =p (217) Do you trust others easily? Yes (218) First person you fell in love with? I don’t know.  (219) Name one person whose arms you feel safe in: Er, no one? (220) Do your friends know you? i guess yeah (221) Friend that lives farthest away: Tori. For sure. Which sucks. For sure.  **********************************************************************************   *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  LOVE, and all that  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  (222) Did you get frightened or uncomfortable seeing that as a section title? ..... no  (223) Do you remember your first love? yes (224) Still love him/her? Yes (225) Do you consider love a mistake? no (226) What do you find romantic? I don’t know. Compliments. (227) Turn-on?  (228) Turn-off?.  (229) First kiss? None! =D. Whew. (231) If someone you had no interest in dating expressed interest in dating you, how would you feel? I wouldn’t. (232) Do you prefer knowing someone before dating them or going "blind"? No experience. (233) Have you ever wished it was more "socially acceptable" for a girl to ask a guy out? Yes (235) Have you ever been romantically attracted to someone physically unattractive? Yes (236) Do you think the opposite sex finds you good looking? No. =[ (237) What is best about the opposite sex?: They…have more feelings? (238) What is the worst thing about the opposite sex? Confusing to me, maybe not to everyone. (258) What's the last present someone gave you? my computer from my mom  (257) Are you in love? no (258) Do you consider your significant other hot? Quite a shallow question. (264) What would you do if you were walking down the street and saw some hot guy/girl standing on the sidewalk? Um, nothing. *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  THE BATTLE OF THE SEXES  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  (267) Have you ever wished you could experience being the other gender? No (268) If you did experience that for one day, what would you do? nothing (269) What do you love most about the other gender? I don’t know (270) What do you dislike most? I don’t know (271) What do you understand least? Everything (272) Honestly, what do you notice first in the opposite sex? The look they have to them. Their aura   *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  POSSESSIONS  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  (273) What is your fave possession? Cat (274) What physical, tangible possession do you want most?  A certain person. (275) How badly do you want it? I don’t need to answer this. (276) Have you ever seen The Exorcist? Yes (277) How long did it take for you to understand why the last question is in this section? 1 second. *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  WHO WAS THE LAST PERSON...  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  (279) That haunted you? None (280) You wanted to kill? None. (281) That you laughed at? Donovan. (282) That laughed at you? Sister (283) That turned you on? . (284) You went shopping with? none (285) That broke your heart? ::sigh::  (286) To disappoint you? Lots of people. (287) To ask you out? It’s never happened. (288) To make you cry? I don’t know, myself? (289) To brighten up your day? Scott  (290) That you thought about? Tori  (291) You saw a movie with? Scott and Emily  (292) You talked to on the phone? Scott. Ride to work.  (293) You talked to through IM? Emily  (294) You saw? Sister (295) You lost? Lost- Lauren. (296) You went head over heels for? Dunno 97) You thought was completely insane? Lot’s of people. (298) You wanted to be? No one but myself. (299) You told off? No idea. (300) You trusted? Eeyore. (301) You turned down? Never been asked.  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME YOU  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  (302) Smiled? Now (303) Laughed? Now (304) Cried? Not so long ago.   (305) Bought something? Today. (306) Danced? I dance all the time! I just get nervous and can’t do it in public (note to some people) (307) Were sarcastic? Today (308) Kissed someone? Never (309) Talked to an ex? Never had an ex (310) Watched your fave movie? Don’t have one (311) Had a nightmare? Yesterday 312) Talked on the phone? Yesterday  (313) Listened to the radio? Months ago (314) Watched TV? Few hours ago, football. I hate football  (315) Went out? Today for thanksgiving to aunts house.  (316) Helped someone? No idea. (317) Were mean? Always (318) Sang? Now, to Good Charlotte, havn’t listened to them since summer. (319) Saw a movie? Today. Bruce Almighty. It was good. I like Jim a lot.  (320) Said "I love you"? Today (319) Missed someone? Today (322) Fought with a family member?lol. 100% of the time (323) Fought with a friend? Few days ago (324) Had a serious conversation? Yesterday (325) Smoked weed? Never (326) Got drunk? Never (327) Had sex? never  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  A LAST TIME for everything...  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  (328) Last book you read: The Things They Carried. I love it. (329)Last movie you saw: Already answered. (330) Last song you heard: Say Anything.  (331) Last thing you had to drink: Cherry 7Up (332) Last time you showered: Few hours ago (333) Last thing you ate: Pumkin Pie (334) Last CD you bought: Matrix Reloaded Soundtrack (335) Last thing you bought: Shoelaces  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  RIGHT THIS MOMENT...  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  (336) Had Sex? no  (337) Are you going to? In my life?  (338) Will it be with your significant other? Stupid survey  (339) Or some random person? Not that kind of person O.o (340) What are you wearing right now? Weird white pants, and my Pirates of Penzance shirt. (341) Body-part you're touching right now: cheek (342) What are you worried about right now? Stuff working out  (344) What's on your mouse pad? I have no mouse pad.  45) Use 5 words to describe how you're feeling: always with the sad feelings (346) Are you bored? yes  (347) Are you tired? very  (348) How long did this survey take u? Almost 50 minutes 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hey I found a poem that I kinda liked  A million voices swirling, But far and wide are those understood.      A teardrop falls,      The emotion calls, Towards the end, which path to choose?  Holding on tight, dazed and broken, no path is clear, there is no order.      A lightbulb flickers,      My brain, it bickers To descruction! It's not a matter of choice.  A shadow of silence drapes over.   Why is it calmest,   Just after the storm? Everything is dull when it's gone.  -Unknown.  Fits the mood!
     

    
</post>

<date>17,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I think I'll just post funny things that happen at work from now on.   Customer- So who is nick? Scott - Uh, the boss. Customer- Well, where is he? Scott - He went home for the night..he doesn't work nights. Customer- Oh, because my name is Nick. Me (as I am finishing up scooping his 4$ ice cream) Well in that case, this will be free. Customer (With a -huge- look of excitement, mouth open and eyes wide) - REALLY? Me - Nope just kidding (ring up the food)  Me (Serving up a two flavoured double cone) - Do you care which flavour is on the top or the bottom? 40 year old customer - No I don't care if I'm on top or --- (looks behind him at the two 14 year old girls) Uh...nevermind.. Me (Can't scoop because of laughter)
     

    
</post>

<date>17,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      7. LEAST FAVORITE SMELLS?  A giant colony of mold covering half of a cantaloupe  21. WHAT WAS OR WILL BE YOUR FIRST CAR? hopefully a lambourghini, viper, benz, or beat up rusty tractor   22. IF YOU COULD MEET ONE PERSON DEAD OR ALIVE WHO WOULD BE?  Jesus, Muhammed, Confucius (Kung-Fu Tzu), Charlemagne, Akenaten or Cleopatra, Alexander the Great,   25. IF YOU COULD DYE YOUR HAIR ANY COLOR WHAT WOULD IT BE?  paleish blue, or some color not visible to human eyes but visible to insect eyes, so bees and hummingbirds would try and get pollen from me, then i could finally see a hummingbird, and take the bees and make them all work together on a beefarm and rake in a ton of cash     Posted without permission. Written by Donovan
     

    
</post>

<date>15,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Happy belated birthday tori........
     

    
</post>

<date>06,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Update: Theater is sucking all my time up! Ahhhh! It's ok though becuase it puts you in a good mood no matter what. All the stress somehow builds up so it's FUN stress! Gotta love that stuff. I've had some REAL conversations with Greg and Spencer lately, and that helps my mood more. I hate that stupid little between-classes-chit-chat stuff. I'd rather talk about life anyday. Too bad the people I can do that with are limited to around four. Well anyways, the cast party was awesome. So much more fun then last years when I just left and didn't talk or anything. Now me and Greg can climb up the back porch and start freaking out when the lights come on! Pool was cool too, even though I beat you every game! mwhahaha. Better luck next time, and maybe we can stay later then 1am tonight. I told Kaz to bring DDR tonight, so if he does that will be sooooooooo cool! If Anna is there she plays too. And I think that would be a good cast party activity. Ummm getting bored now....Everyone did great though...Except whoever bumped the house lights! >. 

    
</post>

<date>06,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       O.o  MakeMeBadAnubis (1:26:55 AM): lol, k, i'll try not to descend our convos into whorish smut talk from now on. bye! need sleep...*falls asleep and bangs head on desk and jolts awake. Gets up and leaves. Opens door. Walks through hallway. Opens door to room. Goes in room and turns off lights. Get's in bed. Telekinetically signs off AOL and shuts down computer. Falls asleep. Dreams about discovering an assassination plot involving Ronald McDonald and the Riverdance Mafia.*   Good 'ol Donovan.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Donnie (1:00:06 AM): but the real question is...which way does the current flow? Scott S. (1:00:16 AM): downstream Donnie (1:00:19 AM): lol Donnie (1:00:24 AM): i mean symbolic Scott S. (1:00:24 AM): the flow of time Scott S. (1:00:29 AM): moves forward Scott S. (1:00:31 AM): downstream Donnie (1:00:35 AM): thats not symbolic! Donnie (1:00:40 AM): what i mean is Donnie (1:01:22 AM): are we eternally damned to be a puzzle broken into peices by the river, or does the current flow towards hope and possibility? Scott S. (1:01:35 AM): if i had that answer... Donnie (1:01:57 AM): then you would save me a lot of time Scott S. (1:02:02 AM): yes Scott S. (1:02:27 AM): im gonna save that question you just asked me Scott S. (1:02:29 AM): i like it Donnie (1:02:42 AM): whats the question? Scott S. (1:03:17 AM): are we eternally damned to be a puzzle broken into peices by the river, or does the current flow towards hope and possibility? Donnie (1:03:46 AM): ah Donnie (1:03:52 AM): i've always wondered that Scott S. (1:03:55 AM): yeah Donnie (1:04:06 AM): entropy, or extropy Scott S. (1:04:13 AM): right Donnie (1:04:14 AM): it's not a matter of choice, is it Scott S. (1:04:22 AM): i dont think so Donnie (1:04:47 AM): so has it already been determined, or will we beasts of humans decide our own fate subconciously Scott S. (1:05:05 AM): god, i've been thinking about this a lot lately Scott S. (1:05:12 AM): i keep going back and forth Donnie (1:05:16 AM): join the club. Donnie (1:05:32 AM): how do we not have a philosophy club in our school Donnie (1:05:42 AM): we have so many people that are interested in it Scott S. (1:05:43 AM): i dont know, but if we did Donnie (1:05:51 AM): always a but. Scott S. (1:06:01 AM): you're the only one i like talking about it with Donnie (1:06:18 AM): yea..i dont want to hear Rami tell me why ecofeminism will take over the earth Scott S. (1:06:25 AM): haha Donnie (1:06:46 AM): so, which side do you lean to at this moment. Donnie (1:06:59 AM): destruction or opportunity...its your call Scott S. (1:07:07 AM): oh geese Scott S. (1:07:38 AM): dont you already know my answer though? Donnie (1:07:47 AM): Not if you are going back and forth Scott S. (1:08:00 AM): i see fire Scott S. (1:08:03 AM): destruction Scott S. (1:08:07 AM): death Scott S. (1:08:11 AM): no more light Scott S. (1:08:13 AM): it's lost Scott S. (1:08:21 AM): why should I die? Donnie (1:08:21 AM): halocaust Donnie (1:08:30 AM): burning Scott S. (1:08:31 AM): see the saga through? Donnie (1:08:42 AM): perhaps there is yet something that can be accomplished Donnie (1:08:45 AM): a purpose of sorts Scott S. (1:09:16 AM): i only see one way two combat the flames of vengence though Scott S. (1:09:35 AM): a total refusal of our current system Donnie (1:09:56 AM): you propose to fight the flames of vengence with your own holocaust Scott S. (1:09:56 AM): which would mean a refusal of school and all structure what so ever Scott S. (1:10:04 AM): i know Scott S. (1:10:08 AM): i dont make sense Donnie (1:10:09 AM): fire will never defeat fire Scott S. (1:10:19 AM): only fuel a larger one yes Donnie (1:10:37 AM): aye, a tyrant amoung destructive times Scott S. (1:10:37 AM): so then let us remove ourselves from the fire! Donnie (1:10:44 AM): into space! awwwwaaayyy! Donnie (1:10:46 AM): lol Scott S. (1:10:48 AM): ha Donnie (1:10:54 AM): no no no. Donnie (1:11:03 AM): it is our duty to extinguish this fire Scott S. (1:11:12 AM): yes it is Donnie (1:11:20 AM): a fire that, make a note, is fueled by unjust morals and lost souls Scott S. (1:11:21 AM): but see, i'm sick of talking about it Scott S. (1:11:34 AM): I'm more than ready to begin Scott S. (1:11:40 AM): but i dont know how! Donnie (1:11:46 AM): just shoot Donnie (1:11:49 AM): shoot and dont look back Scott S. (1:11:51 AM): everyone always asks me "when's the revolution"? Scott S. (1:11:58 AM): and i say "soon" Scott S. (1:12:03 AM): but i dont know how to start! Donnie (1:13:06 AM): Well.. Donnie (1:13:22 AM): There are certain...decisions you must make before anything begins Scott S. (1:13:39 AM): like what Donnie (1:13:48 AM): Never leap blindly into the fire, Scott. For it's flames are decievingly hot. Scott S. (1:14:07 AM): but thats all i know how to do Scott S. (1:14:12 AM): shoot and dont look back Scott S. (1:14:20 AM): just start running... Donnie (1:14:24 AM): Then be prepared to be burned.. Donnie (1:14:34 AM): And take notice, with the fire, you only get once shot. Scott S. (1:14:43 AM): thats why i dont know how to start Scott S. (1:14:47 AM): i know I'm gonna fry Scott S. (1:14:58 AM): so i want to think of another way Donnie (1:15:13 AM): Then perhaps you should not reply soon any longer Scott S. (1:15:23 AM): huh? Donnie (1:15:29 AM): When's the revolution Donnie (1:15:31 AM): soon. Scott S. (1:15:35 AM): oh Scott S. (1:15:39 AM): but Donnie (1:15:44 AM): Say..not soon enough, but it will come Scott S. (1:15:51 AM): i need help! Donnie (1:16:12 AM): But far and wide you will have to look for help with such a dangerous subject! Donnie (1:16:54 AM): However..I can advise you partially Donnie (1:17:12 AM): First order of business: NEVER trust the little old man with the wispy beard Scott S. (1:17:13 AM): I would never ask you to do something you didnt want to do Scott S. (1:17:20 AM): ha, right Donnie (1:17:21 AM): I never said I didn't want to. Scott S. (1:17:27 AM): i know Scott S. (1:17:30 AM): just for the record Donnie (1:17:46 AM): throw the record in the fire Scott S. (1:17:53 AM): done Donnie (1:18:01 AM): then you can proceed Scott S. (1:18:07 AM): ok Donnie (1:18:15 AM): dont tangle yourself in the past, when the future is cumbersome enough Scott S. (1:18:23 AM): true Donnie (1:19:09 AM): You must decide....what type of revolution is in order Donnie (1:19:19 AM): You must factor in many many things from the world as it is now. Scott S. (1:19:31 AM): see thats the thing Donnie (1:19:47 AM): How can you proceed without supporters Scott S. (1:20:19 AM): I dont know Donnie (1:20:33 AM): we both knew it wouldnt be easy, right? Scott S. (1:20:40 AM): right Donnie (1:20:49 AM): im telling you man...Stalin knew what he was doing Scott S. (1:20:55 AM): yeah Donnie (1:20:56 AM): gain power slowly Donnie (1:20:57 AM): and friends Donnie (1:21:02 AM): the more the merrier Scott S. (1:21:05 AM): true  Scott S. (1:21:11 AM): but Donnie (1:21:17 AM): serious;y...we should start saying hello to every person that we know their name Scott S. (1:21:25 AM): ok Donnie (1:21:29 AM): if one person ends up supporting us, it was not a lost cause Scott S. (1:21:34 AM): right Scott S. (1:21:43 AM): but what is our cause Scott S. (1:21:51 AM): thats what i need to figure out Donnie (1:22:13 AM): well...do we need to exinguish the fire, create a more organized one, or just fuel it and let it burn out quickly. Donnie (1:22:24 AM): of of three paths lie before you Scott S. (1:22:28 AM): ooo, well said Scott S. (1:23:03 AM): well lets think Scott S. (1:23:17 AM): i want you to be my number one in all of this Scott S. (1:23:23 AM): we share power 50-50 Donnie (1:23:40 AM): Hmmm...make it 49 - 51 in your favor Scott S. (1:23:44 AM): ha Scott S. (1:23:46 AM): alrighty Donnie (1:24:01 AM): We'll do it like the Las Vegas business...49 51 Scott S. (1:24:05 AM): ok, so what would happen if there was no fire all of a sudden? Donnie (1:24:16 AM): a new one would surely spark Scott S. (1:24:19 AM): right Scott S. (1:24:22 AM): so Donnie (1:24:29 AM): however.. Donnie (1:25:00 AM): when there is no fire, there is no order. when there is no order, there is certainly a new group of people that restore their own order, thus sparking up a new fire. Scott S. (1:25:08 AM): right Donnie (1:25:12 AM): who's to say we couldn't be that group Scott S. (1:25:20 AM): god point Scott S. (1:25:43 AM): i mean Scott S. (1:25:44 AM): good Donnie (1:25:48 AM): understood Scott S. (1:26:05 AM): but what if we just tame it Scott S. (1:26:12 AM): nah Donnie (1:26:20 AM): less risk, less probability of success Scott S. (1:26:25 AM): yeah Scott S. (1:26:27 AM): exactly Donnie (1:26:36 AM): keep in mind that a fire is the quintessence of wild.. Scott S. (1:26:53 AM): right.. Scott S. (1:26:57 AM): i think. Donnie (1:27:01 AM): there is no order the the flicker of its fingers grasping at the air! Scott S. (1:27:11 AM): true! Scott S. (1:27:28 AM): so we are left with-fuel it and let it burn out quickly Scott S. (1:27:32 AM): pros and cons Donnie (1:27:42 AM): less personal Donnie (1:27:46 AM): we do our thing and wait Donnie (1:27:51 AM): perhaps adding this and that Scott S. (1:28:00 AM): and would probably involve.... force Donnie (1:28:00 AM): they both end in the same place...a new order Donnie (1:28:20 AM): perhaps emotional force could be used Scott S. (1:28:28 AM): hmm, interesting Scott S. (1:28:43 AM): well, which one are you leaning to? Scott S. (1:28:55 AM): i think i might actually think about extinguishing it Donnie (1:29:08 AM): sounds better Scott S. (1:29:16 AM): yeah, thats what im thinking Scott S. (1:29:26 AM): we should take lessons from ghandi also Donnie (1:29:32 AM): never read any of him Scott S. (1:29:44 AM): well, neither have i really Donnie (1:29:56 AM): oh. Scott S. (1:29:57 AM): i just know he used all non-viloent resistence Donnie (1:29:58 AM): he sounds wise though Donnie (1:30:02 AM): oh, cool. Scott S. (1:30:08 AM): i think that stuff is REALLY powerful Scott S. (1:30:14 AM): more so than violence even Scott S. (1:30:17 AM): sometimes Donnie (1:30:27 AM): Martin Luther King Jr. Scott S. (1:30:38 AM): right Donnie (1:30:46 AM): this will require some speechcraft, man Scott S. (1:30:56 AM): yeah it will Scott S. (1:31:07 AM): ok, so its decided Scott S. (1:31:14 AM): we put the damn thing out! Donnie (1:31:27 AM): there is always the option of just letting it burn Donnie (1:31:31 AM): its not running away Donnie (1:31:35 AM): dont think of it as that Scott S. (1:31:41 AM): ok Donnie (1:31:50 AM): but just leaving it, and going to another side of the world...perhaps checking up to see its status Scott S. (1:31:54 AM): but if we just let it burn, is that just doing nothing? Donnie (1:32:00 AM): well..yes Scott S. (1:32:24 AM): ...so we run away? Donnie (1:32:29 AM): no no. Donnie (1:32:43 AM): it's only running away if it is your duty to deal with it in the first place Scott S. (1:32:54 AM): isnt it though Donnie (1:32:56 AM): if you think that this was the reason you exist on this plane of existence...then i shall help Scott S. (1:33:15 AM): i finally feel like i have a purpose Scott S. (1:33:23 AM): you need not follow me Donnie (1:33:31 AM): i shall offer what i can Scott S. (1:34:05 AM): well, this is what i need the most help with at the moment- a begining objective Donnie (1:34:31 AM): no Scott S. (1:34:36 AM): thats how we can rally the people though Donnie (1:34:47 AM): that would be jumping towards the fire only half blind Scott S. (1:34:53 AM): ok Donnie (1:34:59 AM): dont act until you can deal with all possible consequences Scott S. (1:35:09 AM): well how do we prepare? Donnie (1:35:40 AM): brainstorm? plan things out well, you wont regret it Scott S. (1:36:15 AM): right, but.. we need an objective of some sort, if only for planing purposes Scott S. (1:36:27 AM): how can i plan if i dont know what im doing? Donnie (1:36:44 AM): On paper Scott S. (1:37:00 AM): yeah, put what on paper though? Donnie (1:37:05 AM): the pen is your sword! the ink is your blood! Donnie (1:37:33 AM): uh... Donnie (1:38:40 AM): a doctrine Scott S. (1:38:47 AM): hmm Donnie (1:38:51 AM): WHY do you want this Donnie (1:38:57 AM): why do you think it's your purpose Donnie (1:39:03 AM): who do you want Donnie (1:39:07 AM): why should they join you Scott S. (1:39:29 AM): but see thats the thing, we need to figure out what "this" is Donnie (1:39:51 AM): the extinguishment of the era, and the dawn of a greater order Scott S. (1:40:03 AM): well put Donnie (1:41:45 AM): how did i keep you online this late? Scott S. (1:42:11 AM): the possibilty of answered questions Donnie (1:42:24 AM): i am sorry if i have not fufilled that Scott S. (1:42:30 AM): no you have Donnie (1:42:35 AM): ah, then no regrets Scott S. (1:42:42 AM): start gaining support Donnie (1:43:00 AM): and you Scott S. (1:43:05 AM): but people want to know "WHAT are you wanting to do?" Scott S. (1:43:14 AM): thats what they always ask me Scott S. (1:43:19 AM): how do i respond to that? Donnie (1:43:25 AM): Hm. Scott S. (1:43:49 AM): we begin with a display! Donnie (1:43:55 AM): Ah. Scott S. (1:44:05 AM): a display to show all those that we are fed up Scott S. (1:44:12 AM): with the current system Donnie (1:44:30 AM): Better untangle the questions within yourself before you place them upon others Donnie (1:44:39 AM): We have time Scott S. (1:44:48 AM): time time Donnie (1:45:05 AM): Remember...you only get one shot Scott S. (1:45:14 AM): i dont think so Donnie (1:45:27 AM): the fire can consume you Scott S. (1:45:36 AM): i could yes Donnie (1:45:37 AM): depending on how much you touch it Donnie (1:45:44 AM): thats key. Donnie (1:45:56 AM): if you get too involved..you will only get one chance Scott S. (1:46:04 AM): yeah Donnie (1:46:06 AM): if you know when to quit and reflect on what to do, then you are ok Scott S. (1:46:15 AM): right Donnie (1:46:37 AM): dwell upon this Scott S. (1:46:56 AM): oh i will Donnie (1:47:08 AM): go to sleep with the quote "And so we beat on, boats against the current, borne back ceaselessly into the past" Scott S. (1:47:18 AM): i cant sleep yet Scott S. (1:47:24 AM): much too much work to be done Donnie (1:47:32 AM): oh really Donnie (1:47:40 AM): see?! i distracted you waay too much Scott S. (1:47:47 AM): no Scott S. (1:47:49 AM): this was good Donnie (1:47:52 AM): ah ok Donnie (1:47:54 AM): no regrets Scott S. (1:47:58 AM): right Donnie (1:49:17 AM): however Donnie (1:49:24 AM): i have a TON of work to do in the morning Scott S. (1:49:30 AM): yeah Donnie (1:49:36 AM): so i shall go enjoy my 4 hours of sleep Scott S. (1:49:43 AM): alright Scott S. (1:49:48 AM): see ya tomorrow Donnie (1:49:58 AM): farewell Donnie (1:50:19 AM): and so we beat on..    Session terminated at 1:50:19 AM 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Do you ever wish a bird from above would fly down and save you from the sorrow of life  do you ever ponder what a savior would be like to lift your spirit, mind, and soul  does the thought ever pass that dreams just might seem slightly more real then the waking hours  here at the beginning of all things the end of all things  do you ever wish you could have your own savior
     

    
</post>

<date>11,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hmmmm.. Banned from computers.  Don't expect a post anytime soon. Har har.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ARGH. Why the hell do people do things just to piss people off?!?!?!?!? I don't get it!!!! What has the world come to when people get joy out of watching others suffer? How does the world not collapse in on its axis and crush every living being when this is going on daily. I don't fucking get it.  this type of bahavior the type that causes kids to bring guns to school and murder hundreds of people........... Not that I would do that. What's worse is that by posting this, I'm giving the person exactly what they were after!!!! How does one end this damn cycle? Why are we still here if this is always happening. I don't. Fucking. Get it.   I'm writing this at school while the rage is still in me, because if I wait until I get home, I know I wont feel the same. Nonetheless, I do not think it's ok for people to feel this way. To torture others for their entertainment. Where is the glory in that...   What happened to the times where kids had morals? I can see how these people that do these things might grow up and see their faults, but what about all the things that have been done and can't be taken back? What about them?! They don't even realize how many people they can break on a day to day basis.    It's damn lucky for both of us that I am calm person, or we might both be in a lot of trouble and/or injured. --------------------------------------------------------------------------   On another note....     screw it   i forgot what i was going to say
     

    
</post>

<date>06,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      HAHAHAHA!! I actually WORSENED things by posting that!! HAhaha ironic!!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok.. Here's my problem. It's seriously ruining my life.   How can I tell the difference between taking too much crap from someone, and just being TOO serious and not joking enough?   How do I draw the line between being a stick in the mud, and being someone that doesn't stand up to anyone.   How do you tell someone the truth when it makes them feel bad.   Why do people do things just to provoke the other person to feel bad?   I can't even tell when I am being stupid. I can't see myself talking. There is no mirror in front of me to show myself. I say things without caring, and people take them so damn serious and think I'm stupid. Why can't I just say things that I don't really mean. That's just how I operate.   Why do you have to joke around about me being stupid so much? I know you're kidding, but it just gets really irratating and makes me feel bad about myself.   I've done some weird things in the past few days, and I think I may have made a few REALLY important people feel bad. I really don't mean to, but watching all those people talk to you.. It drives me crazy! Yet, I can't tell the difference between me allowing too much and me suffocating you. What's the difference, how do I draw the line...I need to know, because if my ideas about how to tell when enough is enough were wrong, then I could have gone through a lot of unneccessary pain. Not that I'm not totally happy with things now, but I need to know, and you need to know, and everyone needs to know...   I am struggling with this so incredibly much, and I really need to figure out if I'm the only one..  I can't concentrate on anything because of that.     Feeling depressed Donnie
     

    
</post>

<date>02,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Weeee, it's been a while since I posted. That's because....NOTHING HAS BEEN HAPPENING. My life, as I know it, is scraping the banks of time, and always falling back into the river below. I finally find a way to proceed farther, and I just get pushed back by some force..Perhaps gravity. Damn gravity, always on the job. Anyways, that's what's up with me. I need to design a perpetual motion machine by the end of the week, by the way.. PAYING WELL!  Although the screen may be clear as crystal What's there is only an illusion The perfect world is out of your grasp It's simply not real, it can give no conclusion How can you overcome this It seems to impossible Within no one's reach..     How 'bout, a revolution?  Right.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      For those of you that still check my blog...    I don't want to discuss my problems. I just feel like adding them to that dense black ball at the bottom of my heart and waiting for it to explode. Are you sticking around for the fireworks?
     

    
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      why do you smile when the rope's around your neck                this fight is not worth fighting
     

    
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A change in the winds! I always thought it a good thing. But when it comes down to it, you don't realize how much you love a daily task until it changes forever and something different takes its place. It's been a long, long time since this has happened to me. One can forget how it feels, and how to deal with it. It's almost incomprehensible to fathom the next day. 24 hours from now, my life will probably be the exact same. In face, there's probably only a .00000000001% chance that anything will be significantly different. But I've figured it all out! I live for that percent! I live for the impossiblity. I live for that minute fraction. Someday, I will experience it. The change of the winds will eventually come. I can't avoid it, and I don't want to.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today... A short story..! I don't even know what story I am going to tell as I type this, but I'm sure I'll think of one...It's going to be about Germany! And the trip last summer! Because, that's where all my summers are....AHA! Thought of one. So we went on the trip with two other groups, one from Minnetonka, and one from Seattle. Now, the Seattle group was composed of Jr. High kids. The Minnetonka one, of seniors. Now, being that the Seattle kids were...Jr. High kids, we -could- have given them a break, but no, they didn't deserve it. For example, one hotel we stayed at was very very nice. You entered the giant wooden French doors, and step in on the marble ground to see a giant lobby, with a comfortable "phone" room off to the left, and three marble steps leading up to the giant receptions desk. There were several comfortable chairs with a medium sized oak coffee table, scattered with phone books, maps of the city, and brocheres for various bussinesses that rented bikes for the day, and other things to do in the city. The receptions desk was positioned in the center of the spiral staircase, so after you dragged your bags up the marble stairs or squeezed into the tiny elevater with 8 other lazy people, you could look right down the staircase and see the desk from a bird's-eye view. This is a pretty large spiral staircase, too, probably 15 feet across. So one night, before check in time actually, the Jr. High kids grab a broom....Now, I don't know what motivated them, but they threw it...Straight down the middle of the staircase...For no reason... It crashed on the desk, scattering papers everywhere. WHAT THE HELL? Ok, ... I don't know why...Wouldn't the thought of that make you angry?! Yeah! Yep. That's a story, I got's a ton of em =D. Too bad no one will read it...Hmm... If someone tells me too, I'll write more stories.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      All better now.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Person 1: What makes you happy? Person 2: I dunno. Person 1: Well, what makes you sad? Person 2: I dunno. Person 1: What are you thinking about? Person 2: I dunno. Person 1: What's important in life? Person 2: I dunno.       heh..
     

    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Sugar and spice and everything nice...          hahahahahahaha
     

    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Late one night in a smoke filled bar, a man stepped up to the smokey and dimly lit stage and struck out the first chord in  From One Conciousness to the Next . The crowd murmered and groaned, their only sign of appreciation in their state of pure inebriation. There were no cheers, and no clapping. The song ended as soon as it had begun, and the man stepped down to get a glass of liquid. Perhaps this was not such a great choice.. One of the drunken customers swept up the stage and grabbed the poor man's guitar. He immediatly smashed it over the nearest amplifier, shattering the better half of it into shards and splints. What remained in his hand was the long neck of the device, which was now more of a sharpened spear. Laughing like a maniac at his own joke, he pointed at the artist with the spear and giggled. "Looook 'ow ol' he iss!" was heard throughout the bar by those still in the condition to decipher conversation. Still laughing like there would be no tomorrow, he jumped off the stage, spear in hand. He didn't quite remember what he was doing up on the stage, but he had some feeling that the artist next to him was a dangerous murderer.     The fender telecaster peirced his chest four times.       Disoriented and unable to breath, his deep red lifeline flowed like a river from his mouth, ears, and of course his torso.       It took the paramedics twenty minutes to get there. Car pile-up just outside the exit ramp that leads to this place..One cat in the middle of the road, and everything goes straight to hell.     "It's a shame.." "Indeed. Want me to make the call?" "Are you joking? It's Friday, I don't want to deal with this." "Ok, to the incinerator then?" "Yeah, quickly though."  His body was incinerated, and the ashes were thrown in a simple blue plastic garbage bag.       Biography of Scott Shaffer's death, by Donnie Hicks. Edited by Scott Shaffer (post humously) 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Since I'm not like most people, and I don't feel like posting about "how my day went," I feel like I should still post something. More people check these things then you might think. It's like..Whoa..Yeah. So anyways, I don't use my blog to "vent" the energy or anger that built up during the day, or to otherwise use it to inform others about what I did today. If you want to know you can ask!   John, do you still check this thing? If you do, we should talk sometime, and think about some questions to think about. That was good...I might have a few things to say..   So. Right now, I'm thinking about...Homework...and not just what everyone says ->  "I'm so lazy!"   "I hate homework!"    "This is stupid!"  Is it possible that one is so unmotivated to do homework at this point in life, but will somehow magically become more motivated once out of high school... As of now, I can't do my homework for reasons I'd rather not discuss, but I feel like once I'm on my own schedule, I will be slightly different. Something weird is telling me that I just wont have the same "forceful" figures beckoning me to start my homework. Maybe I can make my own choices when to start. That's why I want to go to a summer school college. If my thoughts now do not match up to the reality of things, then I'm sorta screwed over gong into college with that kind of mindset...So I dunno...Gotta make a choice. Just like always!  Current music:  !....I don't do that! ..But my computer is making some funny noises....real funny indeed..
     

    
</post>

<date>13,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Germany pictures start on the second page...   http://img35.photobucket.com/albums/v106/silversun/
     

    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok...I'm going to start posting pictures from germany....    If you can't wait, just go to   http://img35.photobucket.com/albums/v106/silversun/   Most of those are from Germany :P
     

    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
         Ahh Germany, I remember you..
     

    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
        var data, p; var agt=navigator.userAgent.toLowerCase(); p='http'; if((location.href.substr(0,6)=='https:')||(location.href.substr(0,6)=='HTTPS:')) {p='https';} data = '&r=' + escape(document.referrer) + '&n=' + escape(navigator.userAgent) + '&p=' + escape(navigator.userAgent) if(navigator.userAgent.substring(0,1)>'3') {data = data + '&sd=' + screen.colorDepth + '&sw=' + escape(screen.width+ 'x'+screen.height)}; document.write(' urlLink '); document.write('   ');  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I also thought of something else to say, about something my friend Yap said.   I am half empty. Someday I will be half full. I am not, right now.    Thanks for telling me your story, I think it was inspiring.       OMG, that was Haiku, right? I didn't even try to do that...
     

    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I guess, it's been a while since I've posted. I didn't even realize people read this.. Then I check the counter every so often and it's always like 100 more hits.. So interesting.  So lately I've been pretty zoned out. My mind is basically always thinking about one thing or the other, but never the right one. I wish I could focus, channel SOMETHING. But nope. That would be too good :D.   So I talked to my friend John about a problem of the world. What do you do with those total jackasses with no respect for people, so shallow their actions can be, and you can only shake your head and wonder why. He concluded, and I had to agree, that the only thing that could be done is to just treat them with respect. Now you may ask yourself, "Why do these people deserve my respect?" Well frankly, they don't. But the thing is, everyone has done bad things in their life, and yet they still can be mean to others that are merely doing what they are doing. If you disrespect them, you are merely perpetuating the hatrid. But that's not what we want. We want it to end. So you can't insult them, because they'll insult you, and a vicious cycle will come. You can only hope that some of them will look back and say "Wow, look what I have been doing." Now not all of them will do this, but you can only hope for those who do. You can't be mean just to make the cycle continue. That brings you to where they are..They only way to end it is to be that light-at-the-end-of-the-tunnel figure. Not ideal, but better then some options.       I aint workin for your father, but I might as well be, I aint lookin' for confusion, but it tends to follow me.  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Last thing..I was thinking about this. I wonder if "popular" people look down on a person like me. Or, is it sad that "a person like me" is an acceptable phrase.  You all may want to talk about how your day went, and what's irking you about your best friend's behavior (completly random example, I have no idea if anyone wrote about this), but I'd rather see what's on people's minds at a deeper level, and give them the same opportunity should they choose to like the same thing. It would be sad, and even tragic, if someone read this, and immediatly got the impression that they didn't like me. Unfair, it's your choice to read this or not...You've made it this far, why not delve deeper into the broken shards of my brain?
     

    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "Hey, this might sound really...weird of me, but, are you getting a ride home?" "Probably." "Ok, just looking out for my fellow human being, sorry for creeping you out if I did, g'night." "It's ok, I actually don't have any ride home, thus my pacing around the parking lot." "Er...Were you planning on sleeping here...?" "I dunno, I was gonna cross that bridge when I got there." "Haha, clever...Can I help you out anyway?" "Well...I'm not one to mooch..." "It's ok, you could always give me a dollar for gas.." "I don't have any money.." "Well then, I shall do it anyway...where to?" Slipping the swinging key into the lock, unlatching the door, and clicking open the handle, I drive home alone, by myself, and with no one. Not exactly eager to forge the next pseudo-conversation.  A black audi races by me, misses my car by about 6 inches, and blows past the stopsign. Teenager, without a care in the world. You only live once, right? Besides, his life was more important then mine, and obviously worth riskining both our lives to get to his destination five minutes earlier. But the million-dollar question is: Does he deserve my respect?  How do you draw the line?  A motley car roves down the street in the opposite direction of mine. Windows open, radio on, one headlight slicing through the night. Male, about 20, on his way home from his friend's house. He hates the fact that he has a bedtime just because "he's under his paret's roof for the time being." Doesn't matter, that's not what is on his mind. He's blissfully lost in his music, because his favortite band is on the radio (he has no cd player, so hearing music he likes is rare) playing one of his favorite songs. It doesn't matter which one. Know why? Because I don't know him, and he's already over 6 blocks behind me.  Incomplete thoughts..Incomplete conversations..Fake meetings..We've got questions,  no one  has answers.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Dr Mr. Anderson. It is with deep regret that we must inform you of your most recent loss. Hundreds of points are lost, and shall never be retrieved. The mood has been set in the company because of this, and as you know, it is not a happy one. The depression is waving over each and every employee like wind over a field. Amazing how one mistake caused all of this. However, I diverge. You, Mr. Anderson, are no longer a valuable asset to this company. There is no redeeming your mistake. There is, however, something you can give us. Nay, you owe us. You no longer need it, so we ask that you sign the forms left on your desk to confirm the repossession of said object. All is not forgiven, or forgotten, but rather, all is lost. After this loss, the company may well go back to its state 20 years ago. You, a single man, an individual, has caused this. You, Mr. Anderson, are the reason and the purpose for this. You, Mr. Anderson, are no longer working here. We are revoking the funds from your previous paychecks, as well as your bank account, for the necessary repairs. We know you will have no objections to this. In fact, you are probably no longer at this location, having run like the coward you have proven yourself to be. You may be gone, but there is still plenty for us to take from you. Goodbye. 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Nutshell!!!***
     

    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      NUTSHELL!*
     

    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      World War II in a nutshell, by Greg Holmes.   So Europe was having this war see, and we were all like "we don't want to mess with that shit" so we just slowly started selling them stuff to make war. like guns and tanks and bombs and shit like that  which was good cause we were kind of in this thing called the depression  so then there were these little yellow people that lived on this big island and they wanted to take over the world  But we were all like "he none of that shit going on while we are around, ok?"  but they said fuck you and bombed us  ok well that gave us an excuse to go kick some ass over in Europe which we did first cause we were all like "man those Germans are white and they can do stuff, we will get those yellow bastards later when we feel like it"  but in the meantime we gathered all the little yellow people in the US up and put them in these camps  and cause all the MEN went of to kick major ass the women had to step in and do the working, again good cause now there is no more depression  Well the women were like "hey this is cool to be treated equally" but the men who were still around were like "none of that shit!!!!! Only while there is a war, then you go back to your kitchens!!!!!"  and so then we were kicking ass all over Africa and then we invaded Europe and freed the French blah blah blah  and the ruskies, commies, bears whatever you want to call them were kicking ass from the other side and Germany was like "oh fuck we are so screwed  and we were all like "HAHAHAHA, yeah!"  And we were also kicking some ass in Italy and they just plain gave up, which made the Germans say "SHIT SHIT FUCK FUCK!!!!!"  But then the bad thing happened!!!!!!!!!! FDR died!! oh so sad :'(  it was ok cause we beat those Germans and that little man with the mustache  Ok right so then we were like "hey, where are those yellow people hiding?"  But … that crazy man with the mustache... well he was so scared of everyone that had bigger dicks than him that he rounded up and killed everyone that did  which explains why all the Jews got it and gays and gypsies  But we found this out and where like dudes that is just not kosher!  and we had been fighting them but we wanted to kill them second  and hahahaha we found out that we had this new mega killer bomb that made a really cool explosion and a neat cloud afterward  so we said "hay this is great cause we get to kill yellow people and white people don't have to die"  so we tried it twice  and like the pansies they are they surrendered before we could get any more  And so we were like “hooray, we win! Those dumb axis people thought they could take over the world, FUCK NO!!!! THAT IS OUR JOB YOU DUMB BASTARDS!!!!!!!" those bastards were making a move on our turf!!!!!!  So then all the MEN came home and they were like "what the fuck are you doing out of the kitchen woman?"  and all the women were like "oh man that was cool to be treated equally"  And the men were like “well that was an accident now shut up and make me a sandwich!!!!!"  and the women were all like "shit this suxs, but ok"  and that's the story of how some yellow people and a bunch of white people tried to take over the world but were stopped by the USA and its' bitches
     

    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am defunctional. I am broken. Shards, broken. Shattered, broken. Precious glassware, broken. I do not work. Work, the bane of my existence, in a manner of speaking. Work, my downfall. Technology, my downfall. School, my downfall. People, my downfall. I fall down. Down, the place I don't belong, yet exist within. Within, the trap I have created. Escape, impossible. Impossible, my quest. To get back to the top. Where I belong, yet do not exist within. The top, outside the cage, outside the metal cage, outside the vinyl cage, outside the saltwater bag of organs, outside the trap. Trap, human life, crawling through the sewage, and for what? Hope, the blind man leading us deaf people through the times. There is no light at the end of the tunnel. Trapped, broken, and fallen.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      this is what i feel like posting                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                       done
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Wow..I'm like, so much happier now that I'm ONE step up from totally alone =D. I know it may seem I am blowing things up and that it can't possibly last ( =( ). It's still nice, good feeling, heh. Argh!
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      You who will pass thousands of lives without notice You who will one day calmly lie in the ground To be human, mortal, careless, and blissful. You, who kills and murders without noticing Forgive us, for we know not of what we do.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      To err is human, to forgive is divine. -Alexander Pope  Lord, what fools these mortals be! -William Shakespear    I'd like to point out that EVERY single entry under "France" is negative in the 21st Century Dictionary of Quotations.  A relatively small and eternally quarrelsome country in Western Europe, fountainhead of rationalist political manians, militarily impotent, historically inglorious during the past century, democratically bankrupt, Communist-infiltrated from top to bottom.    -William F. Buckley  There's always something fishy about the French.   -Noel Coward  (heh)  How can anyone govern a nation that has two hundred and forty different kinds of cheese?   -Charles De Gualle  Boy, those French - they have a different word for everything.     - Steve Martin  Frenchman have an unlimited capacity for gallantry and indulge it on every occasion       -Moliere   (!)  The French complain about of everything, and always.      -Napoleon I  France has neither winter nor summer nor morals - apart from these drawbacks it is a fine country     -Mark Twaine  France is the country where the money falls apart and you can't tear the toilet paper.   -Billy Wilder     That's all of them , haha 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      You who will pass thousands of lives without notice You who will one day calmly lie in the ground To be human, mortal, careless, and blissful. You, who kills and murders without noticing Forgive us, for we know not of what we do.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok so I figured that although I normally don't like to post about my daily life, I will today. I am anxious. That's it. Not worried about finals, not nervous about prom (or lack therof at this point in time), nothing else. I am waiting for AFS to accept me into their German program. If I am accepted, I will be going to Germany for a whole semester next year..Although I have this terrible feeling that I wont get in. That will suck...so much..Anyways, that's it. Anxious.  Conversation of the day:  "Hey." "I see your hey and raise you a "What's up" "..." "It's a joke son." "I see." At this point the a loud snapping noise rings through both people's head and everything goes completely black. They both wake up in a white room, dead. Tied upside-down from the ceiling via heavy chain. Thier souls fall to the ground, stumble around, and mutter something about the room smelling funny. The bodies hang motionless. 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Testing 123
     

    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok so I figured that although I normally don't like to post about my daily life, I will today. I am anxious. That's it. Not worried about finals, not nervous about prom (or lack therof at this point in time), nothing else. I am waiting for AFS to accept me into their German program. If I am accepted, I will be going to Germany for a whole semester next year..Although I have this terrible feeling that I wont get in. That will suck...so much..Anyways, that's it. Anxious.  Conversation of the day:  "Hey." "I see your hey and raise you a "What's up" "..." "It's a joke son." "I see." At this point the a loud snapping noise rings through both people's head and everything goes completely black. They both wake up in a white room, dead. Tied upside-down from the ceiling via heavy chain. Thier souls fall to the ground, stumble around, and mutter something about the room smelling funny. The bodies hang motionless. 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      And so we beat on. Happy birthday.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      One morning I got up from bed and checked the phone. Someone had been knocking on the door. After I got up and put on slippers I opened the door. The floor was very cold. At the door was a fat woman that insisted I come downstairs with her. The hotel was big, so I asked if I could get dressed first. She agreed and waited outside the door while I dressed. My window had been left open, and when I looked out I could just see the markets starting to open for the day. 	Downstairs the woman suggested I sit down with her at a table. The lobby was also very big. I looked around and noted the hotel’s features. She looked up and smiled. “I have a message to deliver to you.” “From who?” I said. “A Mr. Robert Cohn.” “What does he want?” “To meet you at the Rue Soufflot today at noon. He came by last night and didn’t want to disturb you, so I took a message.” 	I took the S bus like always down the streets to get to the restaurant. I knew Cohn would already be there and probably already drunk. From the window of the bus I saw some billboards advertising for some wine. Crossing the street I opened the door to the Rue Soufflot and immediately saw Cohn’s at a table. He looked at me with some sort of Jewish pride look, to show that he had arrived first. It was a fine day and I felt bad going indoors. “Nice to see you, Jake.” Cohn said. “Don’t call me Jake.” “Glad to see me?” “Sure.” I lied. I was still angry after all this time. I barely remember why. I couldn’t remember a lot of things from that time, or any time. We ordered some drinks and started drinking, but not saying much. When the food arrived there was more silence. Not until after all the food was gone and cleared off the table did he say much. “Curious why I am in Paris?” He smirked. “Actually, I am. Why are you here? To bother me?” “Of course not Jake, why would I?” “Why do you do anything? Why do I do anything? It’s always the same reason.” “What’s that?” “Because there is no reason, Cohn. Not for you, or me, or anyone.” 	We were both quiet after I said this, sitting at the table, and sometimes taking drinks from our wine glasses. The waiter came at one point and asked if we would like anything. This broke the silence for a moment, and I said no. Outside the streets were dampening in the weather. I looked back at Cohn and smiled. “I would have thought you would have figured that out by now.” “Jake, you make no sense sometimes. So do you want to go on vacation with me or not?” “What?” “Oh, that’s the reason I came here. Brett and I are going on a business trip to Africa. We are both in the same business, training to be journalists.” “No thanks, I am busy.” I was still smiling. I asked Cohn if he was finished. He left the bar quite confused and angry, unlike me. I didn’t expect to ever see him again, but what did that matter? 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Woohoo. 93rd percentile for ACTs. Not bad for not studying...lol
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hmm...Home now..12:21 to be picky. Wonderful evening. Sitting down now. 12:22, to be picky. Need to start my [approximatly] three hours of homework. Funny, that.  I should have just gone home after my game and worked.  Perkins is more fun.  Dragging one of those huge concrete yellow poles in the middle of the street is more fun.  Saying goodnight to Kathrin in person is more fun.  Homework.   Psh.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It sucks to play a soccer game for 90 minutes with 10 people. It sucks even more to then play two more games the next day with 10 people. It sucks even more to then play another with only 8 people, the very next day. It sucks even more to play yet another game the next day with god knows how few people.  Apathy sucks.         Chilling is with friends is fun. Being alone sucks.  Playing soccer is fun. Being massacred sucks.  Having ideas as to what to do to releive bordom is fun. Being bored sucks.  Being with Kathrin is fun. Being alone....just sucks.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Good god...Never save this much homework to start at 12:30 =)....Only took me until 2:00 AM tho!!! Not bad. As you can tell by scanning, my writing got very....dumb.   Session 2  Assignment 1: Read chapter 2, do vocabulary sentences on page 40 and “Check Understanding” questions 1, 4, 7, and 8.  1.	Charter, a document issued by the government. 2.	Hacienda, a large estate owned by a Californian Spaniard 3.	Cash Crop, a plant grown by a farmer for the intent on selling 4.	Patroon, one who is given a large estate by the Dutch government 5.	Indentured Servant, a person with a contract set up that set up a system of work to repay a debt in order to gain freedom 6.	Mestizo, a person of Spanish and Native American descent 7.	Pilgrim, a traveler to a new land (often religious) 8.	Famine, the lack of food for prolonged periods  Check Understanding 1.	Spanish conquistadors were able to overpower the Aztecs with technology. Cannons, guns, and swords easily crushed the simple spears and arrows of the Aztecs. Not only that, but the Aztec ruler was dead, leaving the remaining Aztecs leaderless.   4.	Jamestown, although initially unappealing to reside in, proved to be a great settlement due to the improvements to the town. One man, named John Smith, was able to lead those not already killed in the harsh winter to improve Jamestown. After making alliances with nearby Native American’s, he pushed people with the quote “He that will not work, will not eat.” After Smith was forced to leave, Jamestown’s future looked grim, until the implementation of a cash crop, tobacco. The Native American’s taught those in Jamestown how to plant tobacco, and the settlers were able to expand Virginia greatly.  7.   Two important ways that the colonies differed were the time they were settled in and the reasons for settlement. The New England colonies were, on the whole, settled first. They were settled primarily for religious freedom, with one of the colonies focusing on a Puritan settlement. The Middle Colonies were settled around the same time as the New England Colonies. They, however, were settled more for trade reasons, with one of the colonies existing as a Quaker society. They Southern Colonies were discovered mostly after the other two areas, and were settled for trade reasons, land reasons, as well as for a Roman Catholic settlement.  9.	William Penn most likely set up a colony with religious freedom because of his own religion. He was a Quaker, and Quakers believe in kindness to others, equality, and religious freedom. He probably wanted to set a colony up in America because anywhere in Europe he might be subject to persecution. Also, he seemed to want to prove that all religions could live together in harmony.  Assignment 2: Write a “Personal Compact.” 	 	My parents are the leaders of my house. I shall respect all of their rules, as well as the spirit of those rules. They have provided me with everything I need, thus I owe it to them to give them my utmost respect. There are also many others with a higher “status” then me, and those that deserve the respect I have shall get it, and I shall abide by their rules, as well as the spirit of their rules. However, it is within my rights as a human being to pursue happiness, liberty, and life. There is a certain finesse in creating boundaries for oneself, but it is within the maturity of a 17 year old to make a valid attempt at this. Structure is certainly necessary, and it is within these higher organizations that a foundation for the limits of my life shall be laid. However, I shall remain in a state that I am able to make my own decisions.   Assignment 3: Compare and contrast Puritans and modern-day.  	I find it nearly impossible to compare something to “modern-day” culture, as that cannot be summed up in one group. There are millions of life-styles, and to put them all into one group is like to divide the world’s population into people with the “right” beliefs and those with “wrong” beliefs. However, there are certainly a lot less people that adhere to the belief that education is only necessary to understand the Bible. Education is still held highly, although. Another thing we share for the most part is taxes, and the belief that everyone can contribute to society by giving money to the government to fund things.    Assignment 4: Skim pages 1-356. Note interesting topics. •	Rebellion in the colonies •	Native Americans in general •	The Gold Rush •	Utopian Communities •	The Civil War •	Industrialization •	“A Revolution in Technology” •	World War I            Session 3  Assignment 1:  Create a map of the Thirteen Colonies. (seperate paper)  Assignment 2:  Investigate the origins of tobacco and how it affected the different nationalities and economy of those that settled in North America.  	Tobacco was all important in colonial times. It fueled the original “city” of Jamestown, as well as the expansion of Virginia with came about all because of this cash crop. It was taught to the settlers by the Native Americans, which we might owe to the positive relationships John Smith built up with them when he was still in the area. Not only that, but it is also the reason for the enslavement of an entire race. If it were not for the great need for thousands of workers in the fields because of how successful this crop was, there may have been no need to capture Africans and force them to work for nothing. It affected the settlers by making those owning plantations rich. Although we can attribute everything that came about in this era to all the cash crops, it was tobacco that was the main reason for slavery, the mercantile system, and everything in between.   Assignment 3: Research the Target Market Movement. What are current issues? How do these compare with colonial times?  	The issues now and then are very different. The main difference is that back then the issues focused around those trying to sell the tobacco, and now the main issue is in the effects on the community that it has. Back then, people only cared about how many slaves were due to ship in, or how much land they could acquire to grow their crop, or maybe the best place to sell their crop. Now, however, there are ads running about how many thousands of people die every month to tobacco, and how secondhand smoke kills a ton of people as well. It is interesting to see how society has changed. The tobacco companies may still be worried about the same things, but much of the general population has wised up and found there are more issues to worry about then growing seasons.   Assignment 4: Read page 54 and answer questions 1 through 4. Write your reaction to the issue of slavery. Who is being “enslaved” today?  1.	Equiano was completely unaware that such people in the world existed. He was obviously not suspecting such an abduction to occur. He also did not have time to react, as his mouth was covered before he could let out a cry. Equiano was probably confused to the point of unconsciousness. 2.	The treatment endured and observed by Equiano was terrible. He was beaten himself, and saw many others getting the same treatment. There was torture as punishment for the simplest mistakes, and he himself was flogged for denying food. 3.	It is difficult to tell Equiano’s reactions, as this piece of writing is very short and emotionless. He says each sentence with a certain starkness, as if it is all he can do to keep calm. Obviously it was beyond terrible, and yet he is able to simply retell the events. 4.	Equiano must have been a very strong person. It is not anyone ordinary that can withstand such torture and live through it. Being able to retell such events shows another kind of strength. He is able to recount what happened for the education of others, even if he is recalling something so terrible that he may simply want to be able to forget it ever happened.  Slavery is obviously terrible. There is nothing I can say that has not already been said a million times over. It was unjust, unfair, brutal, and there is nothing we can do to forget or forgive those that partook. We must simply consider that other societies have done similar things, and yet we are able to make fun of them. To make fun of the enslavement of Africans is complete taboo in modern society, yet people are able to hate others when we have killed so many Native Americans and Africans. It is important to remember slavery in America, as a proof that no nation is perfect. Sometimes Americans get this smug little view that nothing could possibly be better in an already perfect nation. They forget, however, that the world can change at the drop of a hat, and the past cannot be overlooked. The argument “That was then, this is now; besides, we were forgiven by African Americans” is useless. This memory must serve to remind us that we are human, and that a group of us can get together, make bad decisions, and ruin many peoples’ lives. Moving on…I believe that we are the only “slaves” today. We tend to trap ourselves in our own heads. Not everything that should be said is shared. Some things are shared that should not be. We are unable to judge what is right and what is wrong, and unable to distinguish between “different” and wrong. There is far too much misinterpretation of everything. People dare voice out their opinions when they know nothing. It is sad to see people jest others with no basis behind their argument. People need to remember that many people think they believing something is no basis for blind faith in that decision.   Assignment 5: Read a current event and write a response  	(On the issue of torture used by American troops) 	The only thing I have to say is… What do you expect? People are inherently bad. Especially ones that have hatred hammered into their head. Put a bunch of people with the thought “Iraqis are terrible people. Everything they believe in threatens my way of life. The only way to stop them is to kill them” engraved in their skull and then place them in a contained environment where they are bored and think that no one is watching…What do you expect? People think America would never torture others. In reality, the only way to see true behavior is when a person thinks no one is watching. There are so many things that are taboo these days that people covet privacy so they can be themselves. I think that this news story will hopefully awaken people to the fact that no country can be perfect. I am glad this information came out. There is no bliss in ignorance. It’s good to see the truth, even if it hurts.   Session 4  Assignment 1: Read Chapter 4. Complete “Putting Skills to Work” assignment on page 81.  The Road to Revolution	 Event	Year	Significance The Sugar Act	1764	First of many taxes to ensue anger in colonies The Stamp Act	1765	Another unfair tax that caused anger Townshend Acts	1767	Caused the boycott of British business The Boston Massacre	1770	Marked the first Americans to die for freedom The Boston Tea Party	1773	First effective display of American discontent  The Road to Revolution was merely as escalating show of American discontent. Obviously the British were imposing certain taxes on the colonies that they did not agree upon. The British, however, seemed the think that if they paid money for something that benefited America, then the cost should be shared. At first American’s seemed displeased only to the point of silent anger. That was soon to change, when the British pushed their limits in an attempt to set up what was basically a monopoly of America. Protests began to break out when nearly everyone was affected by the taxes. The Stamp Act, the Sugar act, and the Townshend Acts were all imposed on the colonies within three years of each other. These combined set up the monopoly on America. The Tea Act only added to American’s hatred. Protests became physical when the Boston Massacre occurred in 1770. Several people boycotting this British monopoly began to throw objects at the newly placed British patrols. The result was five dead Americans, and shock that Britain would react with such force. In the next few years, the violence continued escalating in small ways such as these. This left only one viable option for these two powers. War.   Assignment 2: What was the cause of the Boston Tea Party? What were its effects?  	The cause of the Boston Tea Party was general discontent. Britain simply pushed America too far in its taxing. Britain attempted to reach too deep into its neighbors’ pockets, which resulted in public showing of disapproval. When the Tea Act was implemented in 1773, Americans were supposed to buy tea only from the British East India Company, which was a private company. However, Dutch tea, if secretly obtained, was much cheaper. This, obviously, was not ok by the British. They imposed the Tea Act which lowered the cost of their company’s tea. The catch was that they were required to buy the tea directly from the British East India Company, thus reducing the American middle-men’s business. This was the cause of the showing of disapproval in Boston in November of 1773. The effect was Britain realizing that something must be done with this colony. Britain, realizing that their port was the backbone of Boston society at the time, chose to punish the colony by blocking all trade in the Boston port until the destroyed tea was paid for. On top of this, Britain emplaced the Intolerable Acts, named so because of their harshness. The only thing this accomplished was to increase anger levels in the colonies. Assignment 3: Map, on seperate paper. Assignment 4: What is the Declaration of Independence? Who and what influenced the content of it? Why is it one of the world’s most important documents?  	The Declaration of Independence is a formal statement representing the beliefs of America. It was written by Thomas Jefferson in 1776 in order to state their independence from Britain. To sign it was treason against “their” king and empire that technically was in charge at the time. One of the main influences in this document is the issue of slavery. Having placed the statement “all men are created equal” in the declaration, proof was given about how true this actually was. Many of the members that signed it owned slaved themselves and were perfectly fine with it. It was still fueling the southern economy, after all. In order to represent all the colonies, Jefferson’s first draft, which attacked slave trade, had to be revised in order to please the southern colonies. It is one of the world’s most important documents because of what it accomplished. It laid the foundation for free thought and the right to change something you don’t like. Without it, America as we know it might still be owned by the British. It took a great deal of courage and faith to create and sign such a document, and luckily it was accomplished.   Assignment 5: What type of protest over government policy is going on today? What happened in Seattle in the year of 1999 called the “Seattle Tea Party?”  	In 1999, groups of people concerned about small businesses and how they would be affected by the coffee tax gathered in Seattle to protest. A 10 cent tax was to be voted on, and the money collected from the tax would be funneled into the education systems. Most agreed, but about 50 people rode down Seattle streets in a covered wagon. Coffee shops were accused of being overly greedy, but that didn’t stop some protesters to dump burlap sacks full of balloons (for an environmentally safe “reenactment”) into Green Lake. 	Protests that are going on today include ones targeted against government itself, one’s against the Bush Administration, and everything in between. There are people that disagree with everything going on in America, but for the most part, there are simply a lot of people that do not like George Bush. Most of the protesting going on is related to him and his “incoherent decision making.” However, there is a million small scale protests going on every day, including those related to city buses and a while back, nurses were protesting. 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      edit- now with proof: http://img35.photobucket.com/albums/v106/silversun/List.jpg     Expectations   "   Abide by all of Hans Peter's and Giesela's rules, as well as the spirit of thier rules. We do not know those rules, but you do. Please respect them. Abide by all of Bob and Kathy's rules, as well as the spirit of our rules.     1. Don't forget about your family. Please don't make all kinds of plans which take you away from us all weekend long. We like having you around. We like to see you. Check in with us and our plans and continue to be a part of them. 2. Don't forget about your friends. Continue to include them with your activities with Donnie. 3. Don't forget about your schoolwork. It is still important that you get your schoolwork done and do the best that you can. 4. It is OK to show affection, but don't let him put his hands all over you in public, and epecially around Mom and Dad. Likewise, don't let him drape himself all over you....I call it a strangle hug. These activities show nothing but immaturity. 5. Weeknights-home by 10:00; Donnie is out the door at 10:00. 6. Weekends- home by 12:00; Donnie is out the door at 12:00. This time is negotiable but if you know of an event that will take you out past this time, please discuss it with us beforehand. If we get a call at 11:30 asking to stay out later, we will consider it, but will be less comfortable granting it. 7. Let us know where you are and who you are with. 8. No "cruising" around in Donnie's car looking for activities. 9. When you are home with Donnie in your room, leave your door open at least a foot. This shows us that we are welcome to come in. 10. When you are downstairs with Donnie watching a movie, leave the door open at least a foot. This shows us that we are welcome to come in. 11. If you are doing something in which we are not welcome to come in, please reconsider what you are doing. 12. Do have Donnie come over to our house. The more we see him, the more comfortable we will become with him and your relationship. 13. Do join us in our conversations. The more we chat with him, the more comfortable we will become with him and your relationship. 14. Do invite him over for dinner at any time. Just let us know so we have enough foor for him. 15. Do ask us if you can invite him to some of the family things we may be doing. We may not always say yes, but we would like to include him if possible and appropriate. 16. Hugging is allowed. Kissing is allowed. Absolutely, positively no sexual intercourse is allowed. There are many reasons for this. 17. What happens in between those two extremes is your choice.....and we wouldn't know anyway. Just be aware that physical contact between two people is very powerful and can cause problems as well as pleasures. (Does he like me just because I "produce" for him; if I don't "produce" will he drop me; do I withhold as punishment; what do I do if he wants it and I do not.) Please use good judgement on this. "  - Compiled and typed by Kathrin's host dad, copied by K-dogg, and re-typed out by me.    ....................... 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hmm...Something funny:  At a graduation party, sitting on a futon. To the right is a couch, and to the left is open space. There are three people on the couch. Three people in the open space. Both having completely independant conversations. I am in the middle, in neither of the conversations in particular. Simply listening. But...it was...very...confusing. To the right is a debate about the tragedy of life and the validity of relationship itself, and to the left is a distorted conversation debating about penises and other rather interesting body parts. Just funny to sit in the middle, not knowing whether to laugh or cry. I laughed.   Something serious:  Outward appearances versus feelings. Good god. In the words of Scott, "I didn't even know there were people like this in the world." How can you be this happy-smiling-outgoing person on the outside, but then transform into this protective shield of a person that can't even decipher their own feelings. I dunno how to deal with it. Not going to even go into it. This wont even make sense to most people. Story of my life      ---------- PS: Sleeping is great. I hate when people abuse thier body for school work...Man, I hope all you IB kids take like a 5 day nap!
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I really feel dumb posting now... Kate just asked me what if I was blogging right as I was typing "blogger.com." I'm not predictable! Anyways, I am now home from Kathrin's graduation party. Oh man, tons of fun. Who would have thought playing frisbee at 11PM would be seen as juvinile fighting, and FOUR cop cars would show up? Oh man..How dumb is that? Sheesh.  Graduation is sad. There were some truely great people that I will never see again. That's destiny for ya'. Take a deep breath and smell the roses, realize how great that smell is, and then watch them wilt away. Haha, such a happy thought. Eh, it's not all like that. It's more like, take a deep breath, smell the roses, then pick 'em and keep them in a greenhouse forever. Yeah...That's more like it.  Time to go to bed. Kathrin, I forgot to give you your letter agian...Haha. What's new ^^, remind me tomorrow!     "It is better to die on your feet then to live on your knees"
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Fertig. Gut. Das freut mich. Huhu! *g   h a h a
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Trying to write my English paper..Since  someone  is making me :P. Found this quote. Thought it was humourous. Was considering adding it at the end of my paper, like...  And in conclusion, Isabel Allende sums it up perfectly when she says             "For women the best aphrodisiacs are words. The G-spot is in the ears. He who looks for it below there is wasting his time."     Author: Isabel Allende         hah! 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "7th" hour. Second to the last day at school. Art tech lab. Noisy room for a lab. Too many people watching online cartoons, with a lot of profanity. Got out of physics early. "Finished" final. Sucked. Big time. I hate it. So much. So angry. I wish I knew what room Speech was. But, I forgot somehow, dumb. So, ten minutes left. No way to burn it. Probably not supposed to be in this room. Wondering how I'm going to do my English paper tonight, study for math, etc. I can't. Nope. Not possible. Knowing me, I'll start at around midnight, type up the crappiest paper ever, and blah blah blah. Every paper is my worst paper ever. I don't enjoy writing anymore, although I used to a lot. Stupid, I wish I still did. It's useful to know how to write, to write letters and whatnot. Now I just stumble along. As you can tell. Which is why my blog is probably not very popular. I just type as thoughts come into my head. Weird thinking about my hands moving this fast. Things that come by instinct are amazing. Playing instruments, typing, etc. Crazy stuff if you think about it. Whatever. Angry that I have to stay to do Biology tests. I could just leave. That would be the "Donnie" thing to do. But no. I have to get some of these points back. I'm building a future here. I guess. Some future, eh? I've seen worse. Incoherent beggars living on the edge of life because they are afraid of change and life itself, in many cases. Yeah, that would suck. Lucky for me, my life will be great until July 11th or so. Yeah, then I'll be afraid of life. Just like about...the past 6 years of my life (save the last month, obvously). Typical. 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hoi. I am at K-Dogg's house right now. At 9:57 PM...On a Sunday night...Hah. Looking around...I see...pictures...A calender...Two calenders...A fish. A fish thast is smimming in all sorts of crazy patters all over the place. Kathrin just asked why Scott declared war on me. I say...I don't know. Hah. You're funny. This is my blog. Welcome. If this is your first time reading...No, I am not stupid. Yes I know how to write paragraphs. This is just how my mind works. Incomplete thoughts and stuff. No sentences finished...I see...my prom picture pasted to her computer screen!!! Cool!! Gotta go, everyone is going to bed and I feel awkward being the guest...And not leaving!! Hah  ---------------------------Later---------------------------  Ok...Home now. It's only 10:40 PM...Woah! This is so great! 10:40 is late for me now! My life was so fucked up before....Every night until 2:00 AM on the computer...And now, I just feel great going to bed at 11...Woah...This is a huge deal for me people. I've been so messed up with the computer the past few years of my life..It's completely ruined parts of me. Then again, I have learned a lot. Um...Anyway... ^^, I feel great is all. I can honestly say, without lying, that I've  never  felt so great in my life. Echt.    Thanks =)
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Looking down before the fray  Gazing at the tilt below      A smile lurks deep within   Regardless of the hardened face  Over all, it thinks it reins   Yet one brave soul can turn the tide  From one consciousness to the next  -Scott and Donnie...Only the first stanza...Felt like posting something...We'll finish it eventually. But we were sitting alone because our ride left already, so we tried doing something productive...It will be a cool song! Promise.   So..Accepted into Germany. I'm going. Semester. Around...5 months? Something like that. Waiting on my host family, and thus my placement. Pretty exited. Doncha know. So, Donnie will be gone for the whole first semester of his senior year. Oh dear.  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "Let the whole world know, as of 12:09 (ERC standard time) I have officially declared war on the blog of one Gordon Hicks III. Rules of engagement are as follows- 1. All forms of attack are acceptable. That is all.   Signed- The Author of this blog (12:13). "    The hell, Scott?  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Six full days of school left. One more year down. Down the drain? Down the proverbial-knowledge-sink-hole? Tests tests tests. What did you learn this year? Why did you learn it is a better question that I would be happy to answer for someone. Writing in yearbooks, feeling awkward at not knowing what to write. Thinking about how pointless it is to tell someone to have a great summer. How trite. How over-done. Gone is the year! Gone is hope? Gone is that shining ray of light? Hardly. One thing I've learned this year is to smile. That's how we're all connected. When I see someone smile, I just realize there are 6  billion  people in this world. That's a lot. It's almost impossible to fathom all the lines of life. Impossible. Not necessarity to try. Merely an Aufforderung zur Bescheidenheit, hah. We could all use one of those.   Germany draws near, and the peak of excitement is coming closly behind. In a few weeks I get the final answer, and possibly my life crushed.  Even though I make it seem like there is all this stuff going on, there is really only one thing, person rather, that I can think about, but I refuse to let  all  those loyal fans of my blog to be bored! Mwha. I refuse to get a girlfriend, and then change my entire style of blog! Hah. I've seen that happen too many times, and although it's not necessarily a bad thing, it's just not what I like! This does not mean she is less important, it just means none of you need to pretend to care about it :D. Rambling...   Hmm...How to end this without being exactly like the millions of other blogs... "Well, that's my rambling for the day" or what not.        Hot dog! 
     

    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Maybe you'll understand this, Christy.  The sky is blue. Writing is addictive And life is relative.. What's priceless to me You can get for free.   Moral of the day :D
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      We're all human in heart. Then again, it's just a heart. A collection of particles, of molecules, and of atoms and electrons. Why...Why did they have to be arranged to form me. Why did this battle need to take place. Life splits of thousands of times every minute. Like a giant family tree. You choose one line, and follow it until the inevitable death. How can I not wonder about the other lines..   These thoughts ran through his head. The thoughs...so light and wispy, much like the light fog entangling his feet, and his enemies' feet. Indicating the cool autumn evening temperature. Blocking an ant's vision of the sky. Just fog. Not nearly as dangerous as the blackened iron and steel forged for one purpose..To end the life of another. Of course, everyone already knows this, so reiterating the commen knowledge of the purpose of a sharp blade is off topic.  Despite the light air that floated around, and the breaths illuminated by the cold air striking the hot, there was a battle to be fought. Not just one battle, but two. Mental and physical. Neurons and metal. Twinge and snap. Victory was not only necessary, but...well, this was more important then the loss of a life. This was a loss of history. Another tick mark on the record book of the "greater being" oppressing the true hero. This struck a smile on his face.  Standing up, the mist parted for his feet as he placed himself on the ground. Leather covered his legs, and a light plate covered his torso. One thing left to do. Choose a path and sprint down it as fast as possible. The ground held strong as he glided across the scape, chasing shadows..  Silence insued. As he reached the treeline, the invisible enemy suddenly became visible. The path had been chosen, and the only part left was death.  -End.        The end, and the beginning. Sacrifice for someone else. Charging the foe and dieing, yet allowing someone else to live. Perhaps that person will go on to give birth to the next world leader, who will crush billions of people. Maybe someone died that day might have saved the life of the next savior. Maybe not. It's impossible to know. Impossible to think about. Impossible to care. Just remember, we are all connected. You do not have to understand this. Just acknowledge it, for the sake of everyone. Realize you are not the only life form that has feelings. Please. Take a second everyday and marvel at how many people you can pass on the street, or driving, that all have a destination and a purpose. And don't try to tell yourself you don't have a purpose. We all do. We are all connected. For what purpose would be greater then affecting hundreds of lives every day?
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Just feel like crawling into a cave. Dark cave. Mm. sdnfkasdf     Di.zzy.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      There comes a time. It's not a special time. It's a meaningless time. Similar to most of the other zones in a person's life. Unimportant, trivial. So, back to where I was beginning. There comes a time. It has not yet come yet. That's the point. The time is not here, the time is not now. Sometime in the future? Maybe. Probably not. We do not deserve this time. But, I personally have faith it will.  This makes no sense. You don't think I realize this? I might as well randomly strike keys and make sure to throw the spacebar in. It isn't supposed to make sense. It's just streaming words. Streaming across my fingers to its final destination of your brain recognizing it, and matching it up with the trillions of past experiences you've had reading things. Coming up empty. Not being able to decipher it.  Then you realize. It really doesn't make sense. Voices in your head. Simiilar to the person talking to me right now. Staring at me. Talking as if I am listening. I don't even know who it is. Gone. Finally. That was irritating.  Am I awake, or asleep?
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am Donnie's broken pride. I am Donnie's broken heart. A million pieces. That's not enough. I am Donnie's greed. A Billion peices. Better.   lol? I write the weirdest stuff..Weirder that I don't even think about it.. I just, write and zone out, lol...Funny.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Absence sharpens love, presence strengthens it    - Thomas Fuller  Absences are a good influence in love and keep it bright and delicate   - Robert Louis Stevenson  Since the house is on fire, let us warm ourselves    -Italian proverb  Great souls have wills; feeble ones have only wishes.  -Chinese proverb  A journy of a thousand miles must begin with a single step   -Chinese proverb  While there's life, there's hope  - Cicero  I wept not, so to stone I grew  - Dante  To be without some of the things you want is an indispensable  part of happiness   - Bertrand Russell  What must be, must be   - Proverb  The intence happiness of our union is derived in a high degree from the perfect freedom with which we each follow and declare our own impressions.  -George Elliot  There is no hope of joy except in human relationships   - Antoine De Saint-Exupery   Umm....Some relevant quotes that I agree on....Mostly relevant!  Ok...D-day getting a bit close. Today I saw a potential summary of what is going to happen after that. I sat at home. My parents weren't home, and I sat at home and played at least 11 straight hours of video games. Only interrupted by pizza and soda. Someone forgot to call me, and the other group of people claimed nothing was going on. Anyways, I played games. All day. That's what I do, I guess.  There may only be a few days left until there is a lot less meaning to waking up in the morning, but I will not be defeated by depression again. This has happened to me too many times in my life. Once is too many. Three is WAY too many. It wont happen again. I...think..  A story to be continued.  As if that will decrease the pain.  How shattered I will be When only a ghost remains Yet... Somehow I know I will survive. It may seem contradictory. But...My bones shake with hope! 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>