<Blog>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      This is my first blog, I just load the editor and I must admit that it seems nice. I do however doubt that I will find the time to publish frequently as the other bloggers do. Last time I got to update my web space was about a year ago, since then It's been a "work in progress" stage. Blah, here goes nothing.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
      It was rough. I'm still hearing a constant creeking noise in my ears. Also my writing skills are greatly hit and damadged since I've been hitting backspace too many times for last two lines. Plus my roomate is listening Led Zeppelin right now. I somehow have the feelin', "yeah baby give me the feelin", that I'll turn all this noise off. Hats off to mr. Hell, a little bit crude, I once felt Fisherspooner and other folks but still, he's OK. Or maybe it's the second hand smoke, who knows. In the end I went back home with my pal Dora, and we ate 2 sandwiches, and to hell with diet! I'm off to sleep, tomorrow it's either JSP or SQL, all day long. (Unless I have a hangover)
     
    
</post>

<date>26,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Saturday, it's going out day. I'm going to  urlLink Link  which is one of the bigger dance halls in Bologna. The guest star is  urlLink DJ Hell  and although I'm not too much into this kind of music, I'd better move my ass from home or else it's gonna get too big :) It's important to get out with your friends even if you diverge with their taste in music. PS. It's important to get out with your loved ones as well, and if you are not the getting-out type, you are going to have troubles, trust me.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
      It's raining today. Bloody hell, sometimes it's all happening at once. I's like to give a tip to all the guys out there. This is something that many will know all ready and some that might claim that there are many better ways to tidy a shirt but these are my 5 ¢. 1. take the shirt by the soulders. 2. make a quick stroke in order to put the sleaves behind, this moove should be executed in a position a bit retracted from the shoulders. 3. straighten the sleeves so that they are in line with the shirt. 4. fold the shirt.  Voila!  One shirt ready for the drawer, it's possible to do the same thing having the shirt laid on some surface, this is helpfull if the back-flip does not work.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
      If you love her/him and she/he loves you let me give you an advice although I don't seem to be getting it right. Give as much of youself as you can, and then some more. If you are being fulfilled, there are good chances that she/he is not. So talk with your partner and do your best. Always have a dialouge and don't be afraid to talk about "touchy" arguments. It's something that you both will appreciate and your relationship will be stronger. SigmaLab's prototype is coming along. Yoghi made a working build where the condivision is being saved to a XML file. I made a prototype of a ID3 tag reader in C# that uses the id3lib COM wrapper, it probably won't be included in the release because COM is a propriatory technology. Is there anyone that has a working ID3v1 and ID3v2 tag reader library written in .NET? If so write on schrepfler AT inwind [dot] it .
     
    
</post>

<date>22,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I saw Matrix: Revolutions the other week. It nicely ended the saga. At this point in time, I'd say that each of the movies brought new stuff to the cinema. In the beggining the first movie gave us spectacular fight scenes and time freezes, excelent sci-fi story, and "an end that is just the begining". Then some excellent intro in the Matrix with Reloaded, or at least just about enough for everyone to make up his own mind. Then in the end... CG, love and some corny dialogues. I forgive it all! Love triumphs in a really poetic way, although just too abruptly. Weird thing is I saw myself and my girlfriend withing the movie. I can just imagine her coming back from New Zealand, then coming to the train station, and then off the train, just like in the movie. It'll be cool. Love you honey!
     
    
</post>

<date>20,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I heard that another satiric TV show was cancelled from the state TV Rai these days. One of Italy's best commedian artists Sabina Guzzanti made recently a great show called Rai8t. The show was simply superb and it hurts only the fact that if you like to hear a good critique today one has to look for a comedy show. Too bad that the best get banned or "warned" to mind their words. All this hiding behind excuses that Rai is a public company so that all sides have to be represented. HA! If you like to represent all sides thay can make more good shows with different sides and not copies of the "competition" (read Mediaset) aired in the same timeslots of the respective counterparts! Sabina has a great sense of irony and captured a great number of problems that afflict the Italian society today, plus she finaly showed her own great face (and figure).  I'd like to quote Sabina: "We live in curious times", too bad it's a chinese curse.  I saw  urlLink this  thread, maybe someone is still sharing the first show.  
     
    
</post>

<date>13,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Me and my pals are starting a web site. It's about promoting of our "p2p" application, written in C#. It's all "work in progress" stuff but if we manage to coordinate university efforts and our project efforts we might just turn some heads. It stared as a project in Software Engineering and in the end we got 30/30. It's not even in alpha so we are estimating around 2 moths of efforts before some release. If someone is interested it's  urlLink http://www.sigmalab.net/ 
     
    
</post>

<date>31,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I wish to all of you the best in this new year. May the world be a prettier place to live in for all of us. Less hypocrisy, more love and understanding is desired. Hope everybody will have a blast and see you next year ;)
     
    
</post>

<date>16,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I moved my static web site (last significant update happened 2002)  urlLink @ CMB  to a new web host. The old ones, inwind.it which now gets referred to as libero.it got greedy. They turned off their POP3 servers, and put horrible ads on my site without asking. I can only say BOOO!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>15,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Adam Kinney on Longhorn  made me conscious of a new word - BlogApathy, and I must say that it has greatly inhibited my blog posting powers. Some stupid things are happening IRL (In real life) so I guess the blog suffered.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It's 3:07 AM, I am studying for an exam tomorrow/today and my mind suddenly drifted away to ask myself a question. Can an OS be developed, based totally on a runtime such as .Net/mono? Written completely in C# or whatever language supported by the runtime's compilers. How long would it take? How long just to make a functioning GNU-like environment (bash clone, etc..). Should we strive for GNU-like environment, POSIX standards, OpenGL etc...? And how about the graphic environment, hardware acceleration, 3D and the works. How can drivers be programmed in a high-level language like C#? Can a well written kernel core help in this task? I don't have answers to any of these question, if anyone reads my blog, please mail me just to have some feedback. Write to schrepfler AT inwind [dot] it.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      My bonsai tree died a month ago. I bought it from a cheap store down the road. It was dying in it, without light and stuffed on a shelf with others of its kind. I managed to grow it with love into full health within a few months (I'll post pictures on my static site in a couple of days). I remember giving it water daily, sitting on the window in the morning breeze, taking the sun. It once popped out 3 green leaves in just one night thanks to an extraordinary warm day this fall. The minty green leaves mingling with the dark ones, peacefully shaking in the air gave me great serenity those days. I advise all to try doing it by yourself, it's a voyage worth taking. Few tips although it's stuff I found out by myself and may be wrong for your kind of bonsai (there are many types, yes, some less famous names are Juniper, Chinese Elm, Hinoki Cypress ecc. more info on Google's top bonsai rank is  urlLink http://www.bonsaiweb.com/ ). I kept it at first in my room and tried in putting it out every day but it was no good, it's a plant that needs sun. Next, it appreciates slight and constant breeze. As for this latest statement, take care since I don't know if it's true, give it a nice half-glass of water each day. As long as I did all these things my bonsai was healthy looking (maybe someone will say that bonsai should be grown more in order to look like a small tree but I liked my larger leaves, I don't know how to do the other thing). Then this winter got cold, I once put him inside the house near the heating and that made a quick end for the little thing. I'm still very saddened for it. I dedicate it this haiku to it, it follows no rule and I make it in this moment:  A strange encounter! One glimpse,One drop,One life. Three leaves in the gentle breeze now fall. 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      First of all I'd like to say that I am not a "code guru", I do programming but may not be the best guy to listen to advice :) This last year I've been dabbling with C# working on a network app-framework project with some colleagues of mine. It has been a great experience and I definitely will continue to explore C# as time goes by. I'll give here homage to two features of the .Net platform, the foreach construct and Reflection as used in C#.  I'll quote the C# Programming Reference:  "The foreach statement repeats a group of embedded statements for each element in an array or an object collection. The foreach statement is used to iterate through the collection to get the desired information, but should not be used to change the contents of the collection to avoid unpredictable side effects."  It's usage is simple: foreach (Type variable_name in expression){...do stuff }   where expression can be either an array, or a SomeClass.GetItems() that returns an array or SomeClass.Items Collection.  For the most things I did up until now the main entry point in doing reflection would go over the Type Class. So to make an example if I'd like to look into the inner guts of a class (ex. TestClass) this might be a nice way of doing it.  TestClass tc= new TestClass(); Type _type=tc.getType;  now the  urlLink System.Type  Class is a MASSIVE thing, providing a huge number of Methods and Properties so I'll be demonstrating only some basic stuff, like getting all the members. Easier said then done they can be get by doing _type.GetMembers(), so why not do: foreach(MemberInfo mi in type.GetMembers()){  }  Now this extracts a bunch of stuff and you might not need them all, one nice thing is the MemberTypes Enum so you can check if the Members are for example Methods, Constructors, Properties ecc.. I would have liked to point something to the MSDN Documentation but I don't have the URLs, but simply looking for the Class or Enum Type on the  urlLink http://msdn.microsoft.com  suffices for most of the occasions.  Now  urlLink System.Reflection.MemberInfo  is a cute thing and you can get a lot of info out of it but not everything, the nice thing is, you can cast it to more specialized types as: System.Reflection.EventInfo System.Reflection.FieldInfo System.Reflection.MethodBase System.Reflection.PropertyInfo >System.Type  So it's possible to do PropertyInfo pi=(PropertyInfo)mi;  and that leads to extensive info on properties ecc, the same principle goes for the other types listed.   When I was doing stuff on it at first glimpse I failed to see  urlLink System.Type  and I had a lot of troubles in understanding if the mi was a Delegate, but once done Type mytype=(Type)_mi;  I was able to do something like if(mytype.IsSubclassOf(Type.GetType("System.Delegate")))  See you soon! :)
     
    
</post>

<date>04,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      My friend Dora had a birthday yesterday. I wish her all best in life, University and everything else :)
     
    
</post>

<date>29,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Bologna has been totally covered with snow. Just as one would think that the winter has passed, here it is, good old 'granny Martha' or as Slavs say it 'baba Martha' shows her temper. I have found out that now I get Atom  urlLink feed  for free it may not be RSS but it's a start, let's just hope that the ugly banner will go away, and some statistics along with pictures would come in nicely. I've had a nice surprise having tried a pre-alpha of the game Painkiller and I must say it's scary :), nice graphics, monsters and a lot of blood. It's a bit slow on my Radeon 9600 but I knew what I was buying. Meanwhile we at  urlLink sigmalab  are opening a  urlLink forum , it's in Italian and mostly covering some programming issues and our software projects. If interest is shown we will open discussions in English as well.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Googleing and reading Slashdot I found this nice site  urlLink MD5CRK . At this moment our P2P Framework is using MD5 as hashing algorithm, perhaps we should change, but I'm worried about performance hits. On the bright side, spring is in the air. My street is filled with pink and white petal trees emanating a very nice smell. I've been thinking and realized that the rising rents might be a result of the unstable market, but then again how come it's Bologna-only?
     
    
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I have some problems in life with paying the second part of the tuition. The "nice" guys at the University administration that deals with reducing the tuition on grounds of financial status got something wrong so now I have to fight them. As usual in Italian bureaucracy they don't give you enough time to complain and the story is just too cliche... Plus the rents in Bologna sky-rocketed since the introduction of the Euro. In the recent news, it was pointed out that there is a number of apartments that may be rented but are left unused. Why do I get suspicious and think that it's a artificial way to keep raising the rents? At this point in time my only hope is that the next major (the candidate for the Left is the former CIGL leader Conferati, aka Chinamen) will try to unblock this fast paced race that is leaving the middle class (if there is any left) in great troubles.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today the funerals for the Macedonian president Boris Trajkovski were held. Condolences to his family in their hours of sorrow.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I've been installing  urlLink Gentoo  these past two days. After two unsuccessful tries this one hit the spot. It loads quickly, has a beautiful framebuffer console, accelerated Ati Radeon drivers for X, and a nice  urlLink bootsplash  to boot (pun intended). I've had some problems including a installation bug parting from stage1 with groff but all problems find solutions on the excellent  urlLink forum  that this community has. I'm a owner of a ASUS P4P800 DeLuxe motherboard. It's a sweet motherboard but it has some issues with Linux. Mainly no official support from VIA in releasing the sources for the Raid VT6410 controller ( urlLink forum ), integrated sound (forums at gentoo help,  urlLink this  one is a bit off topic but shows pieces of code that hits the right spot), integrated LAN 3c940 ( haven't made it work yet but reportedly the sk98lin drivers should work if one includes "Marvell Yukon Chipset / SysKonnect SK-98xx family support" when you compiling the kernel). One nice thing about gentoo is that it makes you edit the config files and the run level apps so you get a better feel of the system. On the bad side I'm not too happy about the compile time. Anyhow I'm still learning it and ít's been loads of fun. I've been on Linux since a guy in Finland send me by snail mail for free a copy of Red Hat 5.0 (thx Pekka Peterson). I've tried most distributions and to this day my preferred is the RedHat. I've tried Fedora RC1 and although it was a bit buggy I'm still having great hopes. Unfortunately for me 1.90 beta was terrible and that resulted in installing gentoo which I'll probably keep until Fedora RC2 comes up. Waiting for MonoDevelop as well, please add it in the portage tree :) !
     
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      My girlfriend is going away to Macedonia for 2-3 weeks, I'm already missing her but I'd like her to get a nice rest from the problems us foreign students are having in everyday life... I opened the gmail service, and started experimenting, seems nice, I'd really like a POP3 access though... 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I don't know if it's a glitch but there seems to exist some problem in running the Tomcat administration tool with NetBeans 3.6. Anyhow, there are things you should know. The password for the managing is generated randomly on start and it's written in your home directory, under WindowsXP it's \\Documents and Settings\Your account name\ .netbeans\ 3.6\ jakarta-tomcat-5.0.19_base\ conf\ tomcat-users.xml I don't know why, but I was getting strange error messages not letting me display the administration util so I compared the same file with the one shipping with the stand alone Tomcat and as it was missing the admin role, I added it  &lt;role rolename="admin"/&gt; &lt;user username="admin" password="your_password" roles="admin,manager"/&gt;   Works fine now...
     

        
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      This is a small HOWTO that will help you get a DataSource with the MSSQL 2000 database using the official MS JDBC drivers and the Tomcat container.  1. Copy the files: msutil.jar mssqlserver.jar and msbase.jar to a directory that will be visible to your java environment; A good one would be the_path_to_your_SDK/jre/lib/ext/ It might be good idea to put them in the containers libs as well and your web application lib folder... you never know :) Just remember to keep all of them in sync. 2. Log into your Tomcat administration utility (probably http://localhost:8080/admin/) and log in. 3. Go to Service > Host > your_web_app_context 4. Go to Data Sources and create a new data source setting these parameters:  JNDI Name:  jdbc/mssql Data Source URL:  jdbc:microsoft:sqlserver://localhost:1433;databaseName=db_name JDBC Driver Class:  com.microsoft.jdbc.sqlserver.SQLServerDriver then fill the user name and password fields. I don't know yet how to determine what are the best connection settings so that's up to you. If you have some advice, please leave some comments.  5. Then you switch to some java coding, go to the place where you'd be putting the Class.forName and DriverManager.getConnection() bits and replace them with something like:  DataSource ds=null; try{ InitialContext ctx= new InitialContext(); ds=(DataSource)ctx.lookup("java:comp/env/jdbc/mssql"); Connection connection = ds.getConnection(); catch (Exception e){ throw new NotFoundDBException("Blah blah blah" + e); }   NotFoundDBException is a class I wrote to handle the exception, you'll have to come up with your own :) that's it, I think.
     

        
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Things are going on, my girlfriend was on TV, Google enabled comments and rewamped the look and feel of Blogger, I'm trying to make things work for my project. Busy busy busy...
     

        
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Mono went out with beta1, looks good and monodevelop 0.3 seems more stable. I do have problems compiling mono-debugger 0.7 though. :(
     

        
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      As I'm left alone I am coerced to do some cooking in-house. I spent some quality time on the market the other day so today I'm ready to dispense this recipe upon the world that is commonly known in Italy as "pasta con broccoli e panna", pasta with broccoli and cream. You need one Teflon-pan (the big ones) and a large pot for the broccoli and the pasta. Fill the pan with water and bring it to the boiling point. Add a bit salt and throw the broccoli washed and chopped off the thick parts. This is the critical part, I'm not sure about timing but you should check it out every now and then to see if it's soft enough, don't take it out too soon because it might be hard to make the sauce if its too hard. My estimate is it has to be at least 20 minutes but I didn't time it. Once taken out put new water to boil for the pasta. In the meantime you should be making the sauce. At first put some olive oil, and chop some onion in it and leave it on fire until it gets some color, you can add some garlic that you can later take out. Once the broccoli are done add them to the pan with the cream, add some white and black pepper. If you think it's hygienic put some of the water in which the broccoli was boiling (the bit rich with broccoli peaces and color) inside the pan, it'll buy you some time until the pasta is done. Once the pasta water gets boiling, put salt as desired and put the pasta in. Once the pasta is to your taste, pour it out, and either put the pasta in the pan or vice-versa. Stir a bit and serve. Don't forget to make a salad as well, it's healthy and your body will be grateful.
     

        
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I find great confort in the fact that my Bonsai tree found a new home. It became a decoration for Paola's turtle garden. Now it's making shade for the small turtle in the warm summer days. So a new haiku is in order.  I'm old,  I'm dead but my shade is someones's bed.  Today is a great day, I'm celebrating 1 year and 6 month with my soulmate Bibi. I hope it'll be as great as it was and better still as time goes by.  
     

        
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Hi all, I've been off the net for a month or two so that's the reason I'm writing this often :) It's a difficult period but it's something that had to be done, the bills that we had to pay were just piling up and we weren't doing anything to diminish them. On the high note, I'm working on my J2EE project, a sort of  urlLink DeviantArt  clone, that I chose to do as a project. As soon it's working without too many problems I'll be posting it on the  urlLink SigmaLab's  site.
     

        
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Yesterday I was in the town square, the "Piazza Maggiore" with my girlfriend to see the movie "Master and Commander". All in all I liked it quite a bit, only problem was that we were sitting too close to the screen so it was difficult to follow the fast paced scenes. One thing really nice was that during the traversal of Cape Horn there was a cold wind breezing so it upped the atmosphere quite a bit, a sort of special effect :) Good thing too was that the story was more emphasized than the effects. To anyone that might pass through Bologna on a hot summer day... Following the Ugo Bassi street, once passed the Ugo Bassi statue, turn to the left and then to the right. In that street is a great ice cream store we call Gianni, it's worth the visit, trust me.
     

        
</post>


</Blog>