<Blog>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      One of the original visions of the web was to have large repositories of information cross-referenced, and in the beginning this was largely true.As many of the web pages were academic, it made sense for content authors to cross reference their work with other articles of note.  However, since the commercial explosion of the web, web pages have become more and more self-contained, as designers became less willing to link to external content, perhaps for fear of losing visitors. Well this bit of information might come as a shock:   Web Users are incredibly selfish   If I want to leave your site to find some information, I will - I only have to type the address in the browser. in terms of effort required, it takes more for me to go and make a cup of coffee. However, if a site actually provided me with an easy way to access the information I am looking for, I would be more impressed because it is doing me a  service . Service drives us as consumers... if we were to receive good service at a restaurant, we would be more likely to return to that restaurant than to one that perhaps had better food, but awful service.  While the food might be preferable at the second restaurant, the experience becomes less pleasant if the waiter is unhelpful and you end up waiting a long time for your food. When talking about the internet, we often use the word  experience   I'm not suggesting that a commercial site should actively be linking to its competitors, but the author should consider the benefits of linking to  relevant  content on the web.  To take a small example: a building company. A website is established, and provides information about the company, history, past projects, services provided and so on. Now if I, as a customer was interested in hiring this company to build an extension to my house, I would have many other questions above and beyond the company - I need to know more about the project. Are there any special planning regulations in my area? How can I find out?  This information is openly available from my local authority, and in the case of a localised business such as a builder - a simple link to the contact details of the planning department would mean that I don't have the hassle of searching for this information myself. My experience of local authority websites has been one of frustration to find the relevant page - and that is from someone who is experienced in using the internet. If as an author of the Builder's website, I was to take the time to find the relevant page on the authority's website, it would mean that my visitors do not have to waste time finding this information out for themselves.  External linking can be seen as a way to improve the poorly-organised web, but it is also important to remember the user's  path  Many external links will open in a new window, for fear of losing a vistor to the external website. Well, if I am finished on the first website, I will close the window anyway, remember  Web Users are Selfish . However, by opening the page in the current browser window, I am allowing the user the full use of their  path . If I want to view what I had on the screen previously, then I only have to click on the  Back Button  to get there. If I have accidentally (or purposefully) closed the previous window, the I have to go back and either search my history folder, or search for the page I started at. A much longer process, and one where I am more likely to visit a competitor's site.  Of course, external links should also be relevant. On my local MP's website, the article on fireworks links to something to do with Labour's manifesto for Swansea:  urlLink Ross Cranston, Labour MP's website  There may have been something about fireworks on the page, but I couldn't see where it was, and was not going to read the whole article just to find out this information.  Remember - I am a selfish, impatient web user!  Perhaps if the author of the Swansea article had made sensible use of  Anchor tags  then Mr. Cranston could have linked directly to the relevant section.  The chances are that the external link had actually changed, and that brings me on to another very important point.  Make sure your external links are kept up to date  By linking to an external website, you are relying on a third party to keep their information up to date. Where possible, obtain a direct, unchanging link to the article. Many sites might simply have a "news.htm" page that they update regularly. This is unsuitable for someone linking externally to your website, as an archived article might be relevant to the page that is linking to it. If you feel that the external link might change, don't use it. Instead, see if you can find a permanent link, or at the least, check your external links to ensure that they are  relevant 
     
    
</post>



</Blog>