<Blog>



<date>28,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, jumping down off my movie high, I've decided that it's time for me to keep a journal.  This isn't the first time I've decided this, but hopefully this time I will follow through, since this journal can follow me wherever I go in life.  I've read some of Andrew's journal, and Jared's journal, so in an attempt to bring some coherence to my sometimes......jumbled life, I too will embark upon a fantastic journey of self-discovery (insert grand, sweeping music here).  And to be really cool, and so that everyone will read my journal, I will from now on, use no punctuation This I believe will set me apart from the crowd I will rule the school and win every football game I will drive a beamer and join the rotary and eat lots of spaghetti.........Ok, this offends my grammar sensibilities, so that's enough of that.    Hmmm.....how does one start off a journal?  It's kinda like a first date.  It's a little bit awkward, you need to get to know the other person, there's some halting, nervous laughter, a little bit of fidgeting, and hopefully, a little bit of action by the end of the night, although you really don't expect it.   Ok, dating parable aside, I need to first evaluate my reasons for keeping this journal.  Do I want to seek out truth in the highest form......or simply catalogue (sic?) my life like so many butterflies pinned to a piece of posterboard?  Or am I doing this because I want people to read it, and think that I'm the coolest?  Or is it just because the voices in my head are rising to a dreadful crescendo, and threaten to evict me if I don't find them a frickin' medium?    This is something I need to ask myself, because it's really something only I can decide.  I know that one thing I want to do with my life is write something really great, that will cause people after they set it down, to just sit and stare, and be unable to do anything for a good five minutes but just think.  Because I've read stuff like that.  I think a lot of people have, and the people that haven't.....well, I love 'em, but shoot, that's just sad.  I started reading Stephen King yesterday for the first time, and even though I was afraid that this would happen, I am absolutely enthralled.  God help me.   I know now I will find myself hard-pressed to read anything else for a while, and that's why I was scared to start reading him.  But I was at a bit of a lull, and I needed something to kick-start my marathon reading habit again, and it turns out that Stephen King is going to pick up for me right where Neil Gaiman left off.   I just hope that I will be able to find my way out of the world for a while, and look around, and see the people. Hmmm....Well, my hair is dry, so time for gel.   And time to go.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh, man. Wow.   I just got done watching Vanilla Sky, and I just couldn't stop crying.   When things come together, at just the right moment, just when you need them most, whether it be people or movies or yellow fruit flies, that is when I most keenly feel the hand of God.   That is when life if beautiful, and you know that tomorrow and the next day, and the next day after that are going to have things of such beauty that your heart is going to burst.  And you continue.  Thank you, God.  And mostly, it's just the little things.  The way a person talks to you on the phone, the feel of a Q-tip, a piece of fruit, a turkey sandwich, the feel of your arm out the window.  That is what makes life good.   The reason I'm so emotional today is because it's Saturday, and I worked by myself for 6 hours, and talked to no one but medical personnel and the Amish, and had a lot of time to myself, and still got nothing done.  And then, just when I feel the lonliness digging in the most, and I feel like it can't go on, I watch Vanilla Sky, and it dead-centers right in on me, and hits me like a ton of bricks. And I think of Ryan.   Ryan, Ryan, Ryan, Ryan, Ryan.  She who is beauty. I'm not going to go into my feelings about Ryan on this public blog, because she knows how I feel, and that's none of your freakin' business.  If you want to know how I feel, just mention her name to me, and watch me smile.  Otherwise, all I'm going to say is I think she's really great.  So I thought a lot tonight, about different stuff and whatnot, and was reading this book that takes things from a demon's perspective on how they look at humans and God (or the Tyrant, as they deem him) and was just overcome with a feeling of hopelessness.  As I was reading this book and how it tells you to be a Christian, I just started downright moping.  I don't know if that means I was coming under spiritual attack, or if it was because I've read the book before, and need something new and challenging, but I just felt like shit. We pull into our own little worlds sometimes, and feel like there's no one, and we sit and we forget that even if there's nobody around, there's God.  And despite all the different things going around about God, he loves you, and just wants his children to get along and love each other.  But it's tough to remember all the things that you seem to need to remember about God, and faith, and grace, and spirits, and denominations, and so sometimes it's good to just sit and know that he is Lord, and that means that he's there for ya.  He's got your back, yo.  I thought about how everytime I feel down, I try to get something new in my life, like a new book, or a new shirt, or a new something-that-is-cool-and-weird.  And I expect that to take the place of the hole that's there.  But what I need to realize is that I have to work on the stuff that I got.  I need to work on the relationships that I have, I need to work on the talents that I have, and I need to take the time to make something myself, and not just get it from someone else.   I need......dang, I don't know what I need.  I guess I won't know until I find it.  So until then, I guess I just pray, and trust, and flow.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Ah, fresh blog.  Ding! Well, here it is, 8 a.m. and I live to see it.  Wondrous indeed is the God who makes such things possible.  Of course, this is due in no small part to the fact that I haven't actually gone to bed yet.  That's right, I beat the system.  And all I had to do was work the late-night shift.  Anyways, the reason I make such a hullabaloo about it is that I am also going to go to church, where I haven't been for a good long while, for a number of different reasons.  One of the reasons, I must admit, is that I've been just darn lazy.  I work mostly evenings, and so it's tough to get up on a Sunday morning and go to church and leave it at the time that you would normally be getting up.  But this is a poor excuse.  But a darn convenient one, I feel.  Another reason is that when I've gone to church in the past year, it's been with my parents.  And I'm going through that whole "parental awkwardness stage" which I understand lasts until I'm 50.  But I simply have wanted to find my own faith experience apart from my parents (nothing against my parents, just birds gotta swim, fish gotta fly).  Unfortunately, my way of doing that is to not go to church.  But I must admit that I have found out things about God and myself that I don't think I would have found out had I been going to church.  Yes, I did go through a bit of a rebellious period.  But I've held steadfast to my faith in God, if not my complete faithfulness (hmmm...).  But I feel like now I have a good foundation with God that's all the better because I built it myself, and now I feel like I can go back to a community-based environment and continue to grow.  But I do still hold some reservations, which lead into my other reason for being a dirty church-skipper; I haven't enjoyed worshipping God with song for a long time.  I went to a church where song-worship was very key, and although it was very good for a while, I eventually stopped   feeling and just started   doing.  And so, since I wasn't feeling it, it became a chore.  And nobody likes chores.  Even now, song-worship kinda grates on my nerves.  So there ya go. 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Is there a right way to be?  Is there a clear-cut, set way that people are supposed to be so that it won't hurt?  If there is, I hope someone tells me, 'cause right now kinda sucks. Are we supposed to be nice to each other?  Is that what people want?  If so, why aren't they nice?   I'm really sick of people not being nice, not taking the time to be a little freaking cordial to their fellow man.   Am I supposed to not be nice?  Would that make people happy?  Would that finally convince them to take their hands out of my cookie jar, and leave me some chocolate chips?  What about sticking up for oneself?  If someone sticks up for themself, but is rude, is that ok?    Sometimes I feel that pleasing people is like pouring water into a bucket with a hole in the bottom.  If I can just find that balance of strength and feeling, empathy and numbness, niceness and courage, life would be good.  And I agree with Jared, I just want to be a pirate.
     
    
</post>

<date>31,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Random thoughts, feelings and happenings from the last couple of days:  I found the perfect way to sum up what I am feeling right now.  I feel like for the first time in my life, instead of looking to the future, I'm looking to the past.  I've always been doing things to prepare me for what is to come, but now that I'm there, I fear growing stale.  I guess that's what I've been feeling in my friendships with some people: staleness.  The stories that we've shared together aren't enough to sustain the relationship, we need to be continually growing and making new stories, having new adventures.    I can beat the crap out of Christopher in chess, but then he puts the smack down in Lunch Money.  I'm really acutely aware of man's propensity to boast.  I do it, and I find that a lot of people are continually vying to have the upper hand in the "coolest experiences, most knowledge on any subject" race.  I know that in American society more than any other there seems to be this overwhelming desire to be the best at everything, to be the coolest guy in the room.  There's a black cat that Mike found outside that is probably the cutest thing ever.  And I want to keep it.  But I don't think we can.  But I'm gonna try anyways.  It's name is Mr. Pinky Johnson and apparently it loves tuna.  Talking with Jared always makes me think, and confuses me.  I'm feeling better than I have for a while.    
     
    
</post>

<date>28,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, I apologize for the lack of posting and for my attempt to look and sound cool by the blog I did before this one.  I mean, I like what it says, but other people think that because its so simple and minimalistic, I perhaps was simply putting something in to appear meaningful without actually having to put any effort into it.  To them I say "Nah."   To my credit, I haven't been in a big blogging mood lately, for a couple of different reasons. The main reason is because I've been down on the world a lot.  If you know me, I'm a painfully optimistic person.   I would like to think I'm also realistic, but that's simply not true.   No, I've been experiencing some reality shock.  Before, I've always had my hopes and dreams to keep me warm at night, but lately, I've been going through some emotional changes and discovering the people are different and maybe not always the inherently good that I would like them to be.  I've learned that it's hard to decide the life to live that will have the most meaning.  A quiet, simple life?  Or something more? For the time being, I've chosen the quiet but not really simple life.   I'm at a time when I'm looking around and saying "This is it?" I know that for centuries people have been looking, searching, questing for some sort of answer to the meaning of life, and right now, that's where I am. I feel like because I'm in what I consider a transitional job and not my life's passion, that I'm not fulfilled.  And while I love the people at my work, I'm just not living up to my potential. But I don't know what my life's passion is, so it's hard to do it. I've tried a lot of different things, but nothing has reached out and kicked me in the shins, saying "Tra-la-la!  You'll love me forever, and I'll fulfill you like crazy!" Well, nothing marketable. So I try to find the meaning in people.  And people let me down.   There are a lot of relationships that I miss, and people that seem to have gone their different ways, and I'm standing here, and looking around and saying "So am I supposed to be best friends with people at work?  Is that what my life is now, work and occasionally home and talking on the accursed phone?" I don't even know what I want anymore, I just don't want to dwell on the past and I'm afraid of the future. 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Is not the light made all the more beautiful by the darkness around it?
     
    
</post>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I am a child of the middle.  I am stuck in that nebulous area between things; the cracks within cracks.  I am from the suburbs; the city makes me fearful, the country makes me bored.  I am conservative with liberal ideas.  I am friends with all manner of people, belonging truly to no one group, unless it be with other people in the middle.  I am neither the nicest person you will meet; nor am I meanest.  I am been publicly taught to stand out and be my own person; privately, subconsciously, I have been taught to stand in line and go with the crowd.  I am tired of being in the middle; the reckoning comes, and I fear, but I rejoice.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      And while I'm at it, I think I'll talk a little about my week, which has been really good.  I've got to re-visit some old friendships, work on current ones, and even make some new friends.  I hung out with Rachel Douglas on Thursday, and even though I had to drive an extra hour (bringing the total up to 2 and a half hours.  Yeow) because of a combination of misleading signs, confusing directions, and my total lack of direction and second-guessing, it was worth it.    Rachel is the type of person who inspires me, both in artistic directions and just life in general.  She's really brave and set in what she wants to do, and she just goes out and does it, with little excuse.  And she encourages me to do the same.  Which is really cool.  The other cool thing is that Rachel is married now.  And while I may not have viewed that as a good thing in a past life, I am really happy for it now.  I have such a high respect for the institution of marriage (perhaps because it seems a lot of relationships are so tenous, and that is a solid foundation (or at least it is it my eyes, perhaps not the eyes of the world)) that it enables me to not even worry about a lot of crap.  As far as I'm concerned, that married woman is a guy.  Still a woman in the sense of how I should treat them, and what I should guard against, but I can at least be free from that nagging sense of promise that hits me every time I meet a new woman.  That's very refreshing.  That enables me to have a lot of emotional honesty that is best received by women, and who I find to have the best insights.  Yeah Ladies!  I finally got to hang out with my friend Meg's husband, who I have heard lots of good things about, and enjoyed in the brief flickers of interaction that we have had.    Myself and Meg and Tim (that's the husband) and Betsy (Tim's sister) and her boyfriend all went to go see Anne E. Dechant, who is this sort of folk-indie-rock hippie singer.  I'd never heard of her before, and I liked her a lot, more for her message than her music.  She was very feminist, which I consider myself, although I like to think of it more as a Equalitist.  Or something.  You know, chicks and broads should be treated the same as men.  Anyways, I liked Tim a lot.  He's definitely educated in pop culture, but in that geek-charm kind of way.  Yeah geek-charm! And perhaps most of all, he just seems like a nice guy.  Although I could get to know him and find out that he eats babies (a definite prerequisite for evil), right now he just seems like a cool, nice guy.  Although I suspect that he has a deep well of sarcasm that he could bring to play (Lord knows that Meg does), I think that it is probably the constructive kind of sarcasm.  Oh, man.  Back to work, I still have stuff to do.  But thank you for listening, whoever you are.  I hope that you enjoyed reading it as much as I enjoyed writing it.  Sam Demos Football Rules!
     
    
</post>

<date>17,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      As I go through life, I continually have mental notations of things to blog about, and I put them on the tablet of my mind, but then when I sit down, that tablet seems to have been wiped clean.  And when I try to write them down, I invariably just lose the papers.  Ah, well.  The curse of the disorganized artist.   Ah, but here, I remember something.  I wanted to write about how I feel distinctly uncomfortable with the past.  I just realized recently that I am a man that not only runs from the past, but doesn't really like it.   I think there is a number of different reasons for this, but I think that the main problem is that I can't remember things easily.  It's like my mind is full of impenetrable fog with a little thought-lighthouse that swings it's light around occasionally. When people talk to me, and they tell me about things that we did together, if it's more than two years old, there's a chance I'm just not going to remember it.  And I don't think it's because I'm stupid.  Although I have this theory about mental retardation that might be the case, but I don't think so.  At least, I hope not. But anyways, I feel when I am around people from my past, in different capacities, I feel that unease and (hmmm?) guilt that I should have been there, we shouldn't be meeting up again after so much time, we should have been together for it. Hmmm.....maybe this is not really a fear of my past, but my problem of consuming guilt.    Or maybe I just feel the need to be the Brian that they might have known then, instead of the Brian that I am now (whoever that is).     This is all part of my continuing journey to rid myself of fear.  Because it seems that fear and guilt are pretty tight traveling companions.  But I will cast them off, eventually.  Brian Hollingsworth is bitch to no emotion, save love.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Had a good weekend...cleared up some stuff, continued to empty out my room and my soul...  So I've been trying to figure out my definition of success...  And I'm still not sure what it means to me.  I think that it means that I am making the world a better place, but that is so...vague and ambiguous.   I just look at everyone else's definition of success, and I don't know what to think:  Good job, lotsa money, great children, great Christian, not hurting anyone, living dangerously, living safely and responsibly, making it big in Hollywood.  I guess that I won't know if I'm a success until my life is over, but it would be nice to find out earlier.  My mom gave me this poem long ago supposedly written by Ralph Waldo Emerson (although there is some debate)   To laugh often and much;  To win the respect of intelligent people and the affection of children; To earn the appreciation of honest critics and endure the betrayal of false friends; To appreciate beauty, to find the best in others; To leave the world a bit better, whether by a healthy child, a garden patch or a redeemed social condition; To know even one life has breathed easier because you have lived. This is to have succeeded.   And I would like to take this as my measure of success, but..... it seems to give me a way out, a way to just slack off and not focus, and I feel like I do that too much already.  And while I seemed to be able to breeze by in college, the life beyond is not affording me the same luxury.....  On it goes...
     
    
</post>

<date>07,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I love driving at night.  There's just something about the long, lonely stretch of highway that's very therapeutic to the soul.  The cars coming the other way, their headlights twinkling like diamonds, reminding you of civilization.  This feeling that wherever I journey to is a place of destiny and promise...  At no other time do I feel the delicious mystery of God in such a way.  The music going full blast, singing at the top of my lungs, getting weird looks from weary passerby.  Mr. Ben Folds, my traveling companion.   The cruelest lies are often told without a word... The kindest truths are often spoken, never heard...   Word.  
     
    
</post>

<date>06,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I added a little section to the side for some community blogs, finally, and later I will hopefully be able to figure out how to do some more stuff.  Man, html is crazy.  It's like, another language or something.    Otherwise, things are pretty good where I am.  I'm currently going through a minimalistic phase, at least as much as I can, the packrat that I am.  But I feel like the physical things that I get rid of will somehow reflect the clutter I feel in my soul.  That, and it's getting hard to maneveur around my room.  A strange thing happened at work today.  One of my co-workers, Angela, had a dream about me last night, where I had somehow overcome my greatest fear, even though Angela does not know that it is my greatest fear.  I don't know if that means that I will overcome that fear someday, although I have a feeling that the decision is kinda out of my hands.  Cryptic enough?  Good.  And for those who know my greatest irrational fear, it wasn't that.  I very much doubt that Angela would dream about zombies.  I really meant to come back and finish the dream blog from yesterday, but I just didn't find the time.  Reader's Digest version : Cats, Death, Mike, Fraternity, and Sparkplugs.  This feels to me like it has been a very administrative blog, as well as random.  Well, if variety is the flute of life, play on!
     
    
</post>

<date>04,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, crap.  I just did this great blog about dreams, and it didn't go through because I left my blog idle for too long.  I guess I'll redo it, but not now.  Gotta go to work.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So here I am at work, able to get through the internet restriction because of my fellow employee's apathy.  Yay!  While working these night shifts throw the rest of my life off, I must say that while I am here, by myself for eight hours, there is a peace.  For a time, I am the master of my domain.   Not to mention the fact that I have an incredible opportunity to do pretty much anything I want for about eight hours, provided I don't leave a family-room-sized area.  The only thing I need to worry about are unpredictable clamorings from my "fans".  I've decided not the first time that I am just not a phone person.  While it is debatable that I am charming and articulate in person, something about talking to people for brief stretches of time on the phone just puts me slightly....off.  Unless I am able to do something by rote, I come away feeling like the person on the other end thinks me a dolt.  Although Dr. Khwaja never made me feel that way, that train has sailed. So I plow on, hoping that people don't think me stupid or mean, and finding slowly that I have started to not care as much, which leads me to overcompensate, which leads me full circle back to (in my ears) sounding like a dolt.  And this is what I do for a living.  Shit.  I dressed up as a Twinkie for Halloween, even though I has thus far garnered only the appreciation of the person I replaced at work, Mike.  But I do have to say that it was worth it to see him smile.  If I've done nothing else at my workplace, I can walk away confident that I have at least made Mike smile on numerous occasions.  He's exactly the unlikely sort of guy that I somehow get along with perfectly.  And given our age difference, that makes me really happy.  I can only hope that I can make Meg (one of my other favorites) smile too. As well as I can only hope that she can make it in on time for she shares my lack of internal clockitude.  Hmm...I'll have to write about Meg sometime....  For now, cheers.  
     
    
</post>

<date>25,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Finally, the anger begins to cool....  I came away from Christmas Eve with my family with two very different emotions raging in my heart.  Pure rage at my sister, pure love for my mom.  I'm trying really hard to focus on the love, but the anger burns at the edges of my consciousness.  And what makes me even angrier is that it's really nothing new.  It's the same old...expletive...that goes on whenever my sister is in the picture.   My sister is very selfish.  She feels that her wants and needs are top priority of the people around her, with no disregard for other's feelings.  And this makes me so angry sometimes I just want to scream at her and force her to open her eyes.    And why don't I?  I'm starting not to know anymore....I know that I didn't before because I was scared that doing so would upset the family unity, would drive her away more than she already takes herself....but this cannot stand.  I cannot abide.  I cannot stand looking at my mother's eyes after my sister goes about her merry selfish way.  It breaks my heart, because I do the same thing my mother does.......I love her and hope, and cover my hurt with a smile.  But it gets harder inside, even as it gets easier outside.  And in the name of truth, I cannot let this continue.    Calm....calm.....  On the flip side of the coin, my mom is probably one of the kindest, self-sacrificing women I've ever met, and I love her more everyday.  Example:  I had to work tonight (Christmas Eve) and had to be at the hospital at 11:00.  Kinda sucks, but I like the shift, and I'm the new guy, and time and a half, so I'm ok with it.   Because of family plans the next day, and the tight schedule, we decide to open gifts on the Eve, and then go to the Richards' house for a party.  It's the old church crowd, and great people, and it's a great time.  After opening the gifts (wrapped by mom, bless her)(for the record, mom and dad were very generous, as per usual (not bragging, just saying they rock))  my sister starts to complain that she is too tired to go to the Richards.  We convince her to go, and we get to the party, and it's great.  My sister really only started to have fun at the end, during the Scrabble game, though, and that's, unfortunately what I had to leave in the middle of.  We all rode together, so she has to leave too.  Immediately, what I cannot describe as anything but whining ensues.  I simmer inside and apologize for going to work, but still she continues.  What am I to do?  I have to go to work; she didn't even want to come to the party.  I simmer.  We start  home, and they decide to drive around and look at Christmas lights after they drop me off.  My sister continues to whine, and right before I get out of the car to go into the house, she accuses me of ruining her Christmas.  At this point, I can't take it.  I just wish everyone a good night, and go into the house to get food for work.  I hate my sister at this point.  I can't help it, I do.  I want nothing more than to have a good Christmas, I try to have a child's delight, but her cynism and selfishness stick a needle in everything I'm trying to feel and project.  I am not an angry man by nature, but I am angry then.  Pissed, in fact. But then. I come back outside and the SUV is still in the driveway.  My dad and my sister are still inside it, but my mom is outside, scraping off my car.  She is out in the cold, cleaning off my car for me so that I can leave for work right away, and so that I don't have to do it.  And my heart cracks.  One side is still angry with my sister, but the other side swells with love for my mom.  And that makes me able to continue to love my sister at that time.  Even as I am so so angry with her, I am able to love her because of my mom.  Because my mom loves her and my mom loves me with a mother's pure love.  And that is Beautiful.  Merry Christmas, everyone.  And God bless mothers. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Is it bad to get attached to things very easily?  I have a roomful of....stuff that says things about me and brings forth emotions, powerful and bland.   But do I need this stuff?  No.  Do I want to throw it away?  No.  And I am the same way with relationships.  I get attached to people, I get loyal to them, and it's very hard to throw them away.  And I guess I come to expect the same thing from them, even though it sometimes doesn't work that way.    And that sucks.  And while I know that some people know and love that loyalty, and some people know and exploit that loyalty, I wonder sometimes if it is worth the pain.  And I have to believe that yes, it is.  Despite all the doubts, despite all the shit that sometimes goes with relationships, I have to believe it's worth it.  But that doesn't mean that sometimes I can't throw some of them away, or throw some of the aforementioned stuff away.  It's just hard to know when to reap, and when to sow.  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, just a little recap of life right now:  Hospital + Flu Scare + Telephone operator = D'Gah!  Busy!  Other than that, life is actually excellent, for...reasons.  By the way, thank you Peter Jackson!
     
    
</post>

<date>13,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Greetings.  Funny Story:  I haven't blogged in a while because the internet at our house has been down because of Lady Misfortune choosing to strike at the heart of my housemate's computer, the self-same one that conducts the internet to the rest of our comps.  Although we are currently investigating a number of different things, Mike's computer remains silent.  The funny part of this story concerns moving my computer into the upstairs bathroom cubby and pleading, conjoling and cursing it into operational status.  Although it does everything else, it still does not accept the Internet.  I will teach it about respect yet.  So here we find me, sitting at work again (I really do have a job that occasionally requires effort, honest injun), fighting the Man, and using the internet illegally.  I've been having a week that as far as I can tell, has been nothing but good.  I've got to see a lot of people.  Some of those people were the Barenaked Ladies (woo-hoo).  Work has been really good.  Our boss came back from her sick leave, so certain....plans and schemes can be set into motion.  Someone from 6100 likes me.  Or so I hear.....  We sat down at home and fleshed out plans, and cleared up uncertainty, and came to realize our own Bungalow mortality.    I worked out with my mom.  I wheeled-dealed with my dad.  Huh.  I continue my campaign to cast off fear and uncertainty, to pursue truth, to enjoy life, and figure out my place in the Plan.  One thing I can say for sure, Neal Hausch rocks.  I'll get back to you about the rest....
     
    
</post>

<date>07,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello again, friends and confidants.  Just sittin' here at work, talking to the occasional person and thinking my long drawn thoughts.  One of the things I'm currently reading is The Sandman Library, a collection of graphic novels by one Neil Gaiman, a fascinating modern writer of our time, dark but piercing.  One of the things I love about Neil is that he shows how the dark side of our life works for a redemptive purpose; after all, is Heaven quite the same without the counter-balance of Hell?  And Heaven and Hell are the two things I want to muse about in this entry.  One of the aspects of religion that drive so many people away is the prospect of Hell.  They view it as a Christian "scare tactic", that people will change their ways simply to stay out of it. The more that I've thought about it, and the more I've viewed human behavior, the more I come to see Hell as not just a metaphysical place but also a state.  C.S. Lewis, in his book The Great Divorce writes about how people are trapped by their own fears, their own sins and trangressions against themselves and others.   The more misery that I hear about and see in real life, the more I believe this.  I feel that people, as a result of their own actions, work towards making for themselves a private Hell here on earth.  This is not to say that I don't believe in Hell after we die, as further punishment for our sins, but it amazes me how people work toward creating it here on earth as well.  This is the argument I use (mostly with myself) against pre-marital sex.  A lot of people suffer the consequences of this act, and yet they can't see how destructive it is, they just focus on the pure physical pleasure. It's not just morals, people.  It's just plain common-sense.  God reserved sex for marriage not only because that keeps it a pure act, but also because it causes a ton of problems performed out of marriage.  It screws up not just your life but the potentiall child born of that act.  I've seen countless examples of "Custody of Child-Services Board of Summit County" under the space where the parents' names should be, right here at the hospital. It makes me really upset, sometimes, the Hell we could avoid with just some restraint.  Conversely, I have been thinking about Heaven, as well.  And how people can attain it here on earth, as well as after death.   To attain it after death, you need to have accepted Jesus into your heart, but to attain it here on earth is not so tricky.  You need to actually live like you have accepted Jesus.  And hey, I know that I don't do that all the time.   But I wish I did.   To live free of that fear, pride, and sin is Heaven.   The best times of my life have been when I know that I am casting all of that off of me, and following Him.   And most of those times have not been in a church.  I know that there is a lot of outside influences that cause people to act the way they do, but I also wish they would try to work past that, to forgive themselves and others, but also to give that extra little bit, help a man when he's down, kiss a boo-boo.  Care.    
     
    
</post>

<date>06,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I am a html thief!  And I love it!
     
    
</post>

<date>06,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      And from the mire of miscommunication I spring forth, a new creature!  It's amazing how low the low times can be, and conversely, how high the high times can be.  It's worth it, really.  I will gladly brave the valleys just to stand on top of the mountains, bare my chest, and bellow.  Yep, it's been another hot and cold week/end so far, with slogs in the dank, dirty mires and gallavanting among the free, open plains.  Relationships make life worth the living, is all that I will say.  Despite my poor bumbling spirit, people are beautiful and continue to amaze and inspire me.  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, real quick.  I'm at work, using the illegal internet.  We still don't have internet at home working again for.....certain reasons.  And they are cracking down on the internet usage here at work.  So I may not be talking for a while.  Sorry.    Suffice to say, I'm pretty good though.  That's all you're getting now, though.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      And.......I'm back.  In a couple of the senses of the word, although mostly it's because we finally have internet and working computers at our house again.  In another sense, I just got back from Belize (Central America, it turns out), and a wedding in Indiana of one of my best friends from high school, Brian Coon.  My apologies to the lady.   ;)  To recap my life right now:  Moving to Chicago in 5 months.   Hoping to get into publishing or maybe do something with theater, but more going for a change of scenery and because I've always wanted to live in a big city. I'm scared about going, but I need to go.  I need to check out Brian in Chicago.  I like Brian in Canton, but he's antsy.  I still honestly have no idea what I want to do with my life.  I get little nudges from God but no big flags waving in my face.  I want big flags, though.  I want to passionately pursue my destiny.  I'm doing a lot of traveling and doing more soon.  It's good to be home but it's a big world out there.  I am a gamer, through and through.  I love games of all kinds and am good at a lot of them.  I have the good blend of patience, competitiveness, and creativity to excell with them.  I'm seeing how I can translate them into a career currently.   That's enough for recap, I'm going to get ready for work.  Peace!    
     
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I'm over at Brian and Rebecca's apartment, hanging out, waiting to Settle Catan and just kinda hanging out while they wish Kendra a Happy Birthday.  I add today to my recent spurt of almost movie days.  Me and Brian almost went and saw  Kill Bill vol. 2 , but couln't find the theater.  Darn you, Akron!  Foiled again!  I almost went and saw  Hellboy  with the Greek, and then Matt Jones, and I might actually be able to see it with Christopher tomorrow.    However, I did see  Secret Window  with Denise, and that was great.  I'm not always a huge fan of Stephen King movies per se, but I love Johnny Depp.  Love, Love, Love. As a friend.  :)  So life has been pretty good otherwise.  I was late to work today, which I hate, but can't seem to avoid every now and again.  I need a new alarm clock.  Or at least need a new one to add to the current jumble of four.  (one doesn't work, but I habitually set it and turn it on, hoping and dreaming)   Or maybe I just need to get more sleep.  Need to start looking for jobs/house in Chicago.  Need to get on that.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I feel really good.  I had a great weekend with my friend Katie Sams and her roommates Bailey and Susie.  I was scared that they wouldn't like me, or I would be really shy, but we took to each other like a mime to silence.  I'd forgotten how much I like entertaining people, and meeting new people, and having kung fu adventures.  Ok, maybe we didn't have any kung fu adventures, but we did talk about yoga at one point.  That's close, right?  I'd forgotten how much I enjoy hanging out with Katie.  She's one of those people that you can just talk to about pretty much anything and have a really good time doing it.  Her comedic reflexes are well-tuned, and she's very caring.  She's good stuff, that Katie Sams.  We did a lot of stuff.  We watched two movies ( Waiting For Guffman  (finally saw it, praise Jesus) and  Y Tu Mama, Tambien ) and went to a short film festival.  We also did the Columbus Art Gallery Hop and went to a pub.  I met Bailey's boyfriend Cameron and he works at Chick-fil-a, but apparently he is quitting in two weeks.  I tried to talk him out of it, but alas.    Man, my soul is bubbling.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I almost forgot, movie shout-outs.  Go see  Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind .  But only if you have been in a relationship.  Any relationship at all.  Go see  Dawn of the Dead .  But only if you have been in a relationship.  With a zombie.  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Feeling a bit down tonight, think it's just because of my irregular work schedule and sleep schedule.  I'm feeling the press of relationships right now, that feeling that I have to be everything to everybody.  Keep in mind, not singling anyone out in particular.  That's not true, I am.   The three dominant relationships in my life right now.  Toph, Mike and Denise.  I have things that I want to be to everyone, and things that I try to be at all times, like funny, and nice, and caring, and fun to be around.  And it disappoints me when I can't do that all the time.  And I guess it's on nights that I dwell on my own limitations that I get really pensive and mopey.  This is one of those nights.  One of the frustrating things about relationships to me are defining them.  I badly want them to be defined, yet I am afraid when they are that they won't be what I want them to be.  Gosh, that was a mouthful (or handful, as it were).  I wish that I didn't want them to be defined.  I wish I was happy just with what they are, or aren't.   Maybe the key to my happiness lies in letting go of this, just feeling the love and friendship when it's there, and moving on when it's not.   But I mourn it when it's not there.  Grrr.....I'm getting frustrated trying to convey what I mean.    I accidently swore at the nursing supervisor at the hospital tonight.  She was calling to let me know she was on call, and I meant to say either "Good Luck", or "Have Fun", but didn't decide which one to say in my head first, and it came out "Good F***".  That took some explaining, but she thought it was funny, and indicative of how the night was going to be.  Heh.  I only played one April Fool's Day joke, on one of the other operators.  I called and asked her how much a baby would cost, preferable an Asian one, and even though she didn't know it was me at first, it was admirable how she played along.  I'm happy, I'm going down to Columbus this weekend to see my friend Katie Sams and go to a short film festival.    Speaking of which, I'm going to bed.    Peace, gentle readers.  If you exist.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Whoosh-Whoosh-Whoosh-Whoosh-Whoosh-Whoosh......  There.  Now we've traveled back in time a week and a half.  At this time, I was still in Ireland with my mum, her knees were still unhurt, and I had not yet seen the most impressive sight that I've ever seen.  After we we took our day-trip to Galway City, my mum and myself went back to our Bed and Breakfast to prepare for our next two days of bus-trips.  And I must say that I was pleasantly surprised to find that the average age on the trips wasn't 90.......  ...................  Actually, screw it.  I can't go back and write about my time in Ireland with as much candor and wit as I would like, especially since I'm also watching  Love, Actually  with my housemate Mike.  And it's a great movie, but mixed memories.  Shit.  Anyways, state of the union time.  I'm doing pretty well.  I'm kinda lonely but inspired.  I have a lot of things that I want to get done, but I more just want someone to cuddle with.  Is that pathetic?  I don't think so.  I think that people need physical/emotional contact.  I don't want kissing (although I wouldn't turn it down).  I just want to hold someone and have them hold me and just....be.  Cyber-sigh.  Watched a good movie last night,  The Tripletts of Belleville .  It was good, but I had to see the whole thing to appreciate it.  The music is fanstastic.  The song haunts.  Do we all have self-preservational things that we do in relationships?  Is this the cause for pain in so many ways?  Why do we go through these cyeles, getting hurt by others and thus hurting others ourselves?       
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Once again I entangle you, gentle reader, in my web of lies.  I said that I would finally put my week-old ireland stuff on this here blog.  I am a big fat liar.  To my credit, I didn't have the alone time I thought I was going to have, Russ came over and we've been gabbing (I feel like an old woman when I say that).  But definitely later tonight, or tomorrow, I will finally put forth sufficient effort to impress you with the tales of my travels and exploits.  I will raise the bar and say that if I don't blog by tomorrow, everyone that reads this can have one free punch to my stomach.  In addition to sating your appetites for violence, it will enable me to find out how many people read my blog.  So the heat is on.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, I'm a big punk.  I haven't put my new Ireland stuff.  But to my credit, I have been truly busy, and last night I was going to do, but there was a big computer party at our house, and I couldn't get on the Internet.  And me and Toph just spent the last hour and a half fixing my computer after said party.  And now I'm really tired, really hungry, and a touch sad.  All of which I will go into tomorrow.  Promise.  I have 2 hours completely free, and this blog is priority uno!
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ugh.  Just got in after 4 plane changes and 5 hours of delays.    Feeling pretty icky, and reaaaaaally tired, so going to bed.  Had no internet access in the area that we went to, so no updates.  Promise to update tomorrow, suffice to say, trip was amazing.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ireland Update:  Hail and 'Ello from the land of Ire.  My mum and myself are currently in Galway, on the far west of island.  Galway is the third largest city in the Republic of Ireland, preceded by Cork and Dublin being tops.  I came to Galway the last time I was in Ireland and enjoyed it immensely, and decided to show my mum the sights.  I also went to Cork last time too, but decided it wasn't worth popping in there again.              The driving situation has improved immensely.  I can now maneuver even the infamous damn dirty roundabouts (Tallmadge Circle type thing, all North-East Ohio folk) with a minimum of crying and screaming.  My mum's navigational abilities have improved immensely as well, thank goodness.  We were a hair-breaths from just saying 'screw it' and turning the car in all together, but we realized that after our shopping, mass transit is not an easily viable option.          While in Dublin we saw Dublin Castle, ate at a pub called the Hairy Lemon, and never managed to find St. Patrick's Cathedral.  We saw Ha'Penny Bridge, a famous footbridge across the Liffey River, and also went to Trinity College, home to the luminescient Book of Kells which is famous for some reason that currently escapes me.  I want to say oldest surviving book of Gospels?  I don't know.    I've had a Guinness each night that I've been in Ireland, and hope to continue that.  It just seems more....right over here.      Tomorrow we are going to see the Cliffs of Moher (haven't been), and the day after that, probably go to the Aran Islands (been there, loved 'em).                 So I'll check in later,                                  friends,                                          countrymen,                                                     and etc.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Top of the morning to ya! (no one really says that, by the way)  Here am I, current and past traveler in the land of Ireland, coming atcha with all my current adventures and misadventures.  Any spelling or punctuation I can fairly attribute to the foreign keyboard.  It's weird.  Me and me Mum came into Dublin Airport at 9:30 in the a.m. after a fitfully slept plane ride.  And that's where it kinda went downhill.  We rented a car and started what turned out to be a long and painful instruction in the art of Irish driving and navigation.  After about three hours of being lost and one busted sideview mirror later, we made our way into the town of Skerrie.  And that's where the shit hit the fan.  Angry and frustrated, exhausted and full of need for the bathroom, we apparently also looked like good people to mug.  Thanks to my quick-thinking Mum, we didn't, but it was pretty scary.  If anyone asks you where the police station is, immediately run away screaming.  This is what I have learned.          After driving lost for a bit more, we got directions from a wonderful little old lady in a craft store who happened to be good friends with the people who we were going to staying with.  We got there with no more big problems.    After checking into the B&B, I immediately fell asleep for about 3 hours, which is amazing because I never nap.  When I awoke, my Mum had made friends with some other Americans staying in the B&B, and they invited us to dinner at a restaurant called the Man O' War.  Before that we went down to Ardgillan Castle (which was really more of a manor house, to castle snobs like myself :)  ) and then booked it back in time to meet the people and go eat.  I soon realized upon entering the restaurant that I was a bit out of place in my Ironic Intermural Basketball t-shirt, so I attempted to act very poised instead.  I also ate a rabbit.  I had some Guiness as well, and remembered how much I missed it.  It's really not the same as it is in the States.  The people we ate with were friends and relations somehow, and the men were both retired military and one couple owned a dude ranch in Texas and in the other the guy was a retired lawyer as well.  I hate to say it, but I never learned much about the women.  They seemed more like motherly types, so I assumed they were mothers.  Which is still a big job.  Um.......bad Brian.  I learned a lot about inseminating cattle, though, and they encouraged me to wait til 30 to marry.  Huh.  Me and Mum are currently in Dublin, going to see Trinity College and St. Patrick's Cathedral.  We are also trying to not get mugged.  To discourage muggers, we glare at anyone that comes within 5 feet of us.  Anyone that comes nearer gets a swift and decisive punch to the midsection.  Man, pregnant ladies sure get pissed easily.  Anywho, I'm off, I will check back in when I can.  Note to Christopher, if he reads this:  I am destined to hate at least one Old Irish Man that I come in contact with.  Luckily, I have gotten it out of the way early.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      To Ireland, I.  Well, this is it.  T-minus 10+ hours till my plane leaves for the Emerald Isle.  I will blog from Ireland on this site, to let everyone know what is going on.  I must return to packing for now.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Mental Note:  When you have loose swords in a room, turn on a light before blindly groping about.  Yikes.    Sorry for all the short entries, but I'm busy.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hell yeah.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I shared a moment with a bunny tonight, and it was great.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ache.  I ache tonight.  And not in that hurt-soul way I usually whine about, just in that body-feels-like-creaky-steps way.  I don't know why I feel this way, I didn't work out or anything.  It must just be my body being pissed as me for the weird sleep schedule.  Ever since I entered the dreaded "9-5 workforce", my body has been pretty good.  I've felt healthier and have been eating better.  But just the past couple of days I have stayed up pretty late and, as is to be expected, gotten up pretty late too.  Today, my body just gave me the finger.  Which stinks, because there was a lot of stuff I wished to accomplish today.  Although I'm not sure I would have actually done them anyways, it's frustrating when your body is a jerk.  I stayed up really late last night with Mike and Toph and The Greek, playing Star Wars and generally being a droid.  Let's just say I fell asleep to the sound of birds chirping.    And while I used to love that, it's just started to feel.... wrong , I guess.  Am I getting older?  Are the sins of the young Brian catching up with the older Brian.  Gee, I sure hope not.  Frankly, I much prefer it just be mono or something.  Well, maybe not, but anyways, I used the enforced time spent inside to ponder, watch  Singles  (I'd forgotten it was by Cameron Crowe), and generally to finally roll up my sleeves and clean my bloody room.  Cleaning my room is one of those things that I enjoy while I'm doing it, but completely dread in the before time.  It's like exercising, scuba diving, and first dates.    I found all the want ads that my mom had saved for me that I'd tossed to the side, since I won't need them, since I'm going to Chicago.  I found all the old bank statements, my Dupont stock, old thank you cards, random pictures, and the most pulverized fortune cookie that still tasted good, even in sand form.    I always feel loved and safe when I do this, but sad that these parts of my life are over.  They were good parts, and I like them.    All the ghosts of my faltered relationships always spin around my head, somehow clinging to my ceiling fan, and reigning down their nostalgia, and while this is sad, it is also comforting and fulfilling, thinking, "I loved and was loved in return, and grew and helped grow.  This was good." . . . . . I don't know where to go from here, so FIN.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, what do you think, faithful reader?  Pretty fancy looking blog, huh?  Yeah, I've got a couple offers from CNN, Fox News, and the Trinity Broadcasting Network to write and do graphic design, but I've turned them down.  My place is here, my time is now.  My people need me.  Plus, I made all that up.  Yup, one thing that hasn't changed about this blog is that lies are a constant.  Purely for humor sake, of course.  Maybe.  Anyway, the incomparable Andrew Rudd helped me to slap a fresh coat of paint on the old nag, and showed me some neat tricks.  In addition, his comments are present, as are others, for my viewing pleasure and for the viewing pleasure of our more opinionated patrons who in turn wish to make their feelings about my state of mental retardation known.  And don't think I don't appreciate it.  Heh.  I do have to do some more work on the links, as most of the other people's blogs links are outdated and coarse, and my personal fun stuff is also needing some revision.  Those links are sooooo last year!   On a more personal note, I am doing very well.  I've been frolicing around with many people and enjoying the companionship of a new group of people, Emily's Friends, who are swiftly becoming referred to in my head as My Friends.  They are mostly younger than me, but very intelligent and quirky.  Other than that, I am doing well.  The turmoil in my soul is settling and I'm starting to just enjoy being.  For now, however, I think I will enjoy being in bed.  
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow, such horrible spelling and paragraphical structure in that last post.  I'm going to fix it.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am an odd mixture tonight.  I'm definitely tired and should go to bed, but haven't gotten the caffeine from the cappucino I drank about noonish out of my system....that's some strong stuff.....thanks hot Daily Brew girl!  So I remain awake, weary but restless.  I'm weary because I'm tired of always having to be the person to call people, to step out and get together, and arrange stuff.  I know that people are doing important things, but I just want some justification that I am important to them.    I have this theory that maybe I'm mentally handicapped and I just don't know it, and people are just nice to me and friends with me out of guilt and charity.  It's only in my lowest moments I resort to this amusing scenario, but it's a thought.  On the rejuvenated side, I saw some people I haven't seen for a while tonight, and had a really good talk with Samantha, and she always knows how to make a person feel worthy and loved.  We've definitely gotten a lot closer lately, partly because of our mutual relationship problems and partly because we just have these amazing late-night restaurant talks.  I think we both feel this need to live a worthy life through caring about people and we both feel that our lives should be a work of art in themselves.  Plus, we both love cards.  I've resolved to be nicer to the people that call me at work.  Answering thousands upon thousands calls a day tends to put a drain on my ability to form connections with people, but I'm gonna try my best.  I resolved this on Memorial Day, and wouldn't you know it, that's when all the crazies called.  I'm tired of feeling sad about girls and my soul is getting to have just about enough. . . . . Man, I've been really mopey lately.     
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, ok.  I have decided that one (Edited for Content) I will expound upon.  I'm not sure who reads this blog, so I wanted to be sensitive, but you know, screw being coy and proper, I want to talk about it.  This journal is for nothing else if not me, right?  I have been dating Kat for a while now, and it's been great.  We're talking my head feels filled with cotton candy, my fingers and toes are electrified, my blood pumps through my veins to the timbre of Kat's laugh.  So that's (one of) my secret posts.  Part of the reason I didn't want to write about it is I'm not sure which of my ex-girlfriends read this blog, and I didn't want to have the online equivalent of when you see the ex at a party, and they are with someone else, and you feel crappy, because I've been through things like that, and they are one of the worst feelings in the world.  But I would like to point out that if they are still reading this, they are taking that chance.  I didn't force them into anything.  I personally still read their blogs with that fear but with the knowledge I still get to read about their lives and see if they are ok.  If we're going to be real honest, I also get to enjoy dark joys once in a while as well, but hey...    If you are still with me at this point, I met Kat's parents last night, and it was truly enjoyable.  Her parents are very animated and inviting, and her sister didn't give me any of the hard time I was warned of and secretly feared.  Side Note:  I find myself drawn more and more to speaking stories instead of writing them.  It's tougher, especially when I make them up on the spot, but it's fun to have the reactions of an audience right there with you.    I get my car back soon, it's fixed, but to the unpleasant tune of $400.  I've been staying at my parent's house and using my mom's car for the most part and it's been kind of nice.  Like a little vacation:  I don't have to clean up much, free food, and nicer accomodations than I'm used to.  BTW- My parents = saints.  I just finished a Stephen King novel, and it was great.  Every time I read his stuff, I'm completely sucked in by his writing style and the way that he artfully crafts horror.  This sucking can be bad, but oh so good.  I'm off, faithful readers, to an Indians game.  Baseball!  :)  My dad got Loge (sp?) seats from PAX 23 'cause his store advertises with them, so I'll go at least for the free beer and food, and so me and Kat can hob-nob with TV executives.    Word.   
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sorry about all the (Edited for Content) stuff in the previous post, but there were some things that seemed public in the deep of night, and more private in the harsh light of day.  So if you want to know more about it, talk to me.  And I just might tell you what the deal is.    
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If I'm glad for nothing else in this life, I'm glad that I have the ability to appreciate irony, and find it amusing.  Many things have been afoot since my last post, so I hope that you will excuse me for my absence, gentle reader.  In no particular order, here's life as it stands...  I have mono.  I have started (Edited for Content).  My car started unhappily smoking today.  I've (Edited for Content).  I won at poker.  In general, it's been a pretty tumultous two weeks since my last post.  I've been pretty busy, and I've had a lot of fun.  Unfortunately, I've also been pretty tired, and my throat has been hurting like the dickens.  Luckily, it's starting to feel better today, and I've been less feverish.  The reason why I can appreciate irony is that if you look at my previous post, I make reference to the fact that I would rather blame my achy body on mono than on getting older, and my wish came true, in that kick you in the nuts kind of way.  So I guess I have to thank God for that.  I'm not going to say much about (Edited for Content), other than I've learned the value of a blown kiss.  :)  My car just started smoking while I was driving it today, and luckily I was able to pull off really easily, and AAA was on the scene lickety split.  The guy that came and towed me was pretty rough, but nice, and taught me all I've ever wanted to know about the towing business, and a bit more.  Dad seems to think it was the A/C that gave out, but I'll call in the morning to see what the damage is.  I guess it's a good thing I've been saving up.  I've (Edited for Content), so that's a problem.  I won at poker!  This is four times out of eight poker nights.  I don't understand, but I like winning, and I like fellowship, and I kinda like the money.  So woo-hoo!  We had a really great turn-out for the poker night, it being the first co-ed one.  And I ate some really good ribs.  So there's me in a bloody great nutshell for right now, just to recap.  I've missed lots of bits and pieces, moments frozen in the amber of my mind, but I just don't have the endurance to put them down right now.  And I would be relying too much on the attention and endurance of my readers as well, all four of you.  :)  So suffice to say, life is good, God is great, despite the road bumps.  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>