<Blog>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
         I started my new workout regime today.  This regime seems more legitimate than my previous ones, which for the past two weeks has been no regime at all.  The method I am using is one I stumbled across on the 'net called HST, or more specifically  urlLink HyperTrophy Strength Training .  It is based on scientific research, and after reading about it I felt blinded -- by science.    Today was the day I figure out my maximum loads for each exercise.  Having not been to the gym for two weeks I felt nearly dead after working out.  I'm sure tomorrow when I wake I will be unable to move a thing.  I have lost 8 pounds in the past two months, mostly due to my diet.  Now I am ready to build up some muscle.  Sitting at my computer working all day is incentive enough to get up and do something physical.  We'll see if I can last the summer on this.  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Row-deo     This weekend was hot, hot, hot. It was really the best weather we've had all year and despite the vicious hail storms and having to work, I managed to spend most of the weekend outside. Friday night I went to the infamous  "Red Mile"   (aka. 17th Ave.) for drinks. Last time I was there with 100,000 Flames fans and a few floozies. Even though there were a lot of people celebrating the Stampede, it wasn't quite the same experience. We ended up at Ming with some friends sweating and drinking.        One of my friends in town from England with her boyfriend and they're on a Bubble-Tea marathon, drinking over 20 in a week and a half. Apparently the Bubble-Tea in London is not easy to find and not very good tasting. In Taiwan (where it originated) and Hong Kong   Bubble-Tea   vendors are everywhere like Starbucks in Vancouver.  I think they just might be more refrshing than beer too.      Saturday night my girlfriend and I hosted a BBQ at Edworthy Park. The BBQ's there are wood-burning, which proved to be quite uncomfortable in the evening heat. On top of that, we forgot to bring wood and so I had to carry a large bag of pine across the length of the park.    This year I vowed not to attend the Stampede because attending it every year for the past 25 years has made me want to hurl. Sunday, the last day of the Stampede, we visited some friends on the outskirts of the grounds who were staging a rather small protest of the Rodeo. It was the Rodeo finals that day and the protestors dropped a massive banner on a hill overlooking the grandstands. Most of the people walking by were true Calgary hicks and hurled unrecognizable profanities at the protesters.   Later that day my girlfriend and I went to the Glenmore Reservoir and rented a Canoe. We both ended up with sunburn. And then it was time for more Bubble-Tea! We ended up sitting on Cresent Hill eating candy overlooking the city until 3am. I ended up taking a few good shots that day of a very green city.      I'm going to Toronto next week for 6 days.  Pretty excited about it.             Elbow River          Glenmore Reservoir          Calgary from Stampede Park           
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       The Stiffy near the Liffey   I went to the travel agent today to get some information on working visa's to Ireland and it got me thinking back to last Spring when I was there.  I started thinking about the General Post Office on O'Connell Street in Dublin and the bulletholes in the pillars.  I don't know why, but I did.  The bullet holes remain from when the Post Office was the headquarters for the 1916 uprising.  In case you are rusty on your Irish history, like me, then the 1916 uprising (Easter Uprising) was when the Irish Citizen Army proclaimed the Irish republic.  But then, suddenly, I began thinking less about the bullet holes and more about the big spike.          Street fighting on O'Connell Street during Rising          O'Connell Street 1940's         A 134-foot pillar, topped by a statue of Nelson and inspired by Trafalgar Square, dominated O'Connell Street for many years until it was blown apart by the IRA in 1966, marking the 50th anniversary of the uprising.  Recently, and to replace Nelson after almost 35 years of sad emptiness, came the  urlLink Dublin spire ; yes, a 120m tall silver spike.  It is 3 meters thick at the base and only 15cm at the top -- ouch.  It was still in construction when I saw it in 2003, and three years late for the millennium celebrations.        What remained of Nelson         The spike, out of Nelson's ashes  Photograph by Al Geraty. Image courtesy educate-yourself.org        There are  urlLink some  who claim the spike harnesses energy, or at least provides mild electrical thrills.  This wouldn't surprise me, considering it is a 120 meter metal rod in a country with frequent storms.  I'll have to try it out myself.  Of course, in good Irish literary tradition renaming monuments is a fun pastime.  Here are a few unofficial names for the spire:    The Stiffy near the Liffey  The Stiletto in the Ghetto  The eyeful tower  The Gleaming Tower of Pizza-land  Bertie's Erection       Now the Dubliners have a tendency to dislike tall building and rightly so because there are so few in the city.  So, it seems strange that they would choose to build a 120m spire in the centre of the city, and draw attention to it by lighting it up at night.  Especially considering that the tallest building in Dublin, Liberty Hall, caused a general fuss over its height and ugliness, which resulted was a law restricting the maximum size of any new buildings in the city.  If you look to the right, you can see why this law might have been passed.  Regardless, the spike seems to have been accepted and I, for one, can't wait to get electrical thrills from it.     Liberty hall         All other images, courtesy  urlLink http://www.fantasyjackpalance.com . 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Personal Hemingway Adventure     Hemingway. D. Levine © dell'Autore   urlLink http://www.museosatira.it/1999/levine.html#i   I just finished  A Farewell to Arms , which is the second book in my personal Hemingway adventure.  I've really gotten into  urlLink Hemingway  since reading  The Sun Also Rises  in my Fiction class a few months ago.  Hemingway himself was much like the characters in his book. He fought on the Italian front in World War I, was a mean boxer, drank like a fish, patrolled the coasts of Cuba for U-boats during World War II, and hunted lions in Africa, who ran from him holding their tails between their legs.  Hemingway's life must have been more interesting than those of his characters.  Such a life would be fertile with stories, I imagine if my life were nearly as interesting I would have enough stories to write for the rest of it.  Too bad it's not.  I think perhaps I should spice up this blog a little bit.  Having now done some web development I think it would be a good place to play around.  I am doing some web work for an organization called  urlLink WildCanada.net , which is an online conservation organization.  The project will spawn  urlLink Actionworks.ca .  Organizations that promote social action share a common goal and therefore are a tight community.  The people genuinely believe in what their work and are more than willing to share their resources with each other.  This goes against all training I have received in Computer Science, where programmers are tools and their code is the product.  Corporate bitches is perhaps the correct term.  If the world really were a stage, then we would be the lighting technicians. Then again the A/V club would likley be more accurate.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I've been the gym two more times since the last post.  I am a rippling muscle-bound hunk now.  OK, maybe not but it's a good start.  The serious stuff starts next week.    I saw  urlLink  Fahrenheit 9/11  a few days ago.  It was a little more gruesome than I expected it to be -- death, bodies, blood, and arms without skin resembling something off of the Terminator.  Moore chose to black out the World Trade Tower's collapse only to follow it with numerous gut-wrenchingly bloody scenes; I think I missed the point of this.  The documentary did, however, lower my perception of Bush from a dirt-bag to an oil-whore faster than the Patriot act could be passed through congress.  I suppose Moore wins then.      Speaking of the Patriot act, some poor artist in the States was  urlLink accused of bio-terrorism  after his wife died of a cardiac arrest.  Seems his art supplies had some bacteria on them.    For Canada day I went into the mountains.  It was a very Irish day with alternating rain and sun.  We watched the yearly Canada day parade in Canmore, which featured the first ever streaker in the parade.  We also went for a hike in Banff around the coal mining ghost town of  urlLink Bankhead . 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>