<Blog>


<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       There is comfort in the knowledge you are of your kind and species that your deeds be not forgotten when your flesh has joined your forbears who have held this land before you and returned to earth, and rotted, in their time and in their season but yet live in you and through you.  You will die, not like the sparrow unregarded, unconsidered, in the dark beyond the chamber, people's names are known, remembered, if they dare to live when living. Your wide actions build tomorrow that your children see without you every deed that's well accomplished lives beyond you, and each sapling that you plant and tend and care for casts its shade into that future that you neither fear nor enter.  All will die, decay and perish and the world will perish with it. In the scale of rocks and oceans you are living in an eyeblink. In the scale of stars and planets life itself too fast to measure flickering green upon the surface. All the gods and stars will perish entropy alone will triumph in cold victory-feasts of stillness.  This is comfort: face it bravely. Your significance, your measure but the scale of your perspective and the way you live while living. That you are a fleeting dust mote is a truth you can encompass and go on, each breath accomplished in the joy of human living till you die and each breath choosing life, and time for love and caring, unimportant and a hero both together, faring forward free of fate, in choice, becoming what you will, your destination.   ~Jo Walton 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink SpaceRef - Space News As It Happens  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Linux is just different, ie, not windows.  But here's some good doc sites:     urlLink The Linux User's Cookbook.    urlLink The Linux Documentation Project.    
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Really going to the bubbles now. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hmm, reminds me that I need to work on the presentation for Johns Manville.  Not sure that I liked how it went in Los Alamos. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Oh, and here's Edward Tufte's article in  urlLink Wired  explaining why PowerPoint is  urlLink the spawn of  the Devil . 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Cool idea, thanks for inviting me!  As long as I'm here, just ran across someone's PowerPoint presentation explaining  urlLink why they would never use the DoubleTree Hotel in Houston again.   I haven't found anything so far that says what the response was.   
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       What else...also need to figure out how to make the scanner work under Linux, though I do not have high hopes.  There are some parts that I like re Linux and some that are a pain in the butt:  * printer does not work * software is harder to install * sound iffy * Netscape makes me choose a new user every time I open it  Email is better.  Surfing faster.    Though I have started getting loads of SPAM and never did before.  Oh, well, I am moving and will have a new email shortly. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I need to do the paperwork to get reimbursed from Berwanger and Los Alamos.  Tomorrow! 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Kamir does not like packing. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Off now to a bubblebath.  3 of the 4 lights in the bathroom burned out this weekend.  Might be time to move.  :) 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Avoiding chores here at this end of the bog.  Considering making something for dinner.  Not hungry, but the waffles that I had were 10 hours ago.  So, I suppose.  Kamir is shadowing me around the apartment today.  He is on the second office chair, squirmed around and upside down in that strange cat manner.  He is sleeping now.  I imagine that he would enjoy some wet and juicy kitty food sometime soon.  I need to finish laundry and make the apartment somewhat fit for public consumption.  The Pet Nanny will come and play with Kamir each day that I am gone.  I wonder if that is tax deductible?  Interesting thing I read today was that I should be able to use Medical Spending Account money for the difference between normal food and celiac food.  That is a new one.  Could put more money in the next one that I have.  Already spent all of the Celanese one this year.  Enough thoughts on taxes...off to cook some rice. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The scientific theory I like best is that the rings of Saturn are composed entirely of lost airline luggage. - Mark Russell 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Dwelling on the negative simply contributes to its power. - Shirley MacLaine 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       One cool thing on the New Mexico trip was Cochiti Dam and Pueblo.  There are some pictures of the dam (one of the ten largest in the US, it is one of four dams on the Rio Grande) at:     urlLink Picture of Cochiti Dam    urlLink Picture of Cochiti Lake    urlLink Picture of Cochiti Lake    urlLink Picture of Road to Cochiti Dam    
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The movie was OK.  A bit out there, but Jackie Chan is always amusing.  Then off to Luby's for dinner.  Had veggies.  Now am tired and considering bed.  Got my New Mexico pictures back from the developer.  Some OK ones of Albuquerque.        urlLink Los Alamos Online Pictures    
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Continuing on the quest for a new job.  Just finished making arrangements to visit OK and CO.  One hopes that I find a new job someplace nice and someplace soon.    I need to edit some more for work, but will do some of that later.  Need to drop off the dry cleaning.  And the pictures from New Mexico.  Then off to the movies.  The Medallion. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         You're a Non-box.    urlLink   What box do you get put in?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink iWon - Horoscopes : "Romance  Be a hero of tenderness and consideration. Bring your sweetheart a surprise. Although this is just a gift to show your love, there may be an implied message. And what if there is? Who's going to say no to a wonderful person like you?"  ROFL, just no freaking comment! 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink CNN.com - Director Elia Kazan dead at 94 - Sep. 29, 2003 : "NEW YORK (AP) -- Director Elia Kazan, whose triumphs included the original Broadway productions of 'Death of a Salesman' and 'A Streetcar Named Desire,' and the Academy Award-winning film 'On the Waterfront,' died Sunday. He was 94.  Kazan was at his home in Manhattan when he died, lawyer Floria Lasky said. She did not give a cause of death."  I wonder...was it um, OLD AGE? 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       YAWN.  Not in the mood, but off to the wars.  Wow, maybe I am a soldier.  The mind shudders to think what kind. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Finished the work that I needed to do today.  I did not think that I could, but I did.    Shot went OK, back again on Wednesday for another.  I am wiped though, I think that I will go to bed now.  Just home from dinner with Lynn, roast beef and green beans from Luby's.  Feel kind of sick.  Throat hurts, but probably just the shot.  Will talk to Mustang tomorrow, I think.  Valero wants me in the running, sounded to me like I was #2 and being strung along, though maybe not.  The recruiter was going to call.  Got an odd letter from Johns Manville as well.  Who knows, no one new calling though, which is odd.  I should jingle the CA people tomorrow.   I wonder if the Nano people are at all interested.  Not sure who to call there.  Ah, well, off to read Madeline Albright... 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I suppose that I should think about the other friends in my life.  I know that they value who I am and I think that some of them will always be with me.  I know that my heart will always be with them.  I guess that I am just sad and there is nothing to doubt or sort out with them.  And I do not think that there is anything much to figure out.  Lisa has been a friend for decades and will always be there.  Karen and I survived the crucible of MIT, things like that bond you forever.  Byron is the kindest man that I have ever known and I am honored to be part of his life.  Though, do not get me wrong, I see him as real and human.  But, there is such kindness in him.  And intelligence and insight.  The years that we had together were the best in my life, no question.  Lynn is a nut and I love her pragmatism and humor.    Norm is great when she has time in her life for me.  Same with Chris and Barb.  Every connection with them is life only seconds have passed since the last hello.  They are simply family.  There has never been a place in my life where I did not find good people to spend time with, so I know that I can take any new job and it will be fine.  And I know that my life will reshape into something that is OK.  I guess that I do wish that I could fashion a life where some of these people were still in it day by day.  But life seems to have ideas of its own. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Funny what they said about some hearts never healing.  I always felt that some of the risks that I was taking were too dangerous.  That there were some things from which I would never recover.  Sometimes these days I cannot even grasp an image of what my heart shape was, hard to repair something when you have lost the plans.  And I really do not have the heart to even bother.  I just *know* that I will never want to try somethings again.  Maybe that is what I have learned...that some things are not meant for me.  I do not think that anyone save him could have taught me that.  He certainly knew me better than anyone...so if he never even wanted to talk to me again, then what I am doing any of this for afterall?  David was a child's heart of euphoria.  Dean a logical choice or at least a choice of compromise.  Stephen was and remains love, but a love that needs to be away for now.  And maybe forever, but I know that he is always with me.  And, at every cross-roads, I reach out in my heart or in reality, and he is there.  Wanting me to be happy, wanting to understand my choices and somewhere deep inside wishing for those two lives or wishing that life will leave me his at some distant other time.  But, Charlie, I thought was this soul-deep connection, a safe harbor where I would always be understood, always be loved, always be wanted in his life.  I had no doubts about that and had this notion of sharing a duplex perhaps and living separate, but parallel lives.  I struggled with the idea of whether or not I wanted that.  I was afraid to trust him, with our past.  And I knew that in some ways it would be a very cold friendship.  I knew that he cared about me, but also knew that demonstrating that caring was hard and that somehow it seemed that he needed to always spend a little more time and money on himself than on me.  But, still we had a strong connection and I decided that it was one that I could consider honoring.   And Boulder had felt like home when I had been there before.  So, off I went.    Yet the first 30 seconds together seemed to crystalize for me that I was wrong in many of my assumptions, though most of these assumptions had been tested and discussed with him.  But, that the distance that I sometimes felt was real and I could see at a glance that he did not really love me and no intention of trying.  I suppose that I should have left then, but something said that I needed to stay and help him sort out his apartment some.  I figured that I was just in a unique position to help.  And, I think if I had left we would have remained better friends and I would have continued on.  But having stayed and heard what he had to say about me to others ground the last vestigages of confidence and doubt out of my soul.  The assumptions to make seemed the only ones left.  And they were not pretty or easy.  But, I suppose that life just is neither or those things. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Protector    urlLink   The ULTIMATE personality test     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Simply amazing how tired I am.  Work to do, but Open Office sucks for real work.  And I am way too tired and too fired to rewire the Windows hard drive.  So, screw em.    Talked to Lisa for awhile, she is OK.  Karen too.  She is still grading.  I am OK.  Cramps from Hell.  Though it has been awhile since I threw up, so progress there I guess.  My eyes sting though.  I read the book "The Five People You Meet in Heaven".  It was good.  Reminded me of a play that I wrote for MIT.  Kind of about how life is all intertwined.  *SOME* people need to learn how their actions impact other people.  But, then again, some people are hopelessly self-absorbed.  Maybe in their next lifetime.    Wow, I must be feverish, I am chilled sitting here.  Perhaps a sign from the universe to crawl back into bed.    Probably will get the Mustang offer tomorrow.  Need to consider what to do, but no one to talk about it to really.  No one really cares one way or the other what I do...at least not enough to voice an opinion that sticks.  Maybe I will hear back from the MRI folks too.  That might be nice to know before taking the Mustang gig with no sick time.  Another shot in the AM too.  Oh joy.  I hope the lymph nodes in my neck go down some this week.  That was icky last week and no one could understand me on the phone on Friday.  That was funny when Byron thought we had a bad cell phone connection and it was only that I had lost my voice almost completely.  OK, I will fold laundry and dream about painkillers now.  Onward (and I am not even a Christian soldier and the wars these days not fought for Christ's sake at all)... 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It is odd.  I had not cried much since leaving CO.  Teary today.  A month since we met.  Another 11 to survive until I can claim to have done this day before.  I really do not imagine that I will make that anniversary.  I am too tired, too spent.  Somehow I think that my tasks are nearly done.  Though I still wonder what I learned and what I have left to bear. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yawn, still tired.  Kamir is following me around.  I think that I will take a bath, maybe that will wake me up.  Nothing much happening today.  Lisa is down and grumpy and seems to act like talking to me is burden.  Karen is grading.  Lynn is busy.  Byron is doing whatever.  So, no one seems to want my company.  Something to get used to, I suppose.  I guess that I have to learn to be solitary again.  It is sad to be solitary in a world so full of people.  Though I would rather be alone.   Since what I really want is something that I can never have. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Tired, but awake.  I think that I will make Kamir his breakfast and something for me.  Then crawl back into bed.  Opening windows to air out the place.  Then later on start laundry.  Goal for the day to pack a few boxes and nap. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Though, of course, there was nothing at his house to make me think that he loved me.  It was politeness perhaps.  I was welcome, though mostly ignored.  The only time that he looked happy was when Terri called.  I think that I will always remember the view of the Interlocken hill, the place where the last of the illusions vanished in the night.  Though I have not sorted out what the rainbow meant. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Still no word.  I remember when he left the first time, how I wondered if it had all just been bullshit.  And if he was just a manipulative person, intelligent enough to know what to say to make me think that he cared.   
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Not sure why I am awake.  Survived the SAT.  No word from him.  Miss him. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Byron wants to go to the art show in Houston.  And came by today after school.  Said to call if I came up with something over the weekend.  I might sleep it away.  Lynn wants to do a movie.  I need to go to Target.  And more resumes to send. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Freshly home from dinner with Lynn.  Interesting responses to my celiac mailing list question.  Seems like many get way sicker for a spell.  Something about losing tolerance after awhile.  Understable.  I need to take out trash, start laundry and change.  Karen and Byron called, so need to check messages.  One more day of the SAT. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ARGH, fever and headache, wonder if it is a migraine.  Off to bed. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ugh...off to bubbles.  HEADACHE.  Grrr.  And other celiac symptoms.  Not sure why.  Stress, I suppose.  Watched The Bachelor.  What a crock.  At least they only waste a limited amount of time.  Unlike me... 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Home again.  HEADACHE.  Off to eat something and see if that helps.  SAT proceeds.  Odd results as I left. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       OK, off to the doctor for yet another shot.    And another day of SAT.  Woohoo.  No word from any recruiters, probably not a great sign.  Wal-Mart greeter, here I come. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Wow, pretty sick.  Not sure why.  Did not eat much and none of it questionable.  :(  Ali suggested a job with Aspentech, not sure what I think.  Cool show at the Houston Museum of Fine Arts:   The Heroic Century: The Museum of Modern Art's Masterpieces, 207 Paintings and Sculptures  The Heroic Century presents more than 200 works that together provide a lucid overview of modern art since 1880, as represented by MoMA's unparalleled collection of painting and sculpture. The closure of the permanent collection galleries during construction of the Museum's new building has enabled the inclusion of a number of works that seldom travel but are nonetheless internationally known as canonical milestones in the development of modern art. Major examples include Vincent van Gogh's The Starry Night, Pablo Picasso's Girl Before a Mirror, Jackson Pollock's Number 1, 1948, Roy Lichtenstein's Drowning Girl, Claude Monet´s Water Lilies, Salvador Dali´s The Persistence of Memory, and Jasper Johns's Green Target. The exhibition is accompanied by a fully illustrated catalogue containing an anthology of texts drawn from the Museum's archives and publications dating from 1929 to 2002.  Museum of Fine Arts, Houston  Houston, Texas September 21, 2003-January 4, 2004  Might have to go check it out. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       YAWN.  Off to make dinner.  SAT about halfway through.  Not all that bad.  Ali will show me the rest of what I need to do to complete my end of the bargain.  Not all that ugly.  Another day of no word.  Sent the missive for the month checkpoint.  I was completely right about him, not sure why I even listened.  Oh well.  I guess that I needed to learn about myself.  OK, Universe, a job!  And a good one! 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Not sure about the allergy shots.  Feel way run down.  SAT starts today.  OK, Universe, keep your fingers crossed.  :)  And I want a job! 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       YAWN.  Off to the allergist.  Then a million things at work.  SAT tomorrow.  Yaya.  Oy.  Kamir is being nice. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am for bed now.  Still tired, but not overwhelmingly so.  Did the laundry, though have the last load on the floor waiting to sort.  I might wash the sheets tomorrow night, so that will sort out the rest.  Lynn and Peggy and I did "Secondhand Lions" and lunch.  It was nice.  Last night out was wonderful.  Kind people.  Intelligent.  Nice place...great food.  Was funny looking at myself in the mirror with the hair and fancy make-up...and the fancy skirt and satin.  Did not look like me.  Though, it looked good.  Reminded me of being 12 and Mom commenting that I should always wear make-up.  My skin is OK, but somehow the rest just makes a strong statement.  We shall see.  Will take out the trash on the way out in the morning.  It is raining now and no need to get wet tonight.  Off to the doctor in the morning.  More shots.  Oy.  Mir is sleeping in his bed.  It is quiet, but peaceful.  It feels good to be at a place in my life where no one is judging me and finding me lacking.  Just people that care about me, ask after me, find the time to check on me.  It centers me and makes it possible for me to think of the future.  Of course, it is likely a future with none of them.  But, I guess that it reminds me that there is some worth in me and that I can survive.  And I hope to carry them with me as well.  Read more on Botswana tonight, though only a little bit.  Sorted out somethings for packing.  Might get some done next week.  Need to decide if I am going to Austin for Monday.  Not sure that it is worth it, will see what financial response I get Monday.  Might be novel.  But not sure that I would relax in that risk.  Time will tell.  Nothing else seems to weigh on my mind, so I am for bed.  May your gods go with you. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yawn.  Funny how I feel.  Hard to put into words really.  I am tired.  Took a couple hour nap and still tired.  Mir napped with me.  He is sweet.  I need to pack more.    And eat, I guess.  Not sure why.  Later... 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So, goodbye. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       OK.  Horoscope said to leave him alone.  So, screw it.  He has not called me in two weeks, so well fine.  No matter what he says when I call, obviously he does not want to talk to me.  I think that he must not *really* have cared.  And I never wanted to be someone that he could talk about like he talked about other people from the past...people that cling to him, or want other things from him, or were just somehow a burden.  Screw that.  He knows how to use the phone.  And he knows how to email...well, he did once.  And I am really tired of getting only things that he copies to her too.  I mean it is one thing to move on, but I think that he moved on before he left.  And if she means that much more to him, why did he ever claim to love me or want something from me?  Though screw it, it does not matter, he wants nothing now, *that* much is clear.  I am a good person, even if he cannot value that.  I am fine alone.  I can make more of a difference in the world that way anyway.  So, that is what I will do. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Sigh.  I wish sometimes that I did not care about people.  But then I would not be me.  Tomorrow should be fun.  Fancy eats, etc.  Of course, I am not hungry much lately...not for years really.  Sunday, Secondhand Lions.  MWF shots.  TWRF SAT. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Oh, well, perhaps the first impression was correct, he never has called since CO. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I dunno.   I told him to think about what he wanted.  And he actually talked to me some. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Called him.  Probably not a great idea.  He just makes me feel rejected. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Back.  Short trip, though perhaps fruitful.  Mir, at least, is happy to see me. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       OK, laundry pretty much ready.  Sad to leave Mir again so soon, but I do need to keep him in kibble as it were.  So, on the road once more... 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Bored, waiting for laundry to dry so that I can pack.  Need to get on the road soon. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       A week passed now.  Odd about life and time.  Sometimes so slow, somtimes so fast.  Sometimes both at the same time. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It is strange as more time passes, I wonder if I knew him at all.  Odd.  I really thoroughly trusted him.  I wonder.  It begins to seem like I will never know.  I will shortly leave here and lose my email, etc.  But, life continues.  And there are people that love me.  I will survive.  I will never have intimacy, but that is OK too. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Of course, now that it is just me I am not sure what to say.  I am tired.  And sad.  No, not really sad.  It is not something about being sad.  It is more about being disillusioned.  And while in the past I might have fallen down the rabbit hole of why am I unworthy or what did I do wrong or why did I misjudge him and his emotions.  That is not how I feel.  I know that I am worthy.  Few people, if any, could love him more or accept the reality of him as freely.  And I was just me.  And he never took the time to know me or my reactions.  How can I feel rejected personally when he never understood how I felt?  He did not take the time to know me personally.   And I was thoughtful and tried to be open about what he was feeling.  I asked questions, forced some discussion.  I guess that what I am saying is that bottom-line...I tried.  I gave it my heart.  I gave it my mind.   And very nearly my soul.  And that is OK.  It was my choice, explicitly considered.  He was not what or who I thought.  And the thing that lingers is wondering why I did not see him more clearly.  Surely there were things that I did see.  And benefits of the doubt granted at nearly every turn.  But, I really never thought that Terri meant more to him than I did...but she does.   As does his mom.   And the cats.   And Anil.  In the end, I really meant almost nothing.  I think that The Line meant more.  And there was such manipulation.  I always have said that if I could not proceed with the assumption that everything was well-meant.  If I could not be accepting and open about relationships, then I would not have them.  And I wonder if I should change or stop.  I mean, I never seem to be what anyone wants in a relationship.  Not a love relationship.  Friendship is fine and good and easy.  Love another kettle of fish completely.  And while my relationships have not been "bad"...I can honestly say that my life has been the poorer since I let that aspect of life into my existence.  Sex seems to me to be a thing of fleeting pleasure and enduring pain.  Pain might be too strong, perhaps loss.  Stephen commented yesterday that I was nicer to him than he deserved.  It surprised me.  I am not nice with any effort.  I am just me.  And he is easy to be nice to really.  Not an effort.  I wonder if it was an effort at some point.  And while I do not want to really see him daily or engage him daily, since he is tethered to other people, his family.  I love him and always will.  And since I know that he loves me and sees me as a truly special woman, then loving him and interacting "nicely" is no effort.  I am not sure where I was going there.  Perhaps one reflection is that I can see how his life is better for knowing me.  I am surely one reason that he knows his kids, remains with his family.  Is capable of loving another.  Has much higher self-esteem.  Knows what it is to be loved.  I know that too, for I know that he loves me.  But I wonder if that makes me stronger.  I am not sure.  I remember days that I regretted knowing what it meant to be loved.  Since it also meant understanding about loss.  Loss is an issue.  Though sometimes I wonder if you ever really have.  So, is loss just the death of illusions.  Why mourn something that never was? 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       OK, converted to just me here.  Made the book blog for Barb and Chris.  And the Ex-Celanese blog. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Weird, tomorrow the last full day at Celanese.  14 years.  Amazing.  Then 2 more nights and gone from Corpus Christi.    Amazing. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Beautiful Disaster : "to be the first in someones life to set the sun and raise the moon in someone else's eyes to see heaven just for a day to hold a moment in your arms and never let it slip away to leap off a mountain top  and feel the rush of love to taste that holy kiss i could never get enough of this rush  to touch the earth before you fall to know that here and now with you remains forever after all to feel the beauty in this maze to finally know that all our questions make perfect sense to break the surface and breathe the air  and feel the rush of love to taste that holy kiss i could never get enough of this rush  to be the first, in someones life, to set the sun and raise the moon, in some else's eyes...." 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink ..oO0 Eternal Thought 0Oo.. : "knowledge was the wisdom given: an answer I already knew -- Acceptance being the only key to remaining friends with you --" 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It is odd.  I used to like writing in this.  It was relaxing...a good time to just sort out how I felt.  And the notion that maybe it might entertain or help someone else was good.  But, now I just wonder if he is reading it and find it constrained.  Then I consider making a new one, but that seems like letting him win. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Results... : "'How Old is Your Inner Child?' - Results:  My inner child is sixteen years old!  Life's not fair! It's never been fair, but while adults might just accept that, I know something's gotta change. And it's gonna change, just as soon as I become an adult and get some power of my own." 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Off to pack.  I need to get this stuff sorted and in boxes.  ASAP!  Time is flying, hard to think that in a couple weeks I will be living in a new city, new job. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       YAWN.  YAWN.  YAWN.  Throat still sore, off to the doctor for a shot.  Then the plant. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ugh.  Awake with sore throat.   Tired.  Off to bed. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Museum was wonderful.  Dinner great...coconut ice cream was outrageous.  We went to a South American place.  Got back to town at midnight, Byron stayed until like 2 AM.  I think that everything will be OK. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Waiting to get on the road to Houston for the art show...Byron overslept. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       now here we go again you say you want your freedom well who am I to keep you down it's only right that you should play the way you feel it but listen carefully to the sound of your loneliness like a heartbeat...drives you mad in the stillness of remembering what you had and what you lost and what you had and what you lost  (chorus) thunder only happens when it's raining players only love you when they're playing women, they will come and they will go when the rain washes you clean you'll know  now here I go again I see the crystal visions I keep my visions to myself it's only me who wants to wrap around your dreams and have you any dreams you'd like to sell? dreams of loneliness like a heartbeat...drives you mad in the stillness of remembering what you had and what you lost and what you had and what you lost  (chorus, repeat to fade)  - the corrs, "dreams"  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       She smiled at him.  And then it arose and struck Vimes that, in her own special category, she was quite beautiful; this was the category of all the women, in his entire life, who had ever thought he was worth smiling at.  -Terry Pratchett, Guards! Guards! 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Tired. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink a walk to remember... : "you cannot lose what you never had" 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Patrick and Teresa Nielsen Hayden :   Inscrutable  A man, a plan, a caret, a ban, a myriad, a sum, a lac, a liar, a hoop, a pint, a catalpa, a gas, an oil, a bird, a yell, a vat, a caw, a pax, a wag, a tax, a nay, a ram, a cap, a yam, a gay, a tsar, a wall, a car, a luger, a ward, a bin, a woman, a vassal, a wolf, a tuna, a nit, a pall, a fret, a watt, a bay, a daub, a tan, a cab, a datum, a gall, a hat, a fag, a zap, a say, a jaw, a lay, a wet, a gallop, a tug, a trot, a trap, a tram, a torr, a caper, a top, a tonk, a toll, a ball, a fair, a sax, a minim, a tenor, a bass, a passer, a capital, a rut, an amen, a ted, a cabal, a tang, a sun, an ass, a maw, a sag, a jam, a dam, a sub, a salt, an axon, a sail, an ad, a wadi, a radian, a room, a rood, a rip, a tad, a pariah, a revel, a reel, a reed, a pool, a plug, a pin, a peek, a parabola, a dog, a pat, a cud, a nu, a fan, a pal, a rum, a nod, an eta, a lag, an eel, a batik, a mug, a mot, a nap, a maxim, a mood, a leek, a grub, a gob, a gel, a drab, a citadel, a total, a cedar, a tap, a gag, a rat, a manor, a bar, a gal, a cola, a pap, a yaw, a tab, a raj, a gab, a nag, a pagan, a bag, a jar, a bat, a way, a papa, a local, a gar, a baron, a mat, a rag, a gap, a tar, a decal, a tot, a led, a tic, a bard, a leg, a bog, a burg, a keel, a doom, a mix, a map, an atom, a gum, a kit, a baleen, a gala, a ten, a don, a mural, a pan, a faun, a ducat, a pagoda, a lob, a rap, a keep, a nip, a gulp, a loop, a deer, a leer, a lever, a hair, a pad, a tapir, a door, a moor, an aid, a raid, a wad, an alias, an ox, an atlas, a bus, a madam, a jag, a saw, a mass, an anus, a gnat, a lab, a cadet, an em, a natural, a tip, a caress, a pass, a baronet, a minimax, a sari, a fall, a ballot, a knot, a pot, a rep, a carrot, a mart, a part, a tort, a gut, a poll, a gateway, a law, a jay, a sap, a zag, a fat, a hall, a gamut, a dab, a can, a tabu, a day, a batt, a waterfall, a patina, a nut, a flow, a lass, a van, a mow, a nib, a draw, a regular, a call, a war, a stay, a gam, a yap, a cam, a ray, an ax, a tag, a wax, a paw, a cat, a valley, a drib, a lion, a saga, a plat, a catnip, a pooh, a rail, a calamus, a dairyman, a bater, a canal. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Hours of Folly : "My apartment is now a home. My new checks arrived, so that's one thing. And I've just thrown out the last of my emptied boxes. Three months. I'm home.  I'm in my back room (foyer? utility room? it's home, but I have not assigned this room a function) with my box cutter. A coin falls out of one box as I flatten it, a penny, dark brown with age. That's an old wheat penny, I think. Sure enough: 1952, wheat. It's good luck. A wheat penny I didn't know I had has followed me to my new place. I'm home." 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink celebrate life. : "I HOPE U DANCE  I hope you never lose your sense of wonder You get your fill to eat But always keep that hunger May you never take one single breath for granted God forbid love ever leave you empty handed I hope you still feel small When you stand by the ocean Whenever one door closes, I hope one more opens Promise me you'll give fate a fighting chance  And when you get the choice to sit it out or dance I hope you dance I hope you dance  I hope you never fear those mountains in the distance Never settle for the path of least resistance Living might mean taking chances But they're worth taking Lovin' might be a mistake But it's worth making Don't let some hell bent heart Leave you bitter When you come close to selling out Reconsider Give the heavens above More than just a passing glance  And when you get the choice to sit it out or dance I hope you dance (Time is a wheel in constant motion always) I hope you dance (Rolling us along) I hope you dance (Tell me who) I hope you dance (Wants to look back on their years and wonder) (Where those years have gone)  I hope you still feel small When you stand by the ocean Whenever one door closes, I hope one more opens Promise me you'll give faith a fighting chance  And when you get the choice to sit it out or dance Dance I hope you dance I hope you dance (Time is a wheel in constant motion always) I hope you dance (Rolling us along) I hope you dance (Tell me who) (Wants to look back on their years and wonder) I hope you dance (Where those years have gone)  (Tell me who) I hope you dance (Wants to look back on their years and wonder) (Where those years have gone)" 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Siren's Song : "Terra Incognizant by Prometheus  You would think by now, I would know my way around, I shouldn't miss you so badly, I should be on familiar ground. How many more lonely years, must meander by, until I learn the lesson, it does no good to cry. What manner of iron will, must some people possess, to be always looking forward, to never accept regress. Perhaps if I was willing, to let someone take me by the hand, they could show me a happy place, in this unfamiliar land. Perhaps I'm only homesick, for all the joys that once were mine, I must accept that they and you, belong to another place and time. But I know that deep within my heart, there's a place where only you reside, and when the pain of loneliness comes, it knows that is where I hide. So if sometimes it seems to you, I'm clinging to the past, it's mostly because I can't yet accept, that our love didn't last. No matter how hard I try, I've yet to get over you, for the part of me that's still alive, believes you love me too. Maybe there will come a day, when that part will finally die, and feeling strong with a heart reborn, a new love I will finally try. And what a splendid day that will be, when I awaken to discover, I'm happily learning a great new land, with a great new friend and lover. " 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Siren's Song : "Murder  Ignorance is bliss Cursed is your kiss So many times been burnt Lesson still unlearnt  Hearken to my pleas Remember me at least A girl whose heart you killed Her love forever sealed" 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Siren's Song : "Blessed are bimbos who don't have to think, and brush away unhappiness with a simple goofy smile. " 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Email from Stephen today.  He was at a wedding at the University Park Hotel by MIT over the weekend.  Was nostalgic and was walking down the hall of old framed MIT photos in the hotel.  Came across one of me at graduation.  Said "It almost made me cry… but it was lovely to see. Quite surprising to say the least. "  Made me smile.  I wonder what photo it is. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hmm, maybe he died. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Is is Worth Running in the Rain?  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Jarretts Blog : "'Women have dicks, they are just in negative inches.'" 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Fortune.com - Technology - Joy After Sun :    
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Youch.  Morphine?  Hoping to be able to crawl to the hospital in the morning.  Back to bed now. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink     What's Your Outlook on Life?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Oh, good...now Mir has a hot nose and is laying about not moving.  NOT! 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink And now, jose?    SOZINHO  by Peninha  Sometimes, after night falls i lay there, thinking of us dreaming awake, trying to piece together the before, the now and the afterwards why do you leave me so alone? why do you let me so free? i'm feeling very lonely.  I'm not - nor do i want to be - the owner of you it's just that i need a little affection. I have my secrets - and secret plans - i would open them up only to you. how can you not be here? and what if i get interested in someone else? and what if he, suddenly, wins me over?  When you love you take care. you tell me you love me but it's all lip service unless you are fooling me and you are just plain immature. where are you now?  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Was considering calling him to make sure he was alive.  Figuring a likely time that he would be out, just checking for voicemail.  But, what is the point?  The thing that is hard is that I figured that one way that it would all swing was that I was just a woman to him.  And that there was a pattern of attitude and behavior that said that he thought women were just a mm above worthless.  And worth only sex and I knew that I was not going to be worth that to him, so I would, if only a woman, be worthless to him and that he would walk, like he has.  And what others say of him and what I found there certianly suggest that all of that is true.  And, so I struggle to find ways for it not to be.  I thought that maybe I was worth more than that, that I was not a woman to him, but a friend.  So, to think that I invested years, tens of thousands of dollars,  and all of the other discarded choices in my faith in him is just kind of stunning.  I had thought that over time my relationships were getting better, more intelligent, stronger emotionally.  But, this moment is the worst ever.  I really can conceive of no way for him to be gone and to have ever cared at all.  The two just do not compute for me.  I do not understand.  If I am supposed to learn to never trust, never be open, never want to tether my life to another, then OK, I do not need to understand.  The why and how does not really matter.  I wish that I felt a little more certain about what next steps to take in my life.  Tomorrow is the big decision day.    I suppose that living in a big city has its advantages.  Opportunity to be nameless and faceless.  I could spend the time to rest and get stronger.  I could return to swimming and meditation.  Find book groups and meditation groups and perhaps a religious group that might not weekly annoy me.  Find something to volunteer to eventually.  And maybe find the time and place to see friends once a year.  It would be a different life, but one that might over time allow me to be stronger.  The question become just one of can I do it at all.  I think that I will wait until I am gone, then call.  If by then I still want to know that he is OK. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       YAWN.  Waiting for water to boil now.  Having fake pasta for dinner.   
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yawn, waiting for them to come pick up the couch.  It will be nice to start over with something new there.  It still seems to remind me of Os.  In good ways mainly, but a new start is in order. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink iWon - Horoscopes : " You need a reality check. Something that seemed like a good idea on paper just doesn't work when the rubber meets the road. You thought this would be a vehicle for your genius, but if you keep pushing it, you'll just have another lemon on your hands. Sit down with a friendly cup of coffee and reconsider the path that leads to your ideal future. You thought you knew what lay beyond the barriers, but now you're beginning to see that it's the wrong time to leap without looking. Peek around the edges before your feet leave the ground." 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hmm, OK.  Did a medical day.  Shot.  Mammogram.  PAP smear.  Pelvic.  Now they want to do an ultrasound on Monday to take a look at the tumor.  Oh, joy. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       YAWN 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Perhaps Wal-Mart is safe from me.  I might not have to greet there afterall. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yawn, another new day.  Off to get my shot and go off to the salt mines.  I wonder if salt miners had high blood pressure? 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       OK, last night of vacation.  New work on the morrow.  Eek. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Safe in Houston.  Mir is roaming. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       39 today, imagine that. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ditto. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Long time since I wrote.  Nothing much to say.  Work is OK.  Settled.  Mir is OK. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ugh, tired of being sick.  Just really ill the last 2-3 weeks.  Need to sort out insurance and go see someone. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       BOOK CHAPTER SENT TO EDITOR. YAYA! 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Alive. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Double yawn. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yawn. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well Kamir likes Baton Rouge...or hotel living...or being with me after three weeks apart. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well Kamir likes Baton Rouge...or hotel living...or being with me after three weeks apart. 
    
    
</post>



</Blog>