<Blog>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      You know what? I’ve begun another alternative set of lyrics for Testosterone (which fits the original title) and reads and sounds much better. Consider my last post a poem of sort; albeit a politically nothing-new statement…It’s good to make mistakes.  I was going to post some big kind of topic - but I can’t be bothered really. I’ll try and condense 2 tried and tested big questions in my own easily imitable way..   Nationality  Morrissey’s recent single  Irish Blood, English Heart  brought comfort to the question of nationality. I have variously on-occasion (not enough to beat myself up; I don’t really care for what I tag myself - I’m only really just a human on Earth like everyone else after all) wondered if I was ‘English’. I never ever had a problem with being ‘British/British Asian’, which is bizarre as both words are truly interchangeable. In terms of locality I am easily Londoner. I used to think, for some reason, that English meant: white and atleast middle class - not even just white alone. The word sounded like a definitive tag. But then Morrissey, who is of Irish heritage is no different to me. Yes his pigment is the same as my preconceived notion of English, but inherently he was born and raised here - to immigrant parents. We live in a land of mongrels - and I don’t say that in a derogatory sense - as England is one of the most well off places for it , as it’s better that than to be inbred - both socially, physically, and even psychologically. Everything I like is not singly one culture - thank you transport and media! I realise that yes, I have South Asian blood; perhaps my home is a kind of internal little district of Asian and Englishness, but beyond any preconceived notion, I am only, simply English. I don’t even speak Urdu (apart from few phrases), I haven’t been to the South East. And if I did, I would be an alien visitor who just happened to be the common colour. Even if I like it or not I am English. And I like it actually. If I’m not English, then backward fascists will hijack the term like they did the flag. Therefore I HAVE to be English.  …So much for writing condensed.   Religion vs. Science  This is always a touchy subject. But I’m alright as I’m right in the middle - I have admiration for religion (atleast my minutely acquired slant on un-distorted Islam) and the common sense to not laugh at science. The debate of religion vs. science is principally heart (science) vs. soul (religion); it will never be, atleast for the foreseeable future be solved, unlike my nationality debate. The big brains of the world still scratch their heads at this. My point here is quite hazy in that I just want both science heads and religious heads to get along. Both should not shove themselves down each others throat. I believe that if there is any current ‘solution’ it’s that science and religion just have to exist together. Religious belief (note that humble good religious followers emphasise belief rather than doubting non-believers) is no different a word to scientific theory. Religious facts also on the other hand have been verified by science. Any erroneous stuff so far, to my knowledge is to do with Christianity. Islam for instance doesn’t back up the claim of there being a ’son of god’, only a messenger of religion. Islam also encourages science and has provided foundations for science that many scientists have warmed too; in which case there is no versus. The Koran supports hypothesis in that it's a book that doesn't consider itself infallible.  You can’t really say religion is all hogwash yet. If it was, it would be easily disproved a long time ago. And why do all religious books reference each other despite being written in very different languages, in different times and places, and before transportation?  But say, religion was hogwash? To some religion would still be a liberating lie. A lazy answer to complex questions. A construction of the mind in which to find solace, or fear depending on your view of religion. I’ll tell you though, if there is a God/system of creation it can’t be interventionist or it would have intervened by now. I’d like to think that in the future science and religion merge to unearth everything. Maybe that’s a bit of romantic twaddle, but that’s my romantic twaddle.  Religion cant prove itself, science can’t disprove it - so if you believe or not, what does it matter? Nobody knows, they just follow their minds. And you won’t go to hell or meet infinite virgins for your decision; that’s common sense. You live life the way you know; judge not lest ye be judged yourself, eh? Law's a religion most of us all follow though!  How do you prove God/creation? Maybe the mind (a tool for science for sure) is a tool to eventuality, or maybe it’s a tool to rally against being a dreamer. Who the hell knows? Who knows anything? Believe what you want and respect each other. Live life how it’s best for you - and others.  …What a piece from an unreligious person eh? I’m off for some tea now - how English (though, Indopak actually… =))!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Diary of a suicide bomber  (aka Testosterone)  *Not finalised   M. Aziz   If there’s no heaven, ‘least I dent hell here If there’s no heaven, ‘least I make it clear; bypass fear If there can’t be peace, my land I can’t seize If there can’t be peace then I’ll make it ease, mass decease  No more sound of guns, no more sight of blood No more smell of fires as I become funeral pyre   Blood will soak your streets Rubble greet your feet We take no defeat; no retreat Watch your people die Like/As when I watched mine Friends and families cry Then it starts again   If there’s no heaven, ‘least I dent hell here If there’s no heaven, ‘least I make it clear If there can’t be peace, my land I can’t seize If there can’t be peace then I’ll make it ease  America has made you blind America has made you hate America will steal and silence those all detriment to itself, and its interests America is deaf to its people America will kill itself  America sells you lies in a glossy package to gorge it on your trusting selves  Redemption!  In prolonging war I shall set the score In prolonging war I will tally up; strap me up I don’t wish to fight, but you have no right I don’t wish to fight, but if might is right, right is might  What’s the point in truce? When trust will be abused? Those few who care for truth Know that we have been subdued
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
         I've got a cool few posts to make before this month's over, and this is one of them! Anyway, where do I begin?  Well, I went to Windsor to spend a little more time with Loz again and we went to  urlLink Legoland ! It was a fun and exhilirating place, as only we'd know. And we weren't the only non-kiddies there, infact there were more adults! I always wanted to go to Legoland as a kid (when Denmark was the only one), so it seems like I've met my dream; passed by nostalgia - particularly as Harry Potter Lego sets are the rifest thing now.  urlLink Right click here for a .zip of 26 640x480 jpegs I took there.   I'm still recovering from the fun a bit, so forgive me if I omit anything. Windsor's a nice place; I'm not really regal-interested at all, but I appreciate the area and it's design a lot now. We ate at  urlLink Bella Italia  which was so gorgeous that it killed us. Also a few cafes played up to our European dining fantasies..And then there was lethargy and slow time kill at Heathrow yesterday!  In between was cosy and personal fun - a great alternative to the yawny Glastonbury weekend.  Coccyx  is also the keyword in a little tale - I overheard a couple that were probably shagging in public (and dealt with by the law) outside the hotel at night (The Christopher/Best Western) and the woman's keyword was "my coccyx hurts" - over and over. This was not us, I assure you - particularly as the woman made no other sounds..Strange indeed.  Also, I've probably completed lyrics for Testos' to share soon, got a rant I've nearly finished, and there's a new BBC writing comp - about travelling, would you believe! My first month of blogging's great. I like this public diary; even if it's attraction is severely limited.  I can't wait to see Loz again though. I think it won't be long before I/we devise another plan! The past fortnight has been the most fun for me yet! And I want more damnit, more!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      No, not a tenner! Not even...a million...A fairly respectable £100 on Thunderball. It's something eh?  It's 22 past midnight and I must go to bed soon, but I feel inclined to post as again it will certainly be the last time for a few days: Legoland Windsor awaits! I've not been to a theme park since I was around 12ish; around half my life ago. I will report on it, and hopefully have pics.  I was very knackered earlier; a cold and slightly wet day was spent at Dave's which was recappingly productive and fun. He got his new amp today - finally after ages - he has now graduated to Marshall owning status! I kind of sang today too..  I'm finding that consoling gifts are reaching people around me, who need them, which I'm thankful of lately; they offer redemption for any degree of darkness that might have engulfed them. I, myself am very happy at the moment and have been for quite a bit now! Only nostalgia has plagued me minorly...Lego was a toy of my youth, a big one, and then I remember the series of computers/consoles I've had since I was 8. My life has always had computers.   I'm old, in a young sort of way, in a couple of months, 25 years of my life will have been marked. My only 'fear' is that it will go on aimless like most people; I don't want that.  Anyway, enough mopey rubbish - I'm off to bed.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Theme For Great Cities by Simple Minds Keep It Down by Kelis Ch-Check It Out by Beastie Boys I Like You by Morrissey   I have to self-impose a deadline for myself for tonight if I'm to complete (atleast mostly) a set of lyrics for 'Testosterone' performance tomorrow. I do have a title and some words; but I've already released half-finished music so I'll keep the courtesy to not show half finished words.  Nothing much to say. Chilling out day. I'm sure I'll post something cool before I disappear for a few days again.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
         I hope it's not illegal to scan and show boarding passes online? In my defence I don't know and have no bad intentions. It's just that again I didn't make use of my camera, so this is the only image I can share.  It was a good fun few days though. Baking heat turned to pelting rain and cold. I spent most of my time just enjoying the company of Loz, as opposed to spending 'days out' and it was good. I got to know her gran a bit more, played with cats as if I was cat myself, without getting bad attention from the dog. And Loz does a good job as a domestic wifey...Not that I plan to impose any chauvinism in the future!  No time for tears or reminiscing though, or any other bull that happens, as I see her again on Thursday! This is cheesy to say, but I'm uncertain how we ever managed to not be with eachother. If God created Mo in September '79, then surely Loz in Feb '80 (6 months-ish later!) was surely meant as the pairing; geography was a bit irritating in our favour though, but we're closer than some pairings, perhaps an owe to parental immigration on my side.  Current movie/music faves: Kelis' 'Tasty', Morrissey's 'You Are The Quarry', Simple Minds' 'The Best Of...' and The Birdcage. Of course all these things are thanks to a certain nice Irish lass.  Rambling will continue again until the fun starts up again, and then who knows when I pop over to Dublin again...Maybe I'll never really 'maintain' this site!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I saw a very, very funny and bizarre South Park episode last night, involving Radiohead; but that’s not today’s subject!  I see that recently there’s been a bit of a kick and scream about an Islamic girl losing the right to wear an extended length gown…Good!  Wha? I hear you say, but you’re Muslim (albeit only by name), you should stand up for it. Firstly, though I haven’t read The Koran, I do know that the stereotypical Islamic female is a bunch of bull.  No woman in my family tree has ever worn any burkha, hijab or anything antiquated like that: because it’s just *not* necessary. The basics of Islamic dress code (which is being played by a lot of educated, unforced Muslim women) is no different to ‘normal’ subtle dress code, that a woman doesn’t dress up like a tart basically. And who’d argue with it? It’s public decency; what’s done indoors is nobody’s business.  Infact men should even be covering up ‘more’ - but do they? No. It is true that a number of women do wear Islamic dress out of want or solidarity, nothing wrong with that - it’s like being part of a club - but it’s backward men that want to oppress them - but bare in mind that it’s not solely Islamic men who can be oppressive; infact women’s rights as defined in the Koran were long defined atleast before the west even acknowledged them. Troubles with Islam are not so much to do with religion as opposed to interpretation and media distortion; but that’s a whole other debate.  Now, seeing as Islamic dress is not necessary, and we live in a secular nation where we must all compromise a bit for unity to work - to not give fuel to fascists who are looking for things to nit pick - why put up a fuss?  This is a wholly removed example, but say for instance vintage punks, who you’d see wearing leather studded jackets - they wear that stuff because of solidarity with others; but in a school environment those studs can be dangerous and they’re banned. Yeah! So an extended Islamic gown (and remember the case is not stating other dress items), which is detrimental to health and safety, should also be banned, yes! It is not necessary!  In regards to other religions, such as Sikhism - even turbans are replaced with the smaller material ones for children. Granted for some Sikhs (not Mona Sikhs - I.e. ones that don’t wear turbans - which is becoming popular). Sikhs are also required to carry a sword; but you’d damn well not want to see a sword in school.  Islamic female dress, unless wantonly chosen, is a very antiquated style of dress. It is of no relevance in the modern society and can be detrimental to genuine female expression. Other reasons against extreme things like the burkha is that with the hiding of identities, these women have more reason to indulge in ‘wrong’ activities as they can’t be singled out. Islamic female dress is used as a deterrent to devious male eyes. But like my fair lass Loz said, men should be taught manners - and it’s true. But at the same time, women should dress with taste in public (and not extremely of course), because if they look like slappers then why should they be surprised if some men pick on them? Dress King’s Cross, expect King’s Cross.  And as for the girl in the case, she really should grow up. Maybe she likes the gown but if it’s not necessary it’s not. Atleast it appears she’s not in a school that enforces uniform, so she’s free enough.  Anyway, I’m off now to Dublin for a few days; so this rant is the last from me for a bit. I’ll return with less confrontational tales! Take care of yourselves…And each other! =D
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      It's nice to be able to write with a non spit-marked TFT screen (thanks to some long sought after computer wipes in Queensway - a trip that involved witnessing a van with a man singing to a happy tune, with bubbles coming out of his exhaust - I don't do drugs!)  I quite like the new single 'Trick Me' by  urlLink Kelis . Infact I liked her last one. I detested her "hate you right now, argh" beginnings, but I wonder should I invest in her 'Tasty' LP?  I had a few things to say as I approached writing this, but, uh, they're slipping away. Couldn't be arsed yesterday.  Dave and I tried to force a 'big phone debate' last night, but it didn't work. It sucks when we agree; there's no heat on things.  Half Life 2 & Doom 3 PC games are out in September! I know what I want for my silver anniversary of living!!! The pre-versions of both games were titles I loved in my teens. Man, development took a long time.  Valve sounds like a good name for something. I dunno how it entered my head, but I'll see what I can do with it. Lazy at the mo. and with going to Dublin soon I have no impetus to do anything proper 'til then or after; even then I'm going Legoland after.  I will waffle a bit on something that I find funny that Dave and I could've expanded on: self-racism (in specific purely colour than stereotype based).  A number of white (or those particularly who like to call themselves 'sickly pale') often want to be darker, and a number of black people want to be lighter (see how many black musicians in videos these days look lightened - or perhaps thats an issue to do with video makers etc.), and those with a skin tone inbetween sometimes pander to either side too and I find it funny. Because: a) 'sickly pale' which as a naturally tan coloured person to me is just a nice cooling white, is way way more attractive than skin cancer Oxo colour or Kat Slater orange. Honestly. b) 'sickly black' is what I'd describe the washed-out appearance on severely made-up black persons (exc. Michael Jackson who has reached an alien see-thru grey). An off coffee looking shade leaves them neither white or tanned. c) 'sickly asian' is Asians of all types (Indians/Japanese etc.) who insist on dying their hair blonde for instance. DON'T! You look horribly wrong and diseased; it's hard to know where your skin/hair begins. And then more funky bright colours don't help either. And then there's the Ali G image *shiver*  My point being is, that modifications are good because they pepper you to individuality. But there are some real no-no's that occur because of dissatisfaction with the self-tone. Black, white or tan, the chances are you look brilliant as you already are. Don't ruin it!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      My my, Labour have been thrashed. Or should it it be  Tony Blair  got thrashed. It was coming, but damn was it more than expected. Don't blame me, I goddamn voted 'em once still..But Labour will bounce back, once Blair's bounced off. I'm going yellow for the general election anyhow.  I'm glad Ken's mayor again; he's alright - but I won't vote him again if I don't 'see' results develop this time.  Lazy and sleepy now. Mustn't stay up past 3am.  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Right, well, I've just been to the polling station so now all I have to do is wait and see if people agree with me, and if they disagree I hope they've made a better choice. I'll explain my voting - which changed considerably from my original plans a week ago:   London Mayor   1st choice: Steve Norris (Conservative)  Ooh...I've never ever voted Conservative before! I did today because a) somehow I never got to vote for mayor last year; my card never showed up! and b) because I've been give 2 choices so I'm allowed to be risky. It's clear that the mayor choice is *only* between the big 3, and though Lib Dem's Simon Hughes could also demonstrate protest against the Livingston/Labour marriage; I find he talks well (like a boxer before a fight) but is pretty vague and too promising on things (rings a bell?...). Norris outlines key areas which I agree with, and perhaps having him tilt Livingstone is natural after losing the last time. This is the 'mayor' we're talking about after all, of just my city, not a full blown Cons assault.  2nd choice: Ken Livingstone (Labour)  Don't say 'what the?' The reason why I don't mind Ken is because my mum's met him twice; once a few years ago and once during the GLC days...But no seriously: He hasn't done that bad a job; it's mainly motorists who dislike him.  Granted public transport's still pretty rubbish etc. But this London Mayor thing is new. He's probably not entirely sure about his role and power extent, and same with the public. Since he's already started the ball rolling, give him some more time to finish it. It may be detrimental to just hand it to someone else mid-way, but to backup no. 1; if it's to be handed to Labour-free blood then a strong party candidate like Norris is the only choice. Lib Dems...I will vote for you when it counts - the big one!   Local & London Assembly   Local: Labour  Yes, Tony and his cronies are crumbling and dwindling and deserve it, but Tony will probably soon be going anyway, and lest we remember the Labour party are still a better choice than the still pseudo-Thatcherite government and the underdeveloped Lib Dems. Yes Labour plunged us into war, but not *all* of Labour were for it; same as the other parties. Tony's irresponsibility was the main problem.   London: Respect  Okay, let's ease off Labour loving. We need a buffer to them, and as is this isn't a general election I will 'throw away' a vote to protest, to George Galloway. If Labour/Cons, even Lib Dem are there I want people with a stance to glare back at them. Fringe party, yes. But if I'm to protest then they're a good one.   European Parliament   Respect  Oh no, George Galloway loving aswell as Labour! I admit I don't know much about this category (but I have been reading a lot - very bizarrely for me - on the categories and the promises) but we need some people with heart and morals probably vacating these seats than tried and tested 'standard' politicians.  ...Of course these are  my  opinions; they maybe full of sh*t - and the rest of the public has the chance to prove so. Tonight we'll find out what happens. I stick by my choices.  On a happy-ish note, after voting and going to Tesco (where I got irritated in the que; long insignificant story...and this post's long enough) a man, probably homeless and/or down, upset in someway, said "It's my birthday, can you spare me some change please?...No worries brother...I'm 40 today...Do I look 40?...30ish? Early, mid or late?...Cheers, it's good to know I look young still. Bye!" This guy was clearly not a tramp; perhaps pissed but I don't want to assume; a fun little chat.   urlLink ...And here's some recently found jpeg images from 2001 in a 1.74mb .zip file  There's pictures of me (I look way different; I've changed in the last few years again people say, and now I know!), Dave and other misc things bla bla bla.  I've blabbed a lot, maybe I'll not post tommorrow. No reason to post everyday is there! Off for tea.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      A sign of musical dedication, or perhaps a disregard for approach, coupled with enthusiasm, leads to injuries in rock...My thumbs are blistered because of drum playing in this heat adding to normal stick friction...I'll survive.  It was worth it as the majority music portion of a thrash thing I wrote (see Testosterone, June 5) has now been indented in Dave's brain.  Tommorrow I vote. I'll tell you who I choose then as I'm still not sure now; I've no reason to hide my choice. I'm making the effort so as to quash any BNP victory, no matter how miniscule.  Not taken my new medication yet...I found some old pics I'd like to share; maybe tommorrow, and Saz sent a funny 1mb video - I'll put that up too maybe.  Saz (Sarah) is someone from my  urlLink secondary/6th form  days. I actually only met her 1/2 times in school; never after, but she's become a bearer of cheery stuff into my email box. If I ever met her again in 'real' life, it'd probably be like The Matrix falling apart or something.  ...Yeah, it's late!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I'm here so I didn't have any problems with setting broadband up - infact it was perhaps smoother than I thought it would be. Now I can enjoy a non-sluggish internet and neither engage the phone line! If you're gonna get broadband yourself: shop around. The ones with the best marketing may not be the best in service or price, so investigate all your options (price - in terms of years and setup, and your hardware kit) and you won't regret it.  I went to the doc today and I got Lansoprazole. Yet another strong antacid; I've had enough with my GP about this. Fortunately my near 5 month long trouble has slightly got better and not worse, so I leave it to time.  Off to Dave's tommorrow to do some rawking...I have absolutely no game plan over what we're doing tommorrow, but it'll be fun anyway. Perhaps not the part where I have to lug my portable electronic drumkit in possibly more sweltering heat.  Also I'm thinking of entering the last currently enterable BBC competition. I'll post my entry here when/if I do it.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Windsor 1-3 May '04 (11 640x480 .jpeg's in a .zip file: 768kb)   I'd have put these pictures up individually, nicely linked by thumbnails, but I just can't be arsed today. These 11 pictures were taken on my ageing 1.5 megapixel camera (still great though) on recent-ish exploits around the area, and in Slough, with my bird Loz (Laura). We're off to  urlLink Legoland Windsor  this month too funnily enough, and I'm off for a few days to Dublin next Wednesday; woo-hoo!  Streamlinenet are okay actually. I doubt I'll get my 2nd year refunded, but atleast I've had no problems today (they still insist 99.9% uptime) and I have a cool sounding domain name - and the price was filthy cheap to allow the odd boo-boo. I will however remain wary about my custom with any hosting co. in future though!  I have to install my broadband modem tonight (an internal one, so I'll be performing minor PC surgery), it seems bewildering almost but I'm sure I'll be on to post again! I got a great deal in all the options I selected.  Seeing the doc tommorrow and 'tis nearly time to vote. Only the Respect party has bothered to write to me..
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink A Genuine Magic Trick (Petty Con)    urlLink Imitating Katherine Walker   *You'll need  urlLink Adobe Acrobat Reader  to view these files.  A few things to say today. Firstly, I wish I chose mo79.me.uk as my domain name; it was most logical and uniquely me. Secondly, I wish I never bought hosting from  urlLink Streamlinenet.  Yes it was mega cheap, but so is the service!  I'm gonna try and salvage my money and get out and go bigwig secure with  urlLink 1&1  who I know I can trust, and just get email. So yeah this blog may either end or become hosted locally on Blogger. i.e. no cool attachments to share. We'll see how it goes. I get broadband on Tuesday; I want things to be all smooth for my transition.  The above files are submissions to recent BBC competitions. The first one was related to the program called Hustle; under rules I had to devise my own unique con; and fortunately I had a recently existing con idea to use, so I thought why not! The second is part 2 of a story by Alexei Sayle.  urlLink 'End Of Story'  is a competition that gets writers to begin a story and comp entrants to finish it. Winners get recognition! I like these pieces and if I don't get anywhere, I don't. It was fun though. Below was my entry to a limerick competition which I have lost as the winners have been announced. Don't you just disagree with them?    The waiter at the Chinese revealed, with my bowl of rice That if I were to simply enter, I’d be sure to win a prize And so I found the BBC were running a competition Not one of stamina or of strength, but one of simple diction …Which was nice.    The idea was to write a comedic limerick about your favourite BBC comedy character. I chose Patrick Nice.  Okay, now I'm going to calm down and eat.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink 'Testosterone' [Work In Progress] (M. Aziz) - MP3 6.25mb (6:50)  *Unless you have a DSL connection I strongly suggest you right click and save.  I don't actually make a habit of sharing unfinished material but this seems a good way to open my site, and the stage the song is in sounds complete in it's own way, atleast to me..  I hope you enjoy this taster of Kanchi (the 2 piece unit I'm in with D. Power), should you download it, and I hope it entices you to hear more (finished) material in the near future.  ...That wasn't so hard to do now. I wonder how regular I'll be with posting here though?
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Whether it’s music or books (explicitly excluding films and games), the sleeve art often determines how I’ll approach an album/book, how I’ll experience it, and what I think of it in the long run. True a poor piece of art is a poor piece of art, no matter how you package it (though we’ll exclude that variable and say that a good sleeve is sometimes the saving grace of something rubbish).  I was listening to some  urlLink Rage Against The Machine  yesterday for example, their second album  Evil Empire . The cover art is a primarily fitting yellow; and the music in most cases has a sun-beaten, lazy, sweat glow to it. I don’t know if I’d have summed it up like that minus the art. Though I guess art sometimes is produced naturally for the music; artists have to do that and I commend that job.  Other great examples include the white clinical feel of  urlLink Radiohead ’s  OK Computer , the very novel film canister of  urlLink PiL ’s  Metal Box , and perhaps anything by  urlLink Anton Corbijn  (mostly  urlLink Depeche Mode ) and Peter Saville (famously Factory Records) - kings of evergreen hip. Books are the same; save for the ones jacketed in publishers uniforms, books like ones by Haruki Murakami come in stand-out bright and zany designs - just like his works.  Whether art is created in response to the music/books, or just matched from a selection later; I think it’s amazing how it’s put together. Visual aids to non-visual arts are a great bonus.  I read recently that Jude Law is going to play Ian Curtis in a(nother) new film about him. Manchester’s Joy Division was the band he started the late 70’s. Save for some extras, there was only 2 albums from this post-punk band and the troubled singer committed suicide in 1980. The death of the band gave birth to New Order who are still around today.  I don’t know Jude Law very well, but I can see why he might be a good choice visually. Joy Division/New Order made (and make) some great music.  Anyway, I’m hoping that as the new month draws in I’ll start posting my own works again; it’s been a while. But there have been some interesting muted developments still.  I see the dentist on Tuesday.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Firstly, I’ve opted for a  urlLink Radeon 9600XT  graphics card - the reason being that it’s a good price, it’s pretty powerful, it’s a refreshing change from an  urlLink Nvidia  card, and above all it will work on my system without me having to buy risky and expensive other things. I’m not hardcore or loony enough to consider anything else.  Worms 3D online and rocking are going great.  I read recently how a lot of young men are harming themselves these days, opposed to just women - something to do with the emotional disability of men compared to girls. This is actually quite worrying if it’s rising, and it is a global male problem.  A lot of young men (myself included) have an armoured exterior when it comes to dealing with problems; women do to, but in men it’s fuelled by stubborn macho-ness - which is ok unless you don’t know when to stop.  And in not talking about things, you either explode externally (violence towards others) or internally (self-harm). If you haven’t exploded yet you will. I think it’s important for guys and their male friends to learn to disable their fronts with each other sometimes, or else the current few generations of males are going to end up in mental asylums, prisons, or 6 feet under. I can honestly say that any problems I have faced or will, are quite well diffused in that I have an artistic outlet - not everybody has that. And having the opposite sex is a great, not only for fun…, but because these intelligent beings know how to pour us out and remodel us - to a degree. Women are a bit bizarre too…   “The male chromosome is an incomplete female chromosome. In other words the male is a walking abortion; aborted at the gene stage. To be male is to be deficient, emotionally limited; maleness is a deficiency disease and males are emotional cripples.”  Valerie Solanos  Moving on briefly to a final ramble; the case about the father who killed his severely disabled young son. It’s sad - but evil and cruel are careful words to choose. The boy was going to deteriorate and eventually die anyway. For a normal (I assume) peaceful man, under tensions, to commit this act, shouldn’t be examined from a good man/bad man point of view. Yes, to take a life is wrong. But if you’re not ‘living’ is it wrong? Perhaps the boy wished to stay alive, or perhaps to die, we won’t know - he couldn’t communicate. If there’s only one life, is it better to live in pain than not live, or is non-existence better than no pain? - It’s a crazy headjam. I don’t this man killed his son in hatred. It’s possibly love that didn’t want to seem him alive. Life, death, love and hate merge in paradoxes; which is why need these things examined before we judge people. But, for the time being he is a criminal - that’s what the law states.  And to point out the obvious I don’t advocate the willy-nilly killing of people with disabilities (everyone should be encouraged to face adversity in a cruel world!). Terminal illnesses maybe. Probably yes. Better a controlled death if possible, than an ugly one.  Just thought of one more thing. Games and violence - one sentence: only severely disturbed individuals kill others because of what they play in games; these numb nuts feed off any catalyst. Dave and I play Worms 3D a lot; it doesn’t mean that we place dynamite sticks next to each other, or launching exploding sheep - though that would be cool.  I’ll end with a final piece of silliness forwarded from Saz; check  urlLink this link.  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Dave and I successfully played some wonderful W3D games online last night; shame that due to one unadressed issue he caught a tricky little virus.  A lesson has been learnt; and we hope that the virus&nbsp;can be removed. It's strange though how only his computer attracts these annoying things!   I gave my mum £50 today for her birthday this 1st Aug - no doubt she'll be glued intermittently to  urlLink QVC  throughout the coming days 'til she finds something!     
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I don’t think I’ve explicitly listed my top ten albums, films, books and games, so I guess here’s an opportunity (these are not in any specific order, and are just chosen off-hand)!:   Albums  Metallica - Master Of Puppets Metallica - Metallica Mogwai - Young Team Depeche Mode - Violator Public Image Limited - Metal Box U2 - Achtung Baby Radiohead - Hail To The Thief Smashing Pumpkins - Adore The Verve - A Storm In Heaven Linton Kwesi Johnson - Forces Of Victory   Films  Robocop The Terminator Pi What About Bob? Rain Man Sister Act (Roger Moore era Bond - as one choice) Finding Nemo A Clockwork Orange South Park - The Movie   Books  Number9dream by David Mitchell The Outsider by Albert Camus Mi Revalueshanary Fren by Linton Kwesi Johnson Veronika Decides To Die by Paulo Coelho The Wasp Factory by Iain Banks A Wild Sheep Chase by Haruki Murakami The Wind-Up Bird Chronicle by Haruki Murakami Norwegian Wood - by Haruki Murakami The Elephant Vanishes - by Haruki Murakami James And The Giant Peach - Roald Dahl   Games  Half Life (PC) Doom (PC) Max Payne (PC) Worms 3D (and Worms and Worms Armageddon) (PC) Super Mario Land 2 (Game Boy) Robocop (Amstrad CPC 464) Super Tennis (Sega Master System) Street Fighter II Deluxe Edition (Sega Mega Drive) Robocop vs. Terminator (Sega Mega Drive) Dragonninja (Arcade)  I also forgot to mention yesterday that I saw  Beavis &amp; Butt-head Do America  the night before. That film came out in ‘96 - it brought back me teen years in great clarity. I loved their stupidity.    I AM CORNHOLIO!! I WANT TP FOR MY BUNGHOLE! DO YOU HAVE TP? YOU WILL BOW TO ME!!  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      My tum's been a little worse for the last few days, but right now I feel I'm in control of it.   To divert attention, I'm thinking of getting a 128mb Radeon 9600XT card; it seems perfect for my system with a nice price tag - and it might come with Half Life 2 for free!  I hear the new Star Wars film is called 'Revenge Of The Sith'...I never cared for Star Wars, or even Star Trek for that matter. I much preffered earth bound sci-fi adventures, which explains my digging out of the Robocop DVD last night.  A hastily compiled half-demo has been prepared for probable listening by members of Slipknot, and plan b seems to be getting on the foreign property ladder.  I'm gonna go and attempt to write something now (exc. this) 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Dave and I tried to play  urlLink Worms 3D  earlier - unsuccesfully; but we will get there when we sort the simple issues out.  That game is our muse, so it's just a natural step that we try to play it from our own homebases.  It's a long time since I've embarked on online gaming, and even then I wasn't hardcore.&nbsp; I begun playing against strangers in the late 90's on games like Duke Nukem 3D ('97), and then I got involved in a small local (sixth form) group of friends indulding in Quake online ('99). Dave used to get killed instantly; I managed to stay alive, JC was alright, Juan was pretty good and Taynor would kill everybody.  ...And then after a night's gaming we'd show up at school with disregard for the virtual butchering we gave eachother. JC and Taynor seem to still frequently butcher people online with the latest games; which is why I wouldn't challenge them now.  Online gaming's fun though - moreso if you're able to have the games, the friends, to get it going, arrange it, and most desirably win! 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      ...And I got it under £20 too!   Shame that Dave's having a bit of problems with his auction buy, but we're seeing how it goes. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      On the other side of the Metallica coin, there's  urlLink Megadeth &nbsp;- a band that split up in 2001 due to an injury that put an end to frontman Dave Mustaine's guitar playing; temporarily.  It seems they're coming back, and though I'm not a huge fan (but I loved them for a brief time), I'm glad as we need preservation of the old-school in these times.  Mustaine was fired as lead guitarist from 'tallica due to drug and alcohol problems that severely affected his behaviour (hmm, why didn't they arrange rehab for him, like recently for a current member...), and despite having songs written on Met's first 2 LP's, he was never with them for their recorded career. Exodus' Kirk Hammett took that well-know role to infinite success. Dave however played a convincing (but troubled) #2 to with Megadeth, despite many line-up changes and a sound and image progression that nearly copied Metallica's.   I downloaded Symphony Of Destruction via  urlLink MSN Music Club &nbsp;today after I heard they were coming back. It's not a song I owned, but it's a great one. Check these words; they work better when you hear them (snarled):    You take a mortal man,    And put him in control    Watch him become a god,    Watch peoples heads a'roll    A'roll...     &nbsp;   Just like the Pied Piper    Led rats through the streets    We dance like marionettes,    Swaying to the Symphony...Of Destruction     &nbsp;   Acting like a robot,    Its metal brain corrodes    You try to take its pulse,    Before the head explodes    Explodes...     &nbsp;   The earth starts to rumble    World powers fall    A'warring for the heavens,    A peaceful man stands tall    Tall...    No doubt about corrupt politicians leading us to destruction...And oh look at the  urlLink art  for the new 'deth LP 'The System Has Failed'. Mustaine's always been amongst the most politically savvy writers in a sometimes retarded metal scene.    
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I’ve been listening to a lot of mid 80’s  urlLink Metallica  recently (not to mention spending ages reading a Metallica biography before), checking out on latest news; and I feel I have to get some words out of my system.   Metallica are my The Beatles. I may have stopped loving their output since ‘96, but from the black album and backwards they earnt being my favourite band of all time - and will continue to be ‘til I reach underground. They connected to me like a strong magnet more than any artist ever - and may fans feel (or felt) the same.  A lot of people diss Metallica for having ‘sold out’. This term I find stupid, as a band are a band; no band ever sells out. They’re not some evil corporation just because they have become successful and changed. And then to back this up if Metallica did ‘sell out’ it’s been on numerous occasions:  a) Metallica gained a major label deal during the mid-life of their second album [a frown inducer in the then metal community], *and* b) that second album contained Metallica’s first ballad. Then c) Metallica’s third album had hints of classical music, *and* then d) Metallica’s fourth album started seeing them put out singles and videos - which they'd never done before; and nor did many thrash metal artists do so. …e) was the black album. f) wasn’t selling out - it was losing touch with Load/Reload. g) was stumbling with St. Anger.  True though, Metallica aren’t as great as they once were. Their (great on-the-tin)&nbsp;name doesn’t quite suit their latest works. Perhaps if they weren’t so definitely monikered they’d be allowed to have changed their style.  But the fact remains is people (myself included actually) shouldn’t bitch about Metallica - if you don’t like their records you don’t have to buy them or can refund them. I’ve become a gullible collector who would probably purchase a blank Metallica branded CD…true!  And dreaming of a return to glory days is also quite sad (particularly as the late bassist Cliff Burton was the musical mastermind driving their 80‘s output, without whom they would not have achieved those albums otherwise - ever: fact).  If Metallica repeated themselves they probably really would have ‘sold out’ as it’s making product for demand; and then we’d accuse them of not doing anything new (*cough* Slayer). It’s highly possible Metallica could make a great record that isn’t like their past (though I must stress Bob Rock‘s glossy Bon Jovi production is tiring now, which would prevent that). They’re ageing to be fast and aggressive now, so a more realistic view would be atleast a heavy and undumb album (i.e. it could be slow).  In defence of the work since ‘96 atleast they pissed off narrow minded metal fans who can’t accept or understand change (though thankfully this has changed considerably, in bizarre part thanks to nu-metal acts) - and even encouraged their loyal fan base to seek out other styles of music.   I sincerely hope that Metallica continue though - even if it is via records I find rubbish. I find their presence very comforting. Binded with the fact that they play more of the older stuff live still. Plus they don’t regard themselves as 'had it’ by putting out a Best Of CD, nor did they split to return for short-changed reunion gigs.  If they continue they could be the next Rolling Stones or something. Hell, in their style of music they pretty much are. Master Of Puppets is probably the greatest and most clever thrash metal album of all time; and black album is probably amongst the best commercial metal albums ever - two peaks! For these albums Metallica can put out a hundred rubbish albums and it won’t dent my respect for their past and a hope for the future. And hope I still have as their latest album has demonstrated a slight metal pulse that just needs coaxing.   I dunno how to wind this up…So I’ll divert your attention by telling you to look at the new links part on the right of this site. My lass Loz has her own blog now - go see it.&nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Sex is good - make sure you're protected though.  &nbsp;  As for drugs and alcohol (or binge drinking&nbsp;specifically), I've never tried those. I have no problems with people who use them (though I'll hang around no one who does hard drugs), but I will probably never try them.  Why? Though my Dad had once drunk an smoked, it's not something that I grew up with&nbsp;- family traditions really. Being an 80's kid I remember the dangers of tobacco and other drugs from gruesome advertisements, and unlike some of my peers I was very affected by them. And as for drinking, I always associated that with turning into a bumbling beast that eventually keels over.  &nbsp;  Of course many people can drink and it's fine, many people even dabble in drugs and veer away from it taking their life, but fact is if you can avoid these things you're living a less riskier life (and financially sound one). The same can be said for not being promiscuous, eating healthily and going easy on caffeine etc. After all, life is life and you can't censor yourself on everything.  &nbsp;  So my point is...Let me think; have fun but be careful. I never thought I'd write a public service announcement here!    
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I am still here...I just haven't thought of anything interesting to write about - not that that's stopped me before. &nbsp; I'm very confused about graphics cards, but from some research I've determined the best buys are either a Radeon 9800 pro (for which I'd have to buy a whole new power supply too; not to mention worry about cooling), or NVIDIA's 5900XT - which seems the more safer, cheaper&nbsp;and easier choice; particularly as I already have a NVIDIA card. I can run Half Life 2 &amp; Doom 3 on my current card it seems; but it's a card that's frequently taken the piss out of (when I bought this machine I admittedly didn't equip it for gaming - but I like it&nbsp;sometimes) and I want to enjoy my new games to the max when I&nbsp;buy them, and there's some good prices. &nbsp; Nothing else to add; so I'll go into hibernation mode again.. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I seem to love discussing about these things! Anyway, I saw The Secret Agent, on BBC1 yesterday - the programme covered a man who had infiltrated the BNP for 6 months (at immense risk to himself) to report the known true colours behind their mainstream party imagery.   After 9/11, it doesn’t particularly matter if you’re not Muslim, as long as you’re of Asian looks to be given vague pointy fingers from some direction.   In defence, to a degree I can understand the climate of fear: I understand people have to evaluate terror on somewhat of a basic instinctive level (I look out for other tan skinned, beardy men - and they me!), but beyond that it’s also being used as a catalyst for racism by fascist groups. To be Asian (whether it‘s correctly South Asian or to a degree, Middle Eastern), fundamentally Islamic (inc. whites/blacks), is to be ‘The New N-Word’ (I dislike using that exact word at all) - in this point in time, more than blacks, Jews, or homosexuals etc. To be an Islamic is to be a juicy, irresistible target for these backward morons, if not, then some are just very misguided folk - stirred up by localised hate propaganda.   The main quote taken from this programme centres around BNP leader Nick Griffin’s fear of ‘Islamification’ - first of all, if Britain were to be Islamified, it isn’t happening by any force. He is forgetting we’re living in a democracy (even if it has dents in it) and a mixed society. If Britain is becoming Islamified it’s because it’s people want to; why fear what people are choosing? And at the same time, I don’t believe that, despite Islam being destined to be the largest religion in the world, will ever whitewash a country out; and if it did - who cares; unless it was being forced upon people. Nick Griffin claming that rape is a tool for Islamation is way off the normality counter.   Secondly, I don’t think Nick Griffin has particularly studied The Koran in any depth to call it a vile, murderous and medieval religion. I’ve never read The Koran, but like all holy writings, there’s no real endorsement for barbarianism. And if it’s barbarianism we’re talking about no religion is untainted, infact no groups of people outside of religion are untainted - in truth we all live in a vile, murderous, world, fuelled by people like these fascists that we want to escape from. Griffin’s Islamic info comes from one-dimensional sources - and I’d like to see him talk about The Koran, only to be muted within seconds by scholars.   The ones who I feel most sorry for are the members/supporters of the BNP who aren’t inherently racist or prejudiced in anyway, but are with them because of some agreement on policies that the main parties won’t address, but can’t see the true colours - they’re so well hidden from public view. And some realise that this party is more than they hoped for.  Issues such as asylum are very sensitive as the race card is bought into play - and it shouldn’t be. The fact that more people are seeking asylum is the bastardness of the UK government to launch an unfounded war, and then to blame the influx of people seeking refuge from Iraq for problems, for example.   The true problems of society are not race, colour, religion, sexual preference etc. These are divertive targets for people disenfranchised with the system. And yet if you put the BNP in power they would do a worse job for everyone, whoever you are - they know how to divide but know squat about unity which makes a country. But then I realise that these are just a few stray barking dogs. Let ‘em bark until successive generations erase their one sentence from history books.  But we must remember: a seed can grow, and we mustn’t drop our guard for Nazism to return to centre stage. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      On behalf of my mate Dave, I/we purchased something from an auction site as it was much cheaper than the normal outlets - a neccesity, to bring his cursed comp back to life! Things have gone smooth; but the process is still going through. I'm sure they can be trusted but I need to see it in action - and hopefully in the future I'll use it buy and sell stuff myself.  My right shoulder is kind of stiff today. Yakult is a tasty and seemingly helpful drink.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Seems that around 6pm yesterday a young woman was murdered at Westbourne Park tube station - my local. Police and press have been doing the 'rounds (they visited us due to near vicinity!), but nothing online or on TV yet. It's a grim episode; and isn't the first of sporadic violent crimes 'round here. Atleast I'm cosy in my room. The Hammersmith & City line was experiencing delays today..  I find the use of the terms 'Islamic Terrorists' and 'Islamic Extremists' funny; Islam means peaceful, so we're dealing with peaceful terrorists and peaceful extremists, lol! Terrorists and extremists, are terrorists and extremists regardless of who - lose the religious tag. I've never heard of 'Christian Terrorism' or say 'Buddhist Extermists'. I occasionally feel edgy (as do probably non Islamic Asians) because of these terms doing the rounds - they don't help; and I did have police presence today; last year I was nearly bungled in a faulty drugs raid. The only drugs I have is paracetamol and Fig syrup..  Oh, and I would like Steve Lillywhite and Flood to produce the 'Mobot' album...Who'd not?
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Probot  was the name of a project album by Dave Grohl ( urlLink Foo Fighters /Nirvana). It basically consisted of old metal style songs (in some cases more old before my time) written and performed in collaboration with a bunch of his old metal heroes.  ...Now, I don't think I could make a whole album (an EP, yes), but I can play drums and guitar, and if I wanted to attract a libel suit here's how I'd go about it:   1. James Hetfield (Metallica: Vox & Guitars)  I think I would actually be  VERY  scared of working with him, aswell as beyond honoured. This man is talented; this man is my own John Lennon to me, as he's wrote the bulk of my favourite songs ever. I would obviously use this opportunity to steer him back into 80's style songwriting, and maybe he'd appreciate that I don't talk as much as Lars.   Sturart Braithwaite (Mogwai: Guitars & Some Vox)  If Metallica made me want to drum, Mogwai made me want to play guitar - because they made it seem like I could do it, and in a mostly non-conventional way.  I'd have to make sure that me and Stu didn't get lost in intricately picking our guitars all day long; easily done. I'd prefer no singing too.   Thom Yorke (Radiohead: Vox, Guitar, Synth)  Nowadays, Thom's music working practices seem similar to mine: use drum machines and synths, but also use guitars and singing. I could do everything for him, but the singing. That'd cheer him up.   Jack White (White Stripes: Guitar, bass, vox)  It wouldn't be hard to replace Meg White on drums, and I don't think I'm likely to attract a fist from Jack White (not that I'd try to piss him off), so this would be an easy end to an E.P.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      iPod or New Walkman? MP3 or WMA? These are questions you have to ponder when dipping into the now legit world of downloadable music; a world which is now becoming a serious distribution mechanism.  I predict atleast, that if 'physical' music is to go, the humble single will go first - you just can't beat the price, and the instantaneousness with broadband becoming more popular every day.  But, before it's 'truly' accepted, some things are gonna have to settle. It's become obvious that MP3's (aside from the still below surface operations) with their zero measures of security won't be adopted as the industry darling, but it will remain, if only because of the strong popularity of those 3 letters, and the vast music files that exist already, and the numerous software and hardware supporting it. It can't be killed. Perhaps slowly, if at all.  The commercial war is between WMA (Windows Media), AAC (Apple) and ATRAC (Sony); WMA has the upper hand in that it features on most pay download sites already, and is supported in hardware and software stakes as much as MP3 - with the added luxury of security for the artists. But, it's fashionable to not like Microsoft, and so the cult of Apple is the prevailing name, despite iTunes selling songs in AAC format, which can also only be put on the iPod hardware unit. Worse off is Sony, who despite being the name in home music, have ATRAC; available at a very low key service, for only their players. Just as Sony's Playstation squashed Sega and Nintendo, Apple and Microsoft may squash Sony in this battleground. Perhaps if Sony alligned with either one of it's competitors, it could concrete the industry standard.  We've had vinyl, cassette, CD and MD, but what really is the natural successor? The battle is still being fought.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I’m listening to Michael Jackson’s  History (Disc 1)  as I write. Man, that stuff’s great pop. Was, is and will be. I hope he abandons further crappy soft R&B ideas and does what he does best, which we last heard with  Scream : Rock. Yes, MJ is a rock star, and he should remember that!  Of course,  a lot  has changed since his glory days; he’s been immensely dented. I don’t want to comment on his face, the abuse accusations and stuff as that’s old stuff. It’s true he won’t resurrect the respect he once did, but his fan base went through the storm and I’m sure it’s still in him to write some good stuff; especially with all the illness and the venom built up behind his faded commercial façade.  I  used  to be a big MJ fan - as a kid. My allegiance went to harder rock, and he became softer and Disney-ish. But, I would buy MJ again if he delivered some good solid pop again.  As I listen, particularly to the  Bad  era tracks (incidentally the only original album I bought of his) the memories come flooding back. My childhood was pretty cool.  It's just a shame that nearly are great artists become lukewarm. Why is this?
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      If you haven’t heard about All Back To Mine, it’s basically a series of compilation albums by selected artists of their all time favourite tracks. I mightn’t have the star studded status to see my selection put in the shops, but I’m capable of burning a CD-R if anyone wanted it! Here goes (in chronological awe), despite saying this is off-hand and mightn‘t be truly definitive of me:   1. Abba - Does Your Mother Know  Out of all the pop music I listened to first as a child (when pop wasn’t a swear word), Abba were the best - and still are. I choose this track as it’s rocky enough to be in line with ‘what’ I am these days.   2. Level 42 - Lessons In Love  A lot of people don’t like Level 42, so this is probably a guilty pleasure. It’s funky and relaxing pop music which was more inviting to me than 80’s indie at the time. If only I still had my cassette of the album featuring this…   3. Michael Jackson - Man In The Mirror  Emotionally, this had a profound effect on me as a child - the lyrics seemed to connect, despite me being 7! It’s about changing yourself and it’s uplifting musically. Damn, it’s been a v. long time since MJ = Great.   4. Bee Gees - You Win Again  Maybe this 80’s comeback track with it’s stomping beat signalled an incoming love for metal or flirtations with industrial? I dunno, but it’s still a great pop song; and was also Maurice Gibb’s particular all time faves, I read.   5. Metallica - One  I still love Metallica despite the trauma they’ve been inflicting since ‘96. The first video I saw of theirs in full (but I was aware of Enter Sandman from my final primary school year, and had shown considerable interest) was One from the album before black album - so a bit of late promotion worked for me! The video was grim and the song was an epic that started melodic and became machine gun aggressive. This made me pick up drums.   6. Motorhead - Overkill  After tape-trading had begun stacking up my rock collection, with grunge remaining at the bottom of the pile (though Nirvana’s In Utero later reconciled with me); I bought the best of Motorhead, and Overkill is just insatiable insane punk metal - period.   7. Megadeth - Addicted To Chaos  Metallica’s before-debut-fired-guitarist did well with Megadeth; so what if they’re a tad copyist? I’m actually glad Dave Mustaine became his own nucleus as the ‘deth had some real original gems to offer too; Addicted To Chaos connected to me.   8. The Verve - Bitter Sweet Symphony  I remember being a miserable four-letter word the year this was out, and this seemed like my soundtrack. I’d love to walk down Portobello road in a weekend and push people over.   9. Depeche Mode - World In My Eyes  This is significant because I met Loz; she got me into Depeche Mode, and not long after I decided to mess with software drum machines. Depeche are great, but the babe who told me about them is better. World In My Eyes is the brill 1st track from Violator.   10. Mogwai - Mogwai Fear Satan  When I got into Mogwai in ‘99, no one around me knew about them, which made them all the more my own personal band. On the first listen I thought they were crap, by the second or third listen I could write reams about how emotional, intricate and dynamic their music is, and it’s instrumental. This track is a blistering example of ‘gwai at their best.   11. Joy Division - Atmosphere  Joy Division aren’t all doom and gloom, but they are some. Ian Curtis’ archaic English croons of despair against textured music and simple melodies make for great songs. This track is just beauty on record.   12. Public Image Limited - Death Disco  John Lydon did better in PiL than in The Sex Pistols in my opinion. Metal Box was an album of experimental rock and reggae, propelled by rubbery, catchy and simple bass by Jah Wobble, Lydon’s great words, and mangled guitar work by Keith Levene; who I think lives not far from me. This was released in ‘79, when I was born. Death Disco is reggae for the demented.   13. Linton Kwesi Johnson - Time Come  With the reggae tip from PiL, and having read a compilation of LKJ’s fab poetry, I had to get this. I don’t have many reggae (or is it dub) albums (and I want more!), but this sole record feels worthy of a hundred. The lyrics are touching and clever and the music and production is warm. Time Come is a classic - end of story.   14. The Doors - The End  Before I discovered them, they seemed ‘old’ to me, but when you hear them, just like Led Zep, they make some modern bands seem disgusting. The Doors are a great mix of poetry and intricate musicianship. The End is an epic example based around Eastern imagery.   15. Simon & Garfunkel - Bridge Over Troubled Water  This is incredibly emotional and weepy; so maybe I should get more butch again! But aside from this S&G, like Abba, made well crafted pop which still stands up a lot today.  Omissions: The Beatles ('cos they do my head in) and Indian film and Qawali music (because I’m more a pop tart than Asian-ly culturally blessed at the moment still)
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Yeah, Dave made me a copy of the  Roots  album by  urlLink Sepultura  - an old album, and one of the last to feature singer Max Cavalera. I'm not a full-on 'pultura fan but this stuff is alright; it's experimentive and it's a prelude to nu-metal; the prelude being better than the actual birth. I also saved Dave from losing faith in 'tallica, but that ain't a story of note. Rocked moderately well today - could do better.  It's been windy, stormy and rainy today!  In regards to this loose talk about Euthanasia going 'round, I'd like to make this clear:  If I'm ever in a condition where my living quality is zero or minus, and there is no hope for me to get better, please don't let me suffer; turn me off. I want this - don't hesitate!  That's grim to say, but I'm clear about that. I don't want to be pumped by machines or just be a living but dead brain; that really is grim.  On a happier note I'm thinking about posting what I'd put on a compilation CD of my life; notable songs from bands in my lifetime so far. Like those  All Back To Mine  CD's.  Must rest now.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I know it’s still early to be pondering about my birthday - but the big two-five is waiting for me ‘round the corner with a big baseball bat. And I know what I want; but some of these things I want I can’t wait for so I’ll see how to get ‘em myself:   urlLink Doom 3  - Doom 2 came out in ‘94; I was in my 3rd year of secondary school. That’s a bloody long time for a new instalment. Although I hear Doom 3 is a modern retelling of Doom 1, which I also had.   urlLink Half Life 2  - The original came out in ‘97, but I never resumed finishing it ‘til a year or so back. Add-on packs came out but I couldn’t be bothered. I am going to be bothered for this!  For these games I also want a decent new graphics card to juice the most out; but how do I go about choosing? I’ll have to investigate.  Other small wants include the  urlLink Creative Muvo 128mb MP3 player , Metallica’s official  urlLink ‘So What’  biography book (aswell as the Some Kind Of Monster EP out this July 13th), shoes, and probably glasses - I should get my eyes checked as my distance vision I’m sure ain’t what it used to be.  But first my Mum’s birthday comes, so I’ll have to focus on that. Nice to drop hints though..  I see Mary Marsh (head teacher of Holland Park for my last years), who’s now head of the  urlLink NSPCC  was on TV recently, and is against smacking…But it’s okay to use that grey voice in assemblies to send teachers and students alike to sleep is it?..  Saz also sent me a  urlLink link  that renews my faith in making money online - this is just funny!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I was thinking about writing about Saddam Hussein, or writing about why I respect America aswell as despise it; but I just can’t be arsed going down those avenues. It’s probably clear as to what I’d write anyway..  I feel an extra tinge of brightness today in that  urlLink Joel McIver , author of  Justice For All: The Truth About Metallica  (which I‘ve nearly finished), replied to  urlLink an email I sent  and put it up on his website. Also I submitted a question to my forgotten loves Mogwai, who also  urlLink answered it on their site!   This is not the first time I’ve e-mingled. I’ve had a number of questions answered by  urlLink Metallica  live themselves on past chat room events, the same with Mogwai. I was also sent a small reply by the man behind  urlLink Broadway Project ..  Stars are easy to reach online; but it’s true you don’t get that satisfaction as when you physically meet them.  I have met some in real-life though; many of the classic 80’s cast of The Bill, and a few more that I can’t remember right now (though meeting Brad and Tom from  urlLink RATM /now  urlLink Audioslave  is never not memorable!). I also went to school, and was in a band with a guy called Leo Ross who had a brief ride with a band called Nojahoda. I wonder where he’s at? Incidentally, his Dad butlered for Queen (the band), one elder sister’s a journalist, the other a very well-to do model (Liberty Ross, anyone?) and his elder brother is of a band called 12 Rounds, who are signed to Trent ( urlLink Nine Inch Nails ) Reznor’s label in America. And due to that last detail I was able to go backstage aftershow at a  urlLink Marilyn Manson  gig in ‘97 - he wasn’t there though.   By reason, with these links (and being in the prestigious area of West London) and some of my friends links; I.e. Suggs from Madness, a few members from the defunct (and truly awful) Symposium,  urlLink Dreadzone , blaady blaady bla, I should be amongst them. Soon, probably. No use being a Greta Garbo wait around though. Which reminds me…Bye!  P.S.: I have been on  urlLink Sky News  at a ridiculously early hour that no-one saw,  urlLink BBC News  (both for school crap) and  urlLink BBC Radio  (also for school crap); I’m primed for stardom!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       "I'm literally paralysed, but there's a lot of people walking around who are paralysed by a lack of self-esteem, feelings of inadequacy. They don't dare to go for their dreams. They're depressed, feel very negative... it's all negative."   "To a certain extent, paralysis is a choice"   If these aren't noteworthy quotes to buck people up then I don't know what is. These are worth sharing.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm just pre-occupied for a bit.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      August welcomes the birthday of my mum - she's in her early 50's, and doesn't want to elaborate further, lol!  And here's a screenshot of what's occupying the late nights of David and I. We are considering rehab.     I hope to have some written work ready to share within the next few days. Ta for now.  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>