<Blog>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Thats the color of my nails... veryother one is Navy Blue, the rest are Hot Pink. My Girlfriend did them for me, lolz. Just thought I should let you all know :-D 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok, fisrt off, I would like to say, My computer is on it's way, I donno how, but it is... will be here on the 30th, I will have it running by the next day! 
 
Tom Hanks stars as foriegn traveler, who gets stranded in an Airport Terminal. Because of a war in his home-country, his Visas, and Passport are invalidated, while he flies to the USA to fufill a promise to his father. For 9 months he finds every way to survive, and thrive, as the Airport security Manager gets pissed with him. He cannot make him leave, because he has fallen into a crack in the system.  
Very good movie... seems dumb when I explain, and at first, I really thought that Steven Spielburg was running out of ideas, but it turned out great.  
No work on anything today, I was out. 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I Always find it amusing, when Microsoft can't do something as good as a compeditor, they A) Try and buy them out... B) Try to make an identical version, so it will cause the smaller company to go bankrupt, or C) Sue them. 
Well, it seems, Microsoft has hit a solid, spiked wall, made of cement. Google. Lolz, yes, Google. Microsoft Emploies use Google's 'Blogger' to do all thier logging. Microsoft's HOTMAIL has raised it's (paid mind-you) Hotmail Service Sotrage Limit to 250 MB (up from 10mb) in order to compeate with Google's 1 gig (1000mb) and a while back, they tried to buy google. 
Microsoft Sucks. E O S... (End Of Story) 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Google is the best search engine on the web at the moment. 
Now, I know you may hear this a lot, and you may think Im just opinionating... but listen up... Google was started as a college project. No real intentions to become big... no money grabbing scheme *cough* MSN *cough* Anywho... Google uses a network of computers to make finding things faster. 
If you have tried Google... and dislike it, think about why it is you don't like it, compared to Yahoo (now, I say Yahoo, because for godsakes, please, don't use MSN) post me a comment about why you dislike it, and I will explain how to make it work for you. 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The PhP is working on the Zr970.Network site again, even though I wont have my new machine for a long while... Im hosting it all off from my other server thats in my basment. 
It is having troubles talking to my databases, so development can not continue until I fix that small problem. 
I am Adding to my project list below. 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Wow, you hear all sorts of religious scandels on the news... but this one is pretty funny... and It happened to my family... 
"These Flowers Are For You. God Bless You" 
This was the note, sent with two sets of flower orders. Both for over 100$ worth of flowers. Also charged to our Credit Card, over 100$ worth of Charity Funds. 
Now, if I am correct, one of the Amendments is, "thou shall not steal" but, is it stealing, if you are sending flowers to the person, from them? lolz... 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The list of projects I have organized, and started to plan, can now be found at THE BOTTOM OF THE PAGE, in a neat little table I set up, lolz.
The CHECK simply means I have actually started coding for it, and the X means I have planned it, but I havn't started to code it yet.
There was a big accident, and the Credit Card I bought my new machine with, was being used as a fraud by someone else... and so, it was cancelled, and so, I wont et my computer, until I reorder it. 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The Code Blog idea isn't going to work as well as I thought. 
I will however, keep special Blog Entries to report on Z Portal Development. 
Today I was trying to setup RedHat Linux to run as a server... I got it running, but, It wont let the outside world see it, so I said screw it. 
My Case for my new computer hasn't been shipped yet :( but I will continue basic HtMl work on ZP this week. Hopefully, in a weeks time, I will have my Case, and my computer wiull be up and running, with XP Corp. like it should be. 
Work on ZP will really start back up, when I get it running, and you will all see great advances on it. My First Projects will be: 
{ Moved to Footer } 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey! 
Summer started about a week ago today for everyone, I started a week from tommorow (I had some left over books to hand back in)... I am currently kinda computerless, My new case hasn't been shipped, but the parts have. When I get that back up, there will be many more updates on here, and more directed towards the development of Zr970.Network. 
Currently, I can be reached at any of the following three e-mails:   
 urlLink Zypha Mail  
 urlLink GoogleMail  
 urlLink HotMail  
   
Well, thats all for this post... I am gonna create a Code Blog in a sec, I will link it here... 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I got my computer, it's pretty damn cool... Yesterday I went to the fireworks with my Girlfriend, and we watched them from her roof... also pretty damn cool... 
The server is back up, but just up, not much of anything on it... you can visit it at: 
 urlLink Port 82 [ Zr970 Home ]  
 urlLink Zr970 Direct Home  
 urlLink Zr970.Network Presents { ZPortal } Home  
 urlLink Zr970.Network Dev Home  
 
We can also be reached at the following addresses: 
 urlLink HotMail [ Wouldn't recommend this one ]  
 urlLink GMail  
 urlLink ZyphaMail  
    
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am still living, I am just waiting for my new computer... it's currently in... uh.... looks* 
Don't know, it's Sunday, no update on it... I will prob. recive it tommorow... or Tuesday.
Anywho, My father is printing, and binding a book on Assemblly Language tommorow at work, Im gonna learn that while I work on .Network and im not too busy. 
I will update tommorow... 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I Love the new Apple Dippers from McDonalds... lolz, I order my usual, plus Apple Dippers :) You should all try them, they are better then the fries, plus, they are good for you, lots of Vitimen C (Don't care if I can't spell, those were good)... I got pretty tired of working today, so my update for the day includes: 
 
 Bold'ing the two sidebar captions 
 Adding the Work Cam (See Below Post, or the one b4 that) 
  
The End... Are you not all proud of me? I need f*ing sleep right now tho, only, Im not tired... wait, nm, I cant see the keyboard nemore, I am tired... blahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh 
Ok, Im done.... Gonna go to bed now, I think, or I might play AoE, and play the Rome Expansion Campaign... but it's pretty hard, so I might not... I may play Harry Potter CoS, but that gets boring too, and Im not in a Programmy mood, which is odd... mabey Im sick... no, don't think so... lolz, 'Programmy' they should have those for good programmers, like me... 
 And Now, The 2005 Programmy Award Show, with your host, *thinks*  .... This year, we have many great nomonies, first up, in the Visual Basic catagory, we have, Jalweber, who just survived CKress's VB Course, that in itself deserves an award... 
Next up, we have   
Our next catagory is PhP, and our first, and best nomonie is...... Zr970, who designed ZPortal Web Portal... 
    
Tired... Bed... Night... 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, atleast, thats the time in wich screenshoots are taken, you can view me working, with screenshots of my monitor system at http://65.19.75.24:82/zr_online/dev.htm 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ah, Tis' true... I once again have more then one monitor... this time, I have 3... lolz 
One is a GeForceMX440, black, ViewSonic (I painted it black, looks nice...) 
The other two are on a GeForceFX5200, Dual Monitor Card... 128mb YEA!!!! (Vaio Monitors, they look SICK!) 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The news on the sidebar for now, will look much like the POLLS Sideaddon... but soo it will include a feature that alerts users of new News Articals, since last login...  But dont expect that till late this summer...   
Update at 3:17 am 7/10/2004  
They should expand in thier individual catagories, not very efficient yet, but Ill figure out a better way... ALSO... the @ {Time} is messed on most of them, thats because I was tweaking the time & Date script... I am gonna make a new Cat. for you to test on... # [ 27 ] (Tester) so try it out... peachy! Byez 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Lolz, I Just finished the campaign of Age of Empires... 3 days on/off play... good game, I learned more from it then I did in my 9th grade Global Studies class... ah well, back to work now I guess... 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       News is up, kinda working... you can add news too... the catagories are surrently 
 25 (School)  26 (PhP)   
Deleting is not yet advalible, nor' is editing... but I hope to have those done by tommorow night, along with styling the News pages, and adding them to the sidebar... 
Tommorow I will also put up some new screenshots,  wow, well, Tommorow = Today... I Didnt see the time, I gotta piss... 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok, Screw that idea with a rooster... 
Im just gonna use advanced CSS files to do this... so much nicer...   
You wont notice any difference, but the new styles are now in place...  Updated: 9:58pm 7/9/04  
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am pondering the idea of attempting to learn XML again, to make the site a bit more consistiant, in terms of tags, text sizes, and styles... Fear-not, it wont cut into the time I spen Dev'ing, just improve the work I do :) 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Other then the colors, how does this look? :  
   
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The Sidebars are beginning to take a beta form... 
I had planned on doing this detail last, but I am fully awake, and it's 1:16 AM... and Im Bored out of my mind. 
Next up, News... finally... and then I guess I will make the Sidebar Componant that alerts users of new news since they last visited... 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, not quite yet, but soon Voting will be working... 
Right now, design for editing the polls is underway. The Voting, part of the 'User Option Selection' is designed after this 'Admin Poll Selection' is done. 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink   
 urlLink   
 urlLink   
 urlLink   
 urlLink   
 urlLink   
 urlLink   
 urlLink   
 urlLink   

 
Sneak Look at the  Polls  Development...  
    
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Under Zr_online, then polls.php, you can watch me as I work on building the Polls Section.  
    
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This page will allow you to see what I am messing up/around with today... mostly new images, possibly some scripts... [ Click Post Title ] 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I started to clean up the site today... 
 Admin Panel Added 
 Add / Edit / Delete Removed from sidebar 
 Added Login (not working yet)  
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        
 
 
  
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok, Tired + Me = Going to sleep soon... Messages are readable, replies for it are under it, I gotta do some organization work and stuff, but yea... 
Cat2 -> Fourms2 -> Last Message = With replies... 
Will finish up for the next week tommorow, comming back 25th, just in time for 10 days in hell worth of tweaking, and Aplha Releasing... 
I am backing up now... Just thought of doing it, for saftey this week... 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Im not going to include the 'In-Site Messenger' in version 1, Im saving it for 2.0... 
My descision to do this, is based on the fact that I need to finish Messageboards, and then work on more acceptable graphics thruout... and make the EDIT, and ADD and DELETE only in the ADMIN panel... 
THEN, I have to learn sessions, and cookies, before Beta release... and all my spelling, and code polishing, uhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh I love this 
I have estimated over 100 hours of work, 33 Blog posts (34 now) 13 PhP files, 1 Concept(html) file, 3 CSS Files, and some small image work... For an Alpha release, thats not done yet, thats quite a lot... Well, Im gonna print off some PhP Session & Cookie tutorials, so I can get that done, wait, no, ill do that next week while Im gone...Im gonna make messages readable now i guess... 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       OH MY FRIKIN GOD! five hours straight, just to do what I have done... as of now, you can do all but: 
 Post, or Reply 
 Read Messages 
 Add Polls, Smilies, other fun features 
 see which messages are new since your last visit 
 
But, Im trying... This next week, I wont get any updates in whatsoever, till next sunday (25th) because we are going camping, but Ive got a lot done so far... Im gonna try to get adding, and deleting messages done before I go tho, so u can play... 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The Concepts for the Message Boards have come thru, the colors could be better, but I like they layout overall, but I think its too much like every other message board out there... please comment with any ideas... 
http://65.19.75.24:82/Zr_online/messageboard_ex.htm 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Uhhhh, this messageboard is gonna be a bitch to setup... I dont have enough energy to do it now, mabey tommorow... but you can add cvats for the fourms... yea, may look a bit fimiliar, thats because its just the news cats, altered.... im too lazy to work right now...
 
The Concepts for the Message Boards have come thru, the colors could be better, but I like they layout overall, but I think its too much like every other message board out there... please comment with any ideas... 
http://65.19.75.24:82/Zr_online/messageboard_ex.htm 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yea, it's a really fun game, if you ignore the fact that, it doesn't follow the storyline all that well, and the graphics card requirements are 16mb, and even with a GeForceFX5200 or my MX440, the graphics still overlapped, some area's were seethru... but the general idea is fun, and its all about hidden secrets, that you can win without finding, but makes the game more fun... 
4 Stars for gameplay 
2 for Graphics 
5 for Strategy, and Secrets 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The database tables for this feature are begginning to take shape... this is going to be by far, the most hectic programming I actually have to do for Alpha. Im gonna finish the one I am working on, then sleep, and wake up, and finish the ground work for tommorow night, when I will finish Postboards...  

-> General Catagory 
--> Fourms. 
---> Messages 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
          
   
       Project Name  
       Project Description  
       Started  
                 
   
      Polls 
      The Polls will be editable by the Admin of the ZPortal. Up to five responses (5 in beta, possibly 10 in final release, or custom) Users vote, and precentages, and a bargraph show results. 
        
                 
   
      News 
      Adnins will be able to post news to thier ZPortals via the control panel. Each news artical can be set to belong to a specified catagory, which can also be set by the Admin of the site. 
        
                 
   
      Messenger 
      An In-Site Messenger will be advalible, where registered users can send e-mail - like messages to one another. 
        
                 
   
      Core 
      The Core of ZPortal. Contains all behind the scenes work. Top Secret Stuff. 
        
                 
 
      Post Board 
      A.K.A the message board, but for now, it will be a very basic, so, I am calling it a 'Post Board' Many features, such including the basics, plus. 
        
                 
  
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Read News added to sidebar, lets you view the news as users will, well, sorta, but good eno0f for Alpha release :) 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Alpha Release: August 5th 
Beta Release: September 9th 
Catagories are done for Alpha, Add, Delete, to your hearts content. 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       As you might be able to tell, Im PISSED! Heres Why: 
 
 Senario 1  
 Cookies are ENABLED for PhP in the configuration file... peachy... BUT! Now, the site refuses to log you out when your done...  
 Senario 2  
 Cookies are DISABLED for PhP in the configuration file... peachy... BUT! Logins don't stick...  
 
If you know anything about how to fix this, post it, PLEASE! 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Errrrrr..... 
No one has commented on it yet, buuuuttttt..... 
Session just regens after u logout... so its impossible to logout, unless u login on the kill page, BUT! Anyone visiting the site at the time, will be logged in as u, the next time they open a page.... :S... 
This part looked easy in the manual... 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Logins, should work! 
Test them with:  
 Username: admin 
 Password: passwd  
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, I am back... I got a new Palm Pilot... not too fancy, but works well... 
back to the wonderous site updates, in preperation for ALPHA *cue music*  
I need to go now tho, I have been away for a week, and need to catch up on SLEEP! 
 Testing Block Quote... Sorry, had too...  
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, Alpha day is done, and I managed to pull off a working logout page... finally... lolz, oh, btw... the Alpha release is advalible  urlLink Here  if you ever find the need to monitor changes from then, and future... all new work is being done on the normal site location.  
Next up, is making Message Boards work properly, then adding features to them...
-Out 
- - Zr 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I finished up most loose ends... Logout should work better (You have to log back in after logging out, or it wont stick...) 
Special 'Alpha' Style temporary changed, not changeable, just colors pulled from the banner... 
We finally made it, I am pretty proud of the amount I have finished, It will work fully by beta, I promise (then I can add new things before Final Release in January 05') 
Here are the stats for the site so far: 
 Files: 139 
 Folders: 12 
 Size: 2 Mb 
 Feature Compleation: 74.8% 
 Final Release: January 1, 2005 
 Thank - You to everyone who gave me support... This blog is going to be archived on the site for later viewing... updates will be very frequent from the 20th of August till School starts, as my girlfriend will be going to college :(, and I will have lots of time to be lonly, and bored... 
Im off for the night! Thanks for a great Alpha! 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, not yet... I got one hour, to finish what I can, and make the Alpha banner... CRRRRRAAAAAAAAAAAAAAPPPPPPPPPP and logins don't work yet... 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, not yet... I got one hour, to finish what I can, and make the Alpha banner... CRRRRRAAAAAAAAAAAAAAPPPPPPPPPP and logins don't work yet... 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, not yet... I got one hour, to finish what I can, and make the Alpha banner... CRRRRRAAAAAAAAAAAAAAPPPPPPPPPP and logins don't work yet... 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
            
1: if(isset($editnow)){&nbsp;&nbsp;$x = $pname;&nbsp;&nbsp;echo "$x";&nbsp;&nbsp;dbn("zr_online", "update zr_polls set poll_title = '$pname' where id = $editnow");}
      
Im sending $pname from a simple HTML Form. I can send Integers, regardless of the ' marks, but any text that is sent, is refused from the database input (From the form only, if I set $pname on the page, it takes it, unless I use $pname=$x after the $x=$pname) So I donno what to do now... :( 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Thats pretty much all I can say... Polls still wont edit, It has something to do with sending text in a form...................(does do ints) nope, it is a text feild, just checked it... 
ah well, site has to be accessed from: 
 urlLink Here  
GAHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!!!!!!!!! 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I got a new server, databasing control is a bit messed, but ill figure it out tonight, until 3, then Im sleeping 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yea, Im taking the site down, not for long, dont fret! 
Just until I get the new server set up... 
I wanna make sure that all old config is DEAD 
 BACKUP  
    
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Something is wrong with some of these databases, they get corrupted oddly... Im going to leave the site up, but rebuild an Apache server aswell, not Foxserv... and the latest PhP, and MySQL if I can get it all working... or mabey a Foxserv Update... Ah, or I could go for a linux server... nah... 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       LoLz, Im just fooling... 
Actually, I did tighten security... You should no longer be able to visit the site without being logged in... 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, the Bug Reporting System (yes, the original one) has made it's way onto our fine site... Im proud to say that you may now tell me, when I mess up. I am actually going to be working on updating my precious system, but that will be on another page, so my flawless one can gloat :) 
    
    
</post>


</Blog>