<Blog>

<date>15,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
         Vijay Bhatter - the MAN you KNOW  Founder Member of  urlLink Cyberax Tech , Software Developer, Microsoft Certified Solution Developer. I talk about technology, internet, business, and my life (not always in that order).   Please note: Everything written here is the personal opinion of me and not my employer CYBERAX.NET. 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Currently researching on Search Engine Positioning & Indexing and did found a lot of interesting facts.  1. It requires a lot of patience.  2. Getting a listing on DMOZ.ORG greatly improves your PageRank on Google.  3. Participate in community Message Boards related to your website  4. If you do find some time while surfing do signup the GuestBook, Free For All Link pages with your website link.  5. Last but not the least always use genuine methods. Avoid using Doorway pages. You might think yourself master the search engine guys are Experts.  Cheers, Vijay Bhatter  urlLink http://www.cyberax.net 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I used to spend at least an hour a week deleting spam from my in-box. Then I discovered filters that would do the job for me. The best, like Spamihilator and IHateSpam, plugs directly into any POP3 compliant mail client like Outlook, Outlook Express (OE), Eudora and catches 80 to 90 percent of the junk, funneling suspect messages into a folder.  Of course, they're not perfect--I still have to delete missed spam from my in-box and review the folder for legit mail that's been caught by mistake--but I spend minutes on the job instead of hours.   So if you are also one of the victims of Spamming. And you user POP3 compliant mail service. I would definitely advice you all to download Spamihilator. IT's FREE and Delete more than 90% of your Spam-Mails! Which could be brought to 98% if you train the software a little.  Spamihilator works between your Email-Client-Software and the Internet and examines every incoming eMail. Useless spam mails (Junk) will be filtered out. This process works completely in the background.   urlLink http://www.spamihilator.com   The new Learning Filter (Bayesian Filter) uses the rules of Thomas Bayes (english mathematician, 18th century) and calculates a certain Spam-Probability for every eMail. You can train this filter! So it will know your messages even better than you and continuously increase the recognition rate.  In addition Spamihilator uses a Word-Filter, that searches messages for known keywords.  Of course, Spamihilator supports Plugins. These useful additional filters protect your system against annoying Spam-Messages.  The program runs with almost every Email-Software, such as Outlook 2000/XP/Express, Eudora, Mozilla, Netscape, IncrediMail, Pegasus Mail, Phoenix Mail, Opera, etc...  The best thing I liked about the software is that Spamihilator is absolutely free!   I hope you would find this tip useful. Keep checking this site for more tips I have gathered during my 7 years of experience with the Internet.  In case you have any tip to share you can mail me.    urlLink Vijay 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
         Taking a break of my regular technical and computers & internet related stuff. I want to share something off the track i.e. the only tv programme i try not to miss. For Indian viewers The Punjabi working woman Jassi in "Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin" has done the seemingly impossible. The new soap has made a dent in Ekta Kapoor's ostensibly inviolable soaps on STAR Plus.  Challenging the perfectly groomed, articulate and flawlessly put-out upper middleclass women in Kapoor's serials, "Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin" seems to be racing to the top in just two weeks since the serial began.  One person who's watching Jassi's adventures avidly is TV tycoon Kapoor herself.   "I'm a big fan of 'Jassi'. I think the show has made tremendous inroads in very little time. It has gone ahead of all other programs currently aired. Looking at the change of viewer taste and the response I decided why not dedicate a page to Jassi and here it is:  urlLink http://www.bhatter.com/jassi .  Most television programmers are dumbstruck by the new "Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin" factor on Indian television.     Concept and Story Line   Jassi Jaissi Koi Nahin is the story of a sweet, simple and less-than-ordinary looking girl with a heart of gold and a persevering nature. Born to ordinary middle class parents, Jassi's simplicity and clumsy ways make everyone fall in love with her.   Like millions of middle class Indian girls Jassi too aspires to make a mark for herself with her never say die attitude yet gullible nature. The show brings out the eternal conflicts between the middle class and the high society; simplicity and glamour; artificial facades and true inner beauty. 'Jassi Jaissi Koi Nahin' has all the ingredients to make it connect well with its viewers - a contemporary setting, a metrosexual male and fashionable socialites contrasting with a plain, ordinary girl aspiring to be accepted in high society and determined to make it big one day.   The show is sure to click with the Indian viewers, as most of them with similar values will strongly relate to Jassi, her aspirations, her attitude and her never-say-die spirit.  It's an adaptation of a South American serial called 'Yo Soy Betty Lafea'. It had a very successful innings in several countries. Sony decided to adapt it to Indian television.  If Jassi's story follows the original script of Yo Soy Betty La Fea then most probably it would be similar to the one given below:   urlLink Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin    Enjoy Reading. 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Currently working on Search Engine Optimization for the following websites:  1.  urlLink Earth Fashions  features Earth Ragz Apparel, Clothing, Blankets, Throws, Accessories, Bed Blankets, Sports Blankets, Comforters, Pendleton Blankets, Online USA Store. All their garments, blankets and accessories are made from 100% pre-consumer recycled fibers. and  urlLink More...    2.  urlLink Cabin Fever America  features Blankets, Throws, Unisex Apparels, Ladies Apparels, currently ships to entire USA and Canada.  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Dear Visitor,  I have collected a small set of inspirational / self development quotes from a article written on Dhirubhai Ambani (Reliance Industries Ltd.) which I feel you all will love to read:  1. Meeting the deadlines is not good enough,     Beating the deadlines are my expectations  2. We bet on people   3. Don't give up, courage is my conviction  4. Our dreams have to be bigger. Our ambitions higher. Our commitment deeper. And our efforts greater. This is my dream for Reliance and for India.  5. Only if you can dream it you can do it.  6. Think big, think fast, think ahead.     Ideas are no one's monopoly.  7. You do not require an invitation to make profits.  8. If you work with determination and with perfection success will follow.  9. Pursue your goals even in the face of difficulties, and convert adversities into opportunities.   Cheers,  urlLink Vijay Bhatter   urlLink http://vijay.bhatter.com   ====================================== Get Professional High Quality Web Site design templates, Flash Intro, Logo Templates at   urlLink Cyberax Design Studio   urlLink http://www.cyberax.net/studio.asp  ====================================== 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hi Friends,  This is for all my friend with whom I have not met me for quite some time now.                 August 2002      August 2003                   January 2004      Today      Since the last 2 pics were taken from a webcam its not of very good quality…  Will keep you all updated. Till then good bye.  Cheers,  urlLink Vijay Bhatter  @ urlLink Cyberax  @ urlLink http://www.bhatter.com  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      In this blog of mine I have tried to answer the following.   As human beings, we always feel that something is missing, even after achieving financial success through business and careers, getting married, attaining homes, cars, vacationing and establishing a family. What is missing component in our life that we all  are searching for?    I can only speak for myself here. As I was searching for something that would sustain me beyond my family, beyond my career, beyond my mind. Not because I was on any kind of esoteric quest (to find the 'theory of everything', the key that unlocks the door to the universe). It was literally a matter of life and death for me. Nothing made sense any more and I was getting more and more freaked out. What was wrong with me and that could'nt be fulfilled even by dependable family, business and a successful IT career ? What was wrong with me...? Why was I waking up at night feeling a kind of dread...? I realise now, I was hearing the call...Simple. Same as Gautama the Buddha...he 'selfishly' left his devoted wife and son, because he couldn't not do it.   Most of us build our lives on sand. Mainly on two things: relationship, and career. If we loose either of these things, our world falls into a state of chaos...and can even collapse completely...It's a big trauma for most of us. So we usually hold on to these two things at all costs...relationship, and career. Meanwhile, life passes. I think that's the pain...that's the missing piece...we need a deeper meaning.   But we live in fear of life! Through the grace of my guru, I discovered that actually, life isn't out to get me! It loves me, actually! It loves us all! It is forever compassionate, it gives us the lessons we need, however hard they are to take, because in it's infinite wisdom, it wants us all to grow...to be at peace.   And Life is the greatest teacher...It's even more than that...it is god itself. Life is god. [That's why we can't see god...because it's in and around us all the time.] The basic human desire, as far as I can see, is for 'home'...for peace...for recognition of godliness.   And we assume that it can only happen on the physical plane. But the world is changing...and people are beginning to realise we have to look inwards for that which sustains us...it's not 'out there'....it's the love for yourself that you share.   I hope I made some sense and thanks for reading it !  Cheers,  urlLink Vijay Bhatter  @ urlLink Cyberax    References: 1.  urlLink The spirit of things   2.  urlLink Discovering Your Soul's Purpose    
     

    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Forwarded by: Anonymous  God : Hello. Did you call me?  Me  : Called you? No.. who is this?  God : This is GOD. I heard your prayers. So I thought I will chat.  Me  : I do pray. Just makes me feel good. I am actually busy now.        I am in the midst of something..  God : What are you busy at? Ants are busy too.  Me  : Don't know. But I cant find free time. Life has become hectic.        It's rush hour all the time.  God : Sure. Activity gets you busy. But productivity gets you results.       Activity consumes time. Productivity frees it.  Me  : I understand. But I still cant figure out.        By the way, I was not expecting YOU to buzz me on instant messaging chat.  God : Well I wanted to resolve your fight for time, by giving you some clarity.        In this net era, I wanted to reach you through the medium you are comfortable with.  Me  : Tell me, why has life become complicated now?  God : Stop analyzing life. Just live it.        Analysis is what makes it complicated.  Me  : why are we then constantly unhappy?  God : Your today is the tomorrow that you worried about yesterday.        You are worrying because you are analyzing. Worrying has become your habit.       That's why you are not happy.  Me  : But how can we not worry when there is so much uncertainty?  God : Uncertainty is inevitable, but worrying is optional.  Me  : But then, there is so much pain due to uncertainty..  God : Pain is inevitable, but suffering is optional.  Me  : If suffering is optional, why do good people always suffer?  God : Diamond cannot be polished without friction.        Gold cannot be purified without fire.        Good people go through trials, but don't suffer.       With that experience their life become better not bitter.  Me  : You mean to say such experience is useful?  God : Yes. In every terms, Experience is a hard teacher.        She gives the test first and the lessons afterwards.  Me  : But still, why should we go through such tests?        Why cant we be free from problems?  God : Problems are Purposeful Roadblocks Offering Beneficial Lessons        (to) Enhance Mental Strength.        Inner strength comes from struggle and endurance,        not when you are free from problems.  Me  : Frankly in the midst of so many problems,        we don't know where we are heading..  God : If you look outside you will not know where you are heading.        Look inside. Looking outside, you dream.        Looking inside, you awaken. Eyes provide sight. Heart provides insight.  Me  : Sometimes not succeeding fast seems to hurt more than moving in the right direction.        What should I do?  God : Success is a measure as decided by others.        Satisfaction is a measure as decided by you.        Knowing the road ahead is more satisfying than knowing you rode ahead.        You work with the compass. Let others work with the clock.  Me  : In tough times, how do you stay motivated?  God : Always look at how far you have come rather than how far you have to go.        Always count your blessing, not what you are missing.  Me  : What surprises you about people?  God : When they suffer they ask, "why me?"        When they prosper, they never ask "Why me"        Everyone wishes to have truth on their side, but few want to be on the side of the truth.  Me  : Sometimes I ask, who am I, why am I here. I cant get the answer.  God : Seek not to find who you are, but to determine who you want to be.       Stop looking for a purpose as to why you are here. Create it.        Life is not a process of discovery but a process of creation.  Me  : How can I get the best out of life?  God : Face your past without regret.        Handle your present with confidence. Prepare for the future without fear.  Me  : One last question. Sometimes I feel my prayers are not answered.  God : There are no unanswered prayers. At times the answer is NO.  Me  : Thank you for this wonderful chat.        I am so happy to start the New Day with a new sense of inspiration.  God : Well. Keep the faith and drop the fear.        Don't believe your doubts and doubt your beliefs.        Life is a mystery to solve not a problem to resolve.        Trust me. Life is wonderful if you know how to live.   ==================   urlLink Vijay  Bhatter    urlLink Web Hosting in India  provided by  urlLink  Cyberax   
     

    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Dear All,  Very good reading on existence of god. Read it at leisure.  Cheers,  urlLink Vijay Bhatter     An atheist professor of philosophy speaks to his class on the problem,science has with Krishna. He asks one of his new students to stand and.....   Professor:  You are a Hare Krishna devotee, aren't you, son?   Student:  Yes, sir.   Prof:  So you believe in God?   Student:  Absolutely, sir.   Prof:  Is God good?   Student:  Sure.   Prof:  Is God all-powerful?   Student:  Yes.   Prof:  My brother died of cancer even though he prayed to Krishna to heal him. Most of us would attempt to help others who are ill. But Krishna didn't. How is this Krishna good then? Hmm? (The student is silent.)   Prof:  You can't answer, can you? Let's start again, young fellow. Is God good?   Student:  Yes.   Prof:  Is Satan good?   Student:  No.   Prof:  Where does Satan come from?   Student:  From...God...   Prof:  That's right. Tell me son, is there evil in this world?   Student:  Yes.   Prof:  Evil is everywhere, isn't it? And God did make everything. Correct?    Student:  Yes.   Prof:  So who created evil?(The student does not answer.)   Prof:  Is there sickness? Immorality? Hatred? Ugliness?.All these terrible things exist in the world, don't they?   Student:  Yes, sir.   Prof:  So, who created them?(The student has no answer.)   Prof:  Tell me, son. Do you believe in Krishna?   Student:  Yes, professor, I do.   Prof:  Science says you have 5 senses you use to identify and observe the world around you. Have you ever seen Krishna?   Student:  No, sir.   Prof:  Tell us if you have ever heard your Krishna?   Student:  No, sir.   Prof:  Have you ever felt your Krishna, tasted your Krishna, smelt your Krishna? Have you ever had any sensory perception of Krishna or God for that matter?   Student:  No, sir. I'm afraid I haven't.   Prof:  Yet you still believe in Him?   Student:  Yes.   Prof:  According to empirical, testable, demonstrable protocol, science says your Krishna doesn't exist. What do you say to that, son?   Student:  Nothing. I only have my faith.   Prof:  Yes. Faith. And that is the problem science has.   Student:  Professor, is there such a thing as heat?   Prof:  Yes.   Student:  And is there such a thing as cold?   Prof:  Yes.   Student:  No sir. There isn't.(The lecture theatre becomes very quiet with this turn of events.)   Student:  Sir, you can have lots of heat, even more heat, superheat,mega heat, white heat, a little heat or no heat. But we don't have anything called cold. We can hit 273 degrees below zero which is no heat, but we can't go any further after that. There is no such thing as cold. Cold is only a word we use to describe the absence of heat. We cannot measure cold. Heat is energy. Cold is not the opposite of heat, sir, just the absence of it. (There is pin-drop silence in the lecture theatre.)   Student:  What about darkness, Professor? Is there such a thing as darkness?   Prof:  Yes. What is night if there isn't darkness?    Student:  You're wrong again, sir. Darkness is the absence of something.You can have low light, normal light, bright light, flashing light.....But if you have no light constantly, you have nothing and it's called darkness, isn't it? In reality, darkness isn't. If it were you would be able to make darkness darker, wouldn't you?   Prof:  So what is the point you are making, young man?   Student:  Sir, my point is your philosophical premise is flawed.   Prof:  Flawed? Can you explain how?   Student:  Sir, you are working on the premise of duality. You argue there is life and then there is death, a good God and a bad God. You are viewing the concept of God as something finite, something we can measure. Sir, science can't even explain a thought. It uses electricity and magnetism, but has never seen, much less fully understood either one. To view death as the opposite of life is to be ignorant of the fact that death cannot exist as a substantive thing. Death is not the opposite of life: just the absence of it. Now tell me, Professor. Do you teach your students that they evolved from a monkey?   Prof:  If you are referring to the natural evolutionary process, yes, of course, I do.   Student:  Have you ever observed evolution with your own eyes, sir? (The Professor shakes his head with a smile, beginning to realize where the argument is going.)   Student:  Since no one has ever observed the process of evolution at work and cannot even prove that this process is an on-going endeavor, are you not teaching your opinion, sir? Are you not a scientist but a preacher? (The class is in uproar.)   Student:  Is there anyone in the class who has ever seen the Professor's brain?(The class breaks out into laughter.)   Student:  Is there anyone here who has ever heard the Professor's brain, felt it, touched or smelt it?.....No one appears to have done so. So, according to the established rules of empirical, stable, demonstrable protocol, science says that you have no brain, sir. With all due respect, sir, how do we then trust your lectures, sir?  (The room is silent. The professor stares at the student, his face unfathomable.)   Prof:  I guess you'll have to take them on faith, son.   Student:  That is it sir.. The link between man & god is FAITH. That is all that keeps things moving & alive.   Contributed by   Shrikanth G Hampiholi  .
     

    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hi Friends,  Recently purchased a new Canon PowerShot SD100.  About the camera:  The Canon PowerShot SD100 is the first of the pocket-sized Digital ELPH cameras to use Secure Digital memory cards instead of CompactFlash.  3.2 megapixels (effective), 2x optical/3.2x digital zoom, autofocus only, program exposure only, JPEG file format, ISO range 50-400, proprietary Lithium-Ion battery, movie mode with sound.  The 16MB Secure Digital card included with the Canon SD100 can only store 8 images at the camera's highest resolution. We strongly recommend purchasing at least a 256MB card, allowing the storage of a minimum of 128 best-quality JPEG images.           For more info visit:   urlLink http://www.powershot.com/powershot2/sd100/   Also started a new Photo blog  urlLink http://vijaybhatter.fotopic.net . Check it out!  Signed up for a new Google GMAIL account with 1000 MB mail space/.  You can also get your own photo space with 250MB of space for FREE. Visit  urlLink http://www.fotopic.net   Cheers,  urlLink Vijay Bhatter   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hi Friends,  Have been to Singapore and Malaysia and it was a great trip. Met friends and business associates there. And overall it was fun. Have been to Genting Highlands (Malaysia),  urlLink Perhentian Island (Malaysia)  enjoyed Scuba diving there at  urlLink Tuna Bay Island Resort  Marine Park, Sentoza (Singapore).     urlLink    Click to enlarge       urlLink Vijay  @ Kuala Lumpur City Central (KLCC) located inside the world's tallest building Petronas Twin Tower     Will keep you all updated...   This site is hosted at  urlLink Cyberax Web Hosting Services, USA & India  
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Victoria Memorial - Kolkata (INDIA)&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Petronas Tower aka Twin Tower in Kuala Lumpur (Malaysia) &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>


<date>05,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
         The perspective of the first few scenes is Jassi’s. We don’t see her, but see the world’s reaction to her. She arrives at Gulmohur for her job interview. First she runs into Wilson and tells him that she has a job interview. She then meets Maria who tells her to go on up to Chairman. There, she runs into Pari who looks at her with an “I can’t believe THIS” look; then she makes the mistake of going to Maddy’s lair, where he pretty much tells her to get out and never come back. She tries to explain that she’s looking for Chairman and he tells her where it is. Berta calls for Pari Fernández and Jassi Pinzón, to meet with Manchanda and another executive. He asks them the same questions since they’re both interviewing to be the Chairman’s secretary. Pari explains that even though she has zero experience as a secretary, she did finish “six semesters in Mumbai at Mumbai University.” Jassi also says that she doesn’t have experience as a secretary, but that she did graduate from university with high honors and has undergraduate and graduate degrees in finance and economics, and also worked as an assistant at Banco de Montreal.    Manchanda asks them about their foreign language skills and Pari says that she knows a bit of English. Jassi answers that she speaks English and French, and a bit of Italian. In addition she lists the other things she can do and knows about, which impresses everyone… Inappropriate as always, Manchanda asks them about their marital status. Pari explains that she is separated from Mauricio Briggman (and Manchanda of course says that he knows him!). Jassi answers that she is single, to which Manchanda says, but of course. Manchanda asks Jassi why she didn’t include her photograph with her résumé. Jassi explains that she’s been to so many interviews that she ran out of photos. Manchanda tells them that he will get in touch with any news, but as they’re leaving the office, he pretty much offers Pari the job right in front of Jassi. Jassi literally runs into Berta, who is carrying a trashcan that flies out of her hands. At that exact moment, Arman and Mr. Suri exit the elevator, and Berta begs Jassi to help her pickup the mess, because she doesn’t want the bosses to see it. Arman notices the trash and starts scolding and yelling at Berta, and doesn’t even notice Jassi, who looks at him in total shock because of his ranting and raving.   Manchanda tells Arman that he’s found his secretary, and shows him Pari’s paperwork. Arman gets mad at him and asks him how he’s going to get through to him, that he didn’t ask him to hire Sharon Stone, that he asked for someone efficient who spoke two languages. And, Arman is especially upset because Pari is Mallika’s best friend. He asks Manchanda if he didn’t pre-select any other candidates and asks him to get him the other résumés for him to look at. Jassi gets home and her mother asks her how the interview went. She says okay and Nandu arrives. She tells him that she went to a fashion house to interview for a job as a secretary, because she doesn’t dare apply for assistant or executive positions because of her looks. And, that they practically hired “a pretty one” in front of her. She reminds them that people are always impressed by her résumé, but when they see her she never gets hired — that it’s simply a problem of “casting.”   ============================================= Unofficial Site on  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin    Join the  urlLink India Forums  to discuss about Jassi. Click   urlLink here   to view  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin   Forum =============================================
     

        
</post>

<date>12,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Meanwhile, Arman, Mr. Suri, and Manchanda are walking around Gulmohur’s production area (we see Arman with his famous “stress ball”), talking about the various applicants. When Arman and Mr. Suri see Jassi’s they are duly impressed and ask Manchanda why he didn’t hire her on the spot. He answers that she’s got a little problem — she’s very ugly. They call Jassi’s former employer at Banco Montreal, to ask about her work there. They give her a glowing recommendation, saying that she’s an exceptional woman, that she’s got all the educational qualifications and can work circles around anyone. Mr. Suri tells Arman that it is his choice to make, hire a pretty woman or hire a qualified one.   Babe shows Jassi and Nandu a copy of the magazine Jet Set, where there is an article about Gulmohur. Jassi reads it aloud, explaining that the article is about Mr. Suri’s last collection as Chairman of Gulmohur. We see pictures from the lanzamiento party and are introduced to each of the key players at Gulmohur — Mr. Suri, Mrs. Suri, Arman, Aryan (who for a change are having AN ARGUMENT!), Mallika, Pari, Raj, Maddy... Aryan is very upset that Mallika voted to make Arman Chairman, and that it was obvious that Arman proposed marriage to buy her vote. Pari begs Mallika for help getting a job because she’s so broke that the next time she sees her will be in jail, where she knows Mallika won’t go visit her. Pari says that she doesn’t want to be a secretary, to which Mallika tells her that it’s the only job available, that she’ll make more money than a secretary, and that she needs her there to keep Arman in line. During the lanzamiento, again setting the tone for the rest of the novela, Mallika and Arman argue about setting their wedding date. He finally gives in and announces publicly that they will be married in September. We see Mrs. Suri crying from joy, Maddy is thrilled for "Marge," as is Pari, while Raj looks like his best friend has been condemned to die a slow death by torture. Aryan looks unhappy to say the least. Nandu has already noticed Pari and is “in love.” As they are talking, Jassi gets a call asking her to go back to Gulmohur the next morning at 9:00 a.m. to meet with Arman.   Arman tells Mallika that he doesn’t want to be stuck with Pari as his secretary, especially since he knows she is going to just be spying on him. Mallika says that she’s the right and most qualified person for the job. He answers back that there is someone truly qualified whom he’s asked back for another interview. Just then, Mr. Suri’s secretary opens the door and shows Jassi in. Mallika and Arman see her and are taken aback by her looks. Mr. Suri arrives and ignores Jassi when she extends her hand to shake his. Jassi tells them about her educational and professional backgrounds, and Mallika, Arman, and Mr. Suri can’t help but be impressed. Arman asks Jassi if she’s sure, with her qualifications, that she wants to be a secretary. Jassi says yes, that she wants to learn about how to run a fashion business and wants to work with people such as them. They ask her to wait outside, and Mallika says that there’s no way Jassi can be Arman’s secretary, that she’s too ugly and can’t be allowed to work in a fashion house. That Pari is THE choice because she’s beautiful. Mallika asks Jassi and Pari to come in and places them side-by-side like in a cattle call, so Arman and Mr. Suri can make their choice. Afterwards, Arman scolds Mallika for how he treated “that young woman.” Mallika and Pari proceed to make fun of Jassi. Because of Mallika’s manipulation, he has to hire Pari but also decides to hire Jassi. When he tells her to go sign her paperwork and start work first thing next morning, Jassi is beyond excited. Mr. Suri formally transfers power to Arman. Jassi comes home and tells her parents the great news, but lies when she tells them that she was hired to be an assistant to the Chairman, rather than her real position of secretary.   Raj scolds Arman for announcing his engagement and wedding to Mallika in public, and begs him to change his mind. Arman tells Raj that he had a fight with Mallika because he hired a secretary that Mallika didn’t agree with. Raj assumes that Arman has hired a “90, 60, 90,” airhead, to which Arman responds no. He’s hired an ugly woman, with a horrid hairdo, weird voice, braces, but who has more brains than the two of them put together (es fea, tiene voz, con un peinado espantoso, brackets, y tiene más cerebro que usted y yo juntos, y es JASSSSSSIIIIIIII) and she’s UGLY!!! Raj tells Arman that he’s going to fry in hell for hiring an ugly woman, to which Arman responds (sounding like a little kid) —“no te escucho, soy de palo, tengo orejas de pescado” (this makes more sense in Spanish — I can’t hear you, I’m made of wood, and I have fish ears). Jassi tells Nandu about Arman standing up for her in front of Mallika. At the same time Raj makes fun of Arman for standing up for Jassi.   ============================================= Unofficial Site on  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin    Join the  urlLink India Forums  to discuss about Jassi. Click   urlLink here   to view  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin   Forum =============================================
     

        
</post>

<date>24,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      The next day is Jassi’s first day at Gulmohur, and right before going into the building Jassi stops, takes off her glasses, and dabs her eyes — she can’t believe she’s got this job! Wilson doesn’t want to let her in and calls to confirm that she’s indeed Arman’s new secretary. Pari and Mallika arrive and can’t believe it when they realize that Arman actually hired Jassi. Arman arrives and shows Pari where she’ll be sitting and takes Jassi to her new office — THE CAVE. A cleaning lady is heard screaming, and tells Arman there’s a spider. Arman’s answer is — well, kill it then! He apologizes to Jassi for the musty smell of the “office,” explaining that this is where his father kept the company’s old files. But that in 15 minutes it will be ready since he’s gotten her a desk, chair, lamp, a computer connected to the office network, as well as two phone lines, including his private line. He tells Jassi to go see Manchanda to finalize the paperwork. Jassi runs into Mr. Suri and Mrs. Suri and says hello. Mr. Suri tells Mrs. Suri that Jassi is Arman’s secretary. Mr. Suri is upset about Arman’s decision to put Jassi in the cave, saying that it is inhumane. Berta and Sofía see Jassi’s photograph and can’t believe Arman has hired her, that maybe he’s lost his touch. Berta says “welcome to Gang, honey.”   Arman, who will call Jassi Rani (empress) a few times because he can’t quite remember her name (jerk!), tells Jassi and Pari what their duties will be. Pari tells him in no uncertain terms that she should be re-classified as his assistant since he already has Jassi as his secretary. He says that if anyone should be his assistant it’s Jassi since she’s extremely overqualified. He tells Pari that Jassi will handle his personal calendar, dealing with the banks and other business contacts. That Pari will be expected to take care of answering the phones outside Arman’s office and getting coffee as needed. Pari is, needless to say, not happy. Raj flirts with Pari but she blows him off. Raj congratulates Arman for hiring Pari, to which Arman responds that he’s hired Jassi as well. Raj peeks in to see Jassi, who says “good evening.” Raj’s only reaction is “¡uy cosa fea!” (how ugly!). They both laugh. Pari whines to Mallika about Arman “treating her badly,” and especially that Jassi seems to be over her in “power.” Mallika is very upset to hear that Jassi will be handling Arman’s personal agenda and tells Pari that she’ll take care of setting Jassi straight, but that anyway Jassi won’t be at Gulmohur for too long. Meanwhile, Jassi is alone in Arman’s office, grabs his jacket and says “tan divino.”   During Jassi's first day on the job, there's a fashion show for buyers and distributors being held in Gulmohur's show room. The Gang is sneaking in to watch. Arman and Raj go to Maddy’s office and are seen flirting with the models. Arman has asked Jassi to bring him his wallet, which he left in his office, and she is by seeing the models (especially the guys!) in their underwear. Jassi volunteers to bring Arman a color chart from the stockroom. As the fashion show is about to begin, Jassi (poor, poor, clueless Jassi) walks on the catwalk calling out Arman’s name… With gritted teeth he says “I’m here, I’m here” as he tries in vain to “disappear” in his chair. Jassi falls off the catwalk (¡pobrecita!) and is helped to her feet by two men. She apologizes (all this while the fashion show is going on behind her!) and goes to Arman to give him the chart. She wants to make sure that this is what he asked for, and he yells at her that it is. Raj tells her to move (“muévase carajo”). Jassi joins Gang in the back and watches the fashion show with them, very excited about this new “world” she’s getting to know.   When the fashion show is over, Maddy has a hissy fit and complains to Arman about Jassi’s behaviour and tells him that he must ensure that Jassi never again sets foot in his office. Mallika didn’t go to the fashion show, instead she went out to dinner with Pari, to whom she confides that she’s okay because none of Arman’s former model flings participated in the fashion show. When Arman comes back to his office, Jassi apologizes profusely for her faux pas, explaining to him (duh, as if he hadn’t noticed!) that this whole “world of beauty” is completely foreign to her and tells him that she’s got his briefcase and jacket ready for him to go home. Very rudely he tells her to just leave his jacket in his office. When Jassi leaves to go back to her office he says to himself, “what a cross to bear, my God, what a cross to bear” (“que cruz, Dios mío, que cruz”). Arman and Raj plan to go out on the town with the models but their plan is thwarted by Aryan’s arrival looking for his sister. He catches Arman with one of the models, which leads Arman to decide to go home to avoid any trouble with Marce. Jassi leaves Gulmohur alongside the Gang but goes home alone. Arman tells Raj that he isn’t really sure that hiring Jassi was such a good idea, especially after the fashion show fiasco. He says that he doesn’t think Jassi will last long at Gulmohur. 
     

        
</post>

<date>30,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      The next day, Freddy plays a cruel joke on Jassi, making her believe that he’s one of Gulmohur’s executives, and gets her in trouble, even yells at her. Arman arrives and Jassi notices that Freddy was pulling her leg when she realizes that Freddy is the messenger. Arman talks to Jassi and tells her that he’s going to entrust his personal address book and calendar to her, which includes the telephone numbers of women with whom he’s been “close” in the past, and that under no circumstances can she give it to anyone (no se la puede entregar “a nadie, pero a nadie, ni aún a Mallika que va a ser mi esposa”), not even to Mallika, his future wife. From her office, Jassi hears Arman arguing. Mallika is upset that Arman gave his personal address book to Jassi, and that he’s giving her too much access. She also chastises him about still having his old model flames fluttering by. At that very moment, one of these old flames, Karina Larson, arrives looking for Arman. Jassi tells Arman about this and he begs him to get rid of her and to make sure that she goes nowhere near Mallika. Karina is adamant about seeing Arman and Jassi is forced to go meet with her at the reception desk to make sure she comes nowhere near where Arman is. This is very funny, because Jassi has been in her office all this time while Mallika has been arguing with Arman. When Mallika realizes that Jassi is in her office, she is quite upset with Arman. Jassi, who's very smart, catches on to the whole Karina Larson thing and asks Arman to come to her office because of some "personnel problems." She covers for Arman by telling him that he's forgotten about an appointment -- this allows him to sneak out and talk to Karina. She also enlists Raj's assistance to make sure that when Mallika calls Arman at his "appointment" he is actually there! This is only the FIRST of many times that Jassi will cover Arman's butt!   This is only Jassi’s second day at work, and she’s already having to play interference for Arman. Pari notices that Karina is hanging around and proceeds to tell Mallika, who is furious that Jassi covered up for Arman, and goes to her office to demand that she give up Arman’s address book, that she’s nobody to deny her access to her future husband’s stuff. Jassi pleads with her, that she just can’t do it, and Mallika threatens to fire her. Arman takes Karina to a restaurant, where he calls Jassi to ask what's going on with Mallika. Again, since Mallika is in Jassi's office, Jassi covers for him and in code tells him what's going on. Mallika calls Arman's cellular while he's arguing with Karina, and he turns it off. Arman makes it to the place of his supposed appointment and calls Mallika... They argue again... Mallika has Manchanda fire Jassi because of insubordination to Mallika! This will mean that Pari can get her grubby paws on Arman's agenda book before he gets back. However, Jassi isn't going down that easily... Arman arrives just at that moment and tells Jassi to make sure she doesn’t give anyone anything and has another argument with Mallika, confirming that he told Jassi not to give the address book to anyone, including her.   Arman scolds Manchanda for firing Jassi, who wants to leave to prevent any more problems with Mallika, but Arman asks her to stay, and caressing her chin tells her that she’s the woman he needs, and that she has accomplished in two days what he expected her to accomplish in two months, so her status as a temporary employee is over. Raj makes fun of the way Arman talked to Jassi, and tells him to be careful of how he talks to the ugly one, because a caress like that is going to make her think that he’s ready to marry her. Arman tells him that there’s no way Jassi would think that. In the meantime, we see Jassi walking outside remembering Arman’s touch.   Mallika talks to Mrs. Suri about the fight she had with Arman, and Mrs. Suri tells her to act cool and calm, and especially in front of Jassi, the most insignificant of all the women who surround Arman. On her way home, Jassi runs into Román and his gang, who tell her that they want her to go out with them, that if she wants to go she should just ask her dad for permission. They’re doing this just to pull Jassi’s leg since they know her father would never let her go. Jassi tells Nandu about her day at Gulmohur, and how Arman stood up for her. She also tells him about the invitation from Román. Nandu is worried that Pari may have gotten fired because of the problem Jassi had at the office, but Jassi assures him that before Pari is fired Arman would be out the door. She tells Nandu to wake up and smell the coffee, that women like Pari are looking for a rich man who dresses well, has the looks of a movie star, at least two platinum cards, a BMW, the best clothes, memberships at the most exclusive clubs… Nandu is oblivious to all this and hopes that Jassi will introduce him to Pari ASAP. Jassi and Nandu talk about their plight because they’re ugly and no one cares for them, and Nandu asks Jassi if she’s planning on staying single all her life, to which she responds no, that she will be a spinster in a few years! Raj shows Arman a computer program he’s put together that will let Arman know which of the many beautiful women in it is best matched to him. Well, lo and behold, who’s picture should pop up but Jassi’s — and Arman says “murcielaguín”? I think Gaitán was dropping hints about the ending of the show from the very beginning! 
     

        
</post>

<date>07,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Jassi goes to eat lunch at Office Cafe and the Gang asks her to join them at their table since there's nowhere else to sit. Each of them introduces herself. Berta, living up to her sterling reputation, tells Jassi that she's replacing Mireya, Arman's old secretary. Jassi asks why Mireya didn't just move positions to work for Arman when he became Chairman. They explain that she resigned because she fell in love with Arman and decided to leave because she couldn't stand being in that situation anymore, and that Arman never realized Mireya’s feelings for him. They warn Jassi not to fall for Arman, and she gives them a nervous answer saying how could they think something like that…   The Gang brings Jassi up to date about how Arman was able to become Chairman, as well as about his sister Camila, who made the mistake of falling in love with a poor man and married him behind her parents’ backs, which is why she's somewhat distant from the family, and only is in real touch with Arman. She separated from her husband and moved to Switzerland with her son. They also brief her about María Jassi, Mallika and Aryan’s sister, and tell her that she's had so much plastic surgery that even she doesn't remember what she used to look like. In the meantime, don Mr. Suri officially passes the baton to Arman during the Board Meeting. He explains that if within a year Arman is unable to meet the goals he has set for himself, Aryan will become Chairman. Aryan responds that he hopes that there will be a business to run, since he thinks that Arman's business plan will lead them to ruin. Sofía lets Jassi know that it was Mallika's vote that assured Arman the chairmanship, and they all say that Arman is paying a high price for that vote. They say that Mallika and Arman have been dating for over two years and that he cheats on her left and right, but Mallika always forgives him and takes him back. Sandra says that Mallika better be careful because one of these days some woman is going to come and take him from her. Maria says that both Raj and Arman only date beautiful women. That Arman stays with Mallika, and Sandra says that maybe that's not the woman that he's really looking for, that he may want a different kind of woman, different from those Hess used to (hmmm, another Gaitán freebie foreshadow!).   At the end of the Board Meeting meeting, Aryan leaves, and Raj talks to Arman and tells him that maybe Aryan is right and Arman's plan is too risky. The Gang and Jassi comeback to work and run into Aryan, Jassi literally, and he yells at her. Mr. Suri tells Arman that he and Mrs. Suri are going to Switzerland to visit his sister and nephew and will later settle down in London. Jassi confronts Pari about making the Board Meeting believe that she had prepared the report, and Mallika butts in to say that one measly report that Jassi prepares isn't going together a promotion. That she's a secretary and that's all shell ever be. Mr. Suri talks to Arman and gives him advice about how to run the business, to make sure that his pride and ego don't interfere with how he runs the company him to do something for which Hess going to be sorry (hey, another soothsayer), to make sure he doesn't get into any shady business. Jassi tells her Mom over the phone that she wants to resign and tells her about what Mallika and Pari did with the report. The entire Gulmohur staff says good-bye to Mr. Suri and Mrs. Suri.   Arman asks Jassi and Pari to come to his office, and since Hess sure that Jassi is the one who put the report together, he asks Pari for the original reports, to which she responds that Jassi has them. Raj congratulates Pari for doing such a good job an asks her out on a date to celebrate. Arman asks for a business plan and asks who wants to do it and Pari jumps in to say that Jassi can do it, but she says that since Pari did so well with the first report to the Board Meeting it’s only right that she should do this one as well, so Arman tells Pari to do it and tells her that it should be a snap for her to put together this plan after what she pulled off in just one day. In Jassi's office, Arman asks her about who really did the report. Jassi responds that he will know who did it once he reads Pari's business plan. Arman and Raj realize that their business plan is totally wrong. Pari tells Mallika about her “problem” and admits that she cant do what Arman has asked her to do and decides to take Raj up on his invitation to go out, so that she can get HIM to help her, so she invites him to her apartment. Jassi says good night to Pari, like “good luck with your little project, honey,” since she knows that Pari is way over her head. Jassi gets home and asks Nandu to work with her to design a business plan because if she doesn't get it ready before the next morning, its going to be her job on the line. Babe asks Jassi what’s going on, and Jassi ends up confessing that she's actually a secretary not an assistant. Babe asks her to tell her father the truth, but when he gets home with one of his friends he’s had a few too many and tells his friend how proud he is of his daughter and her new position, and Jassi loses her nerve.   BIG HINT AHEAD — Arman and Mallika start talking about their wedding, and Arman is adamant that it’s not going to be a church wedding, something that saddens Mallika to no end and they can’t reach a decision. Pari wants Raj to help her put together the business proposal, but he starts kissing her and they end up in bed. So, obviously no business plan was put together! In the meantime, Jassi and Nandu are working on their business plan proposal. Nandu asks Jassi if she’s doing this because she’s worried about her job or because of Arman. She answers that it’s for both reasons.   Jassi and Nandu pull an all-nighter, which makes Jassi be late for work. At Gulmohur, we see Arman ranting and raving in full petulant mode because Raj, Pari, AND Jassi haven’t arrived. When Jassi is almost at work, she falls, hurts her leg, and breaks her eyeglasses (pity Ruby wasn’t there for this one!). When she gets to Arman’s office he starts in on her, asking her whether there was a death in the family, or she broke something, or her bus broke down, to which Jassi has to respond "no señor,” and even though she’s trying to explain to him why she’s late, he won’t let her. He wants to know where Pari and Raj are, and Jassi further enrages him by asking if they’re together, to which Arman says — what do I know, I’m not their mother! He then tells Jassi to find them, and pleads with her to do something for him (“haga algo por mi”). Jassi grabs Arman’s stress ball and gives it to him, and he’s furious (yes, this is a pattern with our beloved bello bobo) and he bounces it on the floor saying, why are you giving this to me, I don’t need it ! 
     

        
</post>

<date>05,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Arman tells Raj that Jassi would be the last woman he’d marry, because with so many beautiful women to pick from, why would he pick an ugly one. Román calls Jassi to see if her dad gave her permission to go out. Jassi asks her dad to let her go, but he tells her no and she runs to her room crying, complaining that she can’t go out, can’t get to know the world. Doña Babe tries to comfort her, and reminds her that Don Balwant has always been this way, making sure she went to a convent school, never letting her socialize much, with the exception of Nandu, whom he considers like a brother to Jassi. She reminds Jassi about how much she suffered when she fell in love with Juan Ramón, a classmate from the university. Babe plays interference and is able to convince Balwant to let Jassi go out. A happy Jassi calls Román to tell him she can go and that she’s waiting for them to go out.   Arman gets to Mallika’s apartment, where he finds a rather “kinky” set up, with Mallika in a black teddie, ropes, special lighting, etc. She tells him that he may be happy with his ugly secretary at work, but that at home she’s the woman for him. They reconcile for the umpteenth time. Román and his friends stand Jassi up, and she still hopes that they’ll come for her, but her dad tells her to go to bed because it’s very late and she needs to go to bed. She starts crying while her dad tries to comfort her after scolding her, and promises that over the weekend the whole family will go out to eat and a movie. Balwant tells Babe that they have to accept the fact that Jassi is going to be a spinster. Jassi starts writing in her diary about Arman and remembers when he told her that she’s the woman that he needs and especially his caress...   The next morning, Freddy asks for Jassi’s forgiveness for the prank he played on her. Jassi finds a picture of Arman in his office and keeps it. Arman tells Raj that he will marry Mallika, and tells him about Mallika’s behaviour the night before. Nandu asks Babe about Jassi’s outing with the neighborhood gang, but Babe tells him that they stood her up. Nandu is upset at the way they treated Jassi and tells Román to apologize to Jassi. Román and his gang make fun of him and hit him. Balwant goes to talk to Román and beats him up. Jassi suggests to Arman that he let her automate his schedule and address book and store it with passwords to prevent others from gaining access to it. Arman asks all the other executives for reports about their departments and that these reports be forwarded to Jassi. He asks her to put the reports together in folders and include her business plan, and a copy of the past year’s numbers. Jassi asks Maria for a recommendation of a good place to have lunch. She tells her to go to el Corrienzato. The Gang en mass is eating lunch there and Jassi sits by herself. Inés asks the others to invite Jassi to join them, but they say that even though they get called ugly, the new secretary is uglier and would further erode their standing.   Babe calls Jassi at work to let her know that Nandu and her dad had a fight with Román, and Jassi tells her Mom that she’s going to be late getting home because she has to prepare a report for the next day's Board Meeting where Arman will officially become Chairman. Pari overhears this conversation, who tells Mallika about it since she doesn't want Jassi to outshine her. Arman and Jassi work out how to handle his personal calendar to make sure that Mallika doesn't have access to it.   The Gang calls a 911 meeting since Maria is crying because one of her beaus broke up with her. Jassi works until late to surprise Arman with the report, and is on her way out the door of her cave, when Arman and Mallika walk into his office and are about to get romantic (very) when Jassi opens the door to leave. Jassi wants to make a good impression at the next days Board Meeting meeting, and wants to look extra nice (poor girl). Her dad and Nandu want to go with her to the office, but she tells them she wants to go by herself. She runs into Román and his gang, who start mocking her, but she gives them a piece of her mind. Everyone is ready to start the Board Meeting, and Jassi is in a hurry to finalize the report, and in her haste, runs into Aryan. She tells him that she's Arman's secretary and he wonders how she knows who he is. She says that she's seen him in business and society magazines, his response is that Arman is wasting money having two secretaries. Jassi is on her way to deliver the reports, but Mallika tells her to give them to her and go ahead to lunch and to just goon to lunch, that Pari can deliver them. Jassi overhears Pari deliver the reports with the implication that she prepared them. Jassi is furious when Mr. Suri praises Pari for such a good report. Aryan argues with Arman because he has two secretaries, and says that if Pari can do such a good job with reports, plus display an “image,” then why have “the other one,” is it because she's pretty? They all make fun of Jassi. 
     

        
</post>

<date>13,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Arman grabs a strand of Jassi’s hair and leads her to her office as if she were a puppet, and when she tries to talk he tells her to , and to stop limping, or is she making fun of him… When poor Jassi goes into her office, Arman does one of his “que cruz Dios mío, que cruz”. Jassi calls the cafeteria to ask for a super double cup of coffee, black, no sugar, and when they ask her if she’s the cute blonde secretary, she says no, that she’s the one in the cave, “yo soy Jassi, Jassi.” Balwant calls Jassi to ask her if she was able to finish the project that she and Nandu were working on, and he hears Arman yelling at Jassi, which bothers him to no end and he runs off to go confront Arman, because he's not going to let anyone treat his daughter that way. Raj gets to work and Arman reads him the riot act, and also tears into Pari, especially after she tells him that she didn’t do the business plan. Arman decides that he’s going to have to put it together himself. Jassi repeatedly tries to talk to Arman to give him the business plan she and Nandu put together, but he won’t let her, and keeps treating her like dirt — he’s just rude, rude, rude.   Balwant gets to Gulmohur and asks to speak to Arman, but Jassi intercepts him and says that he’s actually looking for her, and convinces him to please go home.   Mallika, surprise, surprise, has another fight with Arman, complaining about his foul mood, and starts complaining about Jassi again, to which Arman answers that he’ll get rid of her to make Mallika happy. Maria notices that Jassi is limping and calls a 911 so that Gang can tend to her leg. Mallika and Pari are pleased beyond words at the news that Jassi is going to be history soon. When Jassi gets back to her office, Arman fires her and tells her to collect her things and go. She goes into her office, crying, and after collecting her things she stops by to tell Arman why late. He again doesn’t let her explain, and in a terribly rude way tells her to get out. However, Jassi stands her ground and tells him that shell just give him the reason why she was late. Arman reads the business plan and is overjoyed. Raj comes into Arman’s office to ask if Hess ready to go to lunch and Arman says they're not anywhere because they have to work on the business plan. Raj asks him where it came from and Arman tells him that Jassi put it together, and asks her to give him another copy and to just go ahead and go to lunch, after which she should come back to brief them about the plan. She tells him that he fired her, and he apologizes (as much as Armandito can do at this time, no getting down on his knees and crying for him right now), and asks her to stay.   Jassi goes out to lunch with Gang, but before leaving they witness a fight between el Cheque and Sofía, who later tells Jassi how someone stole her husband at the supermarket! Gang asks Jassi why Arman is in such a bad mood, and she tells them about what happened with Pari — that she didn’t put the report together and was late on top of that. Pari tells Mallika that she went to bed with Raj and that she’s sure he’s going to marry her (yeah, dream ON patico!). When Jassi gets back from lunch, she finds a “new” Arman who treats her in a civilized manner and congratulates her for the business plan she put together. Mallika and Pari (another pattern we’ll see repeated) are astonished to see Jassi is still there, and ask Arman what happened with firing her. He tells them that Jassi took care of the business plan, and tells them that Jassi is pretty much running things in his office and pretty much shoos them out of the office because he has to work with Jassi. Jassi tells Arman and Raj what was wrong with their proposal and that she can work out things to enable them to meet their goals (as we hear the bells tolling a song of gloom and doom! RUN, Jassi, RUN!!!).   Arman asks Jassi once again about the report that Pari presented to the Board Meeting the day before. She responds that he would know that Pari did it once he read Pari’s business plan, which means that Pari didn’t do it. Arman tells Raj that he figures that Mallika played a role in helping Pari pass the report as hers, because there’s no other way that it could have gotten into Pari’s hands. Raj asks Arman about what he plans to do, and Arman says that Jassi is in charge now. Aryan arrives at Gulmohur and Gulati (VPFinance) tells him that Arman’s business plan is not well presented and that this will cause it to fail. Aryan goes into Jassi’s office and finds her asleep, and she apologizes, and he tells her that he wants to confirm an appointment for the next day. Raj and Arman arrive and ask Jassi for the report, to which she says that she’s somewhat behind because she’s had no sleep. Arman tells her to go home and they’ll get together first thing the next day. Maria asks Jassi to give her glasses to Freddy so he can fix them. Freddy starts playing with the glasses. Arman arrives from the elevator and scolds Freddy for playing with the glasses, and warns him not to break them because those glasses are very important to Gulmohur. 
     

        
</post>

<date>23,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Pari agrees to spy for Aryan in exchange for his keeping quiet about her role in damaging Jassi’s PC. Raj and Arman close the deal with Lavina, buying lower quality fabrics and are told by the Lavina reps (Diana and Santanu ) that they can also buy other supplies from them. Santanu, who handles Gulmohur’s account, notices that Jassi has Arman’s complete confidence and asks her if she is the one that reviews the contracts before Arman signs them. Arman hatches a plan with Raj to be able to meet Mandira Vázquez and starts flirting with her. But, his reputation has preceded him and she knows who he is and that he’s engaged to Mallika. Santanu gives Jassi the samples for the other supplies and asks her to review them and tells her that they can also buy these from Lavina and that he will call her the next day to maybe get together for coffee. Jassi tells Arman that everything is ready for signing the contract and since he is flirting with Mandira, he gets upset with her and acts in his usual rude way. Jassi calls home to tell her parents that she is on her way and Balwant gives her the third degree because it’s so late. He asks if Arman is bringing her home and she says yes. After the contract is signed, Jassi wants to talk to Arman, to ask if he needs her to stay, but again he’s trying to woo Mandira and tells Jassi to just go. Mallika calls Arman on his cellular and asks him why he isn’t home yet. He decides to play it safe and goes home.   In his car, Arman is moaning about how he had to let Mandira get away, that Raj is right, that he can’t get involved with women from the fashion world, he needs to get involved with unknown women and starts asking himself where he could find such a woman… At that very moment he notices Jassi walking on the sidewalk down this dark and desolate street. He stops his car and asks her why she’s there by herself and she tells him that she was trying to catch a cab and thought that she’d have better luck if she walked down to a main road. He offers her a ride, which she doesn’t want to accept, but he insists and she agrees.   When they get to Jassi’s house, Arman tells her that he needs her help to be able to make things work. Balwant scolds Jassi for getting home so late. Mallika questions Arman about his latest conquest, and he answers that it is Jassi, and Mallika can’t help but laugh since she was asking him about “another woman” not Jassi. Oh, Marcelita, reality bites!! Jassi writes in her diary about Arman, that she is happy that he is confiding his innermost thoughts to her, that he stands up for her against everyone, and that he needs her because of work, but she needs him because she loves him.   The next day, Balwant tells Bebe and Jassi that he’s on the verge of unemployment because his company went bankrupt. This is of great concern to Jassi and she tells Balwant that she’s getting a raise at work and will be able to take over the expenses at home. She also remembers, to herself, about the Lavina guy’s comments. Nandu asks Jassi to help him find a job at Gulmohur. Santanu calls Jassi to ask her out to lunch. Pari complains to Mallika about her financial woes. Arman asks Raj to be attentive with Pari, to make sure that she doesn’t start spying for Aryan.   Jassi goes with Arman to all the banks to register her signature as an authorized Gulmohur signature, in addition to Arman and Raj. Jassi tells Arman that she has a person in mind for Gulati’s job, her friend who is an economist, and he tells her that he can’t decide just yet, to just give him his résumé and he’ll let her know later. The Gang ask Jassi about the previous night’s cocktail party, and they want to know if he noticed how nice she looked, but she tells them he paid no attention to her. Jassi tells them that she has other plans for lunch and can’t go with them. They ask her with whom, but Jassi says nothing. Arman tells Mallika and Maddy that he wants Mandira to model in the next launching, which makes Mallika jealous, since Arman mentioned that he’d seen her at the cocktail party the night before.   Pari sees when Santanu picks Jassi up to go to lunch. Arman tells Mallika that he, Raj, and Mallika will travel to the Hong Kong and that Jassi will be left in charge while they’re away. Maddy and Mallika are completely opposed to this idea. Santanu asks Jassi if anyone knows that she’s going out to lunch with him and she says no, but that she also wants to know why he is being so mysterious. He tells her that since she has so much influence with Arman, he needs her help to get him to buy the rest of the supplies from Lavina, and that if this happens she’ll get a commission of 5% amounting to Rs.30,00,000. She tells him that this is unethical, that she doesn’t agree, and that she’s not going to risk her job for it. Santanu tells her to think about it because he could give her a 10% discount on the sale. Jassi leaves the restaurant very preoccupied.   Berta and Sofia subject Jassi to an interrogation about her lunch date, and Jassi is still tight-lipped, and they ask her if she had lunch with Nandu, her platonic love, because they are eager to meet him. Sofia asks Jassi if they’ve given her a pay raise now that she’s assistant to the Chairman, and when Jassi says they haven’t, Sofia tells her to talk to Arman. Jassi says she wouldn’t dare. Bebe calls Jassi and tells her that her dad’s situation is pretty bad at work.   Arman, Raj, and Jassi are meeting to figure out the expenses for the new launching, and they’re cutting costs. They ask Jassi for copies of the supply samples and Jassi adds Lavina’s proposal to the pile, which takes Arman by surprise. She tells him that Santanu gave her the samples and offered them a 10% discount. Arman asks to cut corners even more, but his friend asks him not to do it because the cheaper materials are really low quality. But Arman only wants to lower costs so he can meet his goals and doesn’t listen to Raj’s advice. Jassi has to do an analysis of the proposed expenses and has to select the best provider. She mentions San Remo and Lavina and reminds them about Santanu’s offer of a discount, so Arman tells her to contact Lavina to negotiate the sale.   Aryan meets with Pari at her apartment, where she tells him that Arman went to all the banks with Jassi, and tells him that while Arman is out of town on business, Jassi is going to be at the helm of Gulmohur. And also tells him that she saw Jassi with Santanu, adding that this was very suspicious. Aryan tells Pari that he doesn’t care about Jassi’s whereabouts, he wants to know what Arman is up to. But Pari has planted the seed of doubt, so Aryan talks with Gulati to ask about who is well known for offering bribes and asks him to find out if Jassi is being paid under the table by Lavina. Aryan and Pari go to bed, after which he just leaves her and she feels used.   Jassi gets home and is very worried to find her dad drunk and sad, since he is definitely going to be laid off. Jassi tells Nandu about not being able to get him a job at Gulmohur and also to please not show up there because she told her friends that she was in love with him. He is surprised to hear this and asks her when this happened. Jassi tells him not to be an idiot, that she is not in love with him, she’s just using him as an excuse since her co-workers are either married or dating. And that he also can’t show up because she’s described him to them as tall, strong, a real Casanova, with money and power. Jassi tells Nandu about the bribe offer, which she says would be her salvation. She also tells him that Lavina is offering the best prices, that there’s nothing underhanded about their offer. Nandu advises her against taking the bribe. Raj offers to give Maria a ride home, but they end up at a hotel where they sleep together. Jassi confides in her diary that she could accept the bribe without feeling guilty because she knows her family needs the money, but she also feels that doing this would be to betray Arman, but on the other hand she needs to help her dad and it hurts her to see him suffer. So she has to decide between being loyal to her boss or helping her father. She decides to help her dad. She dreams with Arman and is about to kiss him when her mother wakes her from her dream.   Arman asks Jassi to get him in touch with Lavina so they can close the deal. Gulati visits Santanu and gets him to talk about the dealings with Gulmohur. Veeru gets upset when he finds out that Maria never made it home the night before and especially when he realizes that she spent the night with Raj Calderón. Arman asks Raj about why he is late getting to work and Raj tells him about his evening with the receptionist. And, he tells Arman that maybe he should go out with Jassi, but they both decide this isn’t even possible because Jassi is so ugly.   Raj, Arman, and Jassi meet with Lavina to close the deal, and Diana tells Arman that she’s pleased that they’ve decided to buy everything from them. He says that they should thank Jassi since she’s the one that included them in the group of bids. Jassi is obviously uncomfortable, but Santanu and Diana thank her for her help.   Arman is worried that the new line won’t be a success and he tells Raj that they need to establish a phantom company with which to do all their business dealings, and which could put a lien on them prior to the banks doing so. And, that since this would entail a complete take over of Gulmohur, they need to have someone running the company who is completely and absolutely loyal. Arman immediately thinks of Jassi. Santanu calls Jassi and tells her that the business deal will net her Rs.30 lakhs and that he needs to find out how he can get the money to her. She tells him that she’ll call him later. Gulati calls Santanu from Aryan’s office and tapes the conversation, during which Santanu tells him that thanks to Jassi the deal with Gulmohur came through and that he’s going to give Jassi a commission for her assistance.   Jassi goes to lunch with Gang and they are talking about how Maria has landed a rich boyfriend, and they say that it’s obvious that she will be the only one who will be able to climb out of poverty. Maria tells them that the only one will actually be Jassi, since she’s the one with the degrees, with the boss who thinks she walks on water. Sofía tells them that Jassi has a boss that won’t even give her a pay raise and that Jassi will never have that kind of money, to which Jassi responds… who knows what could happen? Jassi remembers her conversation with Santanu and starts to dream about what she would do if she had a lot of money (if I were a rich gal…).   Jassi is still at Office Cafe with Gang and is dreaming about what she’ll do with the money from the Lavina deal. We see her arriving at Gulmohur in a chauffeur (Veeru) driven Mercedes Benz. She is dressed in a Chanel-type outfit in black and white, with a ridiculous hat and huge Bette Davis-like sunglasses. She invites the Gang to lunch at the club and they all pile into the Mercedes like in some old movie where you could just fit tons of people into a car with no problem. They have lunch at the club, and are joined by Arman and Raj, who are fawning all over Jassi. After lunch, Arman and Jassi take a stroll through the club’s grounds, and in the distance we see the Gang and Raj actually FROLICKING, with Raj doing a cartwheel! Jassi introduces her parents and Nandu to Arman, telling Arman that Nandu and Balwant run a business that does the accounting for large corporations. Bebe is wearing a tennis outfit, while Nandu and Balwant are dressed to the nines in golf outfits. Arman tells Jassi that he’d like to take her out to dinner that evening, but as usual, she wakes up and realizes it’s all ONLY A DREAM! (especially the part when Mallika and Maddy are actually civil to her). 
     

        
</post>

<date>22,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Arman tells everyone that the report is ready and that the meeting will take place after all. Aryan is upset because he won’t have the chance to do the audit he planned to do. The Gang helps Jassi to put everything together for the meeting, and kind of fix her up so she’ll look better at the meeting. They rev her up for her big moment with words of encouragement. As Jassi starts her presentation, Mallika gives her one of those “if looks could kill” looks and keeps staring at her to make her nervous. But Jassi is cool as a cucumber and tells everyone that Arman’s first two months at the helm of Gulmohur have been successful and stable. Sandra, who lost an earring during her fight with PC guy, goes back to his office and notices that he is hiding something and tells the Gang about her suspicions. Since they know that Jassi told him not to touch anything, they go back to try to get the papers away from him. Aryan reviews Jassi’s reports and asks her questions to try to trip her, which he fails miserably at because Jassi is able to answer everyone of his inquiries and comes out of the inquisition smelling fresh as a rose. The Gang want to give Jassi the copies that they took away from PC guy, before he realizes, but since Jassi is still with the Board Meeting, they elect Berta to deliver the reports to her. Pari makes fun of the Gang because she says none of them are dressed appropriately to go into the Board meeting. The PC guy realizes that the Gang took the reports he’d printed out.   Mr. Suri congratulates Jassi for her report and presentation, and Aryan says that she should be the Chairman (another BIG clue here!). Arman tells the Board Meeting that Jassi will be promoted to assistant to the Chairman and Robert agrees to this. He says that the next meeting will be held in September, right before Arman and Mallika’s wedding. The Gang fills Jassi in on the latest developments and give her the reports. As the Board members are leaving the room, Mr. Suri congratulates Jassi on her new position which makes Pari furious. Jassi tells Arman about the PC guy’s actions and the fact that the Gang took them away from him.   Jassi and Arman go to see the PC guy and Jassi tells Arman that the guy has copies of all her files. Arman pressures the PC guy to tell him why he’s so interested in those files. He threatens him with dire consequences if he doesn’t get the whole truth out, about who’s behind the whole thing. The PC guy admits that Gulati told him to do it. Arman fires the PC guy and tells Wilson to check him over to make sure he’s not taking anything he shouldn’t be taking. Gulati tells Aryan that Arman knows that they messed up Jassi’s computer, and Aryan reminds him that he wants his name out of it. Arman asks Gulati about the problem with Jassi’s PC, and he says it is because Jassi is trying to take away his job and he wanted her to look bad with the Board Meeting. Arman asks if Aryan is involved and also for the name of the person who actually messed up Jassi’s computer. Gulati doesn’t say anything and Arman fires him. Since the Board members were still taking care of some business at Gulmohur, Arman gets them together again and asks Jassi to join them. He tells everyone about Gulati’s actions and his plot against Jassi.   Aryan says that they should sue Gulati, and that he will make sure that someone is selected to replace Gulati. Arman says that he’s not going to hire anyone who isn’t his own choice. He stands up for Jassi in front of everyone and says that he wants to name her Financial VP, but the Board is dead set against this. He says that then she will be his assistant but that at the next Board meeting the issue will be addressed again. Aryan tells Pari that he knows that she’s the one that messed up Jassi’s computer and tells her that he’ll be waiting for her in his office. Arman congratulates Jassi for everything she did at the Board Meeting, gives her a big hug, thanks her for all her help, and tells her that he’s giving her a raise. Jassi tells the Gang about her promotion. Arman tells Raj that he’s sure of Pari’s role in the situation with Jassi’s PC. Sofia and Berta tell Jassi that the only person who had been around her office had been Pari, who spent quite some time there, which must mean she is the one who messed up her PC. Arman says that he’s worried about Aryan and Pari’s strange relationships, and asks Raj to take care of her and keep dating her. Mallika tells Pari that Jassi keeps getting more powerful, especially now that Arman had said that he wants her as Financial VP. Jassi tells Raj and Arman that it is impossible to reach the goals they’ve set for the company.   Jassi tells Arman and Raj that to be able to reach their goals, they need to lower the quality of the fabrics used for the designs. That they have to reduce costs to be able to increase production, but that even doing that it isn’t sure that they’ll be able to meet their goals without putting the company at risk. Jassi tells Arman that it is best if he talks to the Board Meeting and face them by telling them that he won’t be able to meet his goals. He’s against giving up the chairmanship, and with Raj’s support decides to put it all on the line. That night, Arman asks Jassi to join him to close a deal with RagTela because he wants her to review the contract prior to signing it. She tells the Gang that she is going to a cocktail party with her boss and asks their help to look better. She also calls home to say that she’s going to be late because of a business meting. In the bathroom, the Gang congratulates Jassi and joke that Arman is going to fall for her, since he gives her rides and takes to cocktail parties, something he never did with his old secretary. Inesita gets an outfit from Maddy’s atelier and they fix Jassi up.   As soon as Arman sees her he tells her that she looks “divina,” and Raj and Arman tell her she looks great. However, as we all suspected, this is only one of Jassi’s daydreams. The cruel reality is that Arman doesn’t pay attention to how she looks and just tells her to get ready to go. Since Jassi isn’t used to wearing high heels, she runs into Arman a few times, and to avoid falling holds on to him, which makes him mad. Maria flirts with Raj and when they say good night, Raj kisses her on the lips.   At the cocktail party, they run into Mandira , and Arman doesn’t miss the chance to flirt with her, leaving Jassi alone, who again stumbles and falls, much to Arman’s chagrin. Pari goes to Aryan’s office, where he treats her like dirt and asks her for sex in exchange for not letting everyone know what she did to Jassi’s computer, since this would make her look bad to the Mendozas and Valencias. He also tells her that he needs her to spy on Arman. Pari is offended by his request.
     

        
</post>

<date>19,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      After work, Jassi is waiting for her bus to go home when Arman comes out of the garage in his car and offers to give her a ride home. He tells her that since she’s his assistant, she needs to get a car, and she tells him that with her salary she can’t afford to get a car. He tells her that from now on he’s going to take her home every night. He turns on the radio and the song just happens to be a favorite of both of theirs, which makes Arman somewhat amorous and he invites Jassi to go listen to a jazz band at a favorite watering hole. He says that they’re always talking about work and he’d like to get to know her better. Jassi reminds him that she has to finish the report, but Arman says that they can go out, and then go to his apartment and finish the report together. He holds her hand and tells her that he’s very happy to have her with him. Just at that moment someone yells out Arman’s name, and it’s one of the models who’s leaving Gulmohur – time to wake up from your daydream dear Jassi! The model asks Arman for a ride, he starts his car, which he stops when he sees Jassi to tell her to remember to do the report. When she gets home she tells her mother and Nandu that Arman will name her his assistant at a meeting the next morning.   Mallika complains to Mrs. Suri and Mr. Suri about all the responsibility that Arman is giving Jassi. Nandu tells Jassi that she should be proud of all the responsibility that Arman is entrusting her with when she’s only a secretary. Nandu tells Jassi that she should also be proud that with all the women lusting after Arman, she’s the one that’s making Mallika nervous. At the same time, Mrs. Suri is telling Mallika that she can’t believe that she’s fighting with Arman over a girl as ugly as Jassi, because she just can’t fathom that anything could be going on between them. Mallika laughs since of course Jassi is so ugly, and Arman has much better taste in women than that. Jassi tells Nandu about having to doctor the report to the Board Meeting, and he tells her that she’s treading on dangerous ground and someone can find out what she’s doing. She tells him that all the information is password protected on her computer and that only a real computer genius could access the information. As Jassi is saying this, Gulati is in her office with Gulmohur’s computer guy trying to access said password-protected files. Computer guy tells Gulati that the files are inaccessible. Pari asks Raj to promote her to his assistant AND that he also make their personal relationship known. Raj tells her that this is not the appropriate moment for either of her requests. Jassi tells Nandu that it looks like Pari and Raj are an item, and that if Nandu aspires to anything with someone like Pari, he’s going to need a lot of money for her to notice him!   The next morning, Jassi is running late and has another of her encounters with Wilson, who tells her that he’s going to report her late and is going to get in trouble. To which Jassi, way to go Jassi!, tells him that she’s just going to go back home and that he can tell Arman where she is and that if he needs the report she prepared he can come get it. Wilson begs her to stay because this could lead to Arman firing him, and even gets down on his knees to beg her to stay. Pari arrives and makes fun of Wilson, and Jassi asks him how come he’s not going to report Pari as arriving late.   Gulati and Pari agree to mess up Jassi’s PC so she won’t be able to make her report to the Board. To do this they get her out of her office using some lame excuse and Pari does the deed.   Arman talks to Maddy and Mallika to ask them to not mention the issue of the fabric being used for the new designs. Mallika talks to Arman about his relationship with Jassi, saying that it is negatively affecting theirs because for him Jassi is perfect. When Jassi goes back to her office and turns on her PC, she realizes that she can’t access any of her files. Arman is all over Jassi to get her to fix the problem and scolds her for not keeping backup diskettes with the information. They call the PC guy to fix the computer, but he says that he has to take it with him to look at it. Arman goes on one of his famous tirades and yells at Jassi. She starts yelling back, telling him that he’s making her nervous with all the yelling. He’s taken aback by Jassi’s reaction and tells her to follow the PC guy and stay with him until the PC is fixed.   Everyone is gathered at the Board room and Arman tells them that they can’t have the meeting because the report is in Jassi’s damaged computer. Gulati tells Aryan that he took care of screwing up Jassi’s computer (he calls her “la doble fea,” or the “double ugly” kind of the opposite of triple-papito!). Aryan is not very happy about this and tells Gulati that he doesn’t want his name associated with it. The PC guy tells Jassi to cancel the meeting because he’s not going to be able to get the PC fixed just then and asks her for her passwords. Before the Board members, he says that the PC broke down because it was being misused, and Jassi tells him that this is impossible because she’s an experienced computer user. Aryan scolds Jassi for her failure to have back-up copies of the files and she is left looking like a fool in front of everyone. Aryan is about to leave, but Mrs. Suri asks him to stay for lunch. Mr. Suri tells Arman to give up on trying to promote “la feita” (“the little ugly one”) and to just let Pari take care of the meeting. Arman says that he won’t promote Jassi after all. Jassi is in her office and Arman arrives to get a video and again yells at her. She starts to cry and he asks her not to cry because she’s making HIM feel bad (hello! Mr. Selfish Jerk!!). When the Gang finds out what happened to Jassi, they go to her office to try to cheer her up and she tells them the whole story. Maria calls a friend who’s a computer guru and has Jassi talk to him. He tells her that this is not a big problem and that he can get it fixed in an hour.   In the meantime, Mr. Suri calls a “confidence vote” on Arman’s behalf and says that the next board meeting will be held in two months. Aryan says that he wants to audit the company because they can’t let so much time pass without knowing how the company is running. Arman is opposed to this, but they tell him that this is his fault for not having the report ready and he has to acquiesce.   After lunch, the Board members go to Maddy’s to see the designs. The Gang asks the PC guy to give them back Jassi’s computer so that someone else who can actually fix it quickly can take a look at it. He refuses, but Jassi talks to Arman to let him know what’s going on. The Gang goes at it with the PC guy, including Sandra who hits him! Arman tells Mr. PC guy that he has 15 minutes to straighten things out, while the Gang stands guard because they don’t trust him. He gives Jassi the report and the Gang wants to get the PC away from Mr. PC guy, who starts roaming through the computer to find out what secrets they’re guarding so closely. Jassi tells Arman that everything will be ready for the report in 15 minutes, and he tells her that she’s the only one who can make the presentation to the Board Meeting because she’s the only one who’s familiar with the information. He has to give her a pep talk to convince her, and she agrees. She also tells him that she has to get her computer away from the PC guy. Gulati asks PC guy to make him copies of the reports from Jassi’s computer.  
     

        
</post>

<date>02,November,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Jassi gets a call from Santanu, who tells her that the shipment with the supplies is on its way and that he still needs to know how to get the money to her. Jassi tells him that they’ll talk in 10 minutes. She then calls her dad and tells him what’s going on with Lavina. Her father is furious that she’d even consider taking a bribe to help him. Jassi tells him that this is exactly what she needed to hear from him, and that she’s at peace and will not take the bribe.   Aryan gets to Gulmohur ready to rumble with Arman to give him the news about the bribe. Arman is about to talk to Arman when Jassi asks if they can talk in private about something very urgent. She tells him about Lavina’s bribe. Mallika walks in on them and starts asking Arman why he’s making Aryan wait, and Arman tells Mallika about the bribe offer. Aryan joins them (Jassi is not there at this time) and plays the tape that Gulati made of his conversation with Santanu. Jassi is about to walk back into the room and overhears the tape. Mallika tells Aryan that they already know about the bribe from Jassi. Arman argues with Aryan about the tape, and asks why he’s so intent on getting Jassi in trouble. He defends her and reminds Aryan that Gulati DID accept bribes all the time. Mallika and Aryan leave the room obviously annoyed with Arman’s reaction and defense of Jassi.   Arman goes back to his office and finds Jassi who tells him that she overheard the argument and feels terrible and wants to resign. Arman gets upset with her and tells her that she did the right thing by letting him know ahead of time about the bribe and that she can’t resign just when he needs her the most, that everything is okay. Jassi tells him that she should have told him about it as soon as she knew of the bribe and that she actually was quite tempted to accept the bribe because of the problems at home. That she was about to betray him and her family, and that this is why she needs to resign. Arman tells her that he trusts her implicitly and that she is a human being that has weak moments like everyone else. That he’s never expected her to be a perfect woman, but just a human being who faces her weaknesses and is able to make the right decision. And that because of this he cannot accept her resignation. He hugs her and helps her dry her tears. Aryan tells Mallika that Arman stands up for Jassi more than he does for Mallika herself. And that if things go on this way, Jassi is going to end up as Chairman of Gulmohur (ding, ding, ding, ding — and Aryan wins the GRAND PRIZE!). Raj tells Arman that Jassi may be as ugly as hell, but that she’s an exceptional woman for having fessed up about the bribe and for having refused to be bribed. Arman tells him that Jassi’s behaviour has shown him that she is the right person to run the business they have to establish to save Gulmohur.   Mallika tells Arman how upset she is that he doesn’t count on her when he’s making business decisions, but he relies on “Jassi” for everything. Arman calls Diana at Lavina and scolds her for having tried to bribe Jassi. He demands that they still give Gulmohur the 5% rebate that was part of the bribe, making the discount 15%. Raj tells Arman that Jassi is definitely a woman in love because to not only have rejected the bribe and missed the opportunity to have all that money, but also have confessed that she had been bribed, is not only a sign of loyalty but of love. Arman tells Raj that she has principles, which both of them lost long ago, and also tells Raj that Jassi didn’t take the bribe even though her family is going through financial straits. Arman goes to Jassi’s office and asks her why she hadn’t reminded him to give her a salary increase. She tells him that she felt bad about reminding him. He tells her that she’s getting a raise, which makes her very happy. He then puts his hands on her shoulders and thanks her for all her help and tells her how important she is to him. The door to Jassi’s office opens and Raj arrives with Vasundhra.   Vasundhra greets Jassi very affectionately. They leave Jassi’s office, and when they close the door Raj and Arman make some snide remark about Jassi (hello, what’s WRONG with Arman!?), and Vasundhra tells them not to mock Jassi. Arman tells Vasundhra that they’ve called her to hire her to do the public relations for the first launch under his chairmanship and they go to Maddy’s lair to look at the designs. Raj tries his best to flirt with Vasundhra, who pretty much blows him off and tells him that after two divorces she’s had enough with men, although she tells him that she’s dating someone else. Maddy greets Vasundhra in his usually effusive manner and is overjoyed to hear that they’ll be working together.   Arman asks Jassi to establish a new company, which will be in her name only. She is taken completely by surprise and thinks that Arman is pulling her leg. He tells her that he needs this phantom company to be able to deal with any problems that come up. The capital for the company will be Rs.30,00,000 . Mallika complains to Mrs. Suri and Mr. Suri about Arman’s behaviour with Jassi. Mr. Suri stands up for Jassi, saying that she’s a good person. Mallika keeps complaining, saying that if things keep going the way they are, she wouldn’t be surprised (ha, ha, ha!) if Jassi ended up running the company as Chairman, since she has gone up in the company by leaps and bounds. Mrs. Suri says that only a Suri or a Valencia can fill the chairmanship and that “that woman” could only become Chairman if she took or bought the company from them (no, she’s going to be GIVEN the company!). Raj confirms with Arman that the capital for the new company is the bribe money from Lavina. Arman tells him that he doesn’t want Jassi to know where the money is coming from. Arman finally convinces Jassi to set up the new company and tells her that she cannot mention it to her family, to his family, or to Mallika and Aryan. He also gives her free rein to run the business (investments) as she sees fit.   Vasundhra wants to get detailed descriptions of Maddy’s designs to be able to draft press releases. Arman asks her to please not make any mention of the fabric being used for the designs because they are of lower quality than usual. Vasundhra asks Arman to get Jassi out of her cave-like office. Arman tells Manchanda that he needs to set up Gulati’s old office for Jassi’s use. However, Jassi asks Arman to let her stay in her office because she wants to be near him (no kidding!), if he doesn’t mind. Arman tells her that he doesn’t mind at all and that if that’s what she wants, he’d rather have her near because he needs her, which makes Jassi very happy. When Jassi gets home, she tells her parents about her pay raise. Later in her bedroom, she tells Nandu about the new company.  
     

        
</post>

<date>14,November,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Jassi hires Nandu to help her run the new company, and he gladly accepts. Jassi tells him that her boss trusts her completely and talks about Arman in a very loving way. Nandu tells Jassi that it’s obvious that the new company’s capital is coming from the bribe money and to be careful of her boss. He also notices that Jassi is obviously in love with Arman. Pari is harping on Raj about moving in together. Raj asks her for a month to think about it, which he does to keep Pari happy – he needs to keep her away from Aryan, although he has no intention of moving in with her.   A few days later at Gulmohur…   It’s the day of the launch and Arman is his usual out-of-control self, screaming at everyone, and getting even more upset because Jassi is nowhere to be found. He asks everyone he sees whether they know Jassi’s whereabouts, but no one does. He is very nervous because this is his first launch as Chairman and he wants to make sure that everything goes well. Arman tells Raj that he wants the models to wear the clothes that were made with the LaBela fabrics because he doesn’t want to lie to the buyers (Arman is being, gulp, HONEST?). So, they have to make sure the models don’t wear the one-of-a-kind outfits made by Maddy, but the clothes made in the production line.   In the meantime, Jassi and Nandu are on their way to the Chamber of Commerce to register the new company, called TerraModa, and also go to the Bank, where Jassi meets with her old boss, and open an account for TerraModa. Jassi arrives at Gulmohur and everyone warns her that Arman is looking for her and is fit to be tied. When she goes into Arman’s office he scolds her for being late but she answers back that he’d given her permission to be late since she had to take care of setting up TerraModa. Arman calms down and asks Jassi to please help him to make sure everything is set for the launching.   The models are in the show room and Veeru is doing his “I’m an executive” act, and starts to model in his typically Veeru Stewart Contreras way. Jassi, Sofía, and Berta are watching him and are amused by his antics. However, Maddy, Arman, Raj and Vasundhra’s arrival puts a damper on Veeru’s performance. Jassi asks Arman for permission to start investing TerraModa’s capital and he tells her to do with it as she sees fit. Manchanda asks Arman about what is expected of him while Arman, Raj, and Mallika are out of town for two weeks – obviously he thinks he’s going to be in charge – but Arman tells him that Jassi’s the only one he will let fill in while he’s not there.   Arman is very upset and has an argument with Maddy. Mallika asks Vasundhra to help Arman relax and they go to his office where Vasundhra gives him a massage. Since Jassi can’t see what they’re doing, only what Arman is saying, she thinks the worst and thinks that there’s something going on between Arman and Vasundhra. When she leaves her office she realizes that it’s only Vasundhra giving Arman a massage. Inesita shows Maddy the designs that the models are going to wear and when he realizes that these are the clothes made with the inferior fabrics, he says that he won’t let the show go on. The Gang tells Jassi that they want to go out to celebrate her new position and salary increase, as well as the fact that she’ll be running Gulmohur during Arman’s absence. Arman asks Jassi to stay until the fashion show is over.   Maddy tells the models that there will not be a show, and Mallika asks him why. He tells her about the fabrics and they call Arman, with whom they have an argument. Arman orders Maddy to begin the fashion show, telling him that he’s the Chairman of Gulmohur and he gives the orders – they almost come to blows over this. Maddy refuses to go out on the catwalk and be associated with the inferior quality fabrics. Inesita tells Arman that it would be a mistake to go ahead with the fashion show without Maddy, and Arman’s response is to yell at her and order her to get the models ready. Mallika asks Maddy to please participate, and after much pleading she convinces him. Back in his office, Arman is a nervous wreck and Jassi cheers him up – she daydreams that she’s able to hug him and tell him how she’s always going to back him up, and how much she loves him, and he tells her that her hug makes everything better, and thanks her for her support… Mallika’s knock on the door puts an end to the dream. 
     

        
</post>

<date>21,November,2003</date>
<post>


           
      The fashion show finally takes place. The Gang sneaks in to watch, but Mallika sees them and shoos them away. They sneak into Arman’s office and watch from there. Mr. Suri is not very happy because he can tell that the fabrics are not up to his standards. The Gang goes down to the reception area to wait for Jassi and Inesita so they can go out to celebrate Jassi’s new job, raise, and upcoming two weeks at the helm of Gulmohur. After the fashion show, a very important French buyer asks Vasundhra to see the designs up close, and when he feels the fabrics, he tells her that they’ll have a very hard time selling the collection because of the poor quality of the fabrics.   Mallika tells Arman that he must apologize to Maddy for the way he behaved before the fashion show. Arman refuses and says that Maddy had to do his job, and that if Maddy wants to quit, that’s fine with him – that there are plenty of good designers out there to pick from. He keeps attacking Maddy, who stands by his actions. Maddy tells Arman that he is going to go to the press and will tell them what happened. Mallika is so upset at Arman that she also quits and tells him to run Gulmohur however he pleases. The Gang is still waiting for Jassi and Inesita, when they see a very handsome gentleman arrive. They all start flirting with him and he very kindly tells them how nice they all look. They’re just overwhelmed by this guy! However, at that very moment, the elevator opens and Maddy exits to burst their bubble – this hunk of a man is none other than Rolando, Maddy’s “checito su merced.”   Vasundhra tells Arman about the French buyer’s comments and tells him how hard it’s going to be to be able to sell the new collection. She also advises him that this is not the time to be on Maddy’s bad side because he’s going to need him. Jassi asks her dad for permission to go out with her friends, explaining that she won’t be able to do it afterwards because she’ll be running Gulmohur in Arman’s absence. Mr. Suri goes to Arman to ask him about his poor judgment with the fabrics, telling him that this is very risky behaviour. But, he tells him that he is confident that things will turn out okay and that he’s leaving for Hong Kong and won’t be back until September’s Board of Directors meeting and of course Arman’s wedding to Mallika. Arman apologizes to Inesita for yelling at her.   The Gang tells Inesita and Jassi about Maddy’s beau. Veeru realizes that the Gang is going out to party and wants to go with them, but they don’t let him. Vasundhra talks to Raj and Arman and convinces Arman to try to mend fences with Maddy, telling him that Maddy is a great designer and he needs him on his side, that this is not the time to have Maddy going to the press. She also advises him to make up with Mallika because she’s very good at what she does. Arman goes off to find Maddy since he’ll need to get things straightened out before he leaves on his trip. Mallika’s sister María Jassi tells Arman where he can find Maddy and he leaves. Jassi and the Gang get to the bar where they’re going to be celebrating. Jassi says that she has to go make a phone call and her friends start to kid her that she must be calling Nandu. She says that she has to call her dad to let him know where she is. She says that she doesn’t bother Nandu, who has a lot of dates already. Nandu is actually out with the neighborhood crew, who asked him to join them at a bar just to take advantage of him and have him pick up the tab. Jassi reaches her dad to let him know where she is and give him the phone number of the bar, but ends up having to give him the address of the place.   The Gang starts toasting Jassi and especially how this is going to make Pari feel. Arman gets to the place where Maddy is hanging out, which just so happens to be a gay bar. Armandito has to deal with men who are hitting on him, and even worse he runs into Miguel from Lavina, and is surprised to find out he’s gay (wonder what Miguel thinks about seeing Arman there!). Arman is getting just a tad nervous to be “surrounded” and wants to get out of there ASAP, but at that very moment he sees Maddy arrive. Arman tells Maddy that they need to talk, that they need to clear things up, because Arman is leaving the next day and that they just can’t leave things like that because Arman needs Maddy. To the unknowing ear, this exchange sounds like a lover’s quarrel and Arman has to actually chase Maddy down to the men’s room to make him listen to him. In the meantime, the Gang is pretty much getting wasted.   Arman chases Maddy all over the bar and finally gets him to listen to him. Gang is drunk and Sandra, Mariana and Maria start dancing, and force Berta, Sofía, and Inés to join them. Jassi, who’s very drunk by now stays put, but the Gang finally makes her stand up and dance. Jassi thinks that she’s looking sexy with her dancing, unfortunately, she’s not! The Gang finds out that el Cheque and Jenny are on the dance floor as well and Sofía starts yelling at him, saying that he’s out there spending the money he should be giving to his children. Jenny and el Cheque leave. The Gang tells Sofía to forget about el Cheque and find herself another man. The Gang starts flirting with a table of men, who ask Mariana, Sandra, and Maria to dance, and Berta gets up and starts dancing by herself. Sofía goes off to the bathroom crying, leaving Inesita and Jassi by themselves. Inesita, noticing her friends’ highly intoxicated state, asks Jassi to get everyone together so they can go home.   Arman, after talking and talking to Maddy is finally able to convince him to stay at Gulmohur, but has to agree to a bet that if the new collection fails he’ll have to dress up in a drag queen outfit and go out in public to a party with Maddy. If Maddy loses the bet, he’ll have to keep using the poor quality materials. They hug and the crowd applauds because they’ve “made up”!   The Gang, totally and completely bombed, goes to the bathroom where they find Sofía crying. Inesita is worried about her friends and has called Veeru to help her. Jassi goes to the bathroom and is feeling quite dizzy, splashes some cold water on her face, and faints since she’s not used to drinking. Veeru arrives and carries Jassi out of the bar. Jassi opens her eyes and says “don Arman” to which Veeru answers that she’s delirious. Jassi is dreaming that Arman is carrying her off and she almost faints again and wakes up as she hears her father yelling. Don Balwant is furious that Jassi is in such a state and has had to be carried out of the bar. Jassi denies that she’s drunk. Jassi asks her mother how they ended up at the bar (in pajamas!), since they knew that she had a ride to get home. The Gang and Veeru can’t help but laugh at the whole situation of Balwant going to pick up Jassi. Jassi gets home and her dad keeps at her. Finally, she’s in her room alone and starts writing in her diary about how she’s so in love with Arman and doesn’t know how she’ll be able to handle being apart from him for two weeks. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,November,2003</date>
<post>


           
      The next morning, on her way to Gulmohur…   Jassi tells Nandu about her night out with the girls and that this was the first time she’d ever been drunk and how her parents showed up in pajamas! The Gang has a major hangover and Veeru makes them a special potion to make them feel better. They all ask Jassi about her “Don Arman” comment after she fainted. Arman gets to Gulmohur and talks to Jassi because he wants to make sure that Jassi is ready and able to be at the helm of Gulmohur while he’s away. Jassi assures him that she is.   Arman tells everyone that he, Mallika, and Raj will be traveling to the Hong Kong and that Jassi will run Gulmohur in their absence. Maddy starts making fun of Jassi, and Mallika joins in by laughing at Maddy’s behavior. Pari asks for leave because she doesn’t want to be at Gulmohur while Jassi is running it. Mallika tells Arman that she’s going to take advantage of the trip to the US to buy stuff for their wedding, but he tells her that he doesn’t have time to worry about the details for the wedding and that he trusts her to take care of everything. Jassi is sad to hear that the plans for the wedding are going ahead. Arman tells Jassi that he’s leaving and that he’ll be in touch with her so she can update him about the goings on at Gulmohur. During this conversation Jassi has one of her daydreams and imagines that Arman hugs her and tells her that he doesn’t know how he’ll be able to spend so many days away from her. They’re about to kiss when the phone rings and Arman snaps her out of her daydream. He leaves without even saying goodbye.   Pari tells Mallika that after the trip, she and Raj are going to move in together since he told her that when he comes back they’ll settle their relationship. Maria goes to a hotel with Raj before he leaves on his trip and asks him to formalize their relationship. He tells her that he doesn’t plan to “settle” with anyone. The Gang is hanging around the lobby after lunch and this makes them late coming back to their desks. Pari makes a big deal out of their being late and tells Manchanda about it so he will take action against them. The Gang runs to Jassi to ask for her help, since she’s “boss” now. Jassi is in her office, staring at Arman’s screensaver on her PC (ha, ha, ha – how many people who are NOT Jassi have Shahrukh Khan's screensavers on their PCs?). Manchanda also goes to Jassi’s office to punish Gang, but Jassi tells him that they arrived early from lunch but that she gave them permission to hang around the lobby afterwards. Manchanda is all mad because he can’t do anything about the situation.  
     

        
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Days later…   Bindya holds on to Pari’s paycheck to teach her a lesson since Pari is always saying that she doesn’t need to work to live. Pari complains to Manchanda, who tells her that he can’t do anything about it, that she must go talk to Jassi. Pari goes to Jassi, who is preoccupied waiting for the sales reports and pays her no mind. Arman calls Jassi and she tells him to come home because of the problems with the sales reports. Maddy asks Sofia to draw up the contracts for the “fitting” models and he has selected some models who charge very high hourly fees. Sofia asks for Jassi’s approval, since Arman said that he didn’t want such expensive models hired. Jassi tells Sofia to tell Maddy that Arman’s orders are the law. Sofia tells Maddy, who goes to Jassi’s office with the models and Jassi reiterates that they can’t be hired. Maddy resigns, again, and he and the models make fun of Jassi. Pari also makes fun of Jassi, telling her that she’s “queen for one more day” and that her horse-drawn carriage is going to turn into a pumpkin pulled by mice.   That evening, at Jassi’s house.   Nandu tells Jassi that they’ve made quite a bit of profit in the stock market and that they’ve increased the seed capital for TerraModa. Balwant asks Jassi why she and Nandu are always on the Internet, and she tells him that they’ve been playing the stock market with Arman’s money, and that both of them are getting paid for it.   The next day at Gulmohur...   Yesterday’s models are waiting outside Gulmohur and when they see Jassi they mock her again. A bank manager is looking for Arman, and Pari takes the opportunity to flirt with him and tell him that she’s Arman’s assistant and that in his absence she’s running the company, and asks Sofia and Berta to get them some coffee and bring it to the board room. At that very moment, Jassi arrives and the bank manager recognizes her and asks if they can talk. Jassi asks Pari to get them some coffee (!) and to also get her the list of phone calls to return, which makes Pari absolutely furious. And, Jassi adds insult to injury by asking Sofia if Pari’s pay situation has been fixed, since she’s the Chairman’s beloved secretary. Jassi makes fun of Pari, telling her that as long as Arman is away she’s the boss and that the horse-drawn carriage hasn’t changed back to a pumpkin and mice, which makes Pari even madder. Jassi straightens things out with the bank manager.   Arman and Raj come back to Gulmohur. Jassi has placed some flowers and other things in Arman’s office, as a way to welcome him, but Arman hates them and tells her to get rid of them. She tells him about all the problems with the new collection. Arman asks Jassi for a loan from TerraModa, to be ready to protect themselves from the banks. Jassi calls Nandu to ask him to bring her TerraModa’s check book.   Pari complains to Arman about the way that Jassi treated her, especially treating her as if she were Jassi’s secretary, and also that she still hasn’t been paid. Arman gets mad at Pari for complaining to him and tells her that it was her duty to work with Jassi and support her. Pari complains that the only thing that she didn’t do was to fix her hair every morning, and Jassi (who’s in on the conversation) tells her that all she needed was Pari’s support since she couldn’t do everything by herself. And, that she also told Pari that if she couldn’t do it, the other secretaries were available to help. Pari keeps complaining, and Jassi, who’s standing where Raj and Arman can’t see her, starts making faces at Pari, pulling at her eyes, flattening her nose, and sticks her tongue out at Pari.   Arman talks to Maddy to resolve the problem of his resignation, and Maddy tells him that he will come back when Jassi is no longer running the business. Nandu comes to Gulmohur to give Jassi the checkbook and almost faints when he sees Pari walking out.  
     

        
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      The Gang is at lunch at Office Cafe, and are hatching a plan to get back at Pari. Berta says that she’s going to find a dress just like Pari’s because Pari is always making fun of how she dresses. They also talk about how close Pari is to getting Raj to move in with her, which drives Maria up the wall. Maria also decides to do something to get back at Pari. Arman asks Jassi to sign the check for TerraModa’s loan to Gulmohur. Arman tells Raj that the loan is to prevent any problems with the banks and to allow TerraModa to take over Gulmohur before the banks do.   Maria goes to Raj’s office and starts necking with him so that Pari will catch them in the act. This results in Raj firing Maria. She starts crying and the Gang scolds her for behaving in such a way. Pari is very upset and goes to ask for her check again since she plans to resign. Maddy comforts Pari when she tells him the story about Raj and Maria. Manchanda calls Maria to his office and tells her that she’s fired, but takes advantage of the situation to tell her that they should go out for a drink to see if he can do something to rectify her firing. Arman also scolds Raj for the problem with Maria. Jassi tells Maria that she’s going to talk to Arman about her to see if she can fix things. Aryan asks Manchanda if Pari has handed in her letter of resignation, since he asked her to resign because she is not going along with his demands to have sex with him and also spy for him. Manchanda tells Aryan about the problem between Maria and Pari.   Arman tells Raj to apologize to Pari since they have to prevent at all costs that Pari will spy for Aryan. Jassi asks Arman to help Maria, and tells him that by law Maria can sue them for unjustified termination. Arman asks Jassi if Maria has threatened with a suit, but Jassi tells him that she just wanted him to know what could happen. Manchanda asks Arman what’s going to happen with Maria and Arman tells him that all she’s going to receive is a verbal admonishment. But Manchanda relays the message as saying that it is up to him to decide what will happen with Maria’s future and that they’ll need to get together that evening to discuss it.   Maddy and the fitting models go to Arman’s office to arrange the contracts, but he tells them that he can only hire two of them. Arman asks Jassi to ask Bindiya to draw up the contracts and to place a Help Wanted ad in the paper for another one. Maddy stops Jassi as she’s leaving Chairman and makes one of his world-famous rude jokes. Veeru and Gang don’t want to let Maria go out alone with Manchanda, but he tells her that it’s just the two of them or she’s fired. Maria tells Jassi that Kiran is waiting to see Arman in the lobby, and also to let her know about her upcoming meeting with Manchanda. Jassi tells Arman about Kiran’s arrival and asks him about his final decision regarding Maria, to which he responds that all she’s going to get is a verbal admonishment. Jassi tells Veeru about Arman’s decision and asks him to tell Kiran to come up to Arman’s office.  
     

        
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Hello Friends,  I am really thrilled looking at the response this site has got in a very short period of time. In case you also happen to be touched by Jassi's simplicity do visit the recently launched message forum at  urlLink Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin Forum  at   urlLink http://www.kg2pg.net/default.asp?C=1   Here you can discuss it with other site members.  Cheers, Vijay Bhatter  urlLink http://vijay.bhatter.com  
     

        
</post>

<date>19,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      On Popular demand of Jassi's Real Picture I have uploaded an article which appeared on Mid Day regarding the Real Jassi.  View it on Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin Forum at  urlLink India Forums .  Click  urlLink here  to goto the article ( urlLink direct link )  Cheers,  urlLink Vijay Bhatter   urlLink http://vijay.bhatter.com 
     

        
</post>

<date>18,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Dear Friends,  Thank you for making this small site a instant hit.  Now you can download   1.  urlLink Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin Casting Song MP3    2.  urlLink Wallpapers   3.  urlLink ScreenSaver   4.  urlLink Stills from Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin   and a lot more coming soon at  urlLink Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin Forum  hosted at  urlLink India Forums   Click  urlLink here  to goto to the Download Gallery.  You can even join the Forum and start buzzing about Jassi.  I am also open to ideas of starting other Forum Topics which you can administer. Just send in your ideas through the ShoutBox provided on the right hand side of this page.  Cheers,  urlLink Vijay Bhatter   urlLink http://vijay.bhatter.com 
     

        
</post>

<date>18,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      The next day at Gulmohur:   Bindya is worried that Manchanda is going to fire her for giving out his home phone number. Arman goes to his office and is upset to see that the lights are on, the music is on, the wine glasses, and mess he left behind is still there. He opens the door to Jassi’s office and finds her asleep at the keyboard. He throws the cork from the bottle at her to wake her up and starts yelling at her for being asleep at the office. He asks her why his office is a mess and why she’s sleeping at work, asking her if she had a bad night or is sick. She tells him that she had a terrible night because she was up until 3 am waiting for him to tell her that it was okay to go home, and fell asleep, but that she woke up at 6 am and since she still could hear the music she fell asleep again. Arman is crushed to hear what he did and asks her if she spent the whole night in her office. Jassi said that all she did was follow his instructions to stay in her office until he told her that it was okay to come out. She also tells him that she heard and saw nothing. He tells her that he didn’t do anything, that he left at 2 am and forgot to let her know. Jassi gives him the report she’d prepared the night before and calls a cleaning lady to pick up Arman’s office. Arman feels guilty for what he did to Jassi, apologizes to her, and tells her to go home to rest.   Raj goes to Arman’s office and when he notices the mess asks him how he could be so dumb to leave the evidence in full display. He also asks him for all the details about his evening. Jassi listens in on the conversation, during which Arman tells Raj that the women he’s been with recently, including Mallika, just don’t do anything for him. That he sees them and desires them, but then when he’s close to them he just doesn’t feel anything. That out of all the women in his life the best one is Mallika because she represents stability. Raj tells him that this must mean that he’s leaving the door open for a woman to come in and fill his life with love, but Arman tells him that he doesn’t even know what love is. This fills Jassi with hope. Raj tells him that it is possible that this woman could still arrive and teach him about love, but that hopefully she’ll find him before he gets married, but Arman tells him that he’s too close to getting married and that the woman that he’s going to love will not arrive after all. Jassi comes out of her office and tells Arman that she can clean his office, but Arman refuses to let her do it. He asks her again to go home to rest, and apologizes again. We then see Raj and Arman in the executive bathroom washing glasses and talking. It’s very funny, Raj washing, Arman drying…   Arman tells Raj that he did the worst thing he’s ever done to anyone by leaving Jassi in her office all night. Raj tells him how he could behave as if Jassi didn’t matter, that she’s St. Jassi. Arman tells him that Jassi is a wonderful woman, that he’s never met anyone like her, because she’s loyal, obedient, honest , and is the one person he trusts implicitly. When Jassi gets home she runs into Nandu and tells him about the loan from Kohinoor. 
     

        
</post>

<date>18,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Catch Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin at  urlLink India Forums  at  urlLink http://www.kg2pg.net   Raj helps Arman set up his office for the conquest, with music, vintage wine, and candles. Arman asks Jassi to leave, but she tells him that she’s got a few things to finish and can’t go home yet. He tells her that she has to stay in her office until he tells her that the coast is clear. Jassi can hear what Arman and Kiran are talking about and is saddened to hear that they’re apparently going to spend the night together.   Veeru calls Bindya at home to ask for Manchanda’ phone number since he wants to protect Maria. Meanwhile, Maria is at a disco with Manchanda who’s on the prowl. Pari calls her dad to tell him her financial woes, including that she’s out of a job. Jassi calls home to tell them that she’s working late. Kiran asks Arman if he’s sure about getting married, and he tells her that marriage is not that big a deal, it’s just another event in his life. Raj goes to Pari’s apartment to apologize about what happened at the office and to make up with her. Pari takes advantage of the situation and puts conditions on a reconciliation, including getting married and that he has to fire Maria. Raj tells her that he can’t do either of those things and that they can get back together but with no strings attached. Maria wants to go home after talking to Manchanda but he asks her to stay so they can dance, and later go to a quieter place. Just then, Manchanda’ cellular phone rings and it is his wife, so he has to go to the bathroom to talk. Maria takes the opportunity to call Veeru but they can’t hear each other well because of the noise from the music. However, Veeru is able to at least find out where she is.   Jassi gets all her work done, is exhausted and wants to go home, but when she goes to open her door, she realizes that Arman and Kiran are still there. She’s stuck. Arman and Kiran start necking and when things get a little bit “hot,” she tells him that she doesn’t want to do anything in the office and invites him to her apartment. Jassi doesn’t know that they’ve left because Arman leaves the lights and music on. Manchanda is dancing with Maria when his wife catches him trying to kiss her. She grabbed him by the ear and dragged him home! He leaves Maria to pay the bill, and Veeru, who has just arrived to “rescue her,” has to leave his watch behind to secure payment. Jassi calls home again to say that Arman asked several employees to work late so Balwant can’t argue with her. Jassi is very sad in her office, thinking that the love of her life is off with someone else. Veeru tells Maria about Arman’s decision regarding her firing, and also that he’s the one that called Manchanda’ wife.   Pari goes to Aryan’s apartment to beg him not to make her resign because she needs the money. He again sets down the law about wanting her for sex and information. He then stands up and tells her to undress that he’ll wait for her in his bedroom, she acts as if she’s going to leave, but decides to go ahead and do it. Veeru takes Maria home and she thanks him with a kiss on the lips, which is like heaven to Veeru. After having sex with Pari, Aryan calls a taxi and tells her to go, tells her not to forget to close the door behind her, and goes to sleep.  
     

        
</post>

<date>25,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Bank Manager tells Nandu that they have to acount for all of Gulmohur's property prior to placing the lien.  Maitri tells Bindiya that she has figured out how to get Pari to undergo a pregnancy test and finally figure out if she's faking or not.  The banks start calling Gulmohur since the Chamber of Commerce bulletin announcing the lien by Kohinoor has already been published.  Jassi does her best to keep them at bay.  Nandu tells Jassi that the process has started against Gulmohur.  There's no going back.  Maitri tells Manchanda that Pari hasn't had any of the blood tests required of all new employees and that she isn't covered by a health plan -- "a big problem should she have an accident at work."  Manchanda tells Pari to have the tests Balwante.  She of course doesn't want to get them Balwante, but tough luck...  Even Mallika won't get her out of this one.    Mallika asks Arman if he's okay since she thinks he's looking pretty bad lately.  He tells her that, as usual, he is worried about the upcoming launch.  She bids him goodbye and goes on her merry way to pick up Arman's parents at the airport.  Jassi gets a call from Wilson saying that someone is waiting for her.  She tells Arman that the paperwork for the lien by Kohinoor against Gulmohur have arrived.  Raj asks who is delivering the paperwork and Jassi answers that Nandu , a friend, is making the delivery.  Raj gets very worried and asks Arman if he knows who Nandu is -- whether he can be trusted.  Arman tells him that Nandu is a classmate of Jassi's, a neighbor who is working with her at Kohinoor.  Nandu gives Jassi the paperwork and tells her that the judge is going to send a court official to perform an inventory of Gulmohur's property.  He tells her that this cannot be avoided and that there's no way to know when it will happen.  The phone rings in Presidencia and since Jassi isn't there to answer it, Arman yells out her name...  Raj warns him to stop yelling at "el monstrete" because from this moment forward she owns Gulmohur.  Raj asks Jassi about her meeting with the lawyer he recommended and she tells him about the meeting.  Raj reminds her to make sure that everything is handled very carefully.  Jassi explains that everything is going well, and drops the bomb about the inventory.  Arman has one of his fits of hysteria and starts yelling at Jassi for not taking care of avoiding this, Jassi explains that this is something that is beyond their control.  She is obviously ticked off at Arman and goes to her office.  Raj tells Arman that Jassi is right and that it is important that he stop yelling at Jassi.  Arman goes to Jassi's office and asks her if she has prepared the payment projections...  She tells him that she has them.  Arman then, very calmly, starts to talk to her and tell her that she needs to understand that these are very tough times for him, that he's going to be upset, that he has given his company to her.  Arman hugs her and tells her that he is fearful that they will be found out, that he won't be able to save the company, but Jassi comforts him and tells him that she will take care of everything, that she will be behind him 100%, that they'll work together and be able to conquer it all.  Arman takes a hold of Jassi's hands and tells her that she is the motor that runs his life, and that together with love they'll be able to fly above it all, do great things, fly over the ocean, the mountains...  Jassi tells him:  yes, doctor, we'll go hand in hand, safeguarding one another, you and me against the world, until death do us part, doctor...  Did you really think that this happened?  Sorry!!  Another dream courtesy of Jassi's fertile imagination!     As usual, reality bites and Jassi wakes up to find Arman yelling at her since they have to go to the banks.  Bindiya's husband arrives to talk to her.  Maria calls Bindiya to let her know... Inesita warns Bindiya about keeping a clear head.  Everyone, including Pari, el gang, Veeru and Efraín, is surprised at the new, calm Bindiya.    ============================================= Unofficial Site on  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin    Join the  urlLink India Forums  to discuss about Jassi. Click   urlLink here   to view  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin   Forum ============================================= 
     

        
</post>

<date>24,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Arman asks Maddy not to hire Jenny, but Maddy just to spite Arman and Bindiya hires her. Arman tells Bindiya that he can’t do anything about Maddy’s decision, and Bindiya goes off crying. Mallika didn’t want Jenny to be hired from the first moment she saw her, and when she finds out that Jenny is Bindiya’s husband’s mistress she is even more against it. She tells Arman that they can’t do that to Bindiya, but Arman tells her that he already tried to reason with Maddy and couldn’t. Arman asks Mallika not to tell her brother or his parents about the failure of the most recent collection, and Mallika doesn’t like it. Jassi explains to Arman the consequences of the loan that Kohinoor has given Gulmohur and that she will have to register the business situation with the Chamber of Commerce. Mallika tells Bindiya that Maddy won’t budge on hiring Jenny. Pari tells Mallika that Maria took Raj away from her.   Jassi tells Arman that she feels terrible for the problems at Gulmohur and also that she feels it’s her fault that the collection failed since it was her economic analysis that led to buying the cheaper fabrics. Arman tells her that she shouldn’t feel bad because it was his decision since he accepted the conditions to be able to meet his goals, and he knew that she had told him that she didn’t know anything about the fashion business – that all the responsibility is his. Jassi tells him that she’s there for him and will do everything she can to prevent having to have Kohinoor take over Gulmohur. Jenny calls Efrain (el Cheque, Bindiya’s husband) to tell him that she’ll be working at Gulmohur, but he asks her to leave immediately because Bindiya is going to kill her. Bindiya talks to Efrain as well and demands that he make Jenny leave Gulmohur. Veeru arrives and asks if they already hired the new fitting model because she is a “remamita,” which infuriates Bindiya, who slaps poor Veeru.   Arman tells Jassi that Kohinoor was established with a seed investment of Rs.30 lakhs, but that she was able to lend Gulmohur Rs.60 lakhs – how did she accomplish that? She tells him that she invested the money in the stock market. Arman congratulates her but also asks her how come she always uses the pronoun “we” when talking about Kohinoor. She explains that a friend from school, Nandu, is helping her out, but makes it clear that Nandu is not aware of anything about why Kohinoor was established, that he’s just an employee. Arman reminds her that no one can know the real reason behind Kohinoor, only she, him, and Raj. Veeru tells Maria that Bindiya slapped him because he made a comment about the new fitting model, and Maria tells him that Jenny is Bindiya’s husband’s mistress. Efrain arrive to pick up Jenny, who is making every effort to drive Bindiya up the wall. Inesita tells Bindiya that it cannot be a coincidence that Jenny just happened to show up at Gulmohur, that it has to be Jenny’s way to pay Bindiya back for all the things she told her when they ran into Jenny and Efrain at the bar the night they all got drunk.   Jassi gets home and tells Nandu about how badly things are going at Gulmohur, and also tells him Arman’s plans to protect Gulmohur by having Kohinoor take over it.   Arman arrives at Mallika’s apartment and asks her what will happen if she tells Aryan and his parents about the failed collection. He tells her that if she talks to them, he’ll back out of the marriage, and that if she helps him with the company he’ll “do her the favor” of marrying her… However, at the same time he approaches her and starts kissing her passionately and Mallika tells him that she will help him, but only if he promises that he won’t do anything crazy. Nandu tells Jassi that with the paper that Arman signed for the loan, he practically handed her Gulmohur on a silver platter. Jassi tells him that Arman did it to protect the company and that eventually Kohinoor would put a lien on Gulmohur to protect it from its other creditors. Nandu tells her that if she’s going to participate in this set up, she has to be aware that it may be legal but not ethical. She tells him that she feels like she owes it to Arman to do this, and also makes him promise that he won’t say anything to anyone because she promised Arman she wouldn’t tell anyone either. And, that for the time being they won’t be able to set up a formal office, but that since Arman told her to run the company as she saw fit, she wants to hire her father to do the books for Kohinoor.   ============================================= Unofficial Site on  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin    Join the  urlLink India Forums  to discuss about Jassi. Click   urlLink here   to view  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin   Forum =============================================
     

        
</post>

<date>23,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Manchanda comes to work looking like he’d run into a pack of wild cats, and calls Veeru and Berta to his office to ask them for their letter of resignation since they caused this problem for him at home. The Gang goes to see Arman and ask him to help Veeru and Berta. Arman asks Manchanda what happened, to which Manchanda responds that his cat scratched him. Arman reminds him that he doesn’t have a cat. Manchanda has no other choice than to let Berta and Veeru be. The Gang thanks Arman for his help.   Pari comes to the office and Arman and Raj are dismayed to find out that she’s back. Arman says that she’s like the Terminator, that you think she’s gone and comes back again and again. Pari says that Aryan asked her not to resign, which Arman doesn’t want to hear. Jassi is in her room, writing in her diary, saying that she prays that Arman’s business plan works out, that she would feel guilty if he fails. She also says that she’s scared about the money he borrowed from Kohinoor, and that she is glad to know that she is the most important person in Arman’s life, more than his own fiancée, but that for him she’s not a woman, that she spent a hellish night locked in her office and he didn’t even think about her, that he only sees her as an employee. She heard him say that he’s waiting for the woman of his dreams, but he doesn’t realize that she’s there, just a few feet away from his desk. That she doesn’t have the way to show him that she’s the woman he needs, and that he’ll never know it that only a miracle would make him realize how she feels, and she doesn’t believe in miracles anymore, and much less now that he’s so close to getting married.   Jassi tells Nandu that she’s going to ask Arman for permission to set up and office for Kohinoor, because she wants her dad to do the books for the company. And, she also tells Nandu that they need to have plenty of cash available in case Arman wants to ask for another loan. Arman is very worried because his business/sales strategy was a failure. When Jassi gets to work he asks her for another loan and puts Gulmohur up as collateral. Raj tells him that this means giving Jassi complete control over Gulmohur. Arman says that this is exactly what he’s doing and tells Jassi that since sales were so bad and cash flow into the company was minimal, the banks are going to want to dismantle Gulmohur. Jassi tells him that she can hold off the banks until the next collection comes out, but Arman tells her that they need more time, so he needs for Kohinoor to sue Gulmohur so the banks won’t. Jassi is completely against doing this because even though this would be legally correct, it’s unethical. Arman tells her that this is the only way he can pay back the companies debts, begs her not to abandon him, that he needs her help, and actually questions her loyalty to him!   Jassi goes to her office to think about it and starts thinking about how Arman has always supported her, encouraged and motivated her, stood up for her with Mallika and Aryan, and believed in her. So she decides to help him and tells herself that she cannot leave him stranded. Jassi tells Arman that she is completely loyal to him and that she will do whatever he needs her to do. He tells her to go ahead with the suit over Gulmohur and thanks her for her assistance.   Mallika comes home from her trip to the US and goes in to see Arman and tell him that she’s already bought her wedding trousseau and fabric for her wedding dress. She says this in front of Raj and Jassi, who doesn’t take the news very well. Mallika shows Maddy the fabric for her dress and asks Mariana for the sales reports, and is very concerned to see how badly it has gone. Maddy tells her that it was due to the poor quality fabrics they used. Mallika goes to the board room where she finds Arman, Raj, and Jassi and asks them for an explanation. Mallika blames Arman for being so stubborn about using the poor quality fabrics and asks him how much money they’ve lost… She then aims her guns at Jassi, who’s standing, to tell her since she must know them by heart. Jassi says nothing. He tells Mallika to calm down, that Gulmohur is sufficiently strong to handle this drawback, which is all it was. Arman asks Jassi to please sit down… Mallika gives her one of those if looks could kill looks and tells Arman that for once she’d like to have a conversation in private, meaning without Jassi around, since she’s not a stockholder. Arman tells Mallika that Jassi is for all intents the Financial VP and that he needs her there. Mallika sarcastically gives Jassi a hand and blames her for the financial disaster, but Arman stands up for her saying that Jassi was just following orders. Jassi says that she’d rather leave and go out to lunch and let them talk in private.   After some more arguing, Arman, Raj and Mallika decide that they have to launch a new collection as soon as possible. So they tell Maddy to get going, and Maddy reminds Arman, mockingly, about the fact that the fabrics must be top quality. Maddy has asked Inesita to find select the new fitting model from a group waiting in the lobby. Without realizing it, Inesita selects Jenny, Bindiya’s husband’s mistress. The Gang comes back from lunch and Veeru tells them that he’s seen a model tailor made for him, referring to Jenny, and Maria is very jealous. Maddy reminds Arman about their bet and the fact that he has to dress up in drag. Raj tells Arman that it’s obvious they’re not going to meet their business goals and it’s time to come clean with the board. Arman tells him that he’s not going to hand the chairmanship and his head in a silver platter to Aryan. Bindiya has a fit when she sees Jenny and starts asking for her not to be hired. The Gang tries to calm her down, but she goes to Maddy’s atelier and tell shim that he can’t hire Jenny because she took her husband away from her. Maddy, just to be contrary, tells her that right that moment he was hiring Jenny. Bindiya goes to Arman to tell her about her problem.   ============================================= Unofficial Site on  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin    Join the  urlLink India Forums  to discuss about Jassi. Click   urlLink here   to view  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin   Forum =============================================
     

        
</post>

<date>28,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Hi All,  While researching on the Internet and other mediums I found quite a bit of information on Mona Singh (face behind jassi). Wanna know more like date of birth, height, weight etc. Visit the link provided below:   http://www.kg2pg.net/forum_posts.asp?TID=28&PN=1&TPN=1   Special thanks to Pooja for providing this information. In case you have any other pictures of Mona Singh or Jassi please post on the Jassi Forum at  urlLink India Forums   Cheers :) 
     

        
</post>

<date>28,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      The Face Behind Jassi: For Mona Singh, the trek to Jassi Jaissi Koi Nahin began with this picture that landed her the Asian Paints commercial.   To View the picture click the link below at  urlLink Jassi Forum  :   urlLink India Forums: The Real Face Behind Jassi   But to see Jassi’s glamourous face in the serial, wait till next year.
     

        
</post>

<date>05,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Mallika tells Mrs. Suri that Arman has been behaving very well these past few days, hasn't been cheating on her, and is right now with Jassi -- which helps her to be at ease.  Aryan arrives to say hello to Arman's parents.  Jassi and Arman also arrive and Arman asks her to prepare a report to outline the payment plan to the banks, as well as an overall report of the company's financial picture and have it ready the next morning.  Jassi tells him that she has already prepared those reports and Arman congratulates her for being so efficient.  Kiran walks into Arman's office and asks him to speak to him in private.  He tries to tell her that he can't, and for extra security hugs Jassi's shoulder to prevent her from leaving.  However, Jassi tells Arman that she has work to do and leaves him all alone with Kiran -- which does not please Arman one bit.  Kiran asks Arman to get rid of Jassi so they can spend the night together again.  Arman tells her that he has a lot of stuff to do, that he's busy and doesn't have time to be with her.  She tells him that she'll let him be if he kisses her, which he does and Jassi overhears the whole thing.  Mallika calls Pari to ask her if Arman is at work because his cell phone is off and she can't reach him.  Pari tells her that he has just arrived.  Pari is on her way to Arman's office, which prompts Maitri's radar to go into action and alert Bindiya to call Jassi to let her know that Pari is on her way and might catch Arman in a "compromising" position.  Arman is still going to town with Kiran, when Jassi comes out and tells Arman that she has a message for him.  Arman, because he really is at heart an idiot apparently, gets mad at Jassi for interrupting...  Pari gives Arman the messages and knows something is amiss since his hair is all messed up.  Veeru talks to Maddy to tell him that to ensure that the next collection goes perfectly, he needs to allow Jenny to model!  Maddy makes fun of Veeru.  Maitri's husband calls her to let her know that he is back from  his trip and wants to see the car she bought with the money he left with her.  Maitri is a tad nervous, to say the least.  Jassi finishes one of her unending series of reports about the state of Gulmohur and tells Raj and Arman about the projections for payments to the creditors, which will only work if the next four collections are a success.  Raj tells Arman that there is just no way that they'll be able to meet their outstanding debts and that the only thing left to do is for Arman to save Gulmohur and see what else he can do afterwards.  Jassi recommends that they pursue a strategy that includes exporting the merchandise to try to get rid of the stuff from the failed collections.    After Jassi goes home, Raj keeps talking to Arman about the dire situation at Gulmohur, how Jassi's projections state that they must fulfill all their outstanding debts within the next year, and that if things continue going the way they are prior to the end of that year Arman will have to turn over the chairmanship to Aryan.  However, there WON'T be a company to give Aryan to preside, since it now belongs to Miss Universe also known as the beautiful "jassi."  Raj begins to plant the seeds of doubt regarding Arman's blind trust of Jassi...  Arman tells Raj that he does trust Jassi, that she is completely trustworthy, that any time that he asks for the company back she'd return it without batting an eyelash.  Raj tells Arman to be very careful of the way he treats Jassi, since ALL of them (Arman, Raj, the Suri, the .....) are in her hands.  ============================================= Unofficial Site on  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin    Join the  urlLink India Forums  to discuss about Jassi. Click   urlLink here   to view  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin   Forum =============================================
     

        
</post>

<date>19,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Leena, the model and lover of Bindiya's husband, continues to have problems with Bindiya. Finally, Mallika talks with Bindiya and tells her she can understand but that her behavior is not only childish but counter-productive. She should prove to Leena and her ex-husband that she doesn't need them. Pari convinces Mallika to let her work for her as a publicity assistant (I'm not sure if she really wants to do something useful or needs a pipeline for information to give Aryan). Arman complies with his agreement with Maddy and goes to the cross-dressing party. But he gets a call from Mallika about an important agreement he has to sign at her apartment, where her brother and sister will be. Desperate, Arman calls Jassi to pick him up.   All agree on the new materials. Arman complies with his agreement with Maddy, dresses up and goes to the transvestite ball. Then Mallika calls him to come home at once to sign an agreement; Aryan, their sister and Pari are there. Desperate, Arman calls Jassi for help and arrives home in a too-small suit of Jassi's father. Later, when he explains to Mallika, she doesn't understand why he didn't call and explain the situation to her. Arman and Raj pretend to go to Hong Kong but really go to the factory in ?. Veeru wrecks Arman's car. Pari convinces Mallika that she ought to know the name and number of the new fabric provider and when Jassi finds her in her office, Pari says that Mallika told her to get the information. Jassi finally gets hold of Arman and tells him what happened. He calls Mallika, asks her why she can't trust him, flies home. Mallika calls in Jassi and Pari and the latter admits that she said Mallika had authorized her. Mallika wonders why she cares so much and is really angry with her. After all, Jassi did just what they would expect her to do: tell Arman everything. Arman forgives Veeru and makes up with Mallika. Pari is almost found on the phone with Aryan and either becomes faint or fakes it. Raj takes her home and they make love. Customs agents confiscate the materials before they are delivered: they are contraband goods.   ============================================= Unofficial Site on  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin    Join the  urlLink India Forums  to discuss about Jassi. Click   urlLink here   to view  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin   Forum ============================================= 
     

        
</post>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Grudgingly Arman gets dressed Drag Queen to attend the celebration with Maddy. Mallika says to him to Pari that accompanies it to close a contract with a famous model and it presents/displays it like his assistant.  In spite of all the precautions, a watchman of the company sees Arman disguised of Drag Queen. Mallika suspects that something happens to its fiancè.  Aryan, Mallika and Maria  plan an encounter in the apartment of Arman.  It when coming out has a fight of the party and ends up requesting aid to him to Jassi.  Jassi leaves their house secretly to help their head.  He confesses the truth to him of the bet to Maddy.  Arman has problems with the Police.  In view of which he cannot enter Gulmohur, he must look for a site to take off the disguise.  Balwant suspects that his wife and Jassi are hiding something to him. Mallika worries about Arman.  He asks to him Jassi if he really treats it bad.  Aryan is surprised when seeing his cousin so badly dressed.  Pari tells Aryan takes advantage of the occasion to make be to Arman in front of the new model badly that will be the image of Gulmohur. The samples that Raj sent are approved by Maddy.  Mallika says to Arman that she will travel with him to New York to close the business. Jassi worries because Veeru has not arrived with the car of its head.  Pari intrigues to Mallika with the businesses that are making Raj and Arman.  The insistence of Pari with Mallika was so much so that Arman or Jassi gave the names him of the fabric suppliers for the next collection, that was on the verge of being discovered like informant of Aryan.  Jassi finds in its office looking for something that gave track him on the suppliers.  Pari says to him that Mallika sent to look for it that information.  Jassi communicates it to Arman immediately and this one protests to him as well to its fiancèe, which leaves to very annoying Mallika with Pari.  Pari is not only looking for that Mallika resigning from Gulmohur, but that also ends that friendship of years, because it will not allow that besides to create problems to him in the company, also believes them in its relation with Arman.   Raj before traveling to Bangkok, spends the night with Pari with the only aim to see what information can remove to him.  Pari in as much, thinks that Raj the master and who perhaps fulfills her promise to him to live together. Arman he was very contented because everything seemed legal with the suppliers of fabrics.  It was already watched with the new collection in the market and with gains that the economic stability of Gulmohur would recover Fashion.  Nevertheless, the reality was another one... the day that supposedly would arrive the shipment, in the news is listened to the intervention of customs to recover fabric an originating contraband of Bangkok.  Arman and Raj remain colds!  They were its fabrics... luckyly the name of Gulmohur Fashion is not involved.    But they lost crores that were paid in advance.  Arman reunites to Maddy and to Mallika and says to them that the fabrics would take at least 15 days in arriving then at last hour occurred to account the salesmen who did not have them in warehouse.  Arman does this with the purpose of gaining time and to see if the new plan that it has in mind gives result.    Balwant Walia offers to take to Jassi and Arman to make all the returns of notary, and takes advantage of to tell the history him of its life to Arman. Arman says to Raj that after knowing the family of Jassi trusts more her.    Mallika asks Pari what would she do with obtaining husband. Jassi suggests to him to Arman that they do not follow ahead with the plans of Gulmohur and Kohinoor.  Maithili tells its friends who his husband will give a money him so that he buys car.  Raj and Aryan, each one by their side, confirm one lasts reality that threatens changing the life to them.   Arman speaks to Mallika of a great preoccupation that has suicide to Raj on the brink of madness. Nandu requests to him to Jassi that presents/displays to him to Pari to do a offer to him that will not be able to reject.  Mallika notices Pari that Arman is very annoyed with her and who does not have to abuse her condition of privileged in the company. Aryan cannot be concentrated in the work and begins to have nightmares with Pari.  It gives a speech him of responsibility to Raj.  Matheli and Pari have a new confrontation but this time the Gang is overcome.  Maria proposes to Matheli a play to him to win to him to Pari once and for all, a liposuction.    ============================================= Unofficial Site on  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin    Join the  urlLink India Forums  to discuss about Jassi. Click   urlLink here   to view  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin   Forum =============================================
     

        
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      The lawyer tells Nandu that they have to acount for all of Gulmohur's property prior to placing the lien.  Maithili tells Bindiya that she has figured out how to get Pari to undergo a pregnancy test and finally figure out if she's faking or not.  The banks start calling Gulmohur since the Chamber of Commerce bulletin announcing the lien by Kohinoor has already been published.  Jassi does her best to keep them at bay.  Nandu tells Jassi that the process has started against Gulmohur.  There's no going back.  Maithili tells Manchanda that Pari hasn't had any of the blood tests required of all new employees and that she isn't covered by a health plan -- "a big problem should she have an accident at work."  Manchanda tells Pari to have the tests done.  She of course doesn't want to get them done, but tough luck...  Even Mallika won't get her out of this one.       Mallika asks Arman if he's okay since she thinks he's looking pretty bad lately.  He tells her that, as usual, he is worried about the upcoming launch.  She bids him goodbye and goes on her merry way to pick up Arman's parents at the airport.  Jassi gets a call from Wilson saying that someone is waiting for her.  She tells Arman that the paperwork for the lien by Kohinoor against Gulmohur have arrived.  Raj asks who is delivering the paperwork and Jassi answers that Nandu , a friend, is making the delivery.  Raj gets very worried and asks Arman if he knows who Nandu is -- whether he can be trusted.  Arman tells him that Nandu is a classmate of Jassi's, a neighbor who is working with her at Kohinoor.  Nandu gives Jassi the paperwork and tells her that the judge is going to send a court official to perform an inventory of Gulmohur's property.  He tells her that this cannot be avoided and that there's no way to know when it will happen.  The phone rings in Chairmanship and since Jassi isn't there to answer it, Arman yells out her name...  Raj warns him to stop yelling at "el monstrete" because from this moment forward she owns Gulmohur.   Raj asks Jassi about her meeting with the lawyer he recommended and she tells him about the meeting.  Raj reminds her to make sure that everything is handled very carefully.  Jassi explains that everything is going well, and drops the bomb about the inventory.  Arman has one of his fits of hysteria and starts yelling at Jassi for not taking care of avoiding this, Jassi explains that this is something that is beyond their control.  She is obviously ticked off at Arman and goes to her office.  Raj tells Arman that Jassi is right and that it is important that he stop yelling at Jassi.   Arman goes to Jassi's office and asks her if she has prepared the payment projections...  She tells him that she has them.  Arman then, very calmly, starts to talk to her and tell her that she needs to understand that these are very tough times for him, that he's going to be upset, that he has given his company to her.  Arman hugs her and tells her that he is fearful that they will be found out, that he won't be able to save the company, but Jassi comforts him and tells him that she will take care of everything, that she will be behind him 100%, that they'll work together and be able to conquer it all.  Arman takes a hold of Jassi's hands and tells her that she is the motor that runs his life, and that together with love they'll be able to fly above it all, do great things, fly over the ocean, the mountains...  Jassi tells him:  yes, doctor, we'll go hand in hand, safeguarding one another, you and me against the world, until death do us part, doctor...  Did you really think that this happened?  Sorry!!  Another dream courtesy of Jassi's fertile imagination!      As usual, reality bites and Jassi wakes up to find Arman yelling at her since they have to go to the banks.  Bindiya's husband arrives to talk to her.  Maria calls Bindiya to let her know... Ruby warns Bindiya about keeping a clear head.  Everyone, including Pari, Gang, Veeru and Mohit, is surprised at the new, calm Bindiya.       In the meantime, Mr. Suri asks Mallika how badly hurt Gulmohur came out of the previous collection.  She tells him that the company can withstand the losses, but that it is best if he talks directly with Arman.  Arman and Jassi are talking to one of the bank managers, Dr. Contreras, who tells them that the bank is going to start a process against Gulmohur...  Arman tries to reach an agreement with the bank official, telling him that a very important company has taken over Gulmohur and that he'd like to work out a payment agrement.  Jassi does her song and dance about how Gulmohur will be able to meet its outstanding debts, however Dr. Contreras wants more insurance than that.  However, there's nothing else to give since Gulmohur is now in the hands of Kohinoor.  Arman begs him to be discrete and not make a big scandal about what he's just found out -- and assures him that Gulmohur will pay as promised.  Jassi asks Contreras to consider her proposal.  ============================================= Unofficial Site on  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin    Join the  urlLink India Forums  to discuss about Jassi. Click   urlLink here   to view  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin   Forum =============================================
     

        
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
          Tonight           Tonight, Rohan decides to drown himself because he doesn’t like Jassi befriending Purab. Although Jassi can't swim she jumps into the water to save him...     Previous Episodes     Telecast Date: Monday 1st, March 2004      Jassi is stumped to see her lawyer sitting in Armaan’s cabin. The lawyer is there to serve the notice to Gulmohar. Jassi panics but then, manages to turn the situation in her favour. Meanwhile, Raj gets a call asking him to visit the figure-fine gym at 4.30 pm. Raj goes to the gym, and sees Pari working out on the treadmill. The trainer confirms that she is not pregnant. Raj returns to Gulmohar with an exuberant look on his face and invites the whole clan to his engagement. What is he up to?     Telecast Date: Tuesday 2nd, March 2004      Raj continues to be enthusiastic about his engagement with pari. This is the calm before the storm! That night, during his engagement reception, he decides to call Pari’s father and disclose the good news of the engagement and the pregnancy! Pari panics and blurts out the truth! Raj is free...finally! But all is not well, the caterer calls Jassi and backs out! Who is now going to cook for all the guests?     Telecast Date: Wednesday 3rd, March 2004      The engagement is only a day away and there is no caterer available. Jassi and the clan make all the calls possible, but it’s all in vain. They decide to go to Jassi’s house to make some more calls, when a solution comes up...Amrit has decided to cook for the function! The enthusiasm builds and spreads.... the clan joins in and they have a ball dishing out different recipes. Back at Gulmohar, Pari finds the clan missing and she calls Jassi’s house to check on them. When she realizes that they are all there, she reports this to Mallika and they decide to pay Jassi a visit!     Telecast Date: Thursday 4th, March 2004      Armaan hears Pari and Mallikas conversation and cannot let them go to Jassi’s house as all his plans will get foiled! Back at Jassi’s house, the cooking goes on all night......the day of the engagement dawns and Jassi tells Armaan that of the efforts put in by her family and the clan. Armaan invites her family to the function. Jassi goes to Armaans house to supervise the decorations, flowers, cake....puts in her best. But her heart is sad to see Armaan and Mallika together. That night while the family is getting ready to leave, Jassi decides not to go for the engagement!     Telecast Date: Monday 8th, March 2004      Jassi refuses to attend Amaan’s engagement but finally gives in after the clan convinces her. Nandu understands her state of mind only because he has lost chesta! He sees a diamond ring lying under the divan and decides to try his luck with Chesta once again! Panic hits the Jassi household as Armaans engagement ring for Mallika is missing!,Jassi desperately looks for the ring, while a beaming Nandu proposes to Chesta with it. Armaan calls Jassi for the ring but she manages to cover up the incident. Poor Nandu gets rejected and he returns to Jassis house amidst the "ring search" mission and tells them about the ring.     Telecast Date: Tuesday 9th, March 2004      Nandu produces the ring and Jassi almost shrieks with joy! Everyone leaves for the engagement party. While everyone is at the party, the lawyers arrive at Gulmohar to take inventory and are greeted by Raj. Jassi tries her best to be normal but little does she realise that the entire function is not according to Mallika’s taste. Worse still, Mallika has figured out that Jassi co-ordinated the flowers and the food! Mallika humiliates Jassi and destroys her self-esteem. Jassi walks out from the party, completely dazed while all the guests praise her for the arrangements.      Telecast Date: Wednesday 10th, March 2004     The party is a hit! Everyone loves the food and decor but Jassi is missing! Someone else is missing too; Raj, who is at Gulmohar with the lawyers. Raj is in the mood for celebration and is quite drunk! In his drunken state, he tells the lawyers that Jassi will take a decision in the benefit of the company. The lawyers catch on and become suspicious of the deal. Raj returns to the party in time for the ring ceremony when the lawyer calls and tells him that he is aware of their clever scheme! Raj informs Armaan and they panic and decide to call Jassi. Jassi reaches home and breaks into tears. Bebe and Nandu comfort her but Jassi doesn’t say anything. Armaan calls up and Nandu does not let Jassi take the call.    Telecast Date: Wednesday 11th, March 2004     Raj decides to meet the lawyer. The lawyer gives him an ultimatum, he wants a partnership in the Gulmohar-Kohinoor scheme! Otherwise he threatens to disclose the case in court! Raj tells Armaan and they desperately try to get in touch with Jassi...but fail. Raj chides Armaan for letting Mallika treat Jassi badly and warns him that they could be in trouble...after all; the lawyers could easily contact her. They immediately leave for Jassi’s house. Back at Jassis house, Bebe tries to cheer Jassi...nandu tries to get the truth out of her...but Jassi is quiet...and then, she requests bebe to take her out of town for a while. Bebe and jassi leave.  ============================================= Unofficial Site on  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin    Join the  urlLink India Forums  to discuss about Jassi. Click   urlLink here   to view  urlLink  Jassi Jaissi Koi Nahin   Forum =============================================
     

        
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
        He’s the new man in Jassi’s life. Delhi boy Sameer Soni, a St Xavier’s School alumnus, plays Purab, a cut and dry businessman in Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin on Sony TV.  In the serial, Jassi leaves Gulmohar House when she is sacked by Mallika (Rakshanda Khan) after she gets to know that her engagement party was planned by Jassi (Mona Singh) and Armaan.  Accompanying her parents to a wedding, Jassi meets Purab. “We gel as both Jassi and I have a disjointed life. I play a businessman who finds it hard to express himself but has a heart of gold. He is trying to establish a relationship with his ten-year-old step-brother and Jassi helps him do that,” says Soni.  Having learnt theatre under Barry John, Soni made his Bollywood foray with China Gate and then worked in Baghban  as well. “I’m looking forward to the release of Dance Like A Man, Anoushka Shanker’s debut film. Last year, if you’d asked me if I will do television, the answer would have been in the negative. But the role of Purab is so endearing that I couldn’t say no to the producers,” says Soni.  A graduate in finance from the University of California, Soni’s family wanted him to focus on academics and stay away from the world of glamour. “After satisfying my parents with a degree, I jumped into Bollywood and shifted base to Mumbai seven years back,” says Soni.  Hoping that his character will go down well with the viewers, Soni does agree that television has great reach. “Television has far greater time constraints unlike films that have the luxury of the time. But TV is something new for me and I hope that Purab will get the same acceptance as the other characters in the serial.”   Courtesy: Hindustan Times -Asmita Aggarwal 11 March   urlLink http://www.hindustantimes.com/news/181_609519,0047.htm   ============================================= Unofficial Site on  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin    Join the  urlLink India Forums  to discuss about Jassi. Click   urlLink here   to view  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin   Forum =============================================
     

        
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
        Posted by:  urlLink Ashwirya Shetty      Armaan stops in his track when he enters the boardroom for the board meeting. He has a shocked look on his face. Standing in front of him is Jassi with her head down. Mallika is standing in front of her. Armaan is relieved.  In the room, Aryan, Armaan’s dad, Matty and Raj are also present.   Mallika confronts Jassi about taking leave without any intimation. Before Jassi could respond, Armaan interrupts trying to protect Jassi (or probably himself). But Jassi stops him from saying anything. She tells Mallika she is sorry for going away without informing anyone. Both Aryan and Mallika are not ready to let Jassi off so easily, and continue to confront her. Jassi tells them quite calmly that she has not taken any days off nor have they allowed her to take any holidays. To that Mallika asks her angrily whether Jassi thinks that she (Jassi) is doing Kohnioor’s ‘gulami’. Armaan’s dad speaks up. He says that Jassi has said sorry and that she was right when she said that she had not taken any days off. He added that she has never given any reason for complain, her work has always been perfect and he wanted to take this opportunity to thank her for good work & also for making the perfect engagment arrangement for Mallika and Armaan. Mallika looks angry, but keeps quiet. Everyone starts leaving the boardroom. Jassi turns to go, and finds Armaan is standing in her way. She looks at him, and without saying a word, moves past him.  When Jassi steps outside the boardroom the gang greet her with a garland.   They are thrilled to have Jassi back. They want to know all the juicy details of what she did during her time off. They also wanted to know whether Armaan and she came back together from Alibagh. She looks a little sad when she respond with a no. When they pester for more information about her trip. She tells them that she will provide the details during the lunchtime and goes to her office.  When she enters Armaan’s office Armaan and Raj are there. Armaan keeps looking at her angryily (he just cannot understand her now). It seems like Raj understood that Jassi has changed. He speaks with her nicely. Armaan tells her (angrily) about the problem with the Lawyer. He tells her that the lawyer was bribing them, as he has come to know their secret. She is surprised and wonders how the lawyer could have guessed. Armaan tells that Nandu could have leaked it out. Jassi tells them the way he trust her, similarly, she trust Nandu. Raj shows her the video shot, where the lawyer is taking the money from Raj. They will use this against the laywer.  Armaan tells Jassi to go along with Raj and him for lunch, as they had to discuss more about how to handle the lawyer’s issue. Jassi refuses to go along, which catches both Raj and Armaan off guard. She tells them she has promised to meet the gang during the lunchtime. Armaan is furious, but Raj controls the situation, and tells Jassi to go ahead and have lunch with her friends.  Jassi is in her little office; she opens her drawer and finds the poster with her and Armaan photo on it with heart between the two photos (the one she always keeps in her drawer). She thinks to herself that she has changed now and there was no need to have this poster. She tears the posters into two halfs. Nandu calls her and teases her when she tells him that she has changed. He tells her that if she had changed, she would have met him instead of rushing off to work. Armaan calls her loudly from the other room.   He tells her to get him black coffee (or tea, cannot remember, sorry!). She pauses for a moment, and then continues to talk with Nandu. They decide to meet in the evening. Nandu asks her whether she is sure that she will not be doing overtime as usual and make him wait for her. She promises that she will meet him on time in the evening. She hangs the phone. She then dials the canteen and orders coffee for Armaan.  Pari, the troublemaker, tells Mallika that she feels that Jassi is a bad omen for the company. She feels that the company is doing badl because of Jassi. She tells Mallika that Jassi being in charge of the fashion show will make a mess of it again. Mallika assures that nothing of that sort will happen and she will assign the work to Jassi, and the work would be to stay away from the fashion show.  Mallika goes to Armaan office, where Armaan, Raj and Jassi are present. She tells Jassi to send the all the files relating to the fashion show to her office. Armaan and Raj try to get Jassi as a part of the organizing team for the fashon show. Jassi speaks up and says that there is no need for so many people to get involved in the fashion show and Aryan and Mallika were handling it well enough. She hands over the files to Mallike. Mallika is shocked (worth seeing her face!) so are Armaan and Raj.  Jassi is searching for some file in her office, but cannot find it. She gets frustrated. There is a flashback…she thinks about what Purab told her…that she thinks about the world, but she does not think about herself. She comes back to the present. She decides that now onward she will think about herself. She decides that she will not work in that office.  She leaves her office, Armaan sees her and asks her rudely about his coffee…she turn to look towards the office door. At that moment, the office door opens and a guy comes in with the coffee. Raj gives a look to Armaan as if to say ‘hey man can you take it a bit cool’. Armaan starts to talk about work; she cuts him, and tells him that she wants to say something to him.   Both give her a wary look. She tells him that she will no longer work in the current office. She wants another office for herself, and that she will move out of the old office the next day. Armaan is shocked  ============================================= Unofficial Site on  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin    Join the  urlLink India Forums  to discuss about  urlLink Jassi . Click   urlLink here   to view  urlLink  Jassi Jaissi Koi Nahin   Forum =============================================
     

        
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
        Posted by:  urlLink Ashwirya Shetty      Armaan asks rohan whether he had seen someone with big, gasses and braces. Rohan gets mad at  Armaan and takes him on a wild goose chase. He leaves armaan in middle of the jungle and runs away to where Jassi was staying.  The hotel manager informed Rohan that Jassi and Bebe had already left. Rohan was surprised that Jassi had left without even meeting him. Manager tells him that Jassi has left something for him. He gives Rohan a kite and a letter. Jassi writes in the letter that she is not very good with goodbyes; hence she was leaving without meeting him. She tells him to take care of his brother Purab.  By the time Rohan finish reading the letter, armaan gets there. Armaan wants to know what Jassi has written in the letter. Rohan tells him that it is personal. He adds that Jassi has mentioned in the letter that she is going to the mountains for few days. She might go to Mussourie. Armaan is wondering why Jassi is acting so weird. He is now very tensed. He leaves the hotel and heads back to Mumbai.  Purab is walking on the beach, feeling very sad. He is remembering and missing Jassi. Rohan joins him and they share a nice moment. Malika is looking for armaan. Raj tells armaan jassi and Nandu are nowhere to be found. Armaan is tensed and enters  the office looks around when Maria tells him to go to the meeting. He thinks and says that why did you leave me Jassi! Why? Now he and Raj would have to tell everyone the truth (the mess Gulmohor was in and also about Kohinoor) He enters the boardroom and is shocked by something. What could it be? Is Jassi back?   ============================================= Unofficial Site on  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin    Join the  urlLink India Forums  to discuss about  urlLink  Jassi  . Click   urlLink here   to view  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin   Forum =============================================
     

        
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
        Posted by:  urlLink Ashwirya Shetty      Purab tries to know Jassi better and tries to convince her that she has a golden heart. And that she loves the whole world but not herself.  Raj makes Armaan believe that Jassi loves him and her heart beats for him.  Raj persuades Armaan to get Jassi back from Alibagh.  The Lawyer continues blackmailing Raj and asks for money as a part of the partnership in Gulmohur. Raj gives money to the lawyer in some parking lot and has a Gulmohor employee (sorry cannot remember the name) film him handing the money to the lawyer. The lawyer tell Raj that this money is only the 'shagun', meaning he will come back for more money.  Rohan tells bebe that Jassi and Purab should get married which leaves Bebe thinking. Armaan leaves to get Jassi back escaping Mallika's eye. Bebe is happy to see Jassi come back to her oldself. Jassi tells her that in trying to please everyone else, she lost herself. Now, she has found herself (identity) and is happy. Bebe tries talking to Jassi about Purab. Jassi reads her mind and says that Marriage is not for her, she wants to just concentrate on her work now. Jassi packs her bag to leave.  The Manager informs Rohan that Jassi is leaving. Rohan is surprised and upset and goes in search of Purab. While he is running on the road a car comes and halts next to him (for a second it looked as if it would have hit Rohan). Rohan glares at the driver, the driver roll down the tinted windows...the driver is Armaan...both glare at each other. Armaan in his typical pompous style gestures with his index figure for Rohan to come close.  Preview: Raj informs Armaan that both Nandu and Jassi are missing and their family members are also not aware of their whereabouts. He adds that this is a serious situation. Armaan when entering Gulmohor is thinking how they could let him down especially when he has informed his dad about it.  ============================================= Unofficial Site on  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin    Join the  urlLink India Forums  to discuss about Jassi. Click   urlLink here   to view  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin   Forum =============================================
     

        
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
        Posted by:  urlLink Ashwirya Shetty     Purab saves Jassi from drowning. Purab could not believe that Jassi did not know how to swim yet without giving it a second thought she jumped into the water to save Rohan. He shouts at her, she shouts backs saying she knows she is comes from a middleclass family and that she does not know how to swim, but she would not die, she is a survivor and would somehow survive.  In the meanwhile, Raj is trying all his tricks and luck to know Jassi's whereabouts from Nandu.Raj cannot outsmart Nandu but Mrs. Verma leaks the secret out to Raj indirectly without knowing it. Now Raj know Jassi is at Alibagh.  Purab appreciates Jassi courage, how she selflessly helps others but Jassi is lost in her own world of thoughts. Rohan makes up with Purab and they became friends and true brothers. Later, Jassi finds chocolate coins at a trail written "WE" "ARE" "SORRY". Purab and Rohan say 'sorry' to jassi and make her smile.  The nutty manager also says sorry. When Jassi asked him why he was saying sorry. He said that Jassi smiled and looked happy when Purab and Rohan told her sorry, he thought he would make her more happy if he said sorry too. This makes all of them laugh.  Madi gets mad at Malika and her brother for not getting the right accessories and then says that he will not work until Jassi comes back.   Malika gets angry and tells Madi that she thought that he hated Jassi. Madi says he did not hate her work, he disliked Jassi's looks. Malika tells Armaan that next day at four o'clock there will be a board meeting and Jassi has to there and give them a reason for not being in the office.  If  Jassi is not not present then the board will take a decision without Jassi and move on. Raj comes in and Armaan tells Raj about the meeting. Raj assures Malike that Jassi will be back in Gulmohur at the meeting tomorrow. Armaan is surprised because he doesn't know that Raj knows that he know where Jassi is.  Preview: Tonight, Rohan gets Bebe thinking when he tells her that Purab and Jassi should get married. Meanwhile, Armaan leaves for Alibagh to get Jassi back.Will he find her?   ============================================= Unofficial Site on  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin    Join the  urlLink India Forums  to discuss about Jassi. Click   urlLink here   to view  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin   Forum =============================================
     

        
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
        Posted by:  urlLink Ashwirya Shetty      Jassi and Purab look at each other while Rohan is sulking in the background. Jassi asks Purab about his and Rohan's relationship. Purab asks for Jassi's help as Rohan likes Jassi and might listen to her. Purab calls her Jassi and then apologizes. He asks Jassi if he can call her Jassi. Jassi seems to be a bit surprised to hear her name from Purab. She nods a yes.   Purab quickly tells her that she should not add `ji' after his name and he hates `ji'. Jassi tells him that both the brothers share a lot of hate. That he Purab hates ji while Rohan hates Purab. Purab tells Jassi that one should run away as happiness does not follow everywhere. This sets Jassi thinking about how she is running away. Armaan meanwhile is guarding Jassi's cabin like an experienced watchman. Mallika is adamant to get through. Armaan is thinking about how to stop her. Raj quickly asks Armaan if he has the keys. Armaan is as usual quick to catch on the ishara.   He looks from Raj to Mallika in a but off course fashion and says that he does not have the keys and the door is looked. Mallika and Aryan are amused.   Aryan is shooting wicked smiles. Mallika does not fall for Armaan's lies this time. She smartly asks him if he expects that she would believe that he will not have the keys to the cabin and that he means Jassi locks her cabin and does not divulge with the keys. Armaan sticks to his ground. Mallika and Aryan helplessly leave. Armaan and Raj breathe a sigh of relief and Raj unwisely tells Armaan that it seems that they are at war now. Armaan is very angry, bangs his hand to the pillar and referring to Jassi says that where she has got him in trouble.  Jassi sits on the front stairs leading to their room. She remembers purab's comments about running away and how unknowingly they actually fit her life.   Flashback to Armaan telling Jassi that she is his favorite assistant, Armaan giving her car keys and Armaan giving her a rose. Jassi seems to take a deep breathe and gets up. she then remembers Armaan plainly telling her forget the way she was insulted and head straight to Gulmohur. Jassi thinks that she cannot continue like this.  Next day, Jassi comes out of her room with her hands filled with picnic materials. She seems to be very eager to go and hit the picnic spot. She calls on Bebe and asks her to move quickly. She is very impatient which makes Bebe tells her that she is not of her age. Jassi smiles and says that then Bebe should walk like Jassi's age. They look at each other and smile.   As they turn around their smiles drop. They see Purab and the ever ready to slip into any role sardar on a bullock cart. Purab looks grumpy like Billo usually does. Jassi is surprised to not find Rohan. She asks Purab where Rohan is. Purab says he is sitting behind. Jassi and Bebe walk behind the cart. Rohan is lying down and is sulking because he did not get to sit in the front. Bebe smartly tells him that princes don't drive their carts. Purab is grumpy as ever. Bebe notices this and whispers this in Rohan's ears. Rohan says that Purab is kharoos.  Armaan and Raj are back to square one. Today they have to get Jassi's cabin open to Mallika and Aryan who had warned yesterday about breaking the door if things get out of hand. Both are filling up large cartons with the files from Jassi's cabin. Armaan angrily tells Raj that he has to clear his secretary's cabin. Raj asks him about other titles that he bestowed on Jassi like his assistant, vice- president of finance, owner of Kohinoor. Armaan is angry and tells Raj to shut up as Jassi will always remain his secretary. He is eager to get the files out. Raj asks him to wait and first let him make sure that the coast is clear. He comes out and finds himself face to face with Aryan who wants to know when Armaan will come to he can enter the cabin. Raj lies that Armaan has not yet arrived. Aryan mocks Raj that he has made Armaan's cabin his new home. Raj asks Aryan to stop doing chowkidari. Aryan wryly smiles and reminds him that today they somehow will have to open Jassi's cabin. Raj says he knows. Aryan leaves. Raj and Armaan sigh in relief and quickly grab the boxes and turn to leave. Maithalee comes in and her eyes pop out on seeing Armaan and Raj in their new coolie avatar. She asks them if they want her help. Armaan and nazreen hold one box while Maithalee helps Raj with his box. They make quite a loony pari. Four of them juggle boxes between them and get out of the lift. Bindiya sees pari coming and asks them to go in after first telling the struggling four to come out.   Nazreen and Maithalee push Armaan and Raj back into the lift. When pari comes Bindiya informs her about some manager wanting to meet Armaan. she praises pari and pari looks happy and leaves. when she leaves, the four of them come out again and continue with their balancing act. Armaan is very uncomfortable. Mallika seems to be heading towards them. Trishala tries to keep her at bay by giving her wrong calls. Some Mallika is heading Armaan's way. Ruby's antennae sense this and she warns Armaan and Raj. Raj and Maithalee ungainly walk and hide behind the pillar. Armaan is so taken aback that he leaves the box in nazreen's hand and quickly hides. Nazreen stands like a display statue with her back towards Mallika. Mallika is stopped by ruby who praises Mallika for her choice and leads her away to select outfits for models.  Armaan, Raj and company search Gulmohur and hide the boxes.  Purab and Bebe watch Jassi and Rohan playing. Bebe tells Purab that Jassi is making Rohan understand while he should understand something from that.purab and Jassi walk alone on the beach. Jassi tells Purab that he has to get close to Rohan. She asks him to fold in pants, remove shoes. She leaves Purab thinking. He frowns. Purab, Jassi and Rohan fly kites. Its Rohan and Jassi verses Purab. Jassi tries to make Rohan understand that just like to fly kites air, kite, thread and person handling the kite are important similarly to be happy a house, family rishte etc are important. She gets lost in her thoughts and she mishandles the reel which makes their kite fall. Purab looks sad. Rohan is angry at Jassi and he storms off.  Nandu waters the plants and asks them to not complain to Jassi. someone unknowingly to Nandu enters the house. Nandu goes and sits near the computer. Someone grabs his shoulder and Nandu jumps like he has got an electric shock. He is surprised to see Raj and asks Raj if he cannot simply just say hello and stretch his hand forward. Raj apologizes and tells Nandu that he has not come to know about Jassi but meet Nandu who he believes is a finance genius. Nandu's eyes shine. He says off course he is good at finance. Raj plays along and mentions names of financing companies. Nandu gets excited. Raj takes Nandu to a five-star hotel to talk. They reach the club. Nandu is impressed by the way a girl comes and hugs Raj while Raj does his usual flirt routine. Raj introduces Nandu to the girl and calls Nandu as his finance consultant.  Nandu puts back his shoulders and tells the girl that she can call him Nandu. His dreams seem to have been realized when the girl hugs him. Raj looks disgusted. The girl leaves and Raj guides Nandu to a table. He orders for alcohol and gets Nandu drinking. Nandu talks about how he is quite impressed by Raj. Raj is trying to keep up a smile. Nandu talks about how he cannot sustain his impressions.   Raj tries to get Jassi into the picture with all his talks. Nandu seems to have lost control by now. His glasses are askew and hair ruffled. He looks zonked off and makes kissing sounds in the air. Raj looks sick  Jassi is now with Rohan and asks him if he does not want a home. Rohan says he has hostel. Jassi tries to make him realize that he is lucky to have a brother. Rohan is angry and asks her whose side she is on. Jassi smiles and says she is on both the sides. Rohan is angry and says that he knows she sides Purab and he runs towards the sea. Jassi is worried and runs behind him. Both get deeper into the sea. Jassi cannot even notice Rohan and the salty water in her eyes is making things worst. Purab notices this and runs towards the sea. Bebe shouts for Jassi and sprints behind Purab. Purab shouts for Rohan. Rohan calls out to Purab and says that he is fine but Jassi is not. Purab searches for Jassi but Jassi is nowhere to be seen. He notices Jassi caught in the waves.  Preview- Mady wants Jassi. Mallika is upset and asks Mady that she thought Mady hated her. Mady says that he hates her ugly looks but not her work.  Mallika is taken aback.    ============================================= Unofficial Site on  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin    Join the  urlLink India Forums  to discuss about Jassi. Click   urlLink here   to view  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin   Forum =============================================
     

        
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Hello Friends,  Thanks for the continued support and appreciation.  To make the site easy to navigate daily updates are also being posted to the  urlLink Jassi Forums .   Two new category have been introduced.  1.   urlLink Preview Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin    This section will have the "to be telecast" episode details. There might be some difference as its being taken from the original Betty La Fea script.  2.    urlLink Jassi Jaissi Koi Nahin Daily Update   Read the story of Jassi Jaissi Koi Nahin. The show is telecast on Sony Entertainment at 9:30 PM IST (+5:30 GMT)  Monday to Thursday.  Special credit to  Ashwirya  without whom I think it would not have been possible to update on a daily basis.   Cheers,   urlLink Vijay Bhatter    urlLink http://vijay.bhatter.com   urlLink http://www.cyberax.net    ============================================= Unofficial Site on  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin    Join the  urlLink India Forums  to discuss about Jassi. Click   urlLink here   to view  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin   Forum =============================================
     

        
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
        Posted by:  urlLink Ashwirya Shetty      Mallika calls her friend, Geeta, who works as a journalist for a top fashion magazine. Mallika asks Geeta that how come Geeta has not yet published any  article on Gulmohur's fashion show. Geeta tells her that she is still waiting for model photographs for her to print the article. Geeta hangs the phone in a hurry saying that she is busy. Ruby comes into Mallika's room and complains to Mallika that Maddy is upset because the materials and accessories have not yet arrived and hence he will not able to meet with the deadlines. Mallika angrily says she knows that materials have not arrived. She asks ruby how comes she (Ruby) has not followed up with the suppliers for the material. Ruby tells her that she did call the supplier; the supplier told her that they have spoken with Mallika. Mallika keeps quiet and does not tell Ruby about the showdown she had with the supplier. When Ruby was leaving the room Aryan walks in. Ruby asks him if he has prepared the models' contracts. Aryan coolly says no and that he will get it done later. Ruby gives him a dirty look and leaves. Aryan tells Mallika that the check for the Models has to be signed. Mallika tells him to get it signed by Armaan. Aryan refuses and tells Mallika to get Armaan's sign on the checks. Mallika tells him that they haven't yet received the materials or the model photos. Aryan tells that Armaan is to be blamed, as advanced payment was not made to the supplier. Mallika looks thoughtful, now she has got an excuse for not getting the material on time!  Maddy is pacing angryily in his workarea; he is upset that the models have not yet arrived.  Ruby tells him that since the models is being irregular in their attendance because they haven't got the contract yet. He shouts at her to get the contract in place, she tells him that she is not responsible for this, and that Aryan/Mallika are responsible for getting the contract in place. Maddy does not care, he tells Ruby to fire these inefficient models.  Mallika goes to armaan's office. She tells him that the supplier was rude to her and wonders at the kind of supplier Gulmohor has been dealing with till now.  Armaan angrily tells that they never had any problems with the supplier before this and since she was handling this show why was she telling him all this. She says, that these are his supplier. He angrily tells her to find her own supplier. Mallika gives him the file that has all the invoices/bills. She tells him that advance payment has been done for the model contracts etc.  Armaan opens the file and is shocked to see the amount. He asks sarcastically whether these cost are for trial models or ramp models. Mallika gives him a stare and tells him that it is a responsibility to ensure that the show is a success and she will do whatever it takes. Armaan tries another tactic; he tells her that normally such payments are done afterwards. This does not work; she wants the payment to me done immediately.  Armaan is sitting with his head in his hand, when Raj enters is office in the usual carefree style.  He knows something is wrong when he sees Armaan in this posture. He teases and asks which woman is responsible for this new tension. Armaan tells him what happened (about the episode with Mallika and money shortage etc).  Armaan asks Raj from where the money will come. Raj asks Armaan what he (Armaan) intends to do. Armaan tells him that Kohnioor will have to assist them financially (again!).  Jassi walks in and like always Armaan asks her where she was. Before she could respond, Armaan tells her that if she wants to leave at 6.00pm sharp then she should report on time too. Her stare is itself speaks for her anger. However her voice is cool, she tells him that she went to bank as they were late with their installment payment, so she wanted to apologize to the bank manager. Armaan who does not want to give up angrily tells that she should have informed him. She tells him that she informed Pari. Armaan tells her that Pari did not inform him. Jassi tells him that she cannot take responsibility for pari's action (or inaction) (I loved this dialogue J). Armaan asks her why she did not try to reach him on his cell. She tells him that she did not want to disturb his personal life for such a trivial matter. Armaan is angry, but does not know what else to tell her. Raj seeing that things were going out of hand, tries to calm Raj. Armaan controls his anger, he then tells Jassi that he wants Kohinoor's checkbook. Jassi tells him that she does not have it with her at the moment; she will request Nandu to get it. Hearing Nandu's name Armaan looks irritated.  Next scene they show Jassi's home, where her mom is taking a registered letter from the post-man. The registered mail is for Jassi. Jassi's mom gives the letter to Balwant. It is a job offer letter from a top fashion house for Jassi. Jassi's mom does not like it one bit. At that moment Jassi calls and asks her dad about Nandu. Balwant was tempted to tell her about the job offer, then thought better about it and did not say anything. Nandu was not at their place at that time. Nandu walks in few minutes, and Bebe tells him that Jassi had called for him. Balwant remembers the messages and tells Nandu to take the checkbook and related papers to Gulmohor. Nandu is very please about going to Gulmohor, Why? He gets to see Pari! He gathers all the stuff and is about the leave, when the letter in Balwant's hand attracts his attention. He peers over Balwants shoulder, and reads the letter. He comes to know that it is an offer letter for Jassi. Balwant tells Nandu to reveal this to Jassi and only he (Balwant) will inform Jassi about it. Nandu does not say anything and leaves. He reaches Gulmohor and tells Maria to inform Jassi about him.  Maria is happy to see him and holds his hands while trying to reach Jassi. Nandu looks a little uncomfortable when she is holding his hands. Jassi line is busy, so she calls Armaan extension and tells him that she has been trying to reach Jassi, but found her line busy, hence she was calling his extension. She tells him that Nandu has come for Jassi. Armaa, in is usual style, yells for Jassi. Jassi speaks with Nandu. She then informs Armaan that Nandu will be present in the meetin too. Armaan looked as if he was ready to murder someone. Jassi tells him that Nandu know the finance stuff and would be able to provide better advice. Armaan did not have any choice.  Armaan, Raj Jassi and Nandu are in the boardroom. Armaan turns to Jassi, stretching his hand out on the table, and asks her for the checkbook. Nandu immediately removes the checkbook and keeps it on the table.Jaasi places her hand on top of the checkbook and takes it behind. Armaan and Raj looked bewildered. Jaasi tells them that she need to see the file (that carries all the invoices and bills).  Armaan is very angry and asks her very angrily what did that mean. She tells them (Armaan and Raj) that they (all four) have to be careful now since the court has issued an ordered against Gulmohor and the court will be checking every transaction that takes place between Gulmohor and Kohinoor Armaan asked whether Jassi was going to refuse them the money. Jassi told him that was not what she meant. Nandu offer a suggestion, he tells them to avoid problems, Kohinoor will do the payment to the vendors (all bills etc).   Armaan looses control and walks out of the room; Raj follows him to pacify him. Jassi and Nandu remain in the room. Nandu is curious to know what Raj and Armaan are talking. Jassi tell him to mind his own business.  A cooler Armaan and Raj re-enter the boardroom. Armaan tells that if the models are paid through Kohinoor, they might tell others about it. Jassi agree with him. Nandu suggest that they can pay cash to the models and check to the supplies. Raj agrees, he tells Armaan that supplier do not care from where the money is coming as long as they are paid. They all seemed to agree on this. Jassi tells them that she will get all the paper work done and that she will see Nandu out.  Armaan is very upset, he rants and raves to Raj, that now he (Armaan) is reached such a stage where he has to listen to Nandu Verma! Raj tells Armaan that Jassi is totally for Nandu. She listens to everything that he has to say. Raj tells Armaan that he should break Jassi and Nandu’s relation.  Jassi tells Nandu to wait for a moment. She wanted to speak with Ruby and let her that the contracts have been taken care. She tells Nandu not move from the place till she is back. He is happy to wait, as there chance that he might get to see Pari. He sees Maddy and Mallika fighting and finds it amusing. He comments about the fight to Jassi, Jassi tells him that this happen when there is too much work pressure. In the background, Raj and Armaan are eavesdropping on their conversation. Precisely at that moment Nandu tells Jassi to leave Gulmohor and come to Kohinoor, and they both can make money. He tells her. Nandu tells Jassi about the job offer too. Raj and Armaan hear all this. Raj tells Armaan that he has to win Jassi over…Is that possible?  ============================================= Unofficial Site on  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin    Join the  urlLink India Forums  to discuss about Jassi. Click   urlLink here   to view  urlLink  Jassi Jaissi Koi Nahin   Forum ============================================= Check out  urlLink Vijay Bhatter's personal homepage  
     

        
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
        Posted by:  urlLink Ashwirya Shetty      Armaan asks Jassi why suddenly she wants to move out of her room (office). She tells him that her work and responsibility has increased and hence she needed more space for her work. Armaan tells that he would find it difficult with her working outside his room. She tells him that she is a responsible person and will ensure that there is no problem after she moves to another  room.  When Jassi turns to leave Armaan office, Armaan asks her where she is going. She tells him that it is 6.00pm. Armaan and Raj are surprised. Armaan enquires how come she is leaving so early. She tells him that her work hours completes at 6.00pm. Before Armaan could say something, Raj tells Jassi goodnite. Jassi responds with 'good evening' (which is funny!). Raj tells Armaan, that Armaan should not allow Jassi to leave current her office (which is inside Armaan's office) at any condition.  Nandu is at an open door restaurant. He tells the waiter to get 'lassi' every 15 minutes as he has long wait ahead. He is waiting for Jassi. Jassi  immediately comes, and they both are happy to see each other. Nandu asks  whether Armaan did not make her wait after office hours. She tells him that she has changed. Nandu wants to order something to eat. But Jassi refuses, says that she is fed-up of eating outside food and will go home to eat food  prepared by her Mother. Nandu asks her about her Alibagh trip. Jassi suddenly remembers that Armaan had come searching for her at Alibagh. She asks Nandu whether he had told Armaan about her whereabouts. He says no, but  his 'dushman' mother blurted it out in front of Raj. Jassi tells him that she has a very good time, and she also made friends with two people, one a  kid, Rohan and his brother Purab. She starts to sing Purab's praise. Nandu  does not like it one bit. He is jealous that Purab might have replaced his  position, as Jassi's best friend. He gets angry and walks off. Jassi looks  after him, picks her stuff and leaves too.  When Jassi reaches home, Balwant comments about Armaan making her work overtime. She tells him that she was with Nandu and not at work. He tells  that he knows that she went to Alibagh because she wanted to get away from Armaan. Jassi is dumbfounded; she continues to stare at Balwant. Bebe is standing behind Balwant is gesturing to Jassi that Rohan had called and that is how Balwant knows. But Jassi could not understand Bebe gestures. She  looks at her dad and says I do not understand, which is meant for Bebe. While Balwant was questioning, Jassi mom comes and tells Jassi food is  ready. Jassi uses that as an excuse and escapes from her dad's probing questions.  Raj and Armaan had Jassi's office room cleaned. The room looks much better. Jassi enters her office; Armaan immediately puts his hands on her eyes to  give her surprise about her room. She immediately pushes his hands away from face. Armaan looks perplexed and little hurt. Raj leads her into her room. She and looks around at the changes in the room, but her expression does not change much. They tell her that the one spare room has been given to Aryan and it would be difficult to get her a room right now. She tells them she is willing to stay in the current room temporarily. Armaan and Raj leave her room. Armaan is angry that she is going to stay there only temporarily.  Jassi comes out of her office carrying a file. Armaan asks her where she is  going. She tells him that she is going to the lawyer. Raj offers to go along with her. She refuses says that Nandu waiting for her at the lawyers office.  Armaan looks angry when he hears Nandu's name. Nandu is at Jassi's home, ready to leave for the lawyer office, when Balwants stops him and asks him to work on Jassi's resume. Nandu tries to tell him that he has to meet Jassi, Balwant brushes it away and makes him work on Jassi's resume.  Jassi is at the lawyer's office. She has a serious look on her face. She tells the lawyer that he is her lawyer, but he his taking Gulmohor's side. He has smug look on his face, and indicates that he knows what is happening. She removes the video camera, and shows him the shot where he is taking  money from Raj, and tells him that she will use this against him to show  that he is taking money from Gulmohor to work against her (Kohinoor). She  tells him that he will loose his license. He gets very nervous and  apologetic. He is back on track. He informed her that the court has sent the order against Gulmohor.  Mallika is checking with the gang members whether the work relating to the  fashion show is done. Ruby tells her that Maddy is calling her. She says she is busy and will see him later. When she turns to go, she dashes into Jassi. She gives Jassi a disgusted look and asks her why was she pretending that she was in a rush and all busy, when she was not having any sponsibility  for the fashion show. She taunts Jassi, she tells her that Jassi should come to the fashion show, and see how beautiful and decorated it would be. The  gang is standing few feet away and listening to Mallika. They are upset with the way Mallika is talking to Jassi. Maddi comes rushing and tells her that  the fashion show will not happen and to call everyone concerned to the boardroom. Mallika is stunned. She angrily tells Jassi to inform everyone.  Jassi, Mallika, Maddy and Aryan are in the boardroom. Armaan and Raj enter the boardroom. Armaan is surprised to see Jassi in the room. He asks her when she returned, she does not respond. Maddy tells them the fashion show  cannot happen. Aryan tells them that because  'band' (strike) has been declared for Saturday (the day the fashion show was scheduled for),  everything will be closed. Someone suggested postponing the show by one day. But Maddy says that it cannot be postponed as the model had to fly to France the next day. Then it was proposed to keep it one day earlier. To which  Mallika said no, saying it would not be possible to make it arrangement one  day earlier. Raj responded by saying that he has a 'magic wand', Jassi, who can help Mallika take care of all the arrangements. Mallika gets angry and agrees to do it one day earlier, but she will be in charge and on one else. Armaan tells Mallika that in time of crises she should keep her ego aside. She assures that this will be the best fashion show ever. Aryan smirks at the trio (Armaan, Raj and Jassi). They all file out of the room.  Armaan asks Jassi about her meeting with the lawyer. She tells him that the  entire problem with the lawyer has been solved. She also informs that the  court has sent the orders against Gulmohor. Armaan and Raj look tensed. The  phone in her office rings, she goes to answer it. It is Nandu. Raj and  Armaan listen to their conversation. Nandu tells her that he could not come to the lawyer's office because Balwants wanted him to update Jassi's resume.  Armaan and Raj are stunned.   ============================================= Unofficial Site on  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin    Join the  urlLink India Forums  to discuss about  urlLink Jassi . Click   urlLink here   to view  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin   Forum =============================================
     

        
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Hi All,  I do not know how will Jassi be looking onscreen when she turns from an ugly duckling (sorry she isn'nt that bad) to an aesthetically pleasing dame.   But I am certain that she would be somewhere near Mona Singh (the girl playing the role of Jassi) original looks. And here are some of her pictures.                Courtesy: ModelWatch.IndiaTimes.com & PuneFashions.com    More pictures of her already posted on the  urlLink India Forums  :  urlLink Jassi Jaissi Koi Nahin  in the General Discussion category.  Cheers,  urlLink Vijay Bhatter   urlLink http://vijay.bhatter.com   ============================================= Unofficial Site on  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin    Join the  urlLink India Forums  to discuss about Jassi. Click   urlLink here   to view  urlLink  Jassi Jaissi Koi Nahin   Forum =============================================
     

        
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Courtesy: Deccan Herald ( http://www.deccanherald.com/deccanherald/apr042004/ent8.asp )  - SHAHEEN RAAJ  After Nausheen Ali Sardar, who had played Kkusum in Sony TV’s serial Kksusum to such perfection, walked out of the serial, it was the turn of Jassi nee Mona Singh of Sony TV’s popular serial Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin to follow suit. And she would have almost done it if the makers Deeya and Tony Singh had not given her a well deserved break of bringing a surprise twist, of a new man and a new kid entering her life, to the story and to her character too.   According to the insiders of the Jassi … camp Mona Singh was literally fed up of donning the same ‘Bahenji’ look of Jassi day in and day out which is also not proving to be of any great shakes to further her career, not to speak of the contract that she is bounded and bonded with.   So as of now Mona Singh has reversed her decision of walking out of the serial, but has definitely walked out of her dull and drab boss Armaan Suri’s (Apurva Agnihotri) life and buzzed off to Ali Baug for a well deserved holiday after she was sternly and disgustingly humiliated, on screen of course, by Armaan Suri’s fiancee Mallika (Rakshanda Khan). Not only these, the makers Deeya and Tony Singh now also intend to bring back Jassi in the Armaan Suri camp only in her new, hep and a totally modernised avatar.    ============================================= Unofficial Site on  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin    Join the  urlLink India Forums  to discuss about Jassi. Click   urlLink here   to view  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin   Forum =============================================
     

        
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Hi All,  The Unofficial Site on Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin gets a new look. I hope you will like it.   More importantly you can now post your comments on the site and give feedback on a particular post.  I have also updated my personal homepage at  urlLink http://vijay.bhatter.com   Cheers,  urlLink Vijay Bhatter    
     

        
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Cinema meets TV By: Shaheen Parkar  May 21, 2004  --------------------------------------------------------------------------------     For the first time a character from the big screen will step into the small screen to share space with a serial’s character.   This unique pairing off will unfold in Sony’s soap Jassi Jaissi Koi Nahin on May 27. It will have Bollywood’s current flavour of the season Saif Ali Khan make a cameo appearance in Jassi.   Saif will essay his role of Karan Kapoor, a cartoonist, from his forthcoming film Hum Tum. He will visit Gulmohar House after Jassi invites him over to the fashion house to debate his viewpoints as illustrated in his comic strips — that men are from Mars and women are from Venus. Jassi will beg to differ and so will the bunch of secretaries who, too, are avid readers of his comic strip.  Saif shoot with Jassi yesterday at Chitrath Studios, Powai for the episode. According to Tarun Katiyal, Sony’s executive vice-president, programming and response, “Jassi is a popular show and Saif is a popular star.   As cartoonist Karan Kapoor, the attitude he reflects is quite contrary to what Jassi thinks. This pairing will makes for some great viewing.”  The move to mingle the characters, it is learnt is at the behest of Hum Tum’s producers Yashraj Films. Hum Tum releases on May 28.     Courtesy: Mid-Day Source: http://web.mid-day.com/entertainment/television/2004/may/838 05.htm   ============================================= Unofficial Site on  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin    Join the  urlLink Jassi Jaissi Koi Nahin Forums  to discuss about Jassi. Click   urlLink here   to view  urlLink  Jassi Jaissi Koi Nahin   Forum =============================================
     

        
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
       Vivek Oberoi in Jassi   Another SAif huh..Anyway you guys will love to see Vivek too in Jassi. By IndiaFM News Bureau, June 01st, 2004 - 1300 hrs IST   Vivek Oberoi follows Saif Ali Khan's footsteps. And we are talking of the Jassi effect! So after Saif Ali Khan appeared as his screen character of Karan Kapoor from Hum Tum on May 27 episode of the Sony tele-serial Jassi Jaissi Koi Nahin, Vivek may appear in the same serial sometime soon.   And while Saif promoted his film through the serial, Vivek will promote the Coca Cola brand, which he endorses. The modalities are being worked out between the channel and the Coca Cola Company and if everything goes fine, Vivek will appear as his ad character in multi-colored outfits and thick glasses in the serial.   All one can say is Vivek's retro look may perfectly compliment that of Jassi. Wakaw!  SOURCE:WWW.INDIAFM.COM  ============================================= Unofficial Site on  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin    Join the  urlLink India Forums  to discuss about Jassi. Click   urlLink here   to view  urlLink  Jassi Jaissi Koi Nahin   Forum =============================================
     

        
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
       Sony and Jassi are winners at Apsara Awards   Well guys, Jassi (Mona Singh)  bagged Best Actress In Apsara Awards held On May 31st.Here is the full story coverage, Sony Entertainment Television and DJ’s A Creative Unit, producers of the show Jassi Jaissi Koi Nahin, had reason to celebrate on the evening of May 29. The television show romped home with key trophies at the first-ever Apsara Awards. Instituted by the Film Producers Guild of India (FPGI) on the occasion of its Silver Jubilee year, the awards recognized excellence in both cinema and television.  Jassi walked away with the coveted Best Actress (Mona Singh), Best Drama Series and Best Director (Rohit Khanna) awards, while Sony Entertainment Television was felicitated for its intelligent and innovative marketing of the show. Eagle Video’s Office Office on SAB TV was adjudged the Best Comedy Series, apart from bagging trophies for the Best Ensemble (Cast) in a Television Series and Best Actor (Pankaj Kapoor).  Also on the hallowed list of winners was Crest Communications’ Tenali Raman for the Best Animated Series, NDTV’s Big Story on Afghanistan for Best Factual/Non-Fiction and ZEE’s Sa Re Ga Ma Pa for the Best Musical Show. Balaji Telefilms, though conspicuously absent in most categories, did manage to pocket the Best Television Production Company award, while the title track of Aroona Irani’s Des Mein Nikla Hoga Chand fetched the Best Title Song trophy. NDTV journalists Rajdeep Sardesai and Barkha Dutt were declared the Best News Anchors from a lot that included Prabhu Chawla of Aaj Tak and Deepak Chaurasia of DD News. While receiving the trophy, Sardesai, who is managing editor of NDTV India and NDTV 24X7, waxed eloquent about the need for integrity in the field of journalism. “It is sorely missing,” he said, capping it with a tongue-in-cheek reminder to “watch NDTV”.  Meanwhile, Subhash Chandra, chairman of the Essel Group, which includes companies ZEE Telefilms, Essel Propack, Playwin Infravest, Esselworld, Water Kingdom and Fun Republic among others, was felicitated with a special award for Outstanding Contribution in the field of television.  In the cinema section, the popular awards of Best Actor, Actress, Director and Film went to Hrithik Roshan (Koi Mil Gaya), Urmila Matondkar (Bhoot), Rakesh Roshan (Koi Mil Gaya) and production house Filmkraft (makers of Koi Mil Gaya). Pankaj Kapoor struck it rich for the second time as the winner of the Best Actor in a Supporting Role for the film Maqbool, while the Best Actress in a Supporting Role went to Jaya Bachchan for Kal Ho Na Ho.   Some of the other prominent awardees included Sonu Nigam (Best Male Playback Singer), Alka Yagnik (Best Female Playback Singer) and Shankar-Ehsaan-Loy (Best Music). Thespian Dilip Kumar was felicitated with the Lifetime Achievement award, while directors Raju Hirani (Munnabhai MBBS), Dr Chandraprakash Dwivedi (Pinjar) and Nikhil Advani (Kal Ho Na Ho) took centrestage for Best Debut Direction.   Source: www.agencyfaqs.com   ============================================= Unofficial Site on  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin    Join the  urlLink India Forums  to discuss about Jassi. Click   urlLink here   to view  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin   Forum =============================================
     

        
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
         urlLink    Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin Wallpaper from SetIndia.com&nbsp;   urlLink    Arman Suri and Mallika (Wallpaper) from SetIndia.com&nbsp;   urlLink    Mallika (Rakshanda Khan) Wallpaper from setindia.com&nbsp;  
     

        
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
       I love Armaan Sir     Mumbai, June 1: SMILING from behind the now-so-familiar braces and broad-framed spectacles, Jassi chirps, inviting you for a glass of lassi. That’s her pick up line, she tells VJ Nikhil Chinappa, on the sets of MTV Select. Jassi and Nandu have been invited on the show that will be aired on June 7, at 4 pm.  The two guests talk animatedly about life at Gulmohar House, their friendship and dolphins in Singapore, where they visited with ‘Armaan Sir’. ‘‘The funniest moment was when people started calling me pink dolphin, as I was dressed in pink,’’ says Jassi. Mona Singh, the actor, is living her telly life, refusing to dress or talk out of her character.  Jassi changes from her favourite pink to a shameless red, when she talks about Armaan Sir. ‘‘He was the first person to give me a job, irrespective of my looks.’’ Is marriage on the cards, asks VJ-turned-shrink Nikhil, ‘‘Maybe someday I will marry him, if Babaji (Father) allows.’’ gushes Jassi.  From bungee jumping to learning how to say ‘will you run away to India with me?’ in Chinese, Nandu is confused as ever. Quick to confess that pretty faces distract him, he beams, ‘‘I am sure one day Pari will be mine. She can’t pay her bills anyway, I can support her financially.’’  Never-ending-giggles Jassi and dimpled-cheeks Nandu have the cameramen in splits. Says VJ Nikhil, after losing a round of arm-wrestling to Jassi, ‘‘Doing MTV Select with Jassi was fun. She is the coolest person in India right now and our show is all about being cool.’’  Pink clothes or no pink clothes, life for Gulmohur’s sweetheart has definitely changed. ‘‘I get mobbed when I go out. But it feels nice to be recognised,’’ says Nandu’s best friend, whose identity seems sewn with her screen image.  So do you ever swear under your breath, asks VJ Nikhil. ‘‘I can only say kutta (dog) and gadha (donkey),’’ ensuing another of her loving fights with Nandu. Sourse:http://cities.expressindia.com/fullstory.php?newsid=86416 ============================================= Unofficial Site on  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin    Join the  urlLink India Forums  to discuss about Jassi. Click   urlLink here   to view  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin   Forum =============================================
     

        
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
       I have no identity crisis: Jassi  By IANS Jun 19, 2004, 00:13  Her real name is Mona - but she has completely obliterated her own personality. To that extent, getting to talk to Jassi isn't easy. The makers of "Jassi Jaisi...Koi Nahin" hover anxiously around her to make sure she doesn't slip out of character even when the cameras are switched off. It's been six months since the soap went on air - and its popularity has only multiplied in the interim. "At times I pinch myself. Is all this really happening to me? The character is so real, everyone has met a Jassi. People find it easy to relate with Jassi," says the talented actress in an interview. Jassi admits shooting around the clock for the same serial gets cumbersome at times."Sometimes I do pine for a break. I do get drained, and want to go for a holiday. But this is my chance to consolidate my position."Moreover, since my character and I are so alike, I don't have to make too much of an effort to be Jassi. In my free time I catch up with my close friends. I go out for dinner, or cook at home. "I also get a soothing massage done by this elderly lady who is my Florence Nightingale at the end of the day." Jassi says she enjoys being recognized as Jassi in public places. "I don't mind being known as Jassi. Like I said, she's so much like me. I live all alone in Mumbai - my parents visit once in a while - so my work is my pleasure and life."  Isn't there an identity crisis? Jassi is well versed in fielding that one."No, no identity crisis!" she laughs as though she expected the question, then quickly changes the subject."The other day I had gone to my dentist. And he told me all the kids want braces like Jassi. Isn't that cute?"A lot of viewers feel Jassi has been taking too much trash from the people around her in the soap, specially her boss.  "That's because she has been taught by her parents and grandmother to be good to everyone, even if they're not being good to her."But now there's going to be a drastic change of attitude in her. She won't take any of this lying down any more. "A changed Jassi will really make audiences sit and revaluate Jassi. She's going to assert herself with the boss. "So far she's been living her life for others. Now it's her turn to live for herself. And now my boss Armaan (Apoorva Agnihotri) will woo me in right earnest. But Jassi won't get married in the near future. Let's see what the future has in store." Within six months, Mona Singh alias Jassi has become a household name. "I know. But one has to be very level headed in life. I know success istemporary. So I won't let it go to my head. When I started playing Jassi I never knew it would change my life so drastically. It was a big risk for all of us. And by the grace of God, the gambit worked." She admits playing Jassi has affected her. "I was always very cool-headed. Now all of a sudden I get very hyper, just like Jassi. I keep telling myself: 'Hey it's happening to Jassi, not me.' But Jassi and I are the one and the same."  © Copyright 2004 by MusicIndiaOnLine.com ============================================= Unofficial Site on  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin    Join the  urlLink India Forums  to discuss about Jassi. Click   urlLink here   to view  urlLink  Jassi Jaisi Koi Nahin   Forum =============================================
     

        
</post>


</Blog>