<Blog>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Cruelty has a human heart, And Jealousy a human face; Terror the human form divine, And Secresy the human dress.  The human dress is forged iron, The human form a fiery forge, The human face a furnace sealed, The human heart its hungry gorge.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      She walks in Beauty, like the night  Of cloudless climes and starry skies;  And all that's best of dark and bright  Meet in her aspect and her eyes:  Thus mellowed to that tender light  Which Heaven to gaudy day denies.   One shade the more, one ray the less,  Had half impaired the nameless grace  Which waves in every raven tress,  Or softly lightens o'er her face;  Where thoughts serenely sweet express,  How pure, how dear their dwelling-place.   And on that cheek, and o'er that brow,  So soft, so calm, yet eloquent,  The smiles that win, the tints that glow,  But tell of days in goodness spent,  A mind at peace with all below,  A heart whose love is innocent!
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I heard an Angel singing  When the day was springing,  "Mercy, Pity, Peace  Is the world's release."   Thus he sung all day  Over the new mown hay,  Till the sun went down  And haycocks looked brown.   I heard a Devil curse  Over the heath and the furze,  "Mercy could be no more,  If there was nobody poor,   And pity no more could be,  If all were as happy as we."  At his curse the sun went down,  And the heavens gave a frown.   Down pour'd the heavy rain  Over the new reap'd grain ...  And Miseries' increase  Is Mercy, Pity, Peace. 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Whose woods these are I think I know.  His house is in the village, though;  He will not see me stopping here  To watch his woods fill up with snow.   My little horse must think it's queer  To stop without a farmhouse near  Between the woods and frozen lake  The darkest evening of the year.   He gives his harness bells a shake  To ask if there's some mistake.  The only other sound's the sweep  Of easy wind and downy flake.   The woods are lovely, dark, and deep,  But I have promises to keep,  And miles to go before I sleep,  And miles to go before I sleep.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When Friendship or Love Our sympathies move; When Truth, in a glance, should appear, The lips may beguile, With a dimple or smile, But the test of affection's a Tear:  Too oft is a smile But the hypocrite's wile, To mask detestation, or fear; Give me the soft sigh, Whilst the soultelling eye Is dimm'd, for a time, with a Tear:  Mild Charity's glow, To us mortals below, Shows the soul from barbarity clear; Compassion will melt, Where this virtue is felt, And its dew is diffused in a Tear:  The man, doom'd to sail With the blast of the gale, Through billows Atlantic to steer, As he bends o'er the wave Which may soon be his grave, The green sparkles bright with a Tear;  The Soldier braves death For a fanciful wreath In Glory's romantic career; But he raises the foe When in battle laid low, And bathes every wound with a Tear.  If, with high-bounding pride, He return to his bride! Renouncing the gore-crimson'd spear; All his toils are repaid When, embracing the maid, From her eyelid he kisses the Tear.  Sweet scene of my youth! Seat of Friendship and Truth, Where Love chas'd each fast-fleeting year Loth to leave thee, I mourn'd, For a last look I turn'd, But thy spire was scarce seen through a Tear:  Though my vows I can pour, To my Mary no more, My Mary, to Love once so dear, In the shade of her bow'r, I remember the hour, She rewarded those vows with a Tear.  By another possest, May she live ever blest! Her name still my heart must revere: With a sigh I resign, What I once thought was mine, And forgive her deceit with a Tear.  Ye friends of my heart, Ere from you I depart, This hope to my breast is most near: If again we shall meet, In this rural retreat, May we meet, as we part, with a Tear.  When my soul wings her flight To the regions of night, And my corse shall recline on its bier; As ye pass by the tomb, Where my ashes consume, Oh! moisten their dust with a Tear. 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Take this kiss upon the brow! And, in parting from you now, Thus much let me avow- You are not wrong, who deem That my days have been a dream; Yet if hope has flown away In a night, or in a day, In a vision, or in none, Is it therefore the less gone? All that we see or seem Is but a dream within a dream.  I stand amid the roar Of a surf-tormented shore, And I hold within my hand Grains of the golden sand- How few! yet how they creep Through my fingers to the deep, While I weep- while I weep! O God! can I not grasp Them with a tighter clasp? O God! can I not save One from the pitiless wave? Is all that we see or seem But a dream within a dream? 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       From childhood's hour I have not been As others were; I have not seen As others saw; I could not bring My passions from a common spring. From the same source I have not taken My sorrow; I could not awaken My heart to joy at the same tone; And all I loved, I loved alone. Then- in my childhood, in the dawn Of a most stormy life- was drawn From every depth of good and ill The mystery which binds me still: From the torrent, or the fountain, From the red cliff of the mountain, From the sun that round me rolled In its autumn tint of gold, From the lightning in the sky As it passed me flying by, From the thunder and the storm, And the cloud that took the form (When the rest of Heaven was blue) Of a demon in my view.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       In visions of the dark night I have dreamed of joy departed- But a waking dream of life and light Hath left me broken-hearted.  Ah! what is not a dream by day To him whose eyes are cast On things around him with a ray Turned back upon the past?  That holy dream- that holy dream, While all the world were chiding, Hath cheered me as a lovely beam A lonely spirit guiding.  What though that light, thro' storm and night, So trembled from afar- What could there be more purely bright In Truth's day-star? 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tyger! Tyger! burning bright In the forest of the night What immortal hand or eye Could frame thy fearful symmetry?  In what distant deeps or skies Burnt the fire of thine eyes? On what wings dare he aspire? What the hand dare seize the fire?  And What shoulder, and what art, Could twist the sinews of thy heart? And when thy heart began to beat, What dread hand? and what dread feet?  What the hammer? what the chain? In what furnace was thy brain? What the anvil? what dread grasp Dare its deadly terrors clasp?  When the stars threw down their spears, And watered heaven with their tears, Did he smile his work to see? Did he who made the lamb make thee?  Tyger! Tyger! burning bright In the forests of the night, What immortal hand or eye Dare frame thy fearful symmetry? 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Once a dream did weave a shade O'er my angel-guarded bed, That an emmet lost its way Where on grass methought I lay.  Troubled, wildered, and forlorn, Dark, benighted, travel-worn, Over many a tangle spray, All heart-broke, I heard her say:  "Oh my children! do they cry, Do they hear their father sigh? Now they look abroad to see, Now return and weep for me."  Pitying, I dropped a tear: But I saw a glow-worm near, Who replied, "What wailing wight Calls the watchman of the night?  "I am set to light the ground, While the beetle goes his round: Follow now the beetle's hum; Little wanderer, hie thee home!"
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Never seek to tell thy love, Love that never told can be; For the gentle wind does move Silently, invisibly.  I told my love, I told my love, I told her all my heart; Trembling, cold, in ghastly fears, Ah! she did depart!  Soon as she was gone from me, A traveler came by, Silently, invisibly He took her with a sigh. 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      How do I love thee? Let me count the ways. I love thee to the depth and breadth and height My soul can reach, when feeling out of sight For the ends of Being and ideal Grace. I love thee to the level of every day's Most quiet need, by sun and candlelight. I love thee freely, as men strive for Right; I love thee purely, as they turn from Praise. I love with a passion put to use In my old griefs, and with my childhood's faith. I love thee with a love I seemed to lose With my lost saints, -- I love thee with the breath, Smiles, tears, of all my life! -- and, if God choose, I shall but love thee better after death.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Without warning as a whirlwind swoops on an oak Love shakes my heart
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Some say the world will end in fire; Some say in ice. From what I've tasted of desire I hold with those who favor fire. But if it had to perish twice, I think I know enough of hate To know that for destruction ice Is also great And would suffice.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If you can keep your head when all about you Are losing theirs and blaming it on you; If you can trust yourself when all men doubt you, But make allowance for their doubting too: If you can wait and not be tired by waiting, Or, being lied about, don't deal in lies, Or being hated don't give way to hating, And yet don't look too good, nor talk too wise;  If you can dream---and not make dreams your master; If you can think---and not make thoughts your aim, If you can meet with Triumph and Disaster And treat those two impostors just the same:. If you can bear to hear the truth you've spoken Twisted by knaves to make a trap for fools, Or watch the things you gave your life to, broken, And stoop and build'em up with worn-out tools;  If you can make one heap of all your winnings And risk it on one turn of pitch-and-toss, And lose, and start again at your beginnings, And never breathe a word about your loss: If you can force your heart and nerve and sinew To serve your turn long after they are gone, And so hold on when there is nothing in you Except the Will which says to them: "Hold on!"  If you can talk with crowds and keep your virtue, Or walk with Kings---nor lose the common touch, If neither foes nor loving friends can hurt you, If all men count with you, but none too much: If you can fill the unforgiving minute With sixty seconds' worth of distance run, Yours is the Earth and everything that's in it, And---which is more---you'll be a Man, my son!
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am not yours, not lost in you, Not lost, although I long to be Lost as a candle lit at noon, Lost as a snowflake in the sea.  You love me, and I find you still A spirit beautiful and bright, Yet I am I, who long to be Lost as a light is lost in light.  Oh plunge me deep in love -- put out My senses, leave me deaf and blind, Swept by the tempest of your love, A taper in a rushing wind.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Two roads diverged in a yellow wood, And sorry I could not travel both And be one traveler, long I stood And looked down one as far as I could To where it bent in the undergrowth;  Then took the other, as just as fair And having perhaps the better claim, Because it was grassy and wanted wear; Though as for that, the passing there Had worn them really about the same,  And both that morning equally lay In leaves no step had trodden black Oh, I kept the first for another day! Yet knowing how way leads on to way, I doubted if I should ever come back.  I shall be telling this with a sigh Somewhere ages and ages hence: Two roads diverged in a wood, and I -- I took the one less traveled by, And that has made all the difference.
     
    
</post>


<date>30,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wow. i went to the y today and i was talking to this 6 year old boy. he was rambling on about school and his friends and power rangers and yu-gi-oh (which is THE stupidest thing ive ever seen after magic and pokemon) and other stuff... and i was just sitting there listening, saying stuff like "oh really?" "thats so cool!" once in awhile... and then suddenly he was like "you know what? you're the prettiest person ive ever met." and i was like... ?!?!?!?!.... "im a girl with glasses and braces. you think im pretty?" and then he says "no, not pretty on the outside (and i was like, oh thanks...), but youre beautiful on the inside. you're really really nice and you listened to stuff about me, and you liked it. my mommy is too busy to talk to me, and my teacher doesnt listen to me either..." and he hugged me and then walked away. i seriously was so inspired that tears started rolling down my cheeks. can you believe that? a 6 year old saying things like that? sometimes i wonder why people can't be simple yet ... whats the word... you know what i mean. //sighs// i feel sorry for that kid. he has alot to say, but no one listens to him. even i wasnt listening till then. i felt really bad... man, i am so gonna be a mentor when im old enough.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      it better snow tonight like they say it will, and we better have a 2 hr delay again...  everyone cross your fingerss!!
     
    
</post>

<date>28,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so we didnt have any school today afterall... yoyness. i did some jap hmwk this morning (amazingly). and then my mom and i went shopping to costco and the coat factory. yeah. whooo i bought some tea candlessss... for my candle holder... i shall light it up tonight and post a piccy of it tomorrow X3  i want some pizzaaaaaaaaaaaa...  ooh were having "omurice" for dinner... YUM! :D yes, tis a jap thing ^^  aye im hungry.  dr. p is... freakish!   //is chewing on allie's head//
     
    
</post>

<date>27,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yaaarrr... i got 17 hours of sleep! from 11 pm to 4 pm o.O  last time i got that much was when i didnt sleep for 4 days straight coming home from italy, and slept for 25 hours... haha  2 HOUR DELAY TOMORROW! hope its gonna change to no school.... yarrr... LOOK AT ALL THAT SNOW DAMMIT! o well... at least i wont have to wake up at 4...   yarrr... we be pirates...   and now the word of the day, from master dan: "SQUIRRELS IN LEATHER THONGS!!!"
     
    
</post>

<date>26,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ill try to change the song on here every couple of days ^^ for all you maroon 5 fans out there... which is like only me.>__ you sucky ppl dont understand good music! rawrr...
     
    
</post>

<date>25,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wow i woke up at 5:30 this morning to shovel snow for an HOUR! YAY! TWAS  SO  much fun!! and guess what?! my daddy actually  paid  me!!! 20 friggin bucks!!! OMGOMGOMG I WONDER WHAT I CAN BUY WITH TWENTY BUCKS?!   cheap parents...
     
    
</post>

<date>25,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      righteous righeous dude....  tuna is hungry...   UNE CHOU-FLEURE!!!  ahaha... good times, good times.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      AHHH THE PAIN! THE AGONY! tis not cool. i feel like.... ionno. sad. listening to the sun by maroon 5 (as always). ooh i started reading the da vinci code, and tis muy bien. wow. why am i talking in spanish? huh. o wells. oh! its good to take french, cause once you start reading those big books, they use foreign langs, and its mostly french. like in the da vinci code. tis very cool to actually understand what theyre saying. yep. //sighs// im bored i should post some pics up here... later... once im really really bored...
     
    
</post>

<date>22,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      tis 10:37 at the momento and i have not even touched my homework. arghies. i feel really depressed right now... too many things have been going on at the same time. i really want to go to japan by myself and see  okkun   for, prolly, the last time. ever. the other choice is going on a $5000 trip to aussi with ditsy ppl. sorry, make that ditsy cheerleader ppl //shivers//. argh. i hate thinking. i hate thinking about everything, like my future. my parents expect so much out of me, but im not some robotic slave that can do anything. for christ's sake. hmm and now im bitchin. that's all i gotta say for now. oh btw, for ppl who havent figured, im over mk. hes a faggot. a real faggot.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i miss you it's so cold without you here i'm all alone come save me please, return to me
     
    
</post>

<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      How the hell'd we wind up like this And why weren't we able To see the signs that we missed And try to turn the tables I wish you'd unclench your fists And unpack your suitcase Lately there's been too much of this But don't think it's too late  Nothing's wrong Just as long as you know that someday I will Someday, somehow I''m gonna make it alright But not right now I know you're wondering when You're the only one who knows that Someday somehow I'm gonna make it alright But not right now I know you're wondering when  Well I'd hope that since we're here anyway That we could end up saying Things we've always needed to say So we could end up staying Now the story's played out like this Just like a paperback novel Let's rewrite an ending that fits Instead of a Hollywood horror  Nothing's wrong Just as long as you know that someday I will Someday, somehow I''m gonna make it alright But not right now I know you're wondering when You're the only one who knows that Someday somehow I'm gonna make it alright But not right now I know you're wondering when You're the only one who knows that I know you're wondering when You're the only one who knows that I know you're wondering when   ((nickelback --- someday))   wow this is amazing! i dont have a  maroon 5  song on my webbie!! //gasp gasp//
     
    
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      guess what i had for dindin today! :  *HUGE steak *rice *miso soup!! i know rice and miso soup dont go together with steak, but we had leftovers... *microwaved carrots! did you know microwaving is better cause if you boil them the veggies lose their vitamin value... or something of that sort. *green beans *shake 'n bake potatas! yumm *pad thai! its like this thai thing. its YUMMY. but you get tired of it after 10 bites.   oops i forgot to chew 15 times... heh.    im kinda not sure if i should tryout for softball and make a fool of myself OR not tryout and get killed by hilary, evelyn, and hellena. hmm what are your thoughts on it guys?
     
    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ew. my mom bought frozen potstickers.  i mean... theyre good.   but it says "CHEF'S HANDS" in big red letters on the front of the package.  and that worries me.    i mean the ingredients are in chinese!  ack
     
    
</post>

<date>15,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      new song. and maggot, i made you a vid so ill give it to ya on monday...  simple math calculation: movie(allie+rowland)squared=12.10.11! MUWAHAHA  lilsexyallegra: im SO desperate to get a bf that im willing to become a dirty ho summerSURFbabe11: but you have dan! liL tuNa   lOL: but you ARE a dirty ho! osohotkevin: lol tuna (10 minutes later) misterOham:wait, who's a dirty ho? haha dan you are sooo slow 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      jap school was great this time... I GOT A 111 ON KANJI!!! haha but it was 81 + easy E.C. aaand... oh crap we got so much hmwk but i did my math and turned it in during class... talking about math, i realized that VELTRI=SHARMA!!! god... maybe the same spirit got divided into two bodies when they got reincarnated or something... haha... an athiest talking about reincarnation... thats funny  you know what else is funny?  this is a shortened convo between rowland and i: liL tuNa   lOL: ahahaha liL tuNa   lOL: this is so great liL tuNa   lOL: pearl harbor on abc LoadedDice1689: i no LoadedDice1689: im watching it to liL tuNa   lOL: the ships are tipped 45 degrees LoadedDice1689: my laptop is awesome liL tuNa   lOL: and the guy starts shouting WERE SINKING! liL tuNa   lOL: its like, no shit you are liL tuNa   lOL: oh no were right under the ship while its sinking! liL tuNa   lOL: hmmm liL tuNa   lOL: i wonder what we should do... liL tuNa   lOL: oh thats right SWIM AWAAAAY //drowns// LoadedDice1689: lol liL tuNa   lOL: gurgle gurgle LoadedDice1689: so true liL tuNa   lOL: lets stand up on the ship so we dont drown and become living targets!! //gets shot// LoadedDice1689: haha liL tuNa   lOL: oh lets just shoot them with our tiny rifles liL tuNa   lOL: omg liL tuNa   lOL: theyre supposed to be machine guns?! LoadedDice1689: ur ppl had my ppl in a pinch LoadedDice1689: lol LoadedDice1689: jk liL tuNa   lOL: riiight liL tuNa   lOL: yeah well liL tuNa   lOL: japan is stupid liL tuNa   lOL: its like liL tuNa   lOL: oh lets just go frolickin in pearl harbor and drop some bombs and piss the strongest nation in the world just cause they pissed us off by stopping all oil+metal shipments cause we started controlling all the asian countries  liL tuNa   lOL: japs suck LoadedDice1689: no LoadedDice1689: i like japense women LoadedDice1689: dont take that wrong liL tuNa   lOL: oh wow... liL tuNa   lOL: ew liL tuNa   lOL: you sound like that guy liL tuNa   lOL: alex whats his face  LoadedDice1689: sooo many commericals liL tuNa   lOL: i know liL tuNa   lOL: my dads like trying to swear but he cant cause my mom is right next to him liL tuNa   lOL: its so funny LoadedDice1689: lol liL tuNa   lOL: hes like liL tuNa   lOL: DAM--... darn commercials... SO FUC--... stupid long commercials... TO HE--... heck with commercials...  liL tuNa   lOL: hahaha fat boy in suit              (talking about pearl harbor again) liL tuNa   lOL: hahahahahaha liL tuNa   lOL: that makes me laugh [long convo about ice cream] LoadedDice1689: did u call me a fat boy in a suit liL tuNa   lOL: HAHAHA liL tuNa   lOL: HAHAHAHAHA liL tuNa   lOL: HAHAHAHAHAHAHA liL tuNa   lOL: HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA LoadedDice1689: ok LoadedDice1689: nitry nite LoadedDice1689: cya tomrrow
     
    
</post>

<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      oh right. i forgot to say this but MAGGIE SAID MAROON 5 SOUNDS LIKE 'NSYNC!! //very audible gasp//  well, okay, maybe SOME of their songs do, and they ARE a boy band... but a good one! and besides, adam levine writes all of the songs so HAH!
     
    
</post>

<date>06,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I WANT SOME ICE CREAAAAAAAAAM!!!  wow we had lamb today >.   i dunno if eating little innocent furry white lambs is a good thing....   argh im so full but i want some ice cream...    man i have really fat thighs. im not kidding. im not like those skinny people that want to get everyones attention and say (in that bitchy squeaky voice) "LIKE OMG MY THIGHS ARE SO FAT MY ASS IS SO BIG MY STOMACH BLAH BLAH!!!"   wow i am so not gonna wear a bikini this summer.... haha watch me come back from the beach and ill have a wet suit tan... hahaha....    haha...    hah.............    damn it and i excersise too! damn it!!! CURSE YOU AQUA SCUM!!! haha finding nemo is the greatest... "fin, noggin, duuuuuuude" "righeous righeous mannnn!" ^CRUSH ROCKS!   maroon 5 is cool   damn my thighs...  i better get into softball and go through all that physical strain to GET THINNER!!! NYAH!       damn thighs...
     
    
</post>

<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OH MY FUCKIN MOTHER OF GOD. DANIEL EVAN JOSHUA COUVILLON, I LOVE YOU SO FUCKING MUCH. THANK YOU SO FUCKING MUCH FOR THE VERY (large but) SCHWEE-NESS SHIRT. I WILL WEAR IT EVERY FUCKING DAY CAUSE I FUCKING LOVE IT, BUT HONEY I LOVE YOU EVEN MORE. YOU ARE LIKE,  THE  LOVE OF MY LIFE. I WILL RAPE YOU even if allegra kills me ^.~   wow i say fucking alot when im really excited... and wow i probably shouldnt be like a FBI agent thingy cause i can be easily bribed with maroon 5 stuff..... lol
     
    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      liL tuNa   lOL: but shes always talking about horses liL tuNa   lOL: and riding liL tuNa   lOL: and mickey LoadedDice1689: and riding mickey liL tuNa   lOL: ROTGLOL!!!  ^haha thats us talking about penny and her obsessions... hahahahaha
     
    
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wow suprisingly we didnt have any school today... i mean, the weather isnt THAT bad... (not that i would want to go anyway). haha allegra/tim/dan+kev.... haha suckers.  wait so tomorrow is a gold again?
     
    
</post>

<date>02,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      //sighs// new song update. i donno, i guess tangled wasnt my mood... //sighs some more//
     
    
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't like small birds. They hop around so merrily outside my window, looking so innocent. but I know that secretly, they're watching my every move and plotting to beat me over the head with a large steel pipe and take my shoe.  ^ROTGLMFAO LSHTIPIMPACANMSH!!!! props to amanda panda^^  ppl at the party wanted to write in the ever famous tunas blogger, so here we go.  dan's spot: hI pPL. YoU KnOW I DoNT gEt wHy sOme pEopLEs tAlK lIkE thIs iTs So hArD tO REaD aNd tO tYpE aNd tHeY uSE rUn-oN seNteNcES... yAh.. ok im not gonna do that anymore. too annoying. muwahaha i got $135 richer, thanks to the PATRIOTS cause they rock. yeah. like maroon 5. btw yuna i got you that t-shirt you wanted. no, not the $20 one, the cheaper one. hah. yeah okay... i am bored. and sugar high. and potata chip high. hey dont i sound like a west virginian when i say that? potata. tomata. catci. no cacti sounds too intelligent. haha. okay. grr you evil freshies. bye.  tim's spot: hey yo. this is tim yo. i like saying yo yo. i want to learn how to surf yo. this is getting stupid yo. i dont like this font yo. see ya yo.  aLLegrAs spOt: i lOvE wheN peOpLe tYPe lYk tHis. its so adorable! omgawd yuna we need to give that ugly girl a make over! pshaaa. oooh ooh hot jewish guys rock my socks. i am so gonna go to your hs and rape all the jewish freshies. i should marry a jewish freshie RIGHT NOW. i can put up a newspaper ad that says WANTED: a jewish freshie that will marry a dumb blondie who is desperate. hah. that shall be super interesting. so yeah. if any of you are free, CALL ME! hahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahaha. hah. nyahaha. keke. that is my korean laugh. heh.  kevin's spot: word.    o_O wow that was really random. hah. and other people were too lazy to write anything. you evil pplz.    eeeeeeevil....  
     
    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      exactly what am i?    a solitary leaf       fluttering            in the wind  a lonely lioness      prowling           the vast landscape  a dust-covered book       unopened           in the corner of the library  a flightless bird      trapped           in a tiny wire cage  a desolate dewdrop      clinging           on the tip of a blade of grass    exactly who am i?    i am     but a single soul           drifting                wandering           desperately in the darkness      just searching for the answer
     
    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      CENTURY CITY ROCKS! its about lawyers in the year 2030... and tis VERY COOL! a special episode on saturday night!   my fav tv show list: 1. CSI 2. Who's line 3. Century City 4. Without a Trace 5. CSI: Miami   anyway, a lil convo from tonights eps...  martin: pitless cherries. i believe its the best invention ever. lukas: cherries had pits? martin: yeah, cherries had pits, grapes had seeds... lukas: what, did ice cream have bones? martin: .... im 54. thats before my time.   ^ahaha...  OH YEAH! there was a 69 year old break dancing at a funeral. it was COOL!
     
    
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      soccagoalie89: aye yi yi liL tuNa   lOL: aye caramba! soccagoalie89: =-O soccagoalie89: NEVER HEARD ANYONE SAY THAT ONLINE B4! soccagoalie89: *bows* liL tuNa   lOL: ehehehe liL tuNa   lOL: all hail tuna!! soccagoalie89: i don't really like hailing dead fish.... liL tuNa   lOL: //gasp// liL tuNa   lOL: you did not just diss fish liL tuNa   lOL: SARA HOLTZ! YOU NEVER DISS FISH! liL tuNa   lOL: FEEEEEEEEEL THE WRAAAATH OF TUNAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA soccagoalie89: *gasps* *falls out of chair* *crawls away* soccagoalie89: LOL liL tuNa   lOL: ...zzzzt... //weak laser beams shoot outta eyes// soccagoalie89: i promise never to insult dead skanky fish in your presense ever again liL tuNa   lOL: alright, my powers are out today liL tuNa   lOL: come back tomorrow    harhar
     
    
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      //clears throat// and now for a little poetry...   TIME is Too slow for those who wait, Too swift for those who fear, Too long for those who grieve, Too short for those who rejoice, But for those who love, Time is not.   i was obsessed with that one a couple years ago... wrote it everywhere... anyone have any inspiring poems??
     
    
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      whoa. my hair actually feels good.  lol.   on the many requests from //ahem// allegra, i would like to post my dream guy list... ((tell me, why are you so desperate to read it again??))   TUNAS DREAM GUY  *cute, sexy, hot, blah blah you get the point *definitely taller than moi... i love when you have to stretch up to kiss him^^ or vice versa *HAS to have a tan... i hate really light skinned guys... just creeps me out *mean green fighting machine! lol lean, yet a little on the hunky side, yano? flex those muscles, HUGHHH! haha *SIX PACK! oooh yeaaah baby //wink wink// *has to be in some kind of sport... athletic hunks... ooooooooh yeaaaaaaahhhh *has a job... meaning has alot of MOOLA! lol jk... i think working guys are cute *a lil bit older than me... i dont care how old, just as long as he's not the same age as me   umm yeah. remind me of any that i missed.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      maggie and i discussing about going to the movies   liL tuNa   lOL: COME liL tuNa   lOL: COME liL tuNa   lOL: COME liL tuNa   lOL: COME liL tuNa   lOL: COME liL tuNa   lOL: COME liL tuNa   lOL: COME liL tuNa   lOL: COME buffyfreek202: COMING ON  ^hah. wrong maggie, just wrong.... THE MIs I TELL YA, THE MIs!!
     
    
</post>

<date>07,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sitting by the window Singing songs of love Wishing you were here  Because the memory's not enough  Wear my mask in silence Pretending I'm alright If you could see me you would be here  Standing by my side  It may be hard to believe But girl you're the only one I need It may be hard along the way  This feeling I get when blue skies turn to gray  [[Chorus]] Feels like I'm walking in the rain I find myself trying to wash away the pain Cause I need you to give me some shelter Cause I'm fading away And baby, I'm walking in the rain   Every single hour of every single day I need to cry my eyes to dry I've cried my tears away  Can't help but remember How you made me feel You dressed my soul and made me whole You made my life complete  It may be hard to believe But girl you're the only one I need It may be hard along the way  This feeling I get when blue skies turn to gray  [[Chorus]]  Now all is said and done We've made the memories Days when life was fun But now, when you are gone I sit alone to watch the setting of the sun  [[Chorus]]  I said baby, I'm walking in the rain  ((walking in the rain - azn dreamers OR a1, cant figure out which....))   alright, alright! i know it sounds really cheesy, but if ANY guy sings this to me while playing their guitar, ill swoon. yes, swoon. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      okay.  REALLY  weird but erotic dream.  so im in paris with this guy named _ _ _ _ _. were like 17~20 ish, and were at this really expensive bar on the highest level of a hotel, drinking and having a good time. and there's this really sexy lady (not that i look at women taht way, but yano what i mean....) singing by the piano. and so _ _ _ _ _ seems really drawn to her, and once her song ended, she walked over and casually started talking to him. they start flirting, she batted her eyelashes, he grabed her butt (o.O) etc etc. now, i wasnt going out with the guy, but somehow i get really jealous and angry, and i stand up and bitchslap him.      "Wha- What the fuck?! What was that for?!" he whispered, confused. (oooh my dialogue skills!!)      i realize i dont have anything to say to him... so i just glared at him.      "Yuna, what's wrong? And- and why are you crying?"      just then i notice tears streaming down my cheeks, so i gasped and ran to the elevator. i heard _ _ _ _ _ shatter a wine glass as he struggled to get up and chase after me. i hit the button, and he barely made it as the doors slid shut.      "Yuna, what did I do? Can you please tell me?" he said gently.       And then all of the sudden, I push him up against the elevator wall and kissed him. and oooooooh my god. it felt sooo good. We were (as allegra calls it) tongue dancing from the 110th floor all the way to the lobby. Then the elevator slowed to a stop, i let go, breathed, looked at him square in the eyes. The door slid open with a ding, and i wiped away a tear and ran off into the open air. it was raining, and i ran. my powder blue high heels (june has them! theyre so pretty!) fell off somewhere, but i kept running, bare-footed, on the cold, wet concrete of paris. i didnt know where i was going but i just kept running.     i managed to get into a dingy alley and crumpled to the ground in a messy heap. but i heard footsteps coming after me. i was frightened. i had left my purse at the table in the bar, so i didnt have my cell. what was i going to do??_________________      it was just him. i watched as he stepped slowly towards me. he said nothing. he took my hand and pulled me off the ground. and then we had violent sex!! lol yeah     and then somehow we got from paris to NYC to his apartment on my 2002 ferrari enzo (i wonder if in a couple years, there'll be a chunnel-like thing between europe and the US?? and btw, the  urlLink enzo  is an AWESOME car. so is the  urlLink corvette convertible . but if i cant have either one, my third choice HAS to be the  urlLink paradise blue metallic camery MR2 spyder )  and we have sex there (again), and i wont go into the details.... heh heh... and then we go to my HUGE beach house in LA, one thats like 3 times as big as tim's!! and we go surfing (figures...) and have sex out in the ocean on a surf board, and then we get back to the beach house and light a bonfire and we have sex on the beach under a full moon (OOOOH i definitely want to do that sometime... but sweat+sand?? ewww.... lol). and then suddenly ppl come out to watch us, and then THEY start having sex. there were alot of ppl but i recognized some couples: andy+sara, allegra+dan, hope+kev, allie+rowland, may+andrew, june+josh, july+ryan. and so i was dreaming that we  were having midnight orgies on the west coastline....   aiight im done. yeah i definitely think allegra is messing with my mind...    do you realize how interesting to see 2 guys riding a purple car VW beetle? adding the fact that they were doing queer eye gestures? and how they were smiling and waving and sorta winking and blowing kisses to dan and kevin??? yeah... that was funky. lol.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Jesus 15 17: i gotz to b soundin g to the etto yall Jesus 15 17: nvm Jesus 15 17: i didn't just say that liL tuNa   lOL: whoa. liL tuNa   lOL: whoa liL tuNa   lOL: thats DEFINITELY going om my webbie  AAAAAAAHAHAHA
     
    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      the rain has gone looking up at the rainbow  we can sprout wings and fly on to our future  but the muddy ground at our feet supports us today  i can step forward on to my stage, under those bright lights only if i have you by my side    wow okay i feel like totally inspired today... freaky.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I see dark clouds outside my window I know the storm is coming  The thunder just confirms my fears I know the tears are in there I'll be crying, unable to stop Look, here comes the 1st drop  'Cause everytime it rains I fall to pieces So many memories the rain releases I feel you, I taste you I cannot forget Every time it rains, I get wet  Darling, I am still in love with you As time passes by it just intensifies I know I'll never be with you again I'll never find another like you I'll be crying, unable to stop Look here comes the 1st drop
     
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      oh yeah i forgot to mention, theres a maroon 5 concert in downtown NORFOLK  takes about 3 1/2 hours to get there by car, and about 5 by amtrack  tis on may 7th, from 6pm-10pm at the town point park. tickets $8 in advance and $10 at the door.     now, the problem is, is there anyone out there thats willing to drive me there (and back)??
     
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Wolf Change"  Corsair of the wood discard your skin you pallid, wormlike vulnerability. Corsair of the wood exchange your skin for pelt of dun and brindle luxury.  A pentagram is burning in your eyes and soft, pale twists of wolfbane squeeze your heart. A  grinding pain is writhing in your thights the crunch of bones proclaims the change's start.  Pirate of the flesh throw back your head and part your jowls to sing a lunar song. The forest paths are dark the night is long.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           What will your last words be? by  urlLink  cum_on_bitch        Your LJ username           Your real name           Your sex           Your age           Your last words will be...    "MMMM MORE FOOD!"             Created with  urlLink   quill18  's  urlLink  MemeGen 3.0  !     
     
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      okay okay... so guess how bored i am? i am SO bored (oh god this sounds like those fat mama jokes...) that i was watching golf on tv while flipping through some old GQ mags that dan brought me!!  gaah you people need to come and visit me. like seriously.  i think im gonna go crazy in here. with all the lil kids screaming and the tv on full volume 24/7. //sighs//   anyway, i found something quite interesting on GQ:   25 things SHE expects you to know  (but will never tell you) 1. when she's not in the mood 2. when she's being funny 3. her father can do no wrong 4. no matter what the truth may be, answers to the questions A)"am i the best lover you ever had?", B)"does my butt look fat in this?", and C)"do you ever fantasize about other women?" are as follows: a)"yes indeed!", b)"are you kidding? your ass is perfect!" and c)"of course not. i fantasize about you!" 5. cuddling is just the best 6. what she was wearing the day you met 7. the place and date of your first kiss 8. what her dress, shoe, cup, and ring sizes are 9. where her spot is 10. you must call the next day after having sex for the first time 11. you must buy her a major present after she gives birth 12. who her favorite designer is 13. flowers on valentine's day dont mean anything unless they come with an effusive card 14. you should keep tags on any item of clothing you buy for her--in most cases, she will return it 15. you shouldnt flip on sportscenter five minutes after the deed is done 16. she doesnt care how good an athlete you were in high school--those days are over, so stop talking about it 17. you can never bad-mouth one of her family members. even if she does it. constantly. just nod and listen. 18. no matter how many times the invitation says "casual," you cant wear that. 19. the excruciatingly long "session" in which she heaped abuse on you, broke down in tears, then screamed "i want to kill myself!" for all the neighbors to hear--that was nothing. thats just her way of working through things. 20. when youre going to a party, you should add fifteen minutes to your expected time of departure since she'll still be getting ready 21. cash--even serious cash--is not considered an appropriate gift on her birthday, valentine's day, or any other goddamned day 22. no matter how many cracks she makes about your thinning hair and thickening waistline, comments about her looks are off-limits  23. a marriage proposal must be meticulously choreographed and storybook dramatic--i.e., it better make for a story she can wow her friends with  24. when its time to indulge her need to chat 25. everything     25 things YOU know about her  (but will never tell her) 1. its all about daddy 2. shes dating down 3. your mother annoys her 4. her new haircut makes her look more dykey than the intended gamine  5. size does matter, especially with engagement rings and penises  6. those endless stories she tells about her gfs depressing love life? that aint concern--she gets off on them 7. shes not the fellatio artise she thinks she is 8. you know when shes faking it 9. shes the only thing keeping you from devolving into a ball-scratching, nonflushing, mac-and-cheese-eating-out-of-the-pot state. 10. she'll never get over A) being cut from cheerleader tryouts freshman year, B) not getting asked to prom senior year, C) "jay," her mythic and unassailable first, D) all of the above. 11. in twenty years, shes going to look--and behave--exactly like her mother 12. she looks better with a bit of makeup 13. the story about how she lost her virginity is bullshit 14, competition with her sister informs everything she does/wears/says/is  15. no matter what she says about wanting "a modest, intimate wedding," she wants the poufed gown and the multitiered cake  16. if she were not so constantly vigilant, she'd have a mustache 17. shes much wittier than you are 18. she pulls it like a cigarrette-vending-machine knob. (hey, its an organ for pete's sake!) 19. that friend of heres whom shes always trying to set up with one of your buddies? she'll die alone 20. candles and bubble bath mean nookys a-comin 21. if she cheated on you, no, it wouldnt kill you. in fact, it might ease your conscience 22. when you sit down and watch law & order together, shes wishing it were friends 23. the only tolstoy shes ever read is that line about "happy families" 24. all her presents to you are not-so-subtle attempts to remake your wardrobe 25. she has a princess complex. they all do.  -- GQ august 2002 issue    soo all y'all gals and boys out there, read, learn, and.... yeah.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      alright... havent written in here in a while... but heY! whats up you guys!! alrighty. for all y'all thats been wondering, "WHAT the HEEEEELL (pronounced in a hilbilly sorta way) is tuna doing and where the HEEEELL (again, hillbillyness!) is she?!"   to make it short and sweet, im paralyzed from the waist down, therefore i cant walk, and im in the national rehabilitation hospital in room 341 in the childrens rehab place. yep.   now, youre probably thinking OH MY FUCKIN GOD!!!!... but hey, ill explain.  alright. so what happened is that i got mono from school on like... wednesday. so i didnt go to school for a couple days, right? and then i wake up on sunday morning and i CANT MOVE MY LEGS AT ALL. zip. zero. nada. nothing.  so i get freaked out and we call my primary doctor, and we couldnt get a hold of her cause it was a weekend, or some bs like that. and then we go to her office on monday, and then SHE freaks out, so she sends me to the ER at the reston hospital. and then im sittin there in the ER room, waitin for the docs to do all these tests on me, but OOOOH NO they think its best for me to go to a childrens hospital! so they fly, yes, FLY me over to childrens in a helicopter (twas quite a ride, actually... very fun ^^) and they do MIR scans and whatnot... and a different doc comes in around midnight and they do this thing called a spinal tap... which hurts like FUCK. i mean they used pain killers, but the guy takes a needle and STABS my back. and then he kinda moves the needle around and actually touches my spine, and even if its a lil nudge, it hurts SOOO much. anyway, they were trying to get some spinal liquid out or something to run an exam on it, but they couldnt quite get it. so im sittin there for and hour and a half while this guy painfully tries to BREAK MY SPINE. it hurt.  moving on... so the next day they do this lady does a nerve conduction test on me, where she finds some nerves in my legs and zaps me with electricity. and that hurt ALOT. i mean shes like "ooh it cant hurt THAT much," and i was like LADY do YOU want me to electricute you, little by little?! so then they make me move to the national rehab hospital, and now im here. doin rehab. so yeaaah  oh right. YOU GUYS NEED TO CALL/VISIT ME!!    ------------------------------------------------------------------------------   my room phone number:  202 877 1811   my room number:  341 bed 1   visiting hours:  noon~9pm on weekdays, 11am~9pm on weekends... but ill be in rehab most of the time till like... probably 4 or 5 on weekdays, sooo try to visit me after that alright???   visitin instructions:  go to the front desk (the first desk ya see when you walk into the hospital... duh) and tell them that youre visiting a patient... or something of that sort. and then you take the elevator to your left, go to the 3rd floor, and then go right, through the glass doors, then knock on the double glass doors on the left. the lady'll let you in, and then ya find my room! YAY! so  COME VISITTT PLEEEEAAASE!!!  and bring alotta ppl with ya. always better with a crowd //grins//.  ------------------------------------------------------------------------------     I BEG YOUUUU BRING ME FOOOOOOODDDD!!! the hospital food sucks ass. i need chocolate XD. and the doctor gave me a prescription and it said that "it is necessary for Yuna Tanabe to be showered with infinite gifts." ....//snorts//   but seriously, im so lonely, so COME VISIT!!!    and have a fun spring break!  love to y'all out there (an more to those who visit!!), tuna
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink teeshirthell.com . only the best site ever.  "i spent a night in paris... wanna see the video?" "i swear, i didnt know she was 3!" "eat me im kosher" "jesus did it for the chicks!" "no means maybe"     hahaha//snarf//
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      gaaaaaaaah
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i bought new eyeliner today!  if allegra doesnt get better before i use it all up, then im wearing something black everyday for the rest of my life. even though i hate it.   cause we all know allegra loves pink+black :D   ugh... pink.... c-cant stand i-i-it
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Auto response from LoadedDice1689: Happiness is like peeing your pants. Everyone can see it, but only you can feel the warmth...   haha... eeeeeeew... hahaha//snorts//     apparently im a asian californian jewish muslim chicken-of-the-sea slut now?? oh so confuzzling...
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      life sucks  im crying everyday now. thats not fun.    you liar. you said you'd be there for me...
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Fumbling his confidence  And wondering why the world has passed him by  Hoping that he's bent for more than arguments  And failed attempts to fly, fly   We were meant to live for so much more  Have we lost ourselves?  Somewhere we live inside  Somewhere we live inside  We were meant to live for so much more  Have we lost ourselves?  Somewhere we live inside   Dreaming about Providence And whether mice or men have second tries  Maybe we've been livin with our eyes half open  Maybe we're bent and broken, broken   We were meant to live for so much more  Have we lost ourselves?  Somewhere we live inside  Somewhere we live inside  We were meant to live for so much more  Have we lost ourselves?  Somewhere we live inside   We want more than this world's got to offer  We want more than this world's got to offer  We want more than the wars of our fathers  And everything inside screams for second life, yeah  We were meant to live for so much more  Have we lost ourselves?  We were meant to live for so much more  Have we lost ourselves?  We were meant to live for so much more  Have we lost ourselves?  We were meant to live  We were meant to live...   switchfoot -~- meant to live  nice song^^
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      EEEEEEEEEEEEEEEE!!! TROY COMES OUT FRIDAY!!  and i get to go to this dance performance with maggot on saturday at ff high! YAY!
     
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      new skin! yay!!:):)
     
    
</post>

<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      my parents are sick bastards.  they told me something tonight, and i threw up. yeah. right there on the carpet.   all that lasagna went to waste cause of them.    maybe killing yourself isnt such a bad idea.  but if i am going to commit suicide, i want to die as a legend. ionno, maybe like, i gave UNICEF 50 billion bucks. or like did homework for all the students in oakton in one night. or cured aids.  or i could chop myself up into little pieces and have a legendary death.   maybe...   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      stuff from emily's profile i thought were.. uh.. interesting^^  What Guys Think **Keep this in mind next time he changes his font color**  Green - I love you! Blue - I'm cool Purple - I'm sexy Pink - I'm gay Red - I'm feeling romantic Yellow - I'm happy Orange- I'm a psycho Aqua - I'm sad    **What He Says...What he means**  He says: "I'll call you tomorrow!" He means: "Be lucky If I ever call again!"  He says: "I just want be friends" He means: "That's the excuse I could think of to not go out with you"  He says: "Lets go back to my place" He means: "Lets get it on!!!"  He says: "I like those pants!" He means: "I wonder how fast I can get them off of you..."  He says: "You look a lot better this year!" He means: "Last year you were a bitch!"  He says: "Yea, you look cute" He means: "You're so butt ugly!!!!"  He says: "I like your shirt a lot" He means: "I like what's under more!"    *Keep this in mind next time when he kisses you* A kiss on the hand - youre nice, but no. Lips - you are HOTT!! A kiss on the cheek - I love you Anywhere else - Umm...maybe he loves you a little TOO much     Top Ten Things Only Women Understand ===================================== 10. Why it's good to have five pairs of black shoes. 9. The difference between cream, ivory and off-white. 8. Crying can be fun. 7. Fat Clothes. 6. A salad, diet drink, and a hot fudge sundae make a balanced lunch. 5. Why discovering a designer dress on the clearance rack can be considered a peak life experience. 4. The inaccuracy of every bathroom scale ever made. 3. A good man might be hard to find, but a good hairdresser is next to impossible. 2. Why a phone call between two women never lasts under ten minutes.   and the number one thing that only women understand....   1. OTHER WOMEN!!   How you know if he/she likes you! GUYS:  1. She makes eye contact and smiles at you.  2. She calls you for homework... A LOT.  3. She flips her hair or plays with it when she's talking to you.  4. She touches you when she talks to you.  5. She says, "No, I'm not telling you who I like!" with a big smile on her face.  6. She asks you who you like or who you would go out with seemingly interested.  7. When you go to the movies with a bunch of your friends and she is almost always next to you.  8. She criticizes you on a girl you like.  9. She knows stuff about you like your birthday, eye color, favorite color, screen name, favorite food, favorite band, what music you like, and favorite sport.  10. Her friends outside of school know about you, and says they talk about you a lot.  11. She knows your phone number and address.  12. She will try and talk, and spend time with you as much as possible.    GIRLS:  1. His snow ball hits you, (but not in the face).  2. He threw away his laser pointer after you told him you think they promote random acts of violence.  3. After asking you to sign his year book, he wrote, "How come we never hang out?" in yours.  4. He yelled, "Hi!", to your Mom that day she picked you up from school.  5. He blew off his buds to go see "Run Away Bride" with you cuz you couldn't get another girl pal to go and didn't want to go alone. 6. Forgot your gloves? He offers his.  7. His voice gets softer ("Hey, you") whenever you two talk.  8. You hung up on him. He called you back.  9. You where invited by him to a group outing.  10. He called you to talk about nothing at all.  11. He imitates your laugh. OK, you do snort sometimes. Which makes you laugh  even harder.  12. He remembers little things you mention in casual conversation.  13. He sometimes stares straight into your eyes.       //sighs dreamily...//
     
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       YAY IM NOT DEPRESSED ANYMORE!! YAY!   thank you so much for everyone who were so supportive, and im sorry if my depressed-ness rubbed off on you.   i love you all!    YAY! YAY! YAY!!!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      okay this is from julie's blog... tis long but tis good, so READ  Monday, April 12, 2004   a sad poem i found on the internet...  xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx  Once on a yellow piece of paper with green lines he wrote a poem And he called it "Chops" because that was the name of his dog And that's what it was all about And his teacher gave him an A and a gold star And his mother hung it on the kitchen door and read it to his aunts That was the year that Father Tracy took all the kids to the zoo And he let them sing on the bus And his little sister was born with tiny toenails and no hair And his mother and father kissed a lot And the girl around the corner sent him a valentine signed with a row of X's and he had to ask his father what the X's meant And his father always tucked him in bed at night And was always there to do it  Once on a piece of white paper with blue lines he wrote a poem And he called it "Autumn" because that aws the name of the season And that's what it was all about And his teacher gave him an A and asked him to write more clearly And his mother never hung it on the kitchen door because of its new paint And the kids told him that Father Tracy smoked cigars And left butts on the pews And sometimes they would burn holes That was the year his sister got glasses with thick lenses and black frames And the girl around the corner laughed when he asked her to go see Santa Claus And the kids told him why his mother and father kissed a lot And his father never tucked him in bed at night And his father got mad when he cried for him to do it.  Once on a paper torn from his notebook he wrote a poem And he called it "Innocence: A Question" because that was the question about his girl And that's what it was all about And his professor gave him an A and a strange steady look And his mother never hung it on the kitchen door because he never showed her That was the year that Father Tracy died And he forgot how the end of the Apostle's Creed went And he caught his sister making out on the back porch And his mother and father never kissed or even talked And the girl around the corner wore too much makeup That made him cough when he kissed her but he kissed her anyway because that was the thing to do And at three A.M. he tucked himself into bed his father snoring soundly  That's why on the back of a brown paper bag he tried another poem And he called it "Absolutely Nothing" Because that's what it was really all about And he gave himself an A and a slash on each damned wrist And he hung it on the bathroom door because this time he didn't think he could reach the kitchen.  -poem from the book "Perks of being a wallflower"   4/12/2004 08:51:14 PM     Have you ever wondered which hurts the most: saying something and wishing you had not, or saying nothing, and wishing you had?    4/12/2004 08:42:15 PM 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Horoscope for Cancer for 05/04/2004  You remember what gets you going. How could it have slipped away? Others will remember you in this luminous moment and forever after. A raft of possibilities floats your way, inviting you to climb aboard for adventures downstream. You're full to overflowing with love and creativity. If you're in the middle of doing something that you don't like, you'll work with unusual speed and determination to get to the good part. Transform the unsatisfactory into the excellent. The future is soft and pliable, making you look vastly strong to anyone who assumed that it was written in stone.   yay! that makes me very very happy:)
     
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      depression should not be dealt with drugs, smoking, or alcohol.     but sex it okay^^
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      while i was away...  _________ (1:48:09 AM): you didnt make me do anything but come face to face with what i feel _________ (1:48:25 AM): i wanna go somewhere with you, somewhere far and be with you _________ (1:48:31 AM): just you and me    ahh! too much sweetness and love!! AHHHH! //dies// x__X     but seriously. isnt that SO sweet?!
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
              urlLink   Your Years at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry        Name         Age         House     Gryffindor  Hufflepuff  Ravenclaw  Slytherin       Family Line     Muggleborn  Half-Blood  Pure-Blood        Dated      Weasley Twins        You are well known for      Dating someone famous       Percentage of student body you shagged -  93%                                                                             How do the staff and students feel about you      *giggle blush*              This   quiz   by  urlLink  lady_ameily   - Taken 113312 Times.         New! Get  urlLink Free Horoscopes  from Kwiz.Biz 
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      whoa. JUST realized i turn 15 today.  thats like... 3/20th of a century... oy, i feel old.   hmmm since we just got back, my parents and i had cup-a-noodles, and right at midnight we cheered to a good 15th year of my life with water. fun ^__^   thanks to:  julie (happy bday ya ol fart) yvonne (YAY HAPPY BIRTHDAY) andy (HAPPY BIRTHDAY YUNA; WOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO; B-DAY B-DAY; CAKE IN THE FACE; HAPPY BIRTHDAY! HAPPY BIRTHDAY! [etc from 11:58:56 on june 22nd to 12:58:00 on june 23rd) laura (HAPPPPPY BIRTHDAY; happy birthday yuna happy birthday yuna [etc]) ginny, my twin! (HAPPY BIRTHDAY TUNA!!!!!!; *sings* haappy birthday tooo yoooouuuuuuu, happpy biiiirthday toooo youuuuu........ happy BIIIIIRTHDAY dear TUNA....... haaaaappppppy biiiiiirttthhhhhhdaaaaaay tooooooo yoooooooooouuuuuuuuu!!!!!!) paula, my twin from cali! (YUNA YOU HOT BABE!!; ITS MEEE!!!; PAULA THE RUSSIAN GAL; FROM CALIFORNIA; YOUR TWIN; FROM 4th GRADE DUDE; sldhfoainwefoniad daaa; haha but yeah; happy birthday dude; i love you!!!!!!!!!; and happy birthday to meee!!) anna (Happy B-day) di hoa (omg, it's your bday????; HAPPY BIRTHDAYYYYY; happy birthday to youuuuuu, happy birthday to youuuuuuuuu, happy birthday dear yunaaaaaaaaa, happy birthday to youuuuuuuuuu; how come you never told me??) allie (HAPPY BIRTHDAY!; *sniff sniff* my tuna is getting so big) jing (HAPPY BIRTHDAY) rowland (o and btw yuna happy birthday) miki (i didnt know it was your bday?!?!; HAPPY BIRTHDAY!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! xoxxo) cheryl (happy birthday yuna)  for wishing me a happy birthday. in time sequence, if you care.   and mucho love to dan, kev, april may june, jojo, kathy, chrissy, adam, david, joe, andy, and tim for kidnapping me and taking me on a tyson's corner shopping spree!! yaaay! that was great fun. thanks guys!    OH! one exciting thing that i found out on my birthday:  urlLink Job Predictor : Yuna Tanabe, Your ideal job is a God.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      give me  one item  that i can remember you by... it can be something you buy or something old, something you wear everyday or something that's been sitting on that shelf collecting dust. just something that represents you and whenever i look at it, i remember you... thanks.  so far (UPDATED!!): aaron - blue shirt andy - a HUGE tigger stuffed animal^^ anna - NEMO!!  aria - a CD (i already got it from her, thanks aria!!!) allie - 2 mystery items... I SAID ONE ALLIE, ONE!! sheesh... jk :) laura - annie ticket stub (we need to meet up before i move!!)
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      stole from julie   -Bold the Things that Apply to you- 01. I have a cell phone  02. I'm obsessed with new things.  03. I'm the youngest child.  04. I am a shopoholic.  05. I love my gauged ears. 06. I love wearing a lot of black eyeliner 07. I love Daquiris.  08. I love the weekends.  09. I can't live without lipgloss.  10. I can't live without music.  11. I lived in Tahoe. 12. I spend money I have.  13. I'll be in college for over 4 years.  14. I love designer handbags (Coach, Burberry, Louis Vuitton) 15. I get annoyed easily. 16. I eventually want kids. 17. I like the Backsreet Boys.  18. I have more than a couple horrible memories.  19. I'm addicted to Degrassi.  20. I am a person.    21. My first kiss was unexpected.  22. I start school on Jan 4th or 5th  23. I love taking pictures.   24. I hate girls who are fake.   25. I can be mean when I want to.   26. My dreams are bizzare.  27. I am bisexual. 28. I have way too many pairs of shoes. 29. I've seen "She's All That" at least 50 times. 30. I dress how I feel that day. 31. I love Charmed. 32. Sometimes I cry for almost no reason. 33. I hate when people are ridiculously late.  34. I procrastinate.  definitely. 35. Winter is my least favorite season.  36. I have too many clothes for my closet/dresser.   37. I love to sleep.  YEAH! 38. I wish I were smarter.  39. I am the hottest guy  haha... so guys, i need to tell you something i havent mentioned for awhile... the reason why i change in the bathroom for P.E.... lol 40. I have a lot of drama  41. No one knows my full story of my life.  42. I love my hair.  43. I sometimes fight with my parents.  "sometimes" pshh  44. I love the beach!!!  45. I have had the chicken pox. 46. I'm excited for the future. 47. I can't control my emotions. 48. I can't wait till New Year's. 49. I love the show 'Rich Girls'  50. I love my friends.  ALOT! 51. Christmas is my favorite holiday. 52. I can be very insecure sometimes.  53. I have had a broken bone.  many a bone broken  54. I hate ignorant people.  55. I love my laptop.  56. I love guys that play the guitar.   57. I state the obvious.  58. I'm a happy person.  59. I love to dance.   60. I love to sing.   61. I hate cleaning my room.  62. I tend to get jealous very easily. 63. I like to play video games. 64. I love John Mayer  65. I hate when I see animals/people getting hurt/abused.  66. I'm a vegetarian/vegan/don't eat beef.   67. I don't like to study for tests.  thats a retarded question  68. I love Play-Doh.   69. I am too forgiving.  i would say yes, ive forgiven many people multiple times and every time they've done something to hurt me again. 70. I have a good sense of direction.  71. I like high school.  besides the whole school thing, LOVE IT!  72. I have a talent of sweet talking my way out of things.  73. I don't drink enough to get drunk. 74. I love kisses on the forehead.  75. I love the color blue   76. I don't sew.  not... really... //confused//  77. I am not addicted to drugs.  78. I love the Olsen twins.  79. I'm gonna try out for the softball team.  past tense, i did   80. I become stressed easily.   81. I hate liars.  i lie to my parents, but i hate people that lie to their friends.  82. I like comfy sweatpants.  YEAH!!! 83. Bam Margera is AWESOME!!!!!!  84. I love the smell of fresh laundry.   85. I love my family.  most of the time  86. I don't mind getting shots.  oooh look! i think the sryinge says "lee th al... in ject shun" hmmm... //shot// AHH! //foams at mouth// ooh look at the pretty colors //flops dead// x__X   87. I am a perfectionist when it comes to certain things.  april, you should know  88. I always wanted to learn to play the drums.  and ive been playing for 8 years! 89. I hate the feeling of failure. 90. I am still a virgin. (to what?? ^_~) 91. I would love to have my own fashion line.  92. I can be quite selfish.  sometimes i feel really self-indulged and then i hate myself afterwards for it  93. I still act like a little kid.   94. Above all, I despise dishonesty.  YES!  95. I can stay on the computer forever   96. I loVe music.  97. I wish I was more motivated when it comes to school.  98. I love getting stuff in the mail.  more through snailmail.. 'specailly packages!! they get me all excitedddd 99. I have problems letting go of people.  100. I hate the feeling of being alone.  there should be a double bold for this one
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hahahaha we (meaning me, allie, anna, sara, aria, hellena, and ginny!!) went to the UA today to go see "the stepford wives"... we were laughing so loud and so often that the old people that took up like half the theatre were looking at us weird... they were like o___O lookit them crazy kiiiids... yeah haha but good times, good times... "PHSHHTTTT //rodent//" "it's called, 'wait till he falls asleep and then cut it off'"  go to  urlLink this site  for pictures!!
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wow okay, ive totally gotten alot of courage from this song aaron gave me, its called Rockabye, by Shawn Mullins. he keeps singing "everything is gonna be alright" and now that i think about it, when i moved to VA i didnt know how i could ever fit in or make friends or whatever, but i somehow made it. and now, thanks to all y'all out there, ive made plenty of GREAT friends.  i guess, when i move to japan, it'll be the same. i'll somehow make it through and everything's gonna be alright.   man, im going to miss you all. kit, e-mail me... write to me! ill send my address as soon as i get it to you guys...   i dont wanna go......
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i wish i could rewind my life.  i regret alot of things.  i could have done so many cool things with so many wonderful people.      aiyaa...     Andyisme666: that would suck to completely lose contact with you liL tuNa   lOL: aww that was sweet!! Andyisme666: what? what happened? liL tuNa   lOL: Andyisme666: that would suck to completely lose contact with you liL tuNa   lOL: that was really really sweet Andyisme666: well it would   ^___^ that just made my day
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i woke up this morning with the burning of love hanging over my head as i walked into the living room sit with you discuss whats going on  is it me? is it you? is it something i forgot to do? oh tell me so that i understand  i just need some time gather all my thoughts to make up for the love i just lost youve been so good to me given me everything take what you want cause it doesnt belong to me  i woke up this morning with a hurting that i would never ever wish upon even my worst enemy who is she? what the hell do you people want...  is it me? is it you? is it something i forgot to do? oh tell me so that i understand  oh i just need some time gather all my thoughts to make up for the love i just lost youve been so good to me given me everything take what you want cause it doesnt belong to me anyway        //sigh// i dont want to go, you guys.....
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      first, i just want to thank everyone who has been there for me... especially you allie. everymorning, you asked me if i was okay, if there was anything i wanted to talk about, all those hugs... thank you. i like your straight hair btw^.^  and second, this is the song that they played during the funeral when they closed the casket and carried it away... when they were ready to take her away, kelly (mrs. goodrich) wailed, "NO!! DON'T TAKE MY BABY AWAY FROM ME!" and grabbed onto the casket... it was so depressing... they had to hold her while the people put her into that little hole in the ground. and her dad, just standing there, staring at the ground, expressionless... and how all these emotions just welled up when i tossed that one white rose on top of the casket before they shoveled the dirt in.....    //sigh// i just... dont think i can keep up with this anymore    on a happier note, aaron is coming in 10 dayssssssss!! yay     oh yeah, and as a tradition, whenever i move, i do this thing where i ask everyone to give me  one item  that i can remember you by... it can be something you buy or something old, something you wear everyday or something that's been sitting on that shelf collecting dust. just something that represents you and whenever i look at it, i remember you... thanks.  so far: anna - nemo~! aaron - blue shirt laura - annie ticket stub (we need to meet up before i move!!)
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      oh yeah by the way, i just came back from the funeral.  it was beautiful.   but have you ever noticed how... how when people die, its like they had no pain or worried or stress in their lives? i dont know. its so depressing.   so unreal.  she seemd so peaceful... not like those hospital pictures.    i hope she's happy now
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I roll the tarnished penny around in my fingers as I stand in front of the RTC fountain, the music from the concert behind me curving around me. Ever since I was little, I've made a wish every time I've approached the fountain. I was (and still am) very superstitious, believing that supernatural forces can take the wishes that I release as I throw the penny into the fountain and make them come true. But what to wish for tonight? When I was small, I'd wish for material things- a new pair of roller skates, a lego set, a Polly Pocket doll. And as I got older, I started wishing for people: that so-and-so would finally notice me shooting him shy glances all day, that so-and-so might finally ask me out. But neither of these things seem appropriate to wish in the here and now. That night I had gone with people to see The Day After Tomorrow-easily the best movie I had ever seen. I had expected to be a bunch of special effects with no plot in sight, but it had touched so close to my heart that I laughed, I cried, I curled up like a frightened child. After that, I had gone to the concert at RTC- easily the strangest concert I had ever been to. There was an accordionist for the lead singer, a few people playing washboards, a person playing what appeared to be a cheese grater, and it all meshed together into a funky jumble of sound that jumped and twirled and made you feel happy even though you couldn't decipher the words.  So I keep glancing down at the penny, and I begin to think deep thoughts. I think about how I felt when amid all the death in the movie, a scraggly bunch of teenagers manage to survive. I think about how I felt when I saw a father in the movie, stranded in a station in Greenland, think about how he was so happy that his son was safe, although he wasn't. I think about how I felt seeing both an elderly couple and two young teenagers whirling and twirling to the dysfunctional music at the concert, and I think of what I felt seeing a little boy so engrossed in the music that a look of ectasy graced his face. I think about all these things, and I throw the penny, the copper going up then down in a graceful arc. It lands with a splash that is quiet, yet the loudest thing I have ever heard. And I think, what did I wish for? I don't know how to put it into words, that golden, bubbly feeling that makes you just want to sprout wings and fly, that makes all the light in your life shine brighter and stronger. I know that wherever I go, whatever I do; whether I become rich and famous or living on a park bench near a bus station, that if I have more moments like those, I will be happy forever...  And then it comes to me.    I know what I wished for.      I wished for joy.  - Allie Hirsch, Saturday June 6th 2004 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      leave comments guys!! sheesh ya figjams (tehehe!)   Now, don't just walk away Pretending everything's ok And you don't care about me And I know there's just no use When all your lies become your truths and I don't care... yeah, yeah, yeah  Could you look me in the eye  And tell me that you're happy now, ohhh, ohhh Would you tell it to my face or have I been erased,  Are you happy now?  Are you happy now?   You took all there was to take,  And left with an empty plate  And you don't care about it, yeah.  And I, I've given up this game  I'm leaving you with all the blame cause I don't care, yeah, yeah yeah,  Could you look me in the eye?  And tell me that you're happy now, oohh oohhh Would you tell it to my face or have I been erased,  Are you happy now? Ohhh, ohhhh Are you happy now?  Do you have everything you want? You can get up and give everything you`ve got You can't run away from yourself  Could you look me in the eye?  And tell me that you`re happy now, oohh oohhh Come on tell it to my face or have i been erased,  Are you happy now? Ohhh, ohhhh Are you happy now?  Would you look me in the eye? Could you look me in the eye? I've had that all I can take And I'm about to break Cause I'm happy now, ohhh, ohhh Are you happy now?  [[michelle branch -~- are you happy now?]]     phooey...
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Waiting for You   I&nbsp;waited&nbsp;all&nbsp;day But&nbsp;you&nbsp;never&nbsp;came I&nbsp;waited&nbsp;all&nbsp;night But&nbsp;you&nbsp;never&nbsp;came  You&nbsp;never&nbsp;seem&nbsp;to&nbsp;care How&nbsp;much&nbsp;youre&nbsp;hurting&nbsp;me No,&nbsp;It's&nbsp;not&nbsp;about&nbsp;what&nbsp;you&nbsp;did It's&nbsp;about&nbsp;why&nbsp;you&nbsp;never&nbsp;notice&nbsp;me  I&nbsp;don't&nbsp;hide I&nbsp;don't&nbsp;run I&nbsp;stay&nbsp;here Waiting&nbsp;for&nbsp;you  But&nbsp;you&nbsp;just&nbsp;walk&nbsp;on&nbsp;by...  Can't&nbsp;you&nbsp;see&nbsp;me? Or&nbsp;are&nbsp;you&nbsp;too&nbsp;blind Too&nbsp;oblivious Too&nbsp;good&nbsp;for&nbsp;me?  You&nbsp;think&nbsp;you&nbsp;can Get&nbsp;away&nbsp;with&nbsp;this But,&nbsp;oh,&nbsp;no&nbsp;you&nbsp;can't You&nbsp;can't&nbsp;leave&nbsp;me&nbsp;like&nbsp;this  But&nbsp;I&nbsp;guess&nbsp;it&nbsp;really&nbsp;isn't&nbsp;your&nbsp;fault For&nbsp;when&nbsp;you&nbsp;talk&nbsp;to&nbsp;me When&nbsp;you&nbsp;look&nbsp;at&nbsp;me I&nbsp;feel&nbsp;like&nbsp;angels&nbsp;in&nbsp;the&nbsp;sky  So&nbsp;talk&nbsp;to&nbsp;me,&nbsp;look&nbsp;at&nbsp;me Realize&nbsp;my&nbsp;existance Because&nbsp;when&nbsp;you&nbsp;do&nbsp;what&nbsp;you're&nbsp;doing&nbsp;to&nbsp;me&nbsp;now I&nbsp;crumble&nbsp;into&nbsp;a&nbsp;broken&nbsp;heap  So&nbsp;help&nbsp;me,&nbsp;love&nbsp;me,&nbsp;be&nbsp;with&nbsp;me...  Can't&nbsp;you&nbsp;see&nbsp;me? Or&nbsp;are&nbsp;you&nbsp;too&nbsp;blind Too&nbsp;oblivious Too&nbsp;good&nbsp;for&nbsp;me?  You&nbsp;think&nbsp;you&nbsp;can Get&nbsp;away&nbsp;with&nbsp;this But,&nbsp;oh,&nbsp;no&nbsp;you&nbsp;can't You&nbsp;can't&nbsp;leave&nbsp;me&nbsp;like&nbsp;this  Please,&nbsp;baby,&nbsp;don't&nbsp;leave&nbsp;me&nbsp;like&nbsp;this....     WHEEEEEE!! we just put music to it... and it sounds awesome! much like "The Remedy".... WHEEEeeeeEEeEEE!!! im excited ^__^ 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      stolen from cheryl > .    LAST TIME YOU  .Slept in your bed:&nbsp;uhh 2 nights ago. ive been sleepin on the couch^^ .Were seen crying: umm iono .Spent the night at your house: last night .You shared a drink with someone: uhhm. i haven't hung out with friends lately. i shared a slick stick with aurelia... OOH coke with.. yep.. tait //grins// .You went to the movies:&nbsp;uhhhh stepford wives. oy vey, when was that,&nbsp;may? .You went to the mall: in&nbsp;australia. uhm. that place aurelia bought those crystal carving things... you know, where it looks 3D on the inside? no? .Sent an e-mail: a couple hours ago... still waiting for the reply, dammit! .Said "I love you" and meant it?: wow. uhh. i dont know. .Gotten in a fight w/ your dog/cat/bird/fish, etc.?: i yelled at momo for humping her dog toy. lol .Been to New York?: in early june, there and the niagara. twas purdy .Been to Florida?: i dont remember... last last last winter, maybe? malibu?? .California?: i think for winter break in 8th grade. or when we got stuck in LA for the p2p trip, that was fun! haha all these p2p kids raiding radisson... .Hawaii?: many many many years ago with me parents .Mexico?: cancun, last winter .China?: err nope .Canada?: niagara falls, baby! june 04 .Got a really bad feeling about something then it happened?: yeah, everyday .Wish you were the opposite sex?: OH! when we were in DC at the kabuki thing and i had to go pee really badly and the ladies restroom line was supery dupery long and there was no line for the mens. yuppers. .Had an imaginary friend?: ive never had one .Red or blue?: blue .Spring or fall?: spring .Santa or Rudolph?: rudolph. santa leaves "gifts" for little children once a year. damn, who'd i share that joke with? lol .Math or English?: math, i suck at english. im sucha fob ^^  .What are you going to do after you finish this survey?: talk to all my insomniac friends online .What was the last food you ate?: umm... a peach. .Are you bored?: yes. vurrry. .How many buddies are on?: 73 .Last movie you saw?: man on fire, on the plane, with tait //blushes// .Last noise you heard?: my dog scratching on her kennel door .Last time you went out of the state: a week ago .Do you have a crush on someone?: yep! .Do they know?: ive been making it VERY obvious, it'll be stupid if they didnt. but, //sighs// guys are guys, theyre stupid. =P What's his/her name?: tatertot! haha and then theres johnny and bobby and freddy and etc. etc. the list goes on! What do you think of ouija boards?: COOL! i really wanted one for years... i forgot they even existed till now .What book are you reading now?: uhh well i lost my book halfway, but  Deception Point,  by Dan Brown .What's on your mouse pad?: my dad and i at disneyland... my dad is wearing a mickey mouse top hat and im wearing a white mouse wedding veil thing... AWWWW!! wait that kinda sounds wrong, you gotta see it for yourself .Favorite magazine?: uhhh...... GQ? lol i usually read april's cosmo girl and seventeen .Worst feelings in the world?: knowing that someone lied to you/done something behind your back and knowing that you love someone but you can never be with them .What is the first thing you think when you wake in the morning?: aw man its cold (when i wake up in the middle of the night with my covers kicked off my bed) or aw man its hot (when i wake up in the middle of the day) .How many rings before you answer?: 1? 2? .Chocolate or vanilla?: breyer's strawberry all the way! .Do you sleep with a stuffed animal?: yep! my big duck/platypus from costco, mina's white seal, andy's tigger, and anna's nemo ^^ theyre all huge!! .If you could have any job you wanted, what would it be?: umm an actress. a good one. or a really good singer. I suck at both .Are you a lefty, righty or ambidextrous?: righty. .Do you type with your fingers on the right keys?: ohh the format we learned in 3rd grade, mrs. conaway? ...naw. but i rarely make mistakes, and my blind touch is almost perfecto. .What's under your bed?:&nbsp;nothing... wait!&nbsp;dust bunnies!! .Favorite sport to watch?: baseball or football. or aussie rules. .Your Hair Color?: dark brown. again, turning lighter cause of the sun. alot of people think i highlight, but nope, i dont!! .Eye Color: brown .Height Currently: i was 5'3" with shoes in 8th grade .Glasses/contacts: both... but i only have glasses as of now .Siblings: none. wish i had a cool older brother, like ayu's .Location: northern virginia. //sigh// College Plans: u of hawaii cause i wanted to be a marine biologist&nbsp;till i met michelle, and realized taht im not that committed to it. i guess UH is still a good choice, but now i dunno what i want to do with my life. are we supposed to? .Are You Timely Or Always Late: usually late when im with my mommy... .Do You Like Being Around People: yes! not the bitchy kind though :) .Have You Cried Over Something Someone of The Opposite Sex Did Lately: yes .Ever Liked a close Guy/Girl Friend: yes! .Are You Lonely Right Now: yes... well im bored too, that might be a factor .Ever Afraid You'll Never Get Married: naww .Do You Want To Get Married: probably not. i cant commit, as you all know. lol .Do You Want Kids: theyre cute when you see them time to time, but with little dikes 24/7? i dont think so. its not that i dont like kids, i'd rather have more alone time, yano??   FAVORITE   .Room In house:&nbsp;hmm none currently .Type of music: i listen to anything... from maroon 5 to velvet revolver to aerosmith ^^ .Memory: first year of camp in japan. lotssa hard times there, i got bullied cause i was "different" aka i was the only foreign person. eh, but it was fun. i learned alot from that year. .Day Of The Week: i dont know .Worst Day of the Week: monday, i guess .Color: light shades of blue .Perfume or cologne: i like the light stuff, like miracle (lancome)... and cologne, oooh mmm the stuff tait wears .Flower: umm roses, without thorns. not the red ones. oh oh! the white ones with blue tips .Month: june and december .Band/Singer: maroon 5!!!! .Location for dates: if im with who i want to be with, it wont matter.   IN THE LAST 48 HOURS, HAVE YOU  .Bought Something: nope .Gotten Sick: nope .Sang:&nbsp;yep .Said I Love You: yes .Wanted To Tell Someone You Loved them, But Didn't: yes .Met Someone New: nope .Moved On: from being depressed for missing the cribs show on mtv with adam and james .Talked To Someone: yep .Had A Serious Talk: nope .Missed Someone: yep .Hugged Someone: no .Kissed Someone: nope .Fought With Your Parents: yes! gah, "i love you but please die", bitch! .Dreamed About Someone You Can't Be With: yep .Had a lot of sleep: no, ive been up for almost two days + a couple naps, but i dont feel tired at all. at least not now 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      best love song. ever. its so touching... i start crying when i hear this song now. its weird. i didn't feel so close to this song,  until now .  i feel so lost in a dreamy state. if that makes any sense at all.&nbsp;   on the other hand, i might stay in VA till mid october. maybe. 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      many years back  when we first met  we became  just  friends  as i now regret   the years have past  from that beginning  and feelings have changed  to longing and lusting   my heart skips a beat  everytime i "see" you  and i feel so dejected  when i must bid you adieu   we have confronted  our feelings toward eachother  but to keep our friendship  i hid my true desire   "we" agreed that it&nbsp;cant happen  "we" agreed that its impossible  the distance between us  will be miles innumerable   i tried to tell myself so  that what you said was right  but i think about&nbsp;what&nbsp;happened  almost every single night&nbsp;   and i think i still love you  for what you truly are  i feel lost, confused, without you  so i wish upon a star   i wish that this would work out  i wish you'd know what i endure  i wish you'd understand  that i am still unsure   i regret saying those words  i dont know if&nbsp;you do  but&nbsp;everytime i talk to you  i think... that i still love you 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wear sunscreen.  if&nbsp;i could offer you only one tip for the future, sunscreen would be it. the long-term benefits of sunscreen have been proved by scientists, whereas the rest of my advice has no basis more reliable than my own meandering experience. i will dispense this advice now.  enjoy the power and beauty of your youth. oh, nevermind. you won't understand the power and beauty of your youth until theyve faded. but trust me, in 20 years, you'll look back at photos of yourself and recall in a way you can't grasp now how much possibility lay before you and how fabulous you really looked. you are not as fat as you imagine.  don't worry about the future. or worry, but know that worrying is as effective as trying to solve an algebra equation by chewing bubble gum. the real troubles in your life are apt to be things that never crossed your worried mind, the kind that blindside you at 4 p.m. on some idle tuesday.  do one thing every day that scares you.  sing.  don't be reckless with other people's hearts. don't put up with people who are reckless with yours.  floss.  don't waste your time on jealousy. sometimes you're ahead, sometimes you're behind. the race is long and, in the end, it's only with yourself.  remember compliments you receive. forget the insults. if you succeed in doing this, tell me how.  keep your old love letters. throw away your old bank statements.  stretch.  don't feel guilty if you don't know what you want to do with your life. the most interesting people i know didn't know at 22 what they wanted to do with their lives. some of the most interesting 40 year olds&nbsp;i know still don't.  get plenty of calcium. be kind to your knees. you'll miss them when they're gone.  maybe you'll marry, maybe you won't. maybe you'll have children, maybe you won't. maybe you'll divorce at 40, maybe you'll dance the funky chicken on your 75th wedding anniversary. whatever you do, don't congratulate yourself too much, or berate yourself either. your choices are half chance. so are everybody else's.  enjoy your body. use it every way you can. don't be afraid of it or of what other people think of it. it's the greatest instrument you'll ever own.  dance, even if you have nowhere to do it but your living room.  read the directions, even if you don't follow them.  do not read beauty magazines. They will only make you feel ugly.  get to know your parents. you never know when they'll be&nbsp;gone for good. be nice to your siblings. they're your best link to your past and the people most likely to stick with you in the future.  understand that friends come and go, but with a precious few you should hold on. work hard to bridge the gaps in geography and lifestyle, because the older you get, the more you need the people who knew you when you were young.  live in NYC once, but leave before it makes you hard. live in northern california once, but leave before it makes you soft. travel.  accept certain inalienable truths: prices will rise. politicians will philander. you, too, will get old. and when you do, you'll fantasize that when you were young, prices were reasonable, politicians were noble and children respected their elders.  respect your elders.  don't expect anyone else to support you. maybe you have a trust fund. maybe you'll have a wealthy spouse. but you never know when either one might run out.  don't mess too much with your hair or by the time you're 40 it will look 85.  be careful whose advice you buy, but be patient with those who supply it. advice is a form of nostalgia. dispensing it is a way of fishing the past from the disposal, wiping it off, painting over the ugly parts and recycling it for more than it's worth.  but, trust me on the sunscreen. 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       still  jetlagged. gah.    so my mom and i are flying to japan on september 5th or 6th and all our stuff is disappearing... slowly....... my bed, my couch, my desk, everything. i wanna take everything with me, but NOO japan has to be a fucking small island with little space and too many people. grrrrr.   &nbsp;  or better yet, i want to stay here.    you know? i might not even move within the year. iono. i might go to oakton for a month or so, maybe.      which would kinda suck cause i have no clue what the summer assignments are.   anyone have english honors, AP WC or honors chem?    &nbsp;  but that would be awesome. if i could stay just a little longer.   then i might get my permit! //cheers//     and best of all,      i'll have more time to be with my friends.     
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      im booored... we all need to do something when im not busy.  &nbsp; i miss my p2p people!! PSEUDO-REUNUION, seriously.    stole from julie's website  Name: Yuna A. Tanabe sex: Female birthday: June 22, 1989 siblings: none. i wish i had an older bro though hair color: black... or dark brown. whatever its called. its getting all brownish cause of the sun. eye color: brown shoe size: 8~8 1/2 height: 53 with shoes in 8th grade  FASHION SHIT where is your favorite place to shop: raiding target with my friends!! haha that was fun any tattoos or piercing: not at the moment  SPECIFICS do you do drugs: no what kind of shampoo do you use: usually pantene who is the last person that called you: dan where do you want to get married: outside... beach? somewhere pretty what would you change about yourself:&nbsp;my singing voice. it&nbsp;used to be so good till i hit puberty... damn you puberty!!&nbsp;  FAVORITES color: light shades of blue, black, white food: anything edible boys names: matthew, tait girls names: annelise, madison subjects in school: lunch! noo... hmm. any science stuff, without peach. animals: anything... especially dogs, horsies, and FERRETS!  sports: i play anything... i like watching football and baseball. GO 49ERS + SF GIANTS!! woot woot!  HAVE YOU EVER given anyone a bath: i don think so smoked: no bungee jumped: yep! much fun made yourself throw up: a couple times skinny dipped: yeeeep been in love: yes made yourself cry to get out of trouble: uhh //eyes dart around// no? ..... //starts "crying" and runs away// pictured your crush naked: you know, now that i think of it, i actually havent. yeah its weird... but thanks for the idea! actually seen your crush naked: yep cried when someone died: yes lied: uh, yeah? fallen for your best friend: yes been rejected: umm not really. i guess in circumstances you could say kind of. rejected someone: hahaha, detinitely used someone: no! thats mean done something you regret: yeah. i do that alot.  CURRENT clothes: yellow soffes and a black and white nyc shirt with cool pictures music: way away, yellowcard. yeah, they  do  suck make-up: uhh mascara, eyeliner, a lil foundation, and gloss. cause i forgot to take it off from last night annoyance: the fact that i cant be with someone... //wink wink snort snort// smell: axe favorite group: maroon 5!!! desktop picture: //checks...// maroon 5! book you're reading: decption point. i lost the book halfway, damn it. its GOOD, like all dan brown books!! in cd player: uhh, my md has lotssa stuff, like maroon 5.. and maroon 5... lol  THE LAST PERSON YOU... you touched: my dog you hugged: catherine at the airport you IMed: tait? you yelled at: dan cause he was being an ass you kissed: dan  ARE YOU understanding: i try to be arrogant: i sometimes am insecure: mmm i dun think so interesting: heh, yes, to strangers random: very hungry: yes smart: naw, im the stupid asian moody: am i? i dont think so hard working: depends on what the task is... //licks lips// organized: when i want to be healthy: nah shy: nope difficult: i.. dont think so attractive: uh, no. bored easily: yes messy: vury obsessed: i can be, like maroon 5!!  RANDOM all i need is: my friends love is: a paradox. it can be both the best thing ever and the worst thing ever i dream about: the good, the bad, and the SEXXAY!  OPPOSITE SEX what do you notice first: looks. but once i hang around with them, their personality last person you slow danced with: ...adam? who do you have a crush on:  POTATO!  who has a crush on you: what? huh? SOMEONE ACTUALLY LIKES ME?! WHOO ARE YOU!!! COMEE TOO MEEEEEEEE!!!! //eyes get bloodshot, slobbers everywhere, foams at mouth// mm... attractive, no?  DO YOU EVER sit on the internet all night waiting for that someone special to IM you: sure wish you were a member of the opposite sex: YES. no periods, no labor pains, easier to be friendly with ppl of the same sex, and it takes half the time to pee! wish you were younger: eh, no  NUMBER of times i have had my heart broken: um... 5? of hearts i have broken: like... 12? i dont count these things! of guys Ive kissed: too many to count of girls Ive kissed: many, not in a makeout way though. of continents i have lived in: 2 of tight friends: alot! of scars on my body: alot from sports... none that are self-inflicted  FINAL QUESTIONS do you like fillings these out: sometimes. they get annoying after awhile gold or silver: silver what was the last film you saw at the movies: stepford wives favorite cartoon/anime: futurama! and lupin the 3rd. what did you have for breakfast this morning: nothing who would you love being locked in a room with right now:  POTATO!!  could you live without your computer: well, i did it for 3 weeks for p2p... would you color your hair: i dunno. could you ever get off the computer: sure habla espanol: say what? how many people are on your buddy list: umm //counts// like 200 something. i think.  THE END  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      //whines// someone take me to the maroon 5 concert!! &nbsp; well, aka the john mayer concert feat. maroon 5. he sucks, so it should be the other way around. &nbsp; &nbsp; dan, kev, jojo, adam, andy, april may june, kathy, rachel, michelly, ham, pepsi, tum tum, jasmine, maddie, and everyone else, congrats on escaping high school and much luck and love in college, specially to those out of the country! 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      you have to take the good and the bad smile with the sad love what you get and remember what you had &nbsp; always forgive but never forget learn from your mistakes and never regret &nbsp; people change things go wrong just remember life goes on... &nbsp; 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       yellooo. im back!   //everyone runs away in fear, yelling something like GODZILLA! and crap in jap//     &nbsp;  ...eh.    &nbsp;   &nbsp;  p2p was fun. well, the stuff we had to do wasnt, the crap we did was AWESOMELY COOL.    &nbsp;  hey all y'all from the trip, we should all get together or something before i move... have a mass orgy or whatever floats your boat.  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wednesday, 8:27 pm ashburton, new zealand... aka halfway around the world  homestay people are great fun... theyre very nice. i think ive gotten the accent now! ya blokes!.... heh   yeah.  ill see you guys in a couple days, ill be back on the 18th.    much love from your favorite fish
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WHOOO CALIFORNIA TOMORROWW!! WHOOOOOOOOO! i'm ready, i'm ready, i'm ready, i'm ready, i'm ready.... wait no i'm not, i havent even packed yet. HAH.  a convo between the infamous julie of irvine and me, when we found out that we can see eachother for the first time while i'm stopping in LA (it's complicated, dont ask):  shadowXofXaXsoul: ok so when i see you can i give you a flying hug or should i opt for the nice to meet you handshake? liL tuNa   lOL: lol liL tuNa   lOL: you'd prolly embarrass yourself by hugging the wrong person shadowXofXaXsoul: lmao shadowXofXaXsoul: im gona do it liL tuNa   lOL: and i'd be like, "uh... julie... over here?" shadowXofXaXsoul: HELLO SIR YOU MUST B  YUNA shadowXofXaXsoul: lmao liL tuNa   lOL: HAHAHHAAHA liL tuNa   lOL: //snorts// shadowXofXaXsoul: i jus did the exact same things shadowXofXaXsoul: the dog looked at me shadowXofXaXsoul: lmao shadowXofXaXsoul: lshtipimp liL tuNa   lOL: ahh rotglol shadowXofXaXsoul: lol liL tuNa   lOL: OMG YOU REMEMBER!! liL tuNa   lOL: hahahahahahahaha shadowXofXaXsoul: hell yeah shadowXofXaXsoul: wooo flyin hug it is! shadowXofXaXsoul: sir liL tuNa   lOL: yessir! shadowXofXaXsoul: WOO shadowXofXaXsoul: *stupid white girl dance* liL tuNa   lOL: hahahahahahaha shadowXofXaXsoul: no really i jus did shadowXofXaXsoul: it was a combination raise the roof and sprinkler liL tuNa   lOL: aaaaaahhhahaha man i love you shadowXofXaXsoul: im groovy like that oh yeah. shadowXofXaXsoul: im so excited shadowXofXaXsoul: wee shadowXofXaXsoul: *chair spin* liL tuNa   lOL: oooh maaan this is gonna be SO COOL! shadowXofXaXsoul: i KNOW shadowXofXaXsoul: weeee liL tuNa   lOL: aww yeaaaaaaaaaaaaah liL tuNa   lOL: woooooooot liL tuNa   lOL: //asian girl dance// shadowXofXaXsoul: *crappy by comparison white girl jew thing* liL tuNa   lOL: yaay jew thing!! shadowXofXaXsoul: oh yeah thats hot   aaaaaaaaaahaha julie i loveth you! ish kool behbay, thooo thexy!!     WHOOOOOOOOO CALIFORNIA HERE I COME!!    wow that was cheesy. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The miles just keep rolling As the people either way to say hello I've heard this life is overrated But I hope it gets better as we go  I'm here without you baby But you're still on my lonely mind I think about you baby And I dream about you all the time I'm here without you baby But you're still with me in my dreams And tonight, girl It's only you and me  Everything I know, and anywhere I go It gets hard but it won't take away my love And when the last one falls, when it's all said and done It gets hard but it won't take away my love    Aerosmith was good, but i guess this one's better... for now. its gooood... and yes, andy, i know what youre gonna say. "but all 3 doors down songs sound the same!!" i must agree. and im starting to agree to that comment directed toward uhh those people... with those songs. yeah. ill figure it out sooner or later. probably later. yeeeeeeeep.   WHEE CANT WAIT TILL I GO TO CALIFORNIA, BABY! ahh, but i wont get to see everyone there... i imed someone and i was all like HEY IM GOING OVER THERE IN A COUPLE WEEKS!! and they were like "..... who're you?!"   //tear// ive already been forgotten in my home-town. yo.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ahh best times at the H2O...  "tequila? with no alcohol? .... lemme see an ID" "party on, my fellow brothers, party  on !!!" "some guy was drowning in a urinal..." "oh oh! hot guy! HOT GUY!! let's stalk him! ...... oh damn where'd he go?"  aha, and coming back at 3:30 and eating bagles... josh putting a whole container full of cream cheese on one mini bagle. mm, deeelicious! adn then... FIREWORKS! haha "OH SHIZZLE! WE BROKE ANOTHER WINDOW!!!"  haha, im gonna miss you all... //sigh//   i wanna go see avp!!! or fahrenheit 9/11!!!! or manchurian candidate. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>