<Blog>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
          urlLink BBC NEWS UK Caution call on video game storm   It took a wee while for the nes of this to get round to me but since it's come out I have all these people balbing on at me saying "ahh what do you make of all this Adam, you're a computer game guy ahhh". For a start I find the term "computer game guy" particularly offensive cos it sort of likens me to "Comic Book guy" from the Simpsons. Also you probably play games a lot more than I do. You may even have played Manhunt, which I havent. I don't know anyone that owns it and nobody released a demo for it because it was too violent to put on a coverdisc (because all games mags do fall into the hands of youngsters) and also for the same reason it wasn't in any shops avaliable for the public to try beforte they buy. I advoided it because apparently it's really hard, I'm not totally keen on the hard games, sorry to sound like a wuss and all.   As for this story, listen, I'm sorry that your son's dead and all but banning video games just will not solve your problems and as for Dixons, get that game back on the shelves you cowards! I really got annoyed when i heard this morning that they're going to start campaigning for th banning of games like GTA and Doom 3. I'm not going to be buying Doom 3 likes becauce i doubt that this PC will be able to handle it plus I don't have an X Box but i feel that if you're british, have been looking forward to this game and the yanks are still getting it then you should have th eright to be able to buy it. Same with the forthcoming GTA game. I mean you might as well ban films and books as well. Just got you pick up a gun in a game dosent mean you straight away know how to operate one in real life. You can see much clearly how to use one in a film and a book will give a detailed description.   Then theres the argument that everyone has been mentioning, that the game is an 18 and should not be in the hands of minors. Now one thing that I haven't got straight yet, who was it that had and was influenced by the game? Was it the 14 year old boy who was killed? or the 17 year old killer? Even still neither of them should have been in posession of the game, if the killer was over 18 then there would be no one placing the blame on games. And as it happens now, people ARE blaming games when they really should be blaming the parents, which i do.   
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Not totally interesting, but these are the PS/PS2 games I've decided on taking down to Slips with me this weekend:  PS2: Beyond Good and Evil Burnout 2 Capcom vs SNK 2 Coin McRae Rally 4 Hyper Street Fighter 2 Ratchet and Clank 2 Silent Hill 2 SSX 3 Tekken 4 Time Spliters 2 Tony Hawk underground  Playstation: Crash Bandicoot 3 Street Fighter Alpha 3 Pocket Fighter Spyro Year of the Dragon Wipeout 3 Special Edition  I have room for 12 more discs like
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
         I'm gonna sit here and try to compile my Desert Island Disks because I got the latest issue of Retro Gamer today and I noticed that it has this feature now. They were talking to this boy who made Goldeneye and Timesplitters and I kinda thought to myself "ah, could be fun". Ahem.  Well i have less than a hour to do this so i will try my best. Also I think i will put them in order of when i think they came out.    Wizards Lair  - Spectrum   &nbsp;  Really I havent played this one in a long time. I think it may be one of my first gaming memories. the Spectrum was the first computer we had which i was allowed to play on (i'm sure i saw Pong in the living room though i don't recall playing it so I always assume from that I was never allowed to touch it) and Wizard's Lair was just this really early game we had, I think it was part of a compilation tape we had or maybe it was something we had copied from someone. Turns out it's something of a classic and I guess I could find an emulated file of it somewhere online but I've been thinking lately of gettig a ne Spectrum for myself. it was a top down shootem up where you controlled this wee guy (maybe a Wizard i'm not sure) who resembled a sort of octopus. it was hard as fuck, well it was one of the first games I had played, and i think the object was to collect all the pieces of a Lion in order to complete but every time you'd start the game they'd all be in different places and if you were lucky one would be in the very first room you start in. I also remember having to fanny around with lifts too somehow. i'd take this for nostalgia.    Speedball 2  - Atari ST     A big big 2 player game, though that won't be much use if I'm on thsi Desert Island on my norm eh? Luckily enough it was a great one player game. this was one of my first Atari St games and it remained one of my most favourites for the whole 2 years i bought games for it for. When yo ulook at it now there are flaws which you woill never find in any of the current waves of sports games such as the fact that when you turn it on and go straight to the 2 player mode both teams are just bare, they all have no stats. Today's football games usually have a selection of teams who each have their own attributes and you can't change them, Speedball 2 made you go through the menagerial side every time. Of course it would be great if you could save your powered up team from the one player game and pit them against your friends. I loved the shiny metallic arenas plus of course the blistering fast speeds the game ran at, when you had a powered up team of course. And nothing was more pleasing than recieving a potential 20 points for injuring one of your hapless oponents, superb.    Super Mario Kart  - SNES     Funily enough one of the games that guy in Retro Gamer picked as well.&nbsp; It's a splendid little game which everyone loves.&nbsp; In fact I'm sure that if there IS anyone else on this island and they find out I have a bag of games with me then they're sure to be asking me if I have this.&nbsp; I actually sold my first copy though because I was a bit bored of it though but it was one of the first games i made sure I bought back then i got my second SNES.    Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time  - N64     I'm including this game mainly because I haven't finished it yet and if I could get rid of all the adventure type games I've bought since then I may actually get round to it.&nbsp; But the great thing about this game is that you know that even after you've finished it you know there is loads more in it you haven't discovered yet.    Street Fighter Alpha 3  - PlayStation     I think I would go as far as saying that this is the most complete version of Street Fighter ever.&nbsp; That is why it is the only one I have included here.&nbsp; Of course I needed to put a SF game in there cos if you know me then you know I love SF something sexy.&nbsp; SFA3 pleases old fans of Street Fighter because all the characters from the SF2 series is in here including all the bosses, the new Super Street Fighters, even Akuma who had actually been in the 2 previous versions of this game.&nbsp; It also has enough new characters to please anyone who thinks that the series offers nothing new, of course it's still ye olde 2D fighting you used to know and love, but that's it you have to love it to stand by it, 3D fighing games are fine and all but I always find that anyone can beat an expert 3D fighter just by pounding the buttons, if you study SF inside out an expert can be uneatable unless he's playing another expert.&nbsp; maybe unfair you may think but it encourages people to actually practice at the damn thing.&nbsp; I havent even mastered all the characters yet, theres bloody loads of them.    Wipeout 3 Special Edition  - PlayStation     I love the WipEout games because they're so damn cool.&nbsp; it's also the rush that you get when you're zipping round each track.&nbsp; The special edition of the 3rd game is the ultimate one because it has a couple of the older tracks in it as well as a couple of "prototype" tracks to unlock.&nbsp; If it's easy to find, the version which comes with Destruction Derby 2 for £15 is essential.&nbsp; just stay away from the disapointing PS2 Fusion version.   King of Fighters 2002  - Dreamcast     Just thought I'd put the most recent game i bought in here (well i did this list before i got my 2 new Megadrive games).&nbsp; You can never go wrong with 2 massive 2D fighting games can you?&nbsp; Ok so i may swap this one for another but I feel like I havent explored it all yet, but I could easily have picked Beyond Good and Evil cos I got that recently too and I've barely played it.&nbsp; i also still have to get round to playing Jak 2 and Ratchet and Clank 2.    SSX3  - PlayStation 2     Now what the hell did happen to my Allegra site then eh?&nbsp; This game with it's online play section would last me a while.&nbsp; it's also fun exploring the mountain on your own and completing it 100% with all the characters would take a while.&nbsp; Sublime and totally cool to boot.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Just a quick one.  my MD games came today so i'm gonna be busy all day.  But I'm also working on my Desert Island Disks so look out for that soon too.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink NEO GEO Advanced Entertainment System - System Specs       In the late 1980's the SNK (Shin Nihon Kikaku) Corporation planned to break into the video game hardware market after designing games for Nintendo's NES system. They made a bold move in entering the industry. At the same time they launched the two separate systems: an arcade console and home platform. Each could play games that were exactly interchangeable, bringing Arcade games literally into the home for the first time.   In 1990, the Neo Geo cartridge-based home system was released. Powered by a Motorolla 68000 16-bit processor, it played the very same games as arcade counterpart, the Neo-Geo MVS (Multi-Video System). This exciting option for home game players did have a drawback though, the cartridge based platform retailed for a whopping $899.99. Neo-Geo game cartridges sold anywhere from $250 to $300. SNK did release a good amount of titles for its home console and while the system never made a huge splash, it sold well.   At the time, the Neo-Geo system offered a unique new device: a memory card. It allows players to save levels and positions from any Neo-Geo game release. Not only is the memory card usable on other Neo-Geo home gaming consoles, but it can be inserted into any MVS arcade cabinet featuring the same game and play can be resumed (after inserting a quarter of course) at the same level saved to the card at home.   The system also includes an option named the Multi-Link. For players who crave privacy two Neo-Geo home systems can be linked together, via a cable, for play on two separate televisions. Among the games which support this feature are: Thrash Rally, League Bowling, and Riding Hero.   In 1994 SNK introduced the Neo-Geo CD. As the name would indicate, it is a CD- ROM based system. The price dropped significantly from that of the cartridge based unit. Retail price was $250 and CD-ROMs sold from $50 to $70. Structurally, Neo-Geo CD contains similar hardware as the original platform but the disks are a much cheaper medium for releasing games. Unfortunately, the Neo-Geo CD-ROM drives are single-speed and quite slow. They take a long time to load games into the system's memory.   By the time the ROM units were released, Neo-Geo was not as popular as it originally had been. They followed up Neo-Geo CD with Neo-Geo CDZ. It is a second-generation model featuring a double-speed CD-ROM drive for shorter loading delays. Unfortunately, the CDZ was only released in Japan. In order for the system to run games in English, a language switch must be installed on the system. Imported Neo-Geo cartridges from Japan and Europe are compatible with American systems.   The Neo-Geo home platforms have a loyal following, and SNK claims they intend to support it through the end of 1999.  — Dave Beuscher   Debut Price (1990): $899.99  Processor: 68000, Z80  Processor Speed: 14 MHz  Resolution: 320 x 224  Colors: 4,096 / 65,536  Max Sprite Estimation: 380  Sprite Size: Programable  Sound Channels: 8-FM synthesis, 7-Digital  Internal RAM: Memory Card (a source says the NEOGEO has 56 Mbits of RAM!)  Neo Geo CD:  has all, including a single-speed CD-ROM drive, internal backup RAM, loading screens, and 56 Mbits of RAM      So now i know 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink King of Fighters '95 Game Cheats  Here's a little blast from the past.  Around the time of when  was considering getting KOF2002 I went around looking up stuff on my old Saturn game and i remembered there was a cheat to unlock hidden animations like the blood and Mai's amazing bouncing titties.  Click on that link up there and see who submitted the cheat ;) (it's me by the way, i never say my real name often do i?)
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ok I finally recovered.  Yeah I was talking on my main blog about how i got some post, well i said it was my certificate for college, I also got KOF2002 in the post, i was a little disapointed that i didn't get my Megadrive games yet but that's ok as I've been waiting for this Dreamcast game for over 2 weeks now.  King of Fighters is such a bizarre game.  I'll admit that i havent played any of the proper series since I owned KOF 95 for my Sega Saturn, which was actually quite recent, it was one of the games i sold to that shop just there, I just hadn't played if for ages cos I didn't have a Sega Saturn.  Yeah it's a bizarre game cos although it's now on its tenth year it still basically looks th esame.  now i never really understood what Neo Geo was, I could understand it was an arcade system, but it was also a home console which played these cartridges which cost over £150.  And the console was basically the same as the arcade hardware?  So each of the arcade cabinets had a NEO Geo inside it and to save the arcade owner from buying a new cabinet all he was do do was change the cart?  Is all this right?  Well whatever, one thing that seems clear is that this Dreamcast game is a conversion and a Neo Geo Arcade game and it's quite a faithful one because it looks a little dated.  So the company that does all the King of Fighters games are still using the old technology from 10 years ago?  That's what it looks like cos this game isn't much different from the Saturn game i had in 1997.  It's just that this time there is less loading time.  good though, i quite like the KOF games, they're a little different to Street Fighter, the way the moves feel and all the rest, it's like you can feel the hits more mainly cos of the sound they make when they connect.  Plus they're always loads of characters, I dont think that i had played as everyone on the old Saturn version i had, they're always name copping up every here and there.  I'm keeping an eye on the  urlLink King of Fighter 10th anniversary  site and I'm findng out who's been in what game and all the rest.  But it's great it feels like I have that old Saturn game back except it's on the Dreamcast, i don;t mind though.  A lot of people always moan that all 2d fighting games are the same when people are talking about Street Fighter in fact i was reading this one review of some 2D fighter and they were saying that to say that all 2D fighting games are the same is like saying that NFL2K is the same as a John Madden game.  Though I would say that KOF is unashamedly similar, whereas when yo ulook at a new Street Fighter game they always look better everytime.  Anyway, KOF2002, good stuff, i just wish i could play the newer ones on my PS2 without having to mess around with it's insides, i dunno maybe i better look into buying a Japanese system.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Yahoo! It's arrived. I'm hung over to fuck by the way
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink eBay item 8119237282 (Ends 21-Jul-04 16:53:49 BST) - Super Street Fighter 2 for Megadrive   Managed to win a couple of things on Ebay for myself. I got Quackshot which some mug was selling for £2.99 Buy It Now, ha ha it's all mine. And I also go the above. Finally i have myself a copy of Super Street Fighter II     of course it's the megadrive version but at least I have it now. I actually remember at around the time of me having the Saturn i went into Electronics Buttock and saw the box for this game in the pre owned section, i was cheesing so i took it to the counter, i had been looking for a copy of this for ages likes. Of course the bloody sales boy couldn't find the game in the drawers and asked me to come back a little later so he could find it. I just said forget it. But here it is now. Of course I really could do with the SNES version but it seems that no ons going to give that to me for six quid.  I actualyl had a bit of a session on the Megadrive yesterday, went through all the games and played a little of each. I usually forget I have a Megadrive mainly because when i got it it was just a replacement for the SNES which got nicked off me so it would never measure up. I bought it second hand off David Lynch who was one of my friends in School, he used to smell a lot of sweat cos he was a big lad and his parents were heavy smokers so when i got the console my room just smelt like his it was an absolute nightmare. And now it seems that the actual games still smell like that cos i rarely take them out of their boxes. Also the games never load when you plug them in and turn on for the first time, I always have to take them out blow on the connectors (not sure if that's wise actually) and plug them back in firmly. Anyway what have i got?    Alien Storm  - This game isn't as good as I remembered it, i guess it's fun when you play it with someone else but on my own it only serves for nostalgic value, which was why i also bought the Master System version recently, this Megadrive cart was one of Lynchys though.    Alisia Dragoon  - This is another of Davids games which is shit. I'm not sure why he got it but I'm suspecting it's because he fancies the character you control, ahem. It's just this shitty platform game where you blast flying creatures with a big stick of lightning and you've go tthis dragon following you all the time.    Decap Attack  - I didn't play this because it's not in my posession right now. i sold 3 games to Speedy recently nd threw one in as a borrow but it's been a while since I have seen him and it could still be a while before i see him again as he may not be returning to college. Last time I saw him actually he was really down cos he had fucked up college and I may have sounded a little too proud that i had passed all the classes so a bit of a woops type situation there.    Ecco the Dolphin  - I actualyl had a bit of fun when i booted this one up, swimming around being free. A real hippies game actually so i didn'y play it for too long. It was hyped so much though when it came out but it seems a little dated now. One of Davids games.    Eternal Champions  - I couldnt believe it when i booted this one up. This was a memory heavy fighting game which Sega released in order to rival Street Fighter 2, which was winging it's way to the MD soon anyway. Well the SNES version of ST2Turbo was coming out before so i guess it was doing battle with that too. it was also the first fighting game to make use of the 6 button joypad. Though Lynchy never had one of those so when we played the game at his you had to press the start button to turn your 3 kicks into 3 punches. I made sure I bought a 6 button pad as soon as I bought it all off him. But what a shit game Eternal Champions is, it's just so unplayable. Actually i've just had a peek on Game Faqs to see if anyone agrees with me but it seems to have a page full of glowing reviews so i guess I'll have to say it. All the characters have shit moves, no combos and the one player game is boring as hell, and hard. It's really dated now actually.    Flashback  - YES! now we're talking. FLashback was one of my fave SNES games and I was missing it so much that while I didn't have a SNES i just got it on the ol MD. It's the sequel to Another World but i don't think that it's got anything to do with it. You're this guy Conrad Hart who's lost his memory and has been dumped in this weird jungle area by these aliens so what you have to do is get your emmory back and escape back to earth. I alsways though that Tomb Raider was basically a 3D version of this game, but set in a sort of cyberpunk typed setting rather than the caves and egyptian tombs of that game. In fact Flashback had it's own PSone follow up too Fade to Black which aparently influenced TR as well so there you go. It just brings back lots of SNES memories, especially Christmas 1993 when i got it along with Cool Spot. The idea was to complete the first level but i was a numpty and forgot to pick the injured boy's ID card and couldnt be bothered going back to get it.    Golden Axe II  - A legendary Megadrive game which is a little too dated for me. I get really bored of playing it and...well im embarassed to say but I'm not particularly good at these side scrolling beat em up games for some reason. I'm good at the one on one ones but even though people say that the Golden Axe types are dead easy I can only seem to get myself half way through the game before running out of lives. I think what i need to do is play with a friend all the time. But this is a bit old fo rme this game, i remmeber me and George having a good game of it a few years back and that was good i guess. one of Lynchys.    James Pond 3: Operation Starfish  - I bought this. Cos i like Robocod and I wanted to see what the sequel was like. A bit pish actually, I never worked out what allt he controls were when i bought it though and I was stuck on the first level forever but yesterday i realised that A was run so i manager to get over all the hills and progressed to the secodn level, how boss am i?    Micro machines 2  - It took me a year and a half to get round to buying new Megadrive games for myself, and that was just like 1 week before I got myself a Saturn. So i guess this is (and SF2SCE see below) the most important game in my whole second wave of gaming cos buying it helped me decide that getting back into games was a thing to do. I had a wee bit of fun with it but a second played would have been sound.    Mortal Kombat  - There was no bloody game in the fecking box! Where the hell has Lynchy's copy of MK gome? Actually it's not important because it's shit.    Sonic the Hedghog  - The amount of time's I've played that first level. Over and over. It's ok i will progress one day when i can be bothered to remind myself of the level skip. Actually what I want is to get a hold of all the sequels, or maybe just wait for the Mega Collection for the PS2. Sonic was something of an enigma to me back when it cam eout because I had no access to consoles and this game seemed like a whole new world to me. The first time I played it was at this game show in Glasgow and i had to queue up to play the damn thing. It just looked so polished and hi res that it could never be seen on my Atari ST.    Street Fighter 2 Special Champion Edition  - Teh game i bought with Micro Machines 2. Never really did play it as much as i could have done back in thouse days, i guess I was just screaming out for the SNES version. I had a good look at it this time though and the difference in the quality of graphics compared to the Nintendo version is quite noticable, plus the sound is shit, but it's still the same game. And i didnt have to look up any speed cheat to play the game at its fastest to that was great too.    Streets of rage  - One of Davids games but one of my most favourite MD carts. Even though its a side scrolling fighting game, but it's different to GOlden Axe. Actually i was a level skip for this too, or just to be able to play it with someone so the first few levels arent boring.    Strider  - Wow now this looks so OLD now. Lynchys game.    Taz-Mania  - I think this came out ar around the time the cartoon had started, but i had never seen it so i think it was just on satelite or cable. I used to be really into it but now though the graphics are big and bold it is a bit crap to be honest.     Where in the World and in Time is Carmen Sandiago -  Both are shit. I can only think David got these games because ht wanted to sow that he was a clever lad rather than just someone one who was intersted in blasting bad guys. These games are as boring as fuck.    Wrestle War -  I didnt actually play this one because it's at my sisters, but it's the worst game ever   So there yo uhave it, that's the story of my Megadrive which still feels like it's david's so I guess I'm gonna have to get on Ebay there and flog some of his terrible games then. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This looks a little different, the place i type the text in that is.&nbsp; Ahh well&nbsp;this is a new sub blog i have set up to go with my main blog  urlLink http://www.yaster.co.uk .&nbsp; It's basically a place i can come and write stuff about games which i normally do in my main blog but recently i've been thinking i better stop cos it's making me sound a little sad, so this basically will be the place i go to be sad then, sound! 
     
    
</post>



</Blog>