<Blog>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      After that hellish travel day, I finally arrived at David's and we were almost immediately out the door to go get lunch. We went to  urlLink Au Pied De Cuchon , a favorite spot. Most things on the menu are excellent but what makes it a favorite is their escargot. If you think escargot are gross then you obviously haven't had them here. They cook them in their shells with pesto sauce and bring them out on a metal plate that has indentations for each one. You get tongs to hold the shell and a special little fork to get them out of there. We could be having an intense discussion, arguing or in the middle of a story and as soon as the escargot arrive there's a silence that continues until they are all gone. For the main course I had Magret du Canard. A dish I had been longing for since leaving France the last time. Unfortunately, I was tired and when the waiter asked me how I wanted it, I said, "medium" almost unconsciously. What I should have said is "rare" because that's the way to have Magret du Canard. It was still really good. It came with this fig dish that had philo dough on the bottom and then figs and, I think, beets on top. Very unique flavor. Subtly sweet.  If I wasn't so tired, I'd describe every meal I've had - the amazing Turkish food, the fresh milk camembert, the entrecot, and even the violet soda. The food here is at least a few notches above and usually several notches above food that I have had anywhere else. San Francisco is a great food city but Paris is on a whole other level. No mexican food though so I made sure to get my fill of Tacqueria Cancun before leaving SF.   Oh yeah, we've been getting ready to leave for India in less than two weeks.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A republican I can support.   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I hope he enjoyed that cigarette
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I woke up at 6:10 AM. My friend Robynn scheduled to pick me up at 6:15. I had set the alarm but forgot to turn it on. I had a few drinks with friends the night before in the hopes that it would help me sleep. That's my excuse for going out and drinking, anyway. Still, couldn't fall asleep until at least 4 AM. I'm glad my internal clock was working and I wasn't awoken by the doorbell.   Robynn was on time and I was out of it but ready. Two large suitcases, a box containing my G4, another with the corresponding studio monitor and one more with books and miscellaneous stuff that David and I would need.   The first leg of the trip was to Philadelphia which was good in the way that I could go to the domestic terminal and not have to get there as early. Still, I had to deal with all the extra baggage which cost me $330. Ouch. I was to have a few hours in Philly before leaving for Paris but as the plane approached, there was "extreme" weather conditions and the plane was diverted to Harrisburg where we were to refuel and wait until things cleared up. It was 5:15 by the time we left Harrisburg. It's only a twenty minute flight to Philly but then there is all the waiting for slow ass people to get their shit and get off the plane. Unfortunately, they didn't allow people with connecting flights to deplane first. I was pretty far back on the plane so I had to wait which I did impatiently. Basically, I wanted to kill. I ran from concource C to A, occasionally stopping on the moving walkways to ask someone to get the fuck out of the way and stay to the right if they were just going to stand there. In actuality I was nice and polite but in my lind I was yelling at them to get the fuck out of the way and wondering if that was their first time in an airport and on a moving walkway. I made the plane. Everyone had already boarded. Then we proceeded to wait on the tarmac for an hour or so. Not even close to a full flight so I got to sit alone which is always nice.     Finally arrive in Paris and wait to get my passport stamped. I got in the slow line - probably because there were lots of Africans and other non-whites. After a while I got in a different line and it went relative quickly. Alright, get my baggage, meet up with David and Martin and I'm out of here. I wait and wait for the baggage. Nothing. The carousel belt stops for my flight. Shit. Was I at the right carousel? Did someone see that G4 box and take off with it? No No No. I got to the claim office and wait some more. Luckily I kept my claim tickets and my extra baggage receipt as it wouldn't have been unlike me to toss or lose that shit. Instead of my stuff I have a piece of paper and a number to call. Whatever, just get me outta here. Its been a long time now and I'm hoping David and Martin are still waiting. I get out in the terminal and they are no where to be found. OK. I'll call. I need money. I get in the line to change some money and it takes an incredibly long time. Me and this guy from Quebec who looked like the singer from Anthrax, the bald one with the long goatee, commiserated and wondered how simple math could take so long. I'd say another 40 minutes goes by before I get change but I do and now I have to call David's cell. None of the pay phones take change just phone cards. Fer fucks sake! Just as I'm about to blow a gasket, I see David and Martin who had been told the wrong gate and had themselves been waiting 2 hours for me. Hell.  Later the same day, the courier calls with my bags. He's bringing them. David's apartment is on a passage street. There are big doors off the main street that you need keys for and they open to a passage between buildings which includes the entrance to his building. I wait outside these doors on the main street and wait for the courier because he can't get in. An hour after the courier called David's cell phone to say that he had arrived at the address, he showed up and we lugged all the shit up 6 flights of stairs.  As soon as we got it all upstairs, the hell of the whole experience washed off me. I was in Paris!
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night I heard screaming and so I went out on the balcony. This guy was screaming at the top of his lungs at a woman who was in an apartment building a few buildings down from us. He built a few small fires of things she had given him.  Apparently, she broke his heart.  Leaving for India on the 27th.  Got shots today: Tetanus, Hep A & B, Diptheria, Polio - go back for Typhoid on Monday.  France is the land of the moustache.  Cheese and greens with black cherry confit is a good dessert.  Sometimes when you're drunk, you just have to go to sleep...     and sometimes when you come across a drunk sleeping in the street, you just have to take a picture.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The other day, David and I walked over to Place des Vosges, a gorgeous, intimate square surrounded by 17th century townhouses. Along the bottom of the townhouses is an arched walkway with many galleries and restaurants. Victor Hugo lived in Place des Vosges and his home is now a museum. You can check out the desk where he wrote Les Misserables, marvel at how small his bed was and gawk at his interior design choices.   We stumbled upon Le Photon Des Vosges, an optical shop off the square run by Rene OHana.      Rene is music obsessed. He has intruments all over his shop and iTunes hooked up playing tradtional middle eastern music. He showed us a video and told us about his friend, a Turkish violinist who was performing that evening. This guy was amazing; emotional, precise, frantic style playing.   I have been searching for new glasses for a long time and I never can find anything that I both like and fit my face. Well, I found some that I like and I think they fit. I'm still getting used to them but I think I like them.     David bought some sunglasses and we spent quite a bit of time in there talking to Rene. We talked family heritage. Rene is a Moroccan Jew and I told him that part of my Grandfather's family were from that area. We talked more music and he played us more video footage that he shot of middle eastern concerts in Paris.   Rene needed the rest of the afternoon to put our lenses in so we had to come back later to pick up our glasses which we do. Of course, being french, he hasn't done it yet and we hang out. Then the violinisy friend of his who he had showed us the video of and who was playing that night came in to the store with this sculptor, Albert Hirsch, who had an installation at the Jardin du Luxembourg. A very pretty woman who seemed to be the violinists girlfriend and this boy who was an assistant to  the violinist was there as well. It was a party! The boy had a violin with him which was new that day and so, the violinist decided to test it out. He played some Prokofiev and luckily I had my little camera and it takes video.  urlLink Check it out!   We followed this experience the only way we knew how - with great middle eastern food and wine.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      All tolled we were taking over 400 pounds of luggage, most of which had to be hauled down 6 flights of stairs and, since the apartment is off of a passage street, another 100 yards to meet the taxis. After almost leaving my Apple Studio monitor in the passage, we were off. After more lugging we were checking the bags. Were allowed 60 kilos total for the three of us. We fully expected to pay extra baggage. Usually, it's around $100 extra per bag. Air India was charging us 27 Euros per kilo over our limit! No way we were going to pay that much so much haggling ensued. We got it down to about half which was still outrageous but we were stuck. Ww had to go to the American Express counter to pay and then bring the reciept back before we could get on the flight. When we got to AMEX, the woman couldn't believe that we were being charged that much tellng us that 5 euros per kilo was what all the airlines charged. She insisted on talking to the people at the counter. Super nice of her but got us nowhere. We paid and were ushered to the front of security as all the hassle made us late. Even though we got pillaged, it was so nice not to have all that luggage any more and all we could do was let it go.  The plane was huge and completely packed. Walking down the aisle to my seat, so many people smiled at me and I thought to myself,  "I think I'm really going to like India". The flight was relatively painless. Good food, Starsky and Hutch, an Indian movie that I didn't catch the title of but I liked. It was about two friends, one playboy and one married. The married one visits the playboy and they both envy each other and decide that they want each others lives. Through it all, the married guy figures out what he's got and stays with his wife but the single guy doesn't heed the married friend's warning ends up in love and getting married. Of course, there was some good singing and dancing and though it was somewhat predictable, it had a good feeling to it and good acting as well.  We arrive in Mumbai. In line for customs, more smiles from people. Since we are transferring to another airline we have to collect our luggage and catch a bus to the domestic terminal. Oh, the pain! Lots of hassles about the computer. Why did I bring it? Was I going to sell it? Shouldn't I be paying duty? After seeing 5 or 6 different security guys, the final one asked the other guys why they were hassling us over one computer and let us through. Before getting to the bus we were stopped by a man with the hairiest ears I have ever seen and we had to fill out another form. We get to the domestic terminal and since our flight doesn't leave for another 4 and a half hours and its 2AM, the airline, Air Sahara, is closed. I wondered who came up with Air Sahara's motto "Emotionally Yours" and thought that I'd rather they were physically available than emotionally mine.  We wait it out and finally, they open. Different airline so we have to pay extra baggage again. Fortunately, this time its 50 rupees per kilo. Whatever, just get us there. We are all ready for the travel to be over. Luckily its only a little over an hour to Bangalore.  Finally, we're in Bangalore! We're et at the airport by Subbu and "the boys" who take care of all of our stuff and pack it into this Landrover looking vehicle. We ride in a little sedan. The drive from the airport to Shandilya Creations, where we're staying, is my introduction to the chaos! Everyone drives with one hand beeping the horn while stepping on the gas and basically just avoiding obstacles. There are so many horns that I can't really recognize ours. There are buses packed with people, auto-rickshaws, tons of people on scooters and motorcycles - whole families are on a single scooter: kid in front, dad driving, another kid behind dad and mom sitting sideways on the back, there are cows and oxen, there are people on bicycles, there are people walking in the street. Amazing! All the buildings, all the sidewalks, everything is fucked up yet somehow together.  We arrive at Shadilya creations unscathed, people are great, the place we are staying is great and thats where I'll end it for now.  Here's some pics of the way in from the airport:               
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      These are links:   urlLink I put up some new pictures    urlLink Also a 360 view of the main room of David's apartment where I'm staying. Its an incomplete, quick thing with no tripod but, its something 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Each morning I am awoken by Ashok (one of the servants here - see the last post with pictures) knocking on my door. Actually, that's not true. Each morning, at around seven there is an explosion of noise. The neighbors, whose house is a few feet from my window, begin clanging pots and pans, yelling, singing of what I assume are prayers (this part I like), down the street someone plays some kind of horn, the traffic starts and this means almost constant car horns although we are off of a main street so the really loud horns are intermittent, the local vendors start the yelling of what ever vegetable they are selling from a huge basket that is strapped to the back of their bicycles and then there are all kinds of animal sounds as well. Its an unbelievable racket that seems to all start at once. I lay in bed and anticipate Ashok's knock as i drift in and out of sleep.   Breakfast has been the toughest meal for everyone involved. People here have spicy food right off and while I can handle it sometimes and am ready to go with the flow on it, Martin and David definitely don't want it. They got us some cereal and then shoed up with steaming hot milk to put on it. Ashok came up once with a bottle that had a label that looked like it was apple juice but it was apple cider vinegar! The jam here is awful and the bread that you can get is like wonder bread without the wonder. After many mishaps, we're just having coffee for breakfast.   I have been leaving early in the morning and have been going out to Indian breakfast with Ravi Shankar. I work with Ravi Shankar everyday. It's not Ravi Shankar the famous musician and in fact, it's a common name here but I love saying that I work with Ravi Shankar or that I had lunch with Ravi Shankar because it's true. I've had two main specialties for Indian breakfast: Idli which consists of a plain donut looking thing which is just like a plain donut on the outside but is spongy on the inside and then two round discs that are white and are just like that spongy middle. Then you get some Sambar to pour over it. Sambar is like a spicy vegetable soup. You can get it with chutney instead of the sambar as well. We had it this morning at this little hole in the wall place that Ashwini recommended to me on the phone. It was incredibly good.  An order costs 7 Rupees or about 14 cents. The other special breakfast item is Masala Dhosa. It's a cross between a pancake and a crepe with a potato misture on the inside (often aloo gobi) and then you dip it in a spicy chutney. Very good as well. I love all these things but you can see how one might not be ready for it in the morning. I can't do it every morning although Uncle says it's very good for you and how can I argue with someone that looks that good at his age?  As I said, our cook looks like Kurt Vonnegut and I'll take a picture soon and see if you agree. He's a good cook but for the first 5 days or so, he was pretty much making the same thing. A spicy tomato soup, various types of rice, some days plain and somedays with vegetables, chipatis and then the main dish was like Aloo Gobi (Aloo is potato, Gobi is cauliflower) except substitute the gobi with green pepper. One day, Uncle ate with us and he made a great yellow curry dahl. After a while, we mentioned to uncle that he was making the same thing because Kurt doesn't understand english, and Uncle tore him a new one. Uncle is no holds barred when it comes to his guests or getting what he wants from his employees. He tears the boys a new one consistently and it's funny because he does it and its really intense and then they leave and he kind of cracks up and is gives the look like "not a bad performance, huh?" When ever Uncle's pointer finger comes out, you know you're in trouble. That's his patented look and move. The finger can be a scolding finger or a life lesson finger like the importance of honoring your parents.   After Uncle's dressing down, Kurt kicked it up a few notches. We've had vegetable korma, palak paneer, aloo gobi and okra that seems grilled but I'm not sure exactly how he's doing it but it sure is good. At first, Uncle didn't believe that we could handle the spice and even though we insisted, he was telling Kurt to go mild on us. One day, while I was having lunch out with Ravi Shankar, we were in this tiny village and we went to a restaurant there and ordered a vegetable curry and a spicy dahl dish and by the way, any dish can vary greatly from place to place, really, completely different. I insisted that the chilis were ok and Ravi wasn't sure what to do. "Are you sure? 100% chili? Not 50%? 80%?" They bring our food and it's hot. Even for Ravi. "This is 150%! It's OK?" I said, "It's more than OK, it's great!" and it was. You can never be sure by the looks of a place but we lucked out. Ravi reported back to Uncle that I ate the 150% spice and our spice level has been increased.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We are staying at Shandilya Creations where we, Martin, David and I, have a whole floor. Its a cement building. We each have our own room and there is a living area and dining room.  We all have bathrooms in our rooms which is nice and complete luxury for here. We even have toilet paper! The shower is common and we just got hot water. Life is pretty sweet here. I expected much more hardship. I just have to remember to take my daily Malaria pill.  The first floor has the office and the main editing and sound rooms. Shandilya is a production facility. They edit films, author DVDs, do dubbing and voice over and do their own complete productions. The second floor has another editing room and the kitchen where our cook, who looks like an Indian Kurt Vonnegut, prepares our meals. Yes, we have a cook and there are also "boys" who are basically servants. Its very strange. We're not supposed to be too nice to them and they don't really understand it when we are anyhow. The women who come to clean are even lower on the rung. They have bundle of sticks brooms and they clean the rooms and toilets everyday. The caste system in full effect. Its a crazy thing. It's awful and I'm really getting used to it.  We have the third floor and the fourth floor is a roof deck and a small apartment that I haven't been in. I think some of the boys stay up there. I don't really want to know about their accomodations. I have an idea and its not pretty.  Ashwini Shandilya owns Shandilya Creations. David and I met Ashwini in San Francisco where we created a trailer for another movie the he produced. Without going into it, that started our whole connection and this project coming about. Ashwini will be here for a few weeks and that's it. Ashwini's father, Uncle Lokanath, is a very famous Kannada actor (Kannada is the local language). He's 80 years old and you'd think he was 60. He's still strikingly good looking, has an amazing presence and glare. He has so much energy, its truly incredible. He's a very spiritual man. So gracious. A person that instantly starts treating you like a son. He tells you exactly what he thinks, what his ideas are but is open minded and doesn't force anything on anyone. He is also very concerned with being a good host and he can order around a boy like no other! He's in charge here!  There's so much more to the story but it's time for bed. Everywhere you look is a picture and a story. Its overwhelming.  Hopefully lots of posts this week!
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Pictures! 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Our cook, Krishna.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We, David, Martin and I, finally got out for a night on the town. Though we had never been, we've heard over and  over again that place to go if you want to go out, where there are Pubs, where all the worldly city stuff is in Bangalore is M.G. Road (Mahatma Ghandi Road). Pubs here close at 11PM, the time we would normally go out in San Francisco or Paris. We were told that this curfew was imposed after many drunk driving incidents and deaths. It always seemed to me that the better solution was to keep bars open so that people left at their leisure, when they were ready. Bars closing at 11 or eve 2 means everyone tries to get as drunk as they can by closing time and then everyone leaves together.The way last call works at every bar I've been to seems like a bad idea as well: They call last call, everyone gets a drink and they almost immediately tell you they are closing, that you need to drink up and get out.  We were going out to have dinner as well, so we were ready at 6 or so. Subbu, the bookkeeper at Shandilya Creations, was going with us and he said he'd be ready. We've now learned many times that Subbu is never ready and takes forever to do anything. We wait until after 7 for Subbu and we keep telling him that we want to go and that we're just going to go without him and he keeps telling us that he is ready, "One more minute." He's wasting our out time and we are getting pissed. Finally, he's ready and he comes out and tells our driver where we're going. Subbu is on his motorcycle. He's meeting us there. He knew we wanted to go and made us wait just so he could meet us there anyway. We deal with this kind of thing everyday. Ashok will bring all the food up for us and then go down two flights of stairs to get the plates and silverware while the food gets cold. Then he'll go back down for the utensils to serve the food. Things like this happen constantly and you really start to understand why Uncle breaks out the finger and tears these guys a new one so often. At the same time, Ashok makes a dollar a day if he's lucky. I'm not sure what Subbu's excuse is. I like him but he's frustrating and dare I say, lazy?  It takes almost an hour to get to M.G. Road. It's an hour of choking down pollution that you can see, thick like San Francisco fog. At least Nagesh, our driver, is playing my new favorite song that he, Ravi Shankar and I listen to in the car while location scouting. I had told David and Martin about it. Now they get to hear it. Like many of the songgs here, it's from a film and its goofy and and strange mix of elements. This one has electronic elements, Italian acordian music elements, polka elements and of course, Indian elements, both classical and pop. The singer has a low voice that has a goofy quality to it. There are two places in the song where it stops. Once he says, "I don't say nonsense!" and the other he says, "I don't care!" The verses are in Kannada but the chorus is in English: Danger 15 to 20, Danger 20 to 30, Soldier 30 to 40, Hunter 40 to something in Kannada. I'm hoping to pick up the CD.  We get to M.G. Road. It'sgot bigger buildings than the rest of the city. There are lots of restaurants, Street vendors, western looking places to shop and apparently, pubs too. It's cleaner than most of Bangalore outside of the parks and where the government builders are but still, the dirtiest street in Paris or San Francisco is cleaner. As soon as we get there, it starts to rain. We duck into the first place next to the car which is a large building with shops on the first floor and a terrace restaurant called The Canopy upstairs. Subbu meets us and after deliberation, we decide to go upstairs and have dinner and a few drinks before going to a pub. The Canopy is good not great. We have all decided to keep it vegetarian while we are here so even though they offer and array of North Indian non-vegetarian food, we stick with Vegetarian. We had some spicy vegetables Hyderabadi style, Palak Paneer, another dish I can't recall and, of course, drinks. We all got beers. Kingfisher is the local beer. Some scotch made an appearance as well. At this fancy place with all the food and drinks we spent around $40 for four of us.  It had stopped raining by the time we left the restaurant and we were walking when we saw a club called STYX. Not knowing anything about any place and Subbu, who doesn't drink, dance or ever really go out, as our guide, we decided to check it out.  The place was upstairs and as we got closer to the top of the stairs and the music got louder, I got more surprised. Iron Maiden, the Vikings of metal, was blaring and people were in semi-circles in rock stances banging their heads. There were video screens with the corresponding videos to the songs.  It was an awesome scene. I hadn't seen anyone so into the metal in years. They were so into it and not at all in a Kitsch way. People were drunk and headbanging. It was mostly boys but some girls as well. It seemed to be all Iron Maiden, Metallica and Megadeth. People were friendly and some came up to us like maybe we knew the bands or at least like we were from the land of metal. Subbu hated the place, I don't think Martin was too fond of it either but David and I have some metal i our blood and thought it nice to see the power of the metal being so thoroughly appreciated. All the boys at Shandilya who we told that we went there told us how much they hated that place. I laughed, knowing exactly why they hated it and that I secretly liked it.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Shivaganga is a large hill 60 kilometeres from Bangalore. It's called the four-faced hill and it's supposed to resemble a Nandi (Bull) from the east, a Ganesha (Elephant headed God) from the west, a linga (a half oval symbol with a similar meaning as the Chinese Yin Yang symbol) from the south and a cobra from the north. One who sees all four symbols will have a wish come true. There are two temples as you go up the hill, Honnadevi Temple and Gavi Gangadhareshwara Cave Temple. The Cave Temple is a good hike up and behind the alter there is a narrow passage way that you climb up into where there is a hole in the rock. You reach down into the hole and if you touch and are able to drink the water, it is a blessing from Ganesha and it means you are a good, worthy person and you will have good luck. Shivaganga is a pilgrimage center with people coming from all over to visit and hopefully, to see the 4 faces and drink the water of the Cave temple.     I arrived in Shivaganga with Ravi Shankar in the early afternoon. I had heard about the four faces but I didn't know the history of the temples. With Ravi, I can never tell if we are really understanding each other. He can speak some english and I can always understand what he is saying but a lot of times I think he's guessing at my meaning. "Ravi, we need a house for the family that looks to the mountain." "Yes, families live here." "I mean for the movie."  "I have done lots of movies here. This location." "For our movie. We need a house that the faces the mountain." "Yes, for our movie." "The boy looks to the mountain and tries to see the four-faces." "Our boy? In movie? This is in script?" "Yes." "Ah, this is very good!"     There are a lot of stairs leading up to the first temple and Ravi asks me if I want to go up. I wasn't sure if he didn't want to climb the stairs or if he thought I wouldn't. "Oh yeah", I said and up we went.      We got to the Temple, took our shoes off and went in. Ravi talked to the keeper of the temple, a man in his fifties who is wearing what looks like, not to be disrespectful, a cloth diaper. He has various painted strips and marks on his body, a red dot on his forehead and is wearing a necklace of small white flowers. I'm not sure if he is really considered a spiritual leader or just someone who presides over the temple and the prayers. He invites us into the sacred part of the temple and as we walk through there are varies small rooms off to the sides, all but one of which are not big enough to go into but only big enough for a statue of Ganesha or Shiva. Ravi walks up to each one and does a a small ritual, turns his hands back and forth in front of his face, touches his head and chest and mouths something. Apparently, this is a 1900 year old Temple. I'm pretty sure that's what Ravi said. Either that or its from 1900 and that doesn't make sense! We get to the bigger room and look through the doorway. There is a kind of ramp up to a Ganesha which is decorated in fresh flowers and has all kinds of things around it. Ravi and the man talk again and they talk a little about me and the film as I make out the words "film", "english" and "america". He and I smile at each other while they are talking and, just like everyone else I have encountered so far, is happy to have me there and is very warm and inviting. He brings a tray over that has a goblet that has fire coming out of it and Ravi and I put our hands in the firs and then over our faces. Then, he puts a small amout of milk (when I did this at the Bull Temple is Bangalore, it was water), which we drink. Probably not the smartest idea for me to be drinking strange milk but there I am doing it hoping that Ganesha will protect me from explosive diarrhea.     We leave the Temple and I give a 20 rupee note to a woman who gently begging with her two kids. She is so happy and motions that it will go to feed them. It's less than fifty cents to me and its a good amout of money to her. Its starting to drizzle rain and as we go up there are stairways made from someone carving into the rockface. Along the way there are a few little shelters with people selling drinks and snacks. Everyone smiles as we go by. There are oxen, lots of goats and monkeys. Every so often, Ravi makes sure that I want to continue up to the cave Temple which, of course, I do. We get there right before it really starts to rain and three monkeys and two twin wolf like dogs are standing guard along with a young guy who looks like Kobe Bryant.      The temple is very small and as you go in there are stairs leading up to a shrine of Ganesha. Same as most of the one's I have seen, you look through a doorway and there is a kind of ramp leading up to a decorated Genesha. Ravi, does his ritual and then we go to the right where there is a small passage way that you have to duck and climp up to. As you turn the corner, there is a leg sizzed hole in the rock. We look at it and go through to the other side and back around and out. I knew nothing abut the hole or touching the water but when we got out, a 69 year old man who had traveled 500 kilometers on his pilgrimage, asked me if I touched the water. I didn't understand but Ravi translated. Ravi told him that we didn't even try and he increduously sent us back in. Ravi, went and I wasn't sure why he was going or what was going on and he motioned for me to go, go!      We went back in and Ravi reach down shoulder length into the hole and pulled out some water which he drank. Then I did the same. Still not realizing the significance, we went back out. When the man, his friend and Kobe heard that we had gotten the water, they were very happy. We were blessed. They said that one person can reach in and get nothing and another right after might touch and drink the water. Its up to Ganesha whether you are a good person and if you are worthy. There were times when no one touched the water for 35 years and another time for 50 years. I was going to be very successful they said. After the rain stopped, on the way down the hill, Ravi said, "It's all real. God decides if you get the water. This is very good for the production." "Yeah", I said, thinking to myself about how seriously he and the others took this and that it was all sweet and harmless enough. No reason to reveal myself as a non-believer and whatever gives you hope is fine with me. The fact that they believed it and that it was an amazing experience was good enough for me.  News of our triumph travelled back to Shandilya Creations and everyone was impressed and happy that this had happened. Me too. I'll always have the story to tell.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>