<Blog>

<date>27,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
      back from europe as of yesterday. had a great time in stockholm and am considering moving there for the summer. wondering how feasible this is ...
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
      finished a nice 5 day trip in Paris. saw lots of old pretty buildings and ate french food. it is really a beautiful city and i found the people to be really friendly, even though my french sucks.  it was also great seeing my friends.  currently in stockholm visiting a friend. i have been here before and already did the tourist stuff so now i can just hang out. great weather too. currently at an internet cafe at hötorget tubestop.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
      had an amazing meal somewhere, i think around the bastille.  an enormous dish of shellfish and a lot of white wine.  really fantastic - and we were all treated by a good friend of carine's.   i wish i could remember the name of that place ... i'll have to ask.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Check out of the Hotel de l'Academie and have a brunch and stroll in Le Marais area. Then C leaves for the airport and I move to my new hotel, the "Hotel le Plan d'Etait", which is near Republique. Not nearly as charming as the last place and I'm still making up my mind about this neighborhood/location, but I suppose a walk around will give a better idea. anyway, i'm still downtown and the room is clean. 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Day 2 in Paris. Coffee in the morning on Blvd St. Germain and then we take the metro to Les Halles to have lunch with Carine. We go to a Moroccan restaurant and have a really nice meal. Then C and I go to the Musee d' Orsay and spend a few hours walking around the galleries. She knows quite a bit about art. I don't, but it was really interesting anyway.  Dinner tonight involved looking for an african restaurant called "Omar" near the Republique. Unfortunately the internet connection went down before we could get an address. So we walk forever around the Republique, asking taxi drivers, concierges, etc. One concierge does not know of "Omar" but mentions another african place called "Dogon" just around the corner. we have a look from the corner and decide it is uninspiring. keep walking and looking for "Omar". Finally give up and ask for other restaurant rec's. Almost go to the first place, "Chez Jenny", but it is a bit expensive so we decide to give "Dogon" another shot. We walk up to the restaurant entrance of Dogon and see one guy sitting at the otherwise empty bar. We decide it is closed and walk away. He sees C's union jack umbrella and comes to the door, saying "It's really good! The food here is great! Are you from London? " We walk cautiously back and find out that it's not closed, but the restaurant is upstairs. we walk cautiously upstairs and then are relieved to see a dining area full of people. The man from the bar, Alpha, and his friend, an English teacher in Paris, join us for dinner. He is senegalese, educated in Paris, and living in London as a French & spanish professor. She has just gotten the results from a difficult teacher's inspection and tells us about the process. Sounds very very strict. We spend 2+ hours talking and eating and drinking. I think they are interested in what we do at work. Finally we head back around 1:30am. A really great night.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Day 1 in Paris. Arrive at Gare du Nord and wait for a taxi. Lots of traffic. Get to the Hotel de l'Academie, which is in the Latin Quarter/St. Germain area. Really beautiful surroundings. Our room is so small, I can barely see it. C arrives around 9pm, as expected. We go out to dinner in the nearby area. Appetizers were awesome, main course was alright. Fixed price of 14 euros. A friend of the restaurant staff sat down to chat as we were finishing the meal. He was really nice at first, and more than a bit sleazy later, hitting like mad on my friend. They invite us to a nightclub but we decline.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
      i have my computer sitting on the wide ledge on the inside-side of the window. found an unsecured wireless network outside with boingo! awesome because this hotel has no ethernet port.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
      have arrived in amsterdam. flight was okay but did not sleep. overslept first 1 1/2 hrs of today's second meeting due to my naptime. really it was accidental, i meant to wake up and go. anyway, no one really cared. 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
      sixers lost again. they did what they do a lot: start weak, fall way behind, play amazingly to catch up, bring the score close, and then do something stupid and lose anyway.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
      well i've just started this diary thing...we'll see how it goes. most people seem to be posting their inner monologues. i hope i'm near a computer if my mind wanders someplace interesting.  what with starting a diary so late in life (never kept one before), i suppose i have a lot of territory to cover. better get started.  actually i think i'll just play tetris and worry about it later.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      well back to NYC tomorrow to see some apartments. should be exciting. hope we can find a comfortable space with light. and i dont want to mortgage my first child! well i think future roommate has some good ideas. Future R. is taking an afternoon off for this adventure.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      we got a new gerbil today, she is pretty cool and good at figuring out the new cage-toys i bought.  the first gerbil was not too sure at first of this new addition but i think is enjoying the company now. they act like siblings.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Latest from Burma is that Aung San Suu Kyi is being held in Insein Prison, just in time for her 58th Birthday. No sign of release from this "protective custody", which apparently is the same as being in jail. She has no access to a legal process, since Burma has no such thing.  Her vehicle was attacked by goverment-sponsored thugs at a recent speech in northern Burma, and they jailed her and several other members of the NLD, blaming them for the violence. At the recent ASEAN conference, neighboring nations condemned her imprisonment but said nothing about imposing sanctions. The US is quite serious about furthering sanctions and freezing assets of the Burmese military junta's leaders; however, since the US doesn't trade a whole lot with Burma, the effects would not be as great as sanctions imposed by other SE Asian countries.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      www.oreilly.com's safari site is one of the best idea's i've seen in a while. not only are their reference texts great, but now there are a bunch of them online. i pay 10 bucks a month to have up to 5 books out at a time. you have to keep a book for 30 days but then can swap it (or not) for another selection.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      The struggle of Aung San Suu Kyi and Burma's NLD has been largely ignored by US media   urlLink BBC News Article: "Concerns over fate of Suu Kyi"    urlLink More coverage of recent events   Why is the international community so passive in its involvement? 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      A few things going on, I am trying to move to stockholm for the summer. Then today I got a suggestion to live in NYC. Boss has asked if I want to live in Bangkok.  The more I think about it, living in NYC would be really cool. I could move when I get back from stockholm. Now if I could only get my car sold .. know anyone who wants to buy a 2001 Jetta?  Bangkok would be neat but I dont have any friends there. maybe in the future i will go for a month or two. they offered me a sweet deal of covering airfare and living expenses.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      defragmented c: drive, cleaned out mp3s and digital photos, removed unused program files, freed many gigabytes, ordered a memory upgrade.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      got here yesterday. outside the window of my massive tourist hotel, i can see fallen-apart apartment buildings, a buddhist shrine, and a small canal.   i had a great meal last night and plan to go electronics shopping tomorrow.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      went here last night   urlLink http://www.medusabar.com/   and walked part of the way home in the 4am stockholm sunrise. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink this story  is from the beginning of july. happened right near my house.  in fact i saw it, almost. i was running late for a haircut and stopped at the supermarket for a snack. i noticed all the police in the parking lot and the car covered with a white sheet. well, none of my business, i figured, and i just kept going.  but after i read what happened, i can't help but think "what if" i had gotten there 10 minutes earlier? what if someone had taken notice of this guy, about to kill himself, in a busy supermarket parking lot? i imagine doing something heroic like talking him out of it; but chances are i would have just run from a guy with a gun. 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      okay, i can't get this here in stockholm...thus my want of it quadruples.   urlLink Philips key ring MP3   also i'm starting to think an ipod would be fun to have.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      the best album ever. how did i not find this 10 years ago when it came out?  Liz Phair's  Exile in Guyville  on a related note, my high speed internet is back working
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      have been in stockholm for maybe 3 days. yeah that sounds right. i´m really &¤&/#!!& jetlagged, sleeping mostly in the middle of the day.  the apartment i am renting is great, tiny but great location and well equipped. and also with a weird connection, the brother and sister in law of the landlord live in new york´s east village, 2 streets away from where i am moving in sept.  otherwise, my only complaints are the broken internet at home and my personal non-speaking of swedish.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Ape Culture Haikus: Skymall   urlLink http://www.apeculture.com/skymall.htm 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      can i even start to describe the coolness of my future new york apartment? 100% credit to future roommate for finding and securing it. east village and private backyard!
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Went for a day at the beach in stockholm. If you are swedish and want a good laugh, just ask me to pronounce the name of the beach. Sounds like "Salt-whuey-badn". But the middle sound is really tough for the unswedish.      Photo: the beach   Really beautiful and just a little cold. But not as bad as we, in these photos, would have you believe.       Photos: Beach bums 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      in my project, there are 4 managers and 2 non managers (i am one of the latter). add to that equation that the 4 managers are male and the 2 non managers are not. is this a little weird?
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      and i sound all raspy. not as bad as yesterday but still not normal. i came back from thailand with a cold; good thing they are through with SARS, otherwise i would be convinced of having it. I was violently ill from some thai food the night I left and then i got this cold. But the stickers on Thai Airways Staff luggage were really comforting: "Thailand: SARS-Free".
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      i overhead someone's broken english today that made sense in a weird way. he didn't know to say "the day before yesterday" so he said "last yesterday"
     
    
</post>

<date>29,September,2003</date>
<post>

     
      went to  urlLink patricia ship and nightclub  on sunday, which is gay club night.   had a nice half price meal and saw a very bad performance by stockholm's most famous drag queen, plus some bad karaoke/dance routine by another group of performers.  plus lots of the token too-tight-shirt on muscle-bound and very pretty men who have no interest in me. well, we all had a nice time talking and laughing, and i met some cool people. the building itself is very cool, it's an old ship (formerly of GBritain) that somehow ended up permanently docked in front of slussen.  there are several levels and some outdoor decks (way too cold here right now for that, it was almost snowing tonight).
     
    
</post>

<date>28,September,2003</date>
<post>

     
      as its final performance, my thinkpad crashed.  now windows won't start and even though i have data backups, it will be a real pain to get it working again. the probable cause is a bad hard drive, something is physically wrong with it.   unfortunately i think i have to involve IBM in this process, which means long waits on the phone and generally bad customer service.  i want them to replace the harddrive and send me recovery CDs for windows XP (i asked three times last year for these and never got them).  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,September,2003</date>
<post>

     
      i can't believe my 3 months here is almost over - this weekend i have to clean out and tuesday i fly away. last night i went for drinks at the bar 'boheme' on drottningatan, after seeing a jazz show (oddjob was the band's name) at kulturhuset. i got some going-away gifts from my friends - it was so nice of them! i will really miss them, and although i don't speak swedish and i haven't got common childhood memories of running in the woods with trolls, i've at least got my kånken bag and i'm starting to feel like i fit in here.   well.  resolve: come back in future.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,September,2003</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink check out this band .  i saw them tonight at  urlLink Nalen  music hall in stockholm.   they were fantastic - dramatic, energetic, and had a sense of humor.  also musically quite good.  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,September,2003</date>
<post>

     
      i love my spellchecker because it tried to replace "C++" with "CHIHUAHUA". 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,September,2003</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink BBC NEWS | Science/Nature | Giant rodent astonishes science 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,September,2003</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink CNN.com - Swedes rally for Anna Lindh - Sep. 12, 2003   here's the crowd i couldn't get through ... now i see why!  urlLink  sergelstorg rally   amazing all the people that showed up.  i could philosophize about this country and how they've got everything figured out.  in a crowd of 50,000, everyone still had good manners :)
     
    
</post>

<date>10,September,2003</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink BBC NEWS | Europe | Swedes rally against violence   I went to this gathering, sort of - it was too crowded to get a proper view.  BTW it happened just following the tragic violent death of foreign minister Anna Lindh, who was stabbed in a local dept store and died the next morning.  it's a really awful thing that happened and it sounds like she was one of their most admired politicians.   you wonder what the world would have been like, had she survived the attack.   i should read more about her.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,September,2003</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink mera  for a night of drinks and a lot of people clubbing at  urlLink mosebacke  on 'raw fusion' night and the seasonal opening of  urlLink osaka vs tokyo 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,September,2003</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink UltraEdit   the best text editor ever and well worth $35.  check it out.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,September,2003</date>
<post>

     
      this morning's IM..   johnh: don't say "i'm drawing conclusions out of my ass" ... johnh: say "I'm thinking outside the box." johnh: :)  well i feel better!
     
    
</post>

<date>08,September,2003</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink CNN.com - Bush to ask billions more for Iraq - Sep. 8, 2003 : "President Bush told Americans Sunday night he will ask Congress for an additional $87 billion to continue the wars in Afghanistan and Iraq. He will also ask more nations to help pay the cost."  i'm speechless.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,September,2003</date>
<post>

     
      the theme is "the best day bag ever", by the way.   urlLink fjällräven , kånken model, is the most perfect small backpack.  a nice square-ish shape and nonobtrusive straps.  and certainly not containing the "i'm going camping for 3 weeks and need bungee straps and 18 mesh pockets" philosophy.  come to think of it, my 'porter' bag is square too.  i got that one in japan,  and i hear they have just reached shelves in new york shops.  they are pretty durable and pretty expensive.  but that same label makes great wallets (also square).
     
    
</post>

<date>03,September,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Cheap software recovered my data!  urlLink http://diydatarecovery.nl   Okay, it put the files in the wrong folders, and not all of them are correct, but it worked well enough so that I don't have to spend $400 on professionals (who may just be using similar software after all...)
     
    
</post>

<date>03,September,2003</date>
<post>

     
      okay so when you change the timestamp, it adjusts all entries. actually i would prefer it to only apply the new timestamp to all entries made after the change.  so it reflects your local time.  i change timezones a bit lately.  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,September,2003</date>
<post>

     
      http://rnbhq.org/pipermail/r31/2003-July/000153.html  thinkpad recovery partition, loading from GRUB
     
    
</post>

<date>02,September,2003</date>
<post>

     
      timestamp is 4 sept 00h53
     
    
</post>

<date>02,September,2003</date>
<post>

     
      hard drive crash...lost data... The thing is, i know the data is there!  i just can't get to it because the file table is corrupt. i was resizing a partition using partition magic and my computer crashed mid-process.   well, i have two options, cheap software or expensive professional geeks.  agonizing hours have passed as the cheap software scans my drive...
     
    
</post>

<date>02,September,2003</date>
<post>

     
      because there are zero obvious laundromats in this city! i could have really used this when i first got here.  Laundry & Dry Cleaning City Kemtvatt, Drottningsholmsvägen 9 (tel. 08/654-95-34), does dry cleaning and also laundry by the kilo for same-day delivery if it's brought in before 10am. It's open Monday through Friday from 7am to 6pm and Saturday from 10am to 2pm. Note that the system of coin-operated launderettes is pretty much outmoded in Sweden. The cost for doing laundry is 55SEK ($5.85) per kilo (2.2 lb.). Your clothes will be neatly folded for you as part of the price.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,September,2003</date>
<post>

     
      first post
     
    
</post>

<date>02,September,2003</date>
<post>

     
      1. Giant lizard terrorises Beirut  he's already claimed victims - several cats, a dog and apparently even a horse   urlLink Read more   2. Giant gerbils infest China   urlLink Read more here. 
     
    
</post>

<date>31,October,2003</date>
<post>

     
      well here it is ... halloween in new york .. what a crazy time! ??  looks like my night has been pre-determined to be of the stay-in sort.  a quick reminder that i have no friends here.  i mean, i haven't really been here long enough to have established any sort of social network.  but still it would be nice to have something to do on halloween.    maybe i'll take the roaches trick or treating.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,October,2003</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Slashdot | White House Website Limits Iraq-Related Crawling   that's disturbing.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,October,2003</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink India - Consular Information Sheet :  "It is very important to keep in mind that if a driver hits a pedestrian or a cow, the vehicle and its occupants are at risk of being attacked by passersby. Such attacks pose significant risk of injury or death to the vehicle's occupants or at least of incineration of the vehicle. It can thus be unsafe to remain at the scene of an accident of this nature, and drivers may instead wish to seek out the nearest police station."
     
    
</post>

<date>18,October,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Got here late last night, around 3am due to taxi driver getting lost.  We're at the  urlLink Salaya Pavilion hotel , which is just outside Bangkok city.  Properly speaking, Bangkok starts across the highway.    This area is pretty nice and not as congested as downtown.  There is a 500 acre park nearby and a row of ragged shops and restaurants.  The weather is starting to "cool off" as they say, which is still hot as hell.  at least you can be outside, 90 degrees and 80% humidity (unlike april when it's absolutely truly unbearable).  APEC conference downtown so there is a general buzz.  plus everything is closed, due to the conference (why ?? ), so a lot of regular Thais are on vacation this week.    Tonight we took a walk and took some pictures.  At the park we had Guava juice and Malaysian Roti (a flaky pancake topped with condensed milk).  I'm exhausted so no major dinner plans tonight.    Workshop starts tomorrow morning, we've met some participants already and checked out the classroom.  It is square with 15 rectangular computer desks facing the front.  Everything is the color gray.  It is possibly the most uninspiring room i have ever seen.  At least I dont have to teach until wednesday, which is good 'cause i''ll know our participants better by then and it won't be so alien an experience.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,October,2003</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink BBC NEWS | Science/Nature | Purple frog delights scientists    urlLink National Geographic: Frog Discovery Is "Once in a Century" 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,October,2003</date>
<post>

     
      two hours in tokyo's international airport  purchase list: 1000 yen for internet access plus 6700 yen for a camera case and the replacement camera battery (left mine in the charger in the living room ~ doh!)  food consumption: 1 bad udon prawn tempura, 1 partial iced green tea  internal clock report: body thinks it's: 5:30am ; but instead, it's: 7:30pm  flight here from new york was: long (12 hrs), but with a good emergency exit row seat.  downside: awful food and very cold near the exit door.  in flight movie: "down with love" with renee z. and ewan macgregor.  liked it.  cool thing that happened today:  bought a "national geographic" at the new york airport, good article on cenote diving [yucatan peninsula cavern formation systems].  opened up the article and what do i see but a great big photo of Luis from  urlLink sealife divers , my favorite diveshop in playa del carmen, mexico.     six hours to bangkok and then 10 days on the ground.  gate 27 beckons .. bye for now
     
    
</post>

<date>12,October,2003</date>
<post>

     
      the cockroaches and i are at war.    day 1, 00h00:  start cleaning the entire apartment.  scrub all manner of gross things.  bathtub and bathroom floor actually changed color.  put out roach traps. when i'm done, there's not a single roach in sight, living or dead.  day 2, 13h00:  check email and roach crawls across my foot  days inbetween: one single half-inch roach seen every day, sluggish from poison traps; or with major attitude and does not care about broad daylight or me looming in the foreground with RAID in hand  day five-ish: not a single roach spotted.  too soon to declare victory; either the cold weather will kill them all or drive them indoors.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,October,2003</date>
<post>

     
      finally made it to new york!  a few very stressful days of packing and trying to plan, but i'm here! downside is that i had to leave my desk and super-comfortable bed at mom's house, because there is no way either would fit here.  this location is great and our backyard is super cool, but the apartment is really small.   i guess the main reason i care about space is that i have to set up a home office and it could get pretty cramped.     well this weekend i'm going to clean like hell and hopefully scare away the roaches.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,October,2003</date>
<post>

     
      wow, i can't believe i'm back in the suburbs again!  nothing ever changes here, it barely feels like i left. thank god i'm moving to manhattan soon, i think i would go crazy if i stayed here much longer. i really miss stockholm. well these next few weeks will keep me super super busy, moving into my new apartment and then going to bangkok.  this is a really tight schedule, honestly i don't know how i'm going to manage it.  i'll pull it off somehow .. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,October,2003</date>
<post>

     
      after three unanswered requests last year, this time i get not one but three IBM reps on the phone.  they actually called me back several times, more than was needed. i have to pay forty dollars for the recovery cds but they'll be here tomorrow.  i could have gotten them for free but it would have taken at least two hours of arguing and probably waiting weeks for delivery, since ibm is unbelievably bureaucratic.  even they were confused about which dept handles what, and where should they transfer my call.  state farm, on the other hand, was just one rather brief but still painful phone call.  i cancelled my car insurance and they told me "well, we probably can't stop the automatic payment for next month" but agreed to eventually refund me.  also they said if i want insurance in the future, it might be tough because i will be "starting fresh, as an uninsured driver". but what about the nine years i've been insured by them and my perfect driving record?  apparently any break in coverage erases their memory of you.   idle threats to keep sucking cash is what i think.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
      writing to you from mom's house; dad came over and we cooked cornish hens, stuffing, cranberry sauce, mashed potatoes, green beans.  altogether a great meal and more than we could finish!
     
    
</post>

<date>21,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink BBC NEWS | UK | England | West Yorkshire | Bomb alert over 'break-wind' dog 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
      switzerland and sweden.  looking forward to SWE and maybe SWZ once conference is over.  not looking forward to three days of standing on ceremony, smiling at heads of state who i'm sure havent the faintest idea about what we do, while we hand out 9000 copies of my never-intended-for-public-usage software.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
      pages and pages of "man wanted" adverts, put out by parents for their daughters.  desireable traits included good job, education, social class. my impression: disturbing.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
      home for a whole three weeks!  i'll be cleaning up this place in preparation for my family's visit this saturday - gasp!  then we've got WSIS approaching and the to-do list outpaces the amount of time left.  looks like i'll be leaving town dec 4th and have a quick few days off in stockholm before the big event.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
      on sunday  i was invited  by two american colleagues to visit the city of Jaipur.  Jaipur is located in the Rajasthan state, south-west of Delhi and about a 4 hour drive.   During the early morning still-dark drive we saw a lunar eclipse.  Weather was hot but generally comfortable.  We explored the architectural and historical sites - the Amber Fort, City Palace, Hawa Mahal, and the Observatory.  All in all, it was fascinating and I was lucky to go with two people who know a lot about India and could give relevant historical notes.    
     
    
</post>

<date>07,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
      writing to you from new delhi, india.  got in 2 nights ago and am working from NAB hq.  Lots of blind children in the upstairs school plus this downstairs technology center, which is where i'm at.  traffic here is something quite amazing, every sort of vehicle in a free for all near-deathmatch, but the drivers never look stressed out.   other roadsites are beggars and cows. smog is unbelievable, a thick haze at all times.  warm weather but not too warm and good food - everything quite pleasant so far.
     
    
</post>

<date>31,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      home from switz, philly, and detroit.  finished workshop, saw immediate fam, saw extended fam.  exhausted now.  have to rest up for new years tonight.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      finished kaizers-in-zurich, geneva, and now back in zurich for the workshop.  kaizers orchestra was fantastic, just me, them, and 300 fans in a sweaty little club.  geneva was generally dull but spent off-hours with daisy folk whom i like.  zurich-part-II should be alright, there is a semi-reliable WLAN out the hotel window [the hotel btw is newly decorated and a big improvement over the chavannes de bogis insipid pink scheme].
     
    
</post>

<date>05,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Hello from Sweden! got here last night and looking forward to a relaxed weekend with friends. it's actually colder at home than it is here.  next stop is Switzerland.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      december first, first snow for about three minutes it got very cold and the rain turned to snow
     
    
</post>

<date>11,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Storage Facility  finally, a place to put my backups! 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i've decided to start running ... got a pair of shoes and gone out four times in the last four days so far.  thing is, i can't really run continuously so i followed the advice of some articles online and did 1 min running and 1 min walking (repeat for duration of course - about 1 1/2 miles). windchill has been about 0 deg. (Farenheit) lately so it probably won't get much worse.  urlLink Here is a good article , which emphasizes not overdoing it and listening to your body.  Thing is, I can't always distinguish between if I've overdone it or just merely done it!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      when i was staying in mexico, i found one of  urlLink these  in my room (!!).  I would say its body was a good three+ inches, and with legs (not counting the superlong feeler-antennae legs) it was around 7 or 8 inches in diameter.    i had a late night out and got home around 3am.  the mexican family i was staying with kept the drains covered so as to prevent insects from entering.  i saw my bathroom sink drain lid had been moved so i went around my room, armed with one sneaker, looking for a big cockroach or something.  i did a double take then a horrific recoil to find this on the wall of my clothes-hanging alcove space.  i hovered over it with the shoe and then it ran very very quickly, sideways.   Then i snuck up on it and beat it senseless.  It died several times.  turns out to be a creature called a tailless whipscorpion or whipspider; or more exactly, a member of the order Amblypygi.  they are harmless to humans but are also huge and gross-looking.     urlLink Here is a good story  about a field trip encounter with one of these, found in a cave, eating a frog.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Turntables on the Hudson   Went here for NYE 2003.  Great party in an old ship (the  urlLink  Frying Pan  )
     
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      a last minute airport thought to get a "meow-lingual" cat translation device resulted in the following conversation:  me: hi, i'm looking for a cat translator called "meow-lingual" clerk: shows me the english/japanese electronic dictionaries me: no, it's for cats.  so you know what they're saying.  it's made in japan. clerk: for cats and dogs to use?  i'm sorry, we don't have anything like that. me:  no, it's so i can understand them.  it's a toy. clerk: you want cat food?  me: not cat food.  cat translator.  you know, "cat": "neco" [japanese for cat].  then i mimicked a cat saying "meow" and me holding out a device near it.  i think they understood.  anyway, either that or they were fed up with me.  i was pointed to the next row of shops.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      after managing to get my timetable wrong today, i am now officially going to japan tomorrow.  really i am.  today, stuck with my own bad timing, i dodged a persistent rain and ill-informed airline staff, who almost put me on a flight to NRT via LA, claiming it would get me there shortly after my original arrival time.   what they meant was, yes it arrives in the afternoon, one hour later than your original flight, PLUS ONE DAY later.  glad i thought better of it and avoided a 12 hr layover at LAX.  even my tired brain wasn't quite sure how it was possible to leave the east coast 8 hours later than planned, and arrive only 1 hour later than planned, after taking a longer route and enduring a hideous layover. while back at the ticket counter - to change to a more reasonable flight - i told the attendant what the problem was.  her response was that they don't tell her dates for schedules, only hours and minutes.  she didn't know or care that i might not want something that leaves on the 3rd and arrives on the 5th, if i could have something instead that leaves on the 4th.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
       We're having a face to face in New Delhi, generously hosted by NAB.  We have done exercises called "how to read the documentation" or "look it up before you ask me".   Covered "Basic C++" and "Basic C++ II".    Now just to wait for some working code to come in.  Already submitted: partially working.    To work on:  my patience. No severe stomach pains to report of.   Otherwise, India not much different from before: livestock, nice food, overly attentive hotel staff. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      cozumel - santa rosa wall - bad dive b.c. could not equalize playa del carmen - chun zumbul and shangri la - good dive, strong currents so did two reefs in one dive.  with carine. cenote dos ojos - great as always.  two different dives here. playa del carmen - tortuga reef.  with kate, lydie, and johanna.  great fun. cenote angelita - amazing.  will post links later about this one gran cenote - nice and relaxing
     
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      left my passport in my laundry .. went to pick it up later and had a very confusing conversation with the laundry attendant. he said "you're a problem" (which might have meant: "you could have had a problem") and then after 10 minutes of broken conversation, i found out that my passport survived because he had found it and removed it prior to starting the wash. there was a cryptic note inside my laundry bag that said "my name &lt;something indian&gt;. your passpot my pukt." [pukt = pocket] and then gave a tel. number and address of the laundromat.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      quote from the drunk outside my building: "you're beautiful .. but you're no sacajawea!" 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      1. Always stand at the corners in a bar 2. Women like men dressed in blue, while women in pink give out the signal that they're approachable 3. Wear cinnamon perfume.  Aromatherapy experts say it has aphrodisiacal properties. 4. Smile a lot.  Taken from the Hindustan times (New Delhi), March 2004
     
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      when talking about the construction of the new A380 superjumbo jet: "The wings are 38 tonnes each, and are far too heavy to be transported by air."  [source: http://news.bbc.co.uk/2/hi/uk_news/wales/north_east/3594419.stm]
     
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ...is the worst airport in the world.  stood in lines for 3 hours while checking in, while immigration stamped papers (and acted like they'd never done it before), while security looked dumbly at an xray monitor.    security also had me go through the "women" queue, which was far away from my bags (15ft) and made me nervous (i had 1500 in cash on me).  said bags were thrown on the floor by security man along with the others as they exited the xray conveyor belt.  briefcase had to have laptop removed and sent back through while my cries of "why didn't you say so earlier??!!" were ignored.  needless to say, my flight had been bording for some time now and was ready to leave as soon as we all could get on board.  BA staff told me that the airport is "usually much worse".  
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink BBC News | ASIA-PACIFIC | Scientists cross pigs with spinach 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink iRaq / iPod 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      many new features at blogger since i checked last time.  nice to have  blog-by-email. 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well just got back from a week in NC for the wedding of my childhood best friend.  Really amazing.  30 people in the same house, all having grown up together (more or less).  Ceremony was short but perfect.  Whales appeared in the ocean background (a rare occurance apparently).  Stay tuned for photos!
     
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      artist of the month: Totta Näslund... ...whom I almost saw, actually i did see him play in Mexico, but didn't really know/care about him, and so i sat there at the edge of the bar [la ranita in playa del carmen] just chatting with friends and ignoring the show. seems like it's happened a few times that i'm at a show of someone whom i end up just loving a few months/years later, but at the time i totally ignore them.  and i'm always kicking myself for doing this.  resolve: pay attention to everything all the time.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      cool thing i did this week:   [actually yesterday.] saw, for free, david foster wallace get interviewed by george saunders (both are authors).  they talked about writing and answered audience questions.  audience members were mostly writing students who asked super geeky questions that took longer to ask than to answer. interesting things the authors discussed: +having sean hannity as a character, and writing with an eye for understanding and empathizing with him +why do teachers say "write what you know"? otherwise they get very strange scifi-ish things.  on the flip side, the request can result in generic crap.  but also mentioned that you know more than you think and can prob. extrapolate your experiences to connect with a particularly strange-but-trueish character +self-aware/neurotic attributes of writers +self-collapsing genres who connect with their own kind better than the public, thereby turning their energy inwards  quite worth mentioning:  4 bad trendy consecutive male haircuts in the row front of us.  I will try to remember them in order: "freeze-frame, bed-head", "curly, unshaven, shaggy with hat" (may not be so trendy actually), "slight mullet", "sculpted rock star with elfin sidelocks".  
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      after reading  urlLink my roommate's blog about life in korea , it reminds me of things that i thought were weird about japan.  like how it's okay to be shitfaced throwing up in public [actually it seems like you can do and say anything you want iff you're drunk], and how people think it's cute if you like parts of their culture or language.  i probably didn't have to deal with it as much as he does because i made little attempt regarding the language.  but i would get the occasional not-funny joke if i knocked something over in the cramped office - "oh, you're used to america - lots of room!  japan is too small." which i think they meant to be self-deprecating but actually wasn't at all.  i think i learned some things too, about how to fit too many objects neatly in a very small space, how NOT to plan and proceed through events (very confusing with lots of papers and hands flying, and a good deal of nonsense logic), and how to work with their extreme devotion to harmony (aka how to get your way, nicely.).  where i probably should have learned more but didn't: india.  too many people, animals, cars, dust.  too little toilet paper.  virtues include: patience, persistence.  annoyances include: slowness, harassment.  still wondering if i learned something: mexico, thailand.  wait, someone did tell me the four something-or-others of buddhism in a car ride once thru bangkok.  don't remember it but apparently all your life's events can fit into one of these four categories.  and in mexico i learned spanish (not life-shattering but at least measurable)  
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Having been discontinued in Sweden, I finally found and bought a  urlLink Kånken Computer  bag from a  urlLink German rugged outdoorsy site .  bag is just brilliant. perfectly designed, small size and just enough compartments to separate my things, but not so many that i misplace and forget.  am v. v. happy. almost rapturous.  do other people get this joyous over a bag?  cannot wait to use on next long-ass haul (july, nyc to tokyo).
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      tonight i saw joao gilberto at carnegie hall.  he played "corcovado", "desafinado", "garota de ipanema" (of course), "pra que discutir com madame", "estate" (i was thrilled), "sandalia de prata", "doralice", and 2 hours worth of songs whose names i forget.  the crowd was (mostly) completely quiet while he played, and the quality of the sound was amazing, even from my nearly-as-high-up-as-you-can-be seat.  for the whole set it was just him and his guitar.  he sounded exactly like the voice i've been hearing for years on CD.  just perfect.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Cool site with user-submitted slang-dictionary:   urlLink Redota.com > Uruguayos en el exterior > Diccionario .  Different meanings from  different countries are given.    Another good site is le vieux coq.  An excerpt from  urlLink Letter E of their idiom guide :   # echar palos: 1.- Ir a tomar unos tragos. (Ven.) 2.- Ir a fornicar. Durante el transcurso de uno de mis primeros viajes por América Latina estaba yo recién llegado a México después de pasar una semana en Venezuela y al finalizar la primera larga jornada de trabajo unos tres colegas masculinos mexicanos me fueron a dejar al hotel en auto. Ya llegando al hotel se me occurió la genial idea de invitarlos a echarse unos palos conmigo. Dado el súbito y profundo silencio que descendió en el carro me percaté de que algo no estaba muy bien e indagué sobre el motivo. Las [obvias y coloridamente autóctonas] respuestas que recibí fueron la chispa creadora de este panfleto. (Méx.)   attempted translation :  # echar palos: 1.- Go for a drink. (Venezuela.) 2.- Go have sex [other countries - ed.]. During one of my first trips through Latin America, I had just arrived in Mexico after spending a week in Venezuela, and at the end of the first long day of work, three male Mexican colleagues drove me back to my hotel.  Already at the hotel, it occured to me the idea of inviting them to have something to drink with me.  Suddenly, as a profound silence descended upon the car, I realized that something wasn't right and I inquired as to why. The [obvious and colorful natives'] responses that I got were the spark creator of this "panfleto" [don't know this word -ed.] 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      today i took a walk down to chinatown - specifically to the  urlLink TenRen  teashop.  bought white tea, assorted teas, and jasmine tea.  at $100/lb, I didn't get too much of the latter, but it is amazing stuff.  made by layering tea leaves with just-blooming jasmine flowers, and then removing the flowers when their scent has been absorbed.  according to TenRen:  "Ten Ren's Pearl Jasmine the tea leaves are scented seven or more times to give the tea that strong Jasmine aroma. "  of course there is always the possiblity of drinking too much and  urlLink going mad . 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Canon's tech support website: "Not able to offer the service at present by the obstacle of the system."
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i mean, can you really be unfashionable?  think of some awful outfit - if it's gaudy it's trendy and if it's boring, it's classic or 'understated'.  if it's inbetween, it's casual.  if it's long out of style, it's retro.  if it's recently out of style, you're ahead of the retro-curve.  
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      damn what should i call this blog-thing?  ok, think.. ..  no think harder.  everyone else has a good name for theirs.  what is this about?  well nothing really.  what inspired its creation?  everyone else was doing it.  i hate just picking random names.  like all those new restaurants/shops/clubs/labels - "eleven." "green." "hxykdybqz."   maybe i should just pick something related to my life right now.  "lying in bed typing."  "shopping at the gap sometimes." "contemplating dinner." "hey, how about sushi?." no, all those things suck for titles.  and i hate the no-title-title, which admits you can't think of anything.  well i'm not going to end this post until i've thought of something.  ok, think.. . ... who is my audience?  probably no one.  maybe my roommate in korea and one or two friends in sthlm.  "hello korea and sweden!"   the address is fivealive.blogspot.com. which doesn't really signify anything except some juicebox from my 80s childhood. my last one was jacinto.something.com, which meant something, sort of, as jacinto was the codename for a sw project i worked on.  we drew up this ridiculous chili-pepper cartoon icon named jacinto and used it as the inside-joke company mascot.  [company since got acquired; website features no chili peppers.  like it ever did.].  "why am i up this early thinking about blog-titles?." "not even a bad pun comes to mind." 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      going to carnegie hall this friday to see joao gilberto!  excited!
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Seems that my credit card, which I haven't used in a year, got copied and travelled across Mexico !  MBNA just phoned to ask if some charges were mine - Mexico city and somewhere else.  There were trips to the salon, grocery store, restaurant .. pretty ordinary things.   addendum... got the replacement card in the mail.  still has the same damn ugly lion-statue image on it! 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink BBC NEWS | Americas | Ladies' nights 'discriminatory' 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      saw Ojos de Brujo again in central park!    free concert.  Dad came with as he was visiting.  And then later on that night I got to say hello, when I saw some of the band members (I think it was Xavi and Marina) hanging out in front of a bar on first ave. Was really thrilled to meet them. Hope they play new york again and often, as they are the best live act ever. 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      named "ojos de brujo".  from bcn. witnessed at SOBs on varick/w. houston last night.  2 hours and they barely stopped to catch their breath! flamenco, rap, hip hop.  with a DJ.  lots of percussion (at one point a cajon trio, accion-reaccion-repercussion) (a cajon is a wooden box).  lot of advanced hand clapping techniques.  electric funk bass and nylon string guitars.   check it out!:     urlLink OJOS DE BRUJO :: Music and Revolution :: " La onda zapatista " ::  
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      is my new japanese word after hearing boss say it 100 times during presentation to funding org.  means "visually disabled".  which makes sense since that's what we're about. oh yeah i just got back from tokyo, a 5 day trip.  many meetings.  got good support for project and am happy about results - getting funding to hire "freshers" in bangalore, with a team lead that i know and have worked with and like.  also closer synch. with indian assistant manager which should be great. anyway ... am very very tired now.  seemed like getting home from the airport took longer than the flight from NRT !??!  long passport control lines and late trains.  long taxi stand queue and longer ride home.  &lt;yawn&gt;
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ...Colin powell (??!)  urlLink BBC NEWS | Asia-Pacific | Powell goes disco for Asean forum   apparently this happens every year.  not so funny is that my tax $$ probably paid for the costumes.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      About Ireland's new public smoking ban:   urlLink BBC NEWS | Europe | Irish take smoking ban in stride : "The pubs certainly look cleaner and the air is definitely better.  (Excerpt) Mind you, one national radio presenter recently complained that the air was so fresh that these days in pubs you could now smell a lot more of the customers' farts - something that the smoke had previously disguised.  That complaint is frequently heard but most people believe it is a small price to pay, if only because you cannot get cancer from the passive inhaling of farts."
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      why is it so impossible for people to follow instructions?  what is so hard about opening a document and reading steps #1-5, then doing, in order, the absolutely menial tasks therein??  example. of. my. frustration.:  Me: what i said was to do "cvs co Module" Me: and actually that's what I meant, because if you don't, it won't work. person: cvs comodule  ?  .. aaarrrggghhhhhh!  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ..or.."a few months past planting season, i decide to do something about my yard."  making my way home from union square's weekend market: first get a taxi.  not easy since i have to transport a small fortune in medium sized plants.  hide the plants away from the curb where they will be out of sight to an approaching car (a truck was right next to me so that obscured the view).   taxi pulls up and i wait for him to stop and open the trunk before carting everything over, with the help of a gold-toothed lanky (suspected) chinese nursery assistant.  second drive the short distance to my house.  on the way the driver asks if i am married, i say no; he says he thought i might be because "it is usually married women who are getting the trees and plants and things."  i suddenly feel prematurely domesticated.   i mean, if he only knew how little planning went into this day of yard work, that i started out just sweeping the patio and then thought to get some big pots, then plants, then dirt - at any step with no intention of really completing it all that day, or perhaps ever; and then all the sweat that was involved in ripping out fifteen foot sumac seedlings and hauling bags of dirt and digging and et cetera, maybe he would not have said that.  i'm really confounded by that statement actually. third, i actually finish it all before dark.    the next morning there was one attempted suicide of a flowerbox, which had thrown itself to the ground, as it wasn't mounted that well.  hung it back up and am keeping an eye on it. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>