<Blog>

<date>22,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      My first entry. Testing this out to see how it works. Cool stuff to follow
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today was my first day at Auto Bell carwash. I got there at 11:00 and I had to retake a drug test because I wasn't able to do it right or something yesterday. I did that for about 30 minutes while the store manager was there with me and I guess I wasn't getting anywhere with the test so he left and then the general manager came in and sat with me for a little bit while I had this thing in my mouth. He sat there for about 15 minutes and then he told me to take it out so he could examine it. I then asked him if I might have to retake it and he said I might have to and then he left without saying anything else to me. I then sat there in the office by myself, not knowing what to do next, for the next half hour or so and then I got up and went outside to see the store manager. He at once said, yea you can start working. I was like, ok I didn't know that. No one told me that. So I went ahead and put on the shirt he gave me and the general manager told me what to do.  My job today was to vacuum cars out before they passed through the auto carwash. Nothing else. I worked until 3:30 when the store manager said I could go home. I worked a total of about 3 hours today.  If I'm gonna be working 3 hour shifts then I'm gonna need to find another job to work alongside this one. Maybe a night job, maybe at a movie theater as my mom suggested. So I'll talk to the manager tomorrow about my schedule and what hours I'll be working and stuff like that.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I finally get a job! I'll be working for Auto Bell carwash. They're gonna pay me $5.15 an hour and then whatever tips I get from customers.  Hey, at least it's a job and it'll help to pay some stuff off. I go in tomorrow at 11:00am.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Aftenposten Norway, Norwegian news in English   Damn, I want to work for these people! 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm feeling a little frustrated now... I had an interview at 10:00 with Auto Bell car wash. As I was on my way there, I got into an accident. I was driving down the road and a car ahead of me was wanting to turn left at an intersection that had a light so I went ahead and drove on into the right lane so I could pass the guy. Well about halfway into the lane, a car that I didn't see came up behind me on my right and sideswiped me and took out my right front blinker light. That in turn scratched up the left hand side of their car. No one got hurt. I was just shaken up a little because it was my first car accident. The people (it was just a man and a woman) seemed to be nice about it. I apologized to them right off saying I obviously didn't see them and said I was sorry. I asked them if they wanted to report this to the police and they said no because it was just a minor damage. So we exchanged names and cell phone numbers and I gave them my license tag number and insurance name. They said they didn't have their insurance with them or something like that.  Now I have to figure out what to do next.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      New stuff...testing.
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink How would Americans feel if we were invaded? 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Isn't it interesting that two men who were on former president Nixon's watergate committee, died yestereday.   urlLink http://quote.bloomberg.com/apps/news?pid=10000103&sid=aceTxMotBhUM&refer=us 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So I didn't get to work today because there wasn't enough cars coming in and they weren't that busy! I really need to get another job because I can't depend on this one for now.   This is the second day of being at the hous by myself. My parents come back sometime Sunday afternoon/evening. I'll be picking them up at the airport.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      An engraving on a Vietnam-Era zippo lighter:                               We are the unwilling,                             led by the unqualified,                             doing the unnecessary,                             for the ungrateful. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>