<Blog>

<date>16,April,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Police say woman bit suspect following rape  BY BEN SCHMITT , FREE PRESS STAFF WRITER April 16, 2002   A 31-year-old Detroit man suspected of raping a woman who bit and nearly severed his penis has spent most of his adult life in prison, court records show.  Detroit Police Cmdr. Dennis Richardson said Monday that investigators are trying to determine whether the suspect could be connected to any other rapes. Investigators questioned the man Monday after his release from St. John Northeast Hospital, where he received stitches for the injury.  The suspect is under arrest on preliminary charges of criminal sexual conduct and armed robbery, police said.   The suspect served 11 years in prison on a 1989conviction in Wayne County Circuit Court for assault with intent to commit murder. He was released on Oct. 1, 2000, according to state Department of Corrections records.   On Sunday, police allege that the man robbed and attacked a 36-year-old woman on Detroit's east side and dragged her at gunpoint into an abandoned home at 14461 Mayfield. He approached her on the street with a gun about 5 p.m., ordered her to "walk with me," and took her into the home, ordering her to remove her clothing, according to police reports. He stole $42 from her purse and two gold rings from her fingers as she undressed, police said.   Then he allegedly raped and sodomized her, telling her, "You make a sound, I'll kill you," according to police reports.   The woman told the attacker that she couldn't breathe, police said. He ignored her and she ended the attack by biting and lacerating his penis, police said.   Police said the suspect then ran to his nearby home, where he told his wife that he injured himself on a backyard fence while running from a dog. She took him to the hospital.   Meanwhile, investigators interviewed the rape victim and followed a blood trail from the location of the assault to the suspect's home, where they found a large puddle of blood in his dining room, according to the police report.   Police said they located the suspect after calling area hospitals and matching his description with a man who was being treated at St. John Northeast.   Carey Goryl, a spokeswoman at Turning Point crisis center in Mt. Clemens, praised the victim for doing what she had to do to stop the attack and stay alive.   "It's amazing what people will do to get out of a terrifying situation," Goryl said.   
     
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Flasher escapes after being caught in his own zipper By CINDY CLAYTON, The Virginian-Pilot © April 4, 2002   VIRGINIA BEACH -- A 12-year-old girl confronted by a flasher in an elevator Monday night reacted quickly: She grabbed his zipper and yanked it up.  The two were in an elevator at the Suburban Lodge in the 400 block of South Independence Boulevard at 7:50 p.m., said police spokesman Mike Carey.   The man was injured, and the girl ran out of the elevator and found her stepfather to tell him what happened, Carey said. The stepfather found the suspect running from the building, and the two men fought. The suspect broke free and ran away.   Because he suffered blood loss, the man probably suffered injuries significant enough for him to seek medical treatment, Carey said. Investigators have been checking for him at area hospitals.   The suspect is described as 5 feet 7 inches tall with a medium build and dark, curly hair. He was wearing a black T-shirt and tan vest. He may have fled in a purple Ford Ranger pickup truck with four-wheel drive.   The man faces a felony charge of taking indecent liberties with a minor. The case is being investigated by Detective Mark Vidrine of the police department's Special Victims Unit.   Police said the girl was unharmed.   Anyone with information is asked to call Crime Solvers at 1-888-LOCK-U-UP. 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Sexy tree too much for some Westside neighbors  Santa Cruz Sentinel May 09 2002  By DAN WHITE Sentinel staff writer    A Westside resident called the cops Monday to report an allegedly phallic tree.   Officers responded to the Liberty Street home but found no wrongdoing. They said the 20-footer — actually an evergreen hedge of the Luma genus — is protected by its owner’s right to artistic freedom.   "We contacted the city attorney," said Sgt. Brad Goodwin. "It could be interpreted anywhere from being free speech to being artistic. It’s really nothing we have control over."   All trees can be seen as "phallic," but some would argue this eugenia is especially so. Viewed from the front, the hedge looks to have testicles, or perhaps bosoms.   Eugenia is a common plant noted for white flowers and edible fruits, according to the Sunset Western Garden Book. Sunset says the plant "performs best" in well-drained soil.   The owner of the tree, Gillian Greensite, said she found it peculiar the plant has been there at least 15 years and suddenly someone is mad about it. She said no one has complained to her about the plant.   Greensite, director of UC Santa Cruz’s rape prevention and counseling program, also questioned what the offended neighbor was really seeing in this tree.   "If they want to see phallic, they see phallic, I guess. I see trees," said Greensite, an outspoken advocate of tree preservation in the city.   She added the eugenia was "not trimmed for any particular purpose."   The complaining neighbor could not be reached for comment Tuesday.   A second neighbor, who asked that her name not be used, said she found the tree irksome but has grown "numb" to it over the years. But she said it’s annoying to "all of a sudden hear kids screeching and laughing about the tree.   "They’re good neighbors, believe me," she said, referring to Greensite’s household. "(But) we have older folks around here."   The neighbor also said the tree has become a beacon for annoying sightseers.  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Laughing women rebuff nude launderer By Tribune staff May 3,2002  La Crosse police are searching for an unidentified man who entered a Cass Street laundromat Wednesday evening, stripped naked, placed his clothes in a dryer and started to strike up a conversation with two female customers.   One of the female customers told police that the man went to a restroom in the laundromat at 710 Cass St. and removed all of his clothes. After putting the clothes in a dryer, the naked man stood behind a table and started to visit with the women.   According to police reports, the man told the women he had recently moved to La Crosse from the Austin, Minn., area. He said his clothes got wet and he wanted to dry them, although the women noted that his clothes did not appear to be wet.   After having his clothes in the dryer for about five minutes, the woman told police, the man grew irritated because the women began to laugh at his nakedness, so the man gathered his clothes, got dressed and left through a back door.   The man is described as being in his mid-20s, 6 feet 3 inches tall and having a muscular build and very dark, short hair. He might have been wearing a baseball cap. 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Lesbian sues over attire for yearbook  The Tampa girl who didn't want to don a female drape for her senior photo files a lawsuit in federal court.   [Special to the Times] Nicole "Nikki" Youngblood could not wear a jacket and tie for her senior yearbook picture. Instead, her mom paid for a separate photo.   By GRAHAM BRINK, Times Staff Writer © St. Petersburg Times published June 20, 2002    --------------------------------------------------------------------------------   TAMPA -- A Robinson High student who was not allowed to pose for her senior yearbook picture in a jacket and tie filed a lawsuit in federal court Wednesday, claiming the school's actions violated her constitutional rights.   Nicole "Nikki" Youngblood, 17, alleges in the suit that the school's dress requirement for yearbook photos is discriminatory. All female students are required to wear a scoop-necked drape and all male students must wear a white shirt, tie and dark jacket.   Youngblood, a lesbian, hasn't worn traditionally female clothes in several years. In spring 2001, when she went to be photographed by the studio under contract with the school, she was told she had to wear the drape or get a note from the school allowing her to wear the shirt and tie.   School officials refused, saying that the compromise could lead to problems, including boys wanting to wear the drape as a gag. They told Nicole she could pay for her own picture and run it in the back of the yearbook in the advertising section, the suit states.   Nicole and her mother, Sonia Youngblood, thought the policy was inappropriate and discriminatory and decided not to pay for their own picture. A formal picture of Nicole does not appear in the yearbook, the suit states.   Nicole graduated early in December "due in large part to the discrimination she experienced with regard to her senior portrait, the attitude of the principal and school administrators handling her complaint and the ongoing harassment from other students directed at her," the suit states.   Among other things, the suit seeks a monetary award and attorney's fees.   
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      'Mother' makes dog of a call  Covington woman cited for 911 misuse  06/19/02 By Paul Rioux St. Tammany bureau/The Times-Picayune  When a frantic Covington woman called 911 on a pay phone and said her 3-year-old had stopped breathing, dispatchers sent two fire trucks, two sheriff's deputies and an ambulance crew to a gas station near Mandeville. The rescue workers raced to the scene only to discover that the youngster in question had four legs, a tail and a cold, wet nose.   In all the commotion Saturday night, Camille Wood, 19, somehow failed to make it clear that she was seeking medical attention for her mixed-breed dog, Aurora Faye, said St. Tammany Parish Sheriff's Office spokesman James Hartman. After explaining that they were not trained in canine CPR, deputies escorted Wood to a nearby 24-hour animal hospital, where the dog recovered after receiving a shot. Meanwhile, Wood was cited for misusing 911 for leading dispatchers to believe her dog was a child, Hartman said.   Wood, who acknowledged she initially told the 911 operator that her "daughter" had stopped breathing, said she commonly refers to her pets as if they were children. "I have two sons and two daughters, and they're all animals," said Wood, who also has a dog named Frisco Otis, a rabbit named Hopper and a chicken called Ellie Mae.   Wood said she made it clear that she was seeking help for a dog about 20 seconds into the 911 call. "They asked me if her skin was turning blue, and I told them I couldn't tell because she is a dog and is covered in hair," Wood said. "If I intended to mislead them about the species of my daughter, I would not have said she was a dog."   Hartman said the 911 operator eventually realized Wood was calling about a dog, but not until the rescuers had begun arriving on the scene. Wood said she decided to drive Aurora Faye to an animal hospital near Interstate 12 and U.S. 190 south of Covington after the dog lost consciousness in her home at 70447 First St. Dismayed to discover the hospital was no longer there, Wood called 911 at a nearby Exxon station. "I was panicking because she was dying in my arms," she said. "I assumed the 911 operator would be able to tell me where the hospital was and how to keep her alive until I got there."   After taking Wood and her dog to the Louisiana Veterinarian Referral Center in Mandeville, deputies issued her a summons to appear in court for misusing 911, a misdemeanor that carries a fine of up to $500 and 30 days in jail, Hartman said. He said motorists were needlessly endangered as the five emergency vehicles raced to the scene using their lights and sirens.   "While we understand that many people regard their pets as members of the family, summoning lifesaving personnel via 911 is inappropriate to say the least," Hartman said. But Wood disagreed and defended her decision to call 911. "All of my kids are extremely good kids," she said. "If they stop breathing, they deserve help just like a person would." 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Police: Abducted Pa. Girl Freed Self Wed Jul 24,12:24 AM ET  By DAVID B. CARUSO, Associated Press Writer   PHILADELPHIA (AP) - A 7-year-old kidnapped girl escaped her captors Tuesday night by chewing through duct tape binding her arms and legs, smashing a window and then calling to nearby playing children for help, police said.   One of the children rode a bike from the abandoned building where Erica Pratt was being held down the street to alert officers who were on patrol, Lt. Michael Chitwood said. The girl had been abducted, kicking and screaming, from in front of her home Monday evening and held for ransom.   Police were searching for two suspects late Tuesday. Chitwood said Erica had only minor injuries.   While being held in a police officer's arms, Erica waved to television cameras and beamed with a wide smile as she was returned to her grandmother's home.   "She's an amazing little girl," Chief Inspector Robert Davis said.   The girl had been left on a mattress in the basement of the building in northern Philadelphia with duct tape around her arms and legs and covering her eyes, police said.   "She was eventually able to free herself from the duct tape, she broke through the basement door, she made her way to the first floor and she couldn't get out, so she smashed the window," Chitwood said. "And she summoned help of a couple of little kids who were playing in front of the house."   The children pulled Erica out of the window, and one of them rode a bike to where the officers were patrolling, Chitwood said. Erica was taken to a hospital, where doctors evaluated her and removed the duct tape stuck in her hair. Police said she had a corneal abrasion on one eye, possibly from the tape.   "Our biggest concern is that the baby come back to us in good health and this is what she did," said the girl's great-grandmother, Geraldine Tate.   Police said they were searching for James Burns, 29, and Edward Johnson, 23, who are considered suspects in the abduction. Earlier Tuesday, police had said the men were known to the girl's family and that their names had been provided by two witnesses.   Erica was playing Monday with her 5-year-old sister in front of their grandmother's rowhouse in southwest Philadelphia when two men drove up, called her by name and dragged her into their car as she screamed and resisted, witnesses told police said.   Less than 20 minutes later, Erica's grandmother and primary caregiver, Barbara Pratt, received the first of at least six calls from a man who threatened to kill the girl unless he received a $150,000 ransom, police said.   During one call, police said the kidnappers allowed Erica to speak briefly with her grandmother.   Residents said many adults in the neighborhood were down the street at a block party at the time of the abduction. The area is pockmarked with abandoned buildings and roamed at night by drug dealers.   Erica's mother, Serena Gillis, had pleaded for her safe return. 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      July 6, 2002 Posted: 7:01 AM HKT (2301 GMT)  MUZAFFARGARH, Pakistan (AP) -- Police searching for four men accused in the gang rape of an 18-year-old girl as a tribal punishment believe they have fled their village to evade authorities.  Pakistan's Supreme Court on Friday criticized police for failing to arrest the four men and ordered they return to court on July 11 to report on their progress.  As outrage at the teenager's rape grew, the government handed her a check for 500,000 rupees ($8,000) as compensation and said a new school would be built in her honor.  The gang rape took place June 22 in Meerwala village in southern Punjab province.    Police said a tribal council ordered the rape as punishment for the victim's family after her 11-year-old brother was seen walking unchaperoned with a girl from a tribe considered higher-caste.  The victim's family were from the Gujar tribe, the other tribe were Mastoi.  Pakistan has a tradition of tribal justice in which crimes or affronts to dignity are punished outside the framework of Pakistani law.  The Human Rights Commission of Pakistan has demanded an end to punishments by tribal councils.  Police say the tribal verdict was illegal, and that they have detained eight relatives of the suspects to pressure the perpetrators into surrendering.  The suspects are well known in the village but have disappeared since the rape.  New school  Police are questioning Meerwala residents about whether the suspects had relatives living in cities or large towns in other parts of Pakistan to which the accused men may have fled.  "We are doing our best and hopefully the accused persons will soon be arrested," Deputy Inspector General Police Asef Hayyat told The Associated Press on Thursday.  Attiya Inayatullah, Pakistan's women's' affairs minister, visited the family Thursday to hand over the compensation check.  She said President Pervez Musharraf had ordered that an Islamic religious school be built in the village in the victim's name.  Villagers told local officials who visited Meerwala on Wednesday that the rape was the second in the region recently. A week earlier, a girl in a nearby village committed suicide after being raped by two tribesmen, villagers said. Local police said Wednesday two men had been arrested in that case.  On Thursday, Inayatullah promised that the government would vigorously pursue suspects involved in such crimes.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      MEERWALA, Pakistan (AP) -- For two nervous hours, the teenager worried for her 11-year-old brother as their father pleaded before a Pakistani tribal council that the boy had done no wrong in walking unchaperoned with a girl from a different tribe.  The council was unconvinced, and ordered a brutal punishment: The boy's sister would be gang-raped to shame her whole family.  Shortly afterward, four members of the council took turns raping the 18-year-old sister in a mud hut as hundreds of people stood outside laughing and cheering.  "I touched their feet. I wept. I cried. I said I taught the holy Quran to children in the village, therefore don't punish me for a crime which was not committed by me. But they tore my clothes and raped me one by one," the young woman told The Associated Press on Wednesday.  As she spoke, her mother Allah Bachai sat beside her at their home in Meerwala village in southern Punjab province, wailing.  Senior police and provincial government officials visited Meerwala on Wednesday.  Asef Hayyat, Punjab's deputy inspector general of police, said the top officer at the local police station had been suspended and several close relatives of the suspects were detained to pressure the perpetrators into surrendering.  "We will soon arrest the real culprits," Hayyat told reporters.  Outside of the law  Pakistan has a tradition of tribal justice in which crimes or affronts to dignity are punished outside the framework of Pakistani law. The Human Rights Commission of Pakistan has demanded an end to punishments by tribal councils.  The June 22 rape has outraged rights groups, who say the number of atrocities against women in Pakistan is increasing. And Pakistan's Supreme Court on Wednesday directed top Punjab police and government officials to attend a special hearing Friday on the case.  Cited by Pakistan's government-run news agency, Chief Justice Sheikh Riaz Ahmad described the case as a violation of human rights.  Rana Ijaz, the Punjab government's law minister, was among officials who visited the village, and promised a full investigation and assistance to the victim's family.  "This is a very sad and shocking incident," Ijaz told reporters.  Villagers told him the rape was the second in the region recently. A week earlier, a girl in a nearby village committed suicide after being raped by two tribesmen, villagers said. Local police said Wednesday two men had been arrested in that case.  Lower-class tribe  In the June 22 rape, the Mastoi tribe demanded punishment after the teenager's brother was seen walking unchaperoned with a Mastoi girl in a deserted part of the village. The brother and sister are from the Gujar tribe, which is considered to be lower-class.  The Mastoi tribe called a meeting of the tribal council. The teenager's father, Ghulam Farid, 54, said he pleaded for clemency with the council, telling them the Mastoi girl was safe with his son because he was too young to have sex.  "I told the tribal jury that my son is ready to marry (the girl) if they think she had been molested," Farid told AP. "But Mastoi tribesmen rejected this proposal saying how could they give their daughter to me, a low caste tribal."  "I begged them ... my daughter is a very pious girl," he said. "I reminded them, 'She has been teaching holy Quran to your children, you are fully aware of her character,"' Farid said.  But the Mastoi girl's father rejected the pleas and demanded the gang-rape as punishment, Farid said. Among the men on the tribal council was Mohammed Ramzan, the Mastoi girl's uncle, he said.  "Nobody supported me. There was no one to protect my daughter," Farid said.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Rape - silent war on South American women  South Africans are mobilizing against sexual violence  By the BBC's Carolyn Dempster Johannesburg  Rape is endemic in South Africa.  On this the police, politicians, sociologists and rape survivors all agree. There is a silent war going on, a war against women and children.  It is a fact that a woman born in South Africa has a greater chance of being raped, than learning how to read.  One in four girls faces the prospect of being raped before the age of 16 according to the child support group, Childline.  Charlene Smith, rape survivor and campaigner believes the solution to combating sexual violence lies in:   the way mothers bring up sons     greater community responsibility for members' actions     better policing     harsher sentences     reform of criminal justice system        Sexual violence pervades society, with one of the highest reported rates of rape in the world, and an alarmingly high incidence of domestic violence and child abuse.  The official crime statistics tell only part of the story.  In 1994, the year South Africa became a democracy, 18,801 cases of rape were reported. By 2001 that figure had risen to 24,892.  The South African Police Service readily admits that even though there is now a greater awareness of the problem, more stringent penalties, and better policing, the vast majority of rapes and attempted rapes still go unreported and unpunished.  During a recent parliamentary debate on child abuse in South Africa, it was reported that there has been a 400% increase in the sexual violence against children over the past decade.  Baby rape  The majority of the victims are 12 years old or younger. Many of the perpetrators are themselves children.  "Baby Tshepang" was just 9 months old when she was brutally raped in the Northern Cape town of Louisvale in the early hours of 27 October, 2001.  Baby rape is not a new phenomenon in South African society, but it is becoming more common.  One possible reason, say Aids activists, is the myth, widespread in southern Africa, that sex with a child or baby will rid a man of HIV or Aids.  South Africa already has more than 4.5 million people living with HIV, more than any other country in the world.  As the HIV pandemic becomes an Aids pandemic, rape can also be a death sentence.  So why is it so bad?  At the root of the problem, says Dr Rachel Jewkes, a senior scientist with the South African Medical Research Council, is men's attitude towards women.  "In South Africa you have a culture where men believe that they are sexually entitled to women. You don't get rape in a situation where you don't have massive gender inequalities.  One of the key problems in this country is that people who commit rape don't think they are doing anything wrong."  'Can't say no'  Her findings are borne out by the experience of Rose Tamae, a survivor of gang rape, who is HIV positive, and counsels abused women and children in the sprawling township of Orange Farm which lies across the highway from Soweto, west of Johannesburg.  With the Aids pandemic, rape can be a death sentence  "In our culture, as a woman, you don't say no to a man. Sex is not open for discussion," she says.  "So they think they can do as they like.  "In a place like Orange Farm, where most people are unemployed, and the women have to go looking for work far away, often the children are left at home in the care of men, or strangers.  "They are vulnerable. In one case a little girl was being given food in return for sex, and she didn't want to go home empty-handed to her mother, who had Aids and was sick. "  Apartheid legacy  A "culture of violence" has also been a dominant feature of South African society for decades, say sociologists, and it has spawned attitudes which are tolerant of sexual violence.  South Africa's Deputy President Jacob Zuma blames apartheid for "sowing the seeds for the breakdown of the institution of the family."  He believes that the molestation of children and infants today is a symptom of this degeneration.  Zuma blames apartheid for family breakdown  Apartheid HAS left a damaged society in its wake, but the criminal justice system is also failing women and children in South Africa.  Out of the 24,892 rapes reported last year, only 1,797 resulted in successful convictions.  To its credit the government, and South African society, is responding to the scourge.  The justice system has prioritized sexual offences with a review of the law and stiffer sentences.  Police officers are being trained to care for rape survivors.  Many private hospitals now offer specialized rape care and counseling, and insurance companies have introduced policies for rape survivors to enable them to afford expensive anti-retroviral drug treatment to reduce the risk of contracting HIV and Aids.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Furious mom busts suspect: Bat in hand, she confronts man accused of kidnap try by Laurel J. Sweet -bostonherald.com Friday, November 15, 2002  A hulking homeless man accused of trying to snatch school girls off the streets of Lynn twice in the past five months is behind bars thanks to a mad-as-hell mom who took justice - and an aluminum baseball bat - into her own hands.   "It was a natural instinct,'' Lamosha Bell said yesterday of her familial fearlessness.  Despite having been indicted in August for attempted kidnapping by an Essex grand jury, Richard Scott, 42, was free on bail when he allegedly began stalking Bell's 11-year-old daughter Tuesday as she walked home from the Fecteau-Leary Middle School.   ``You look beautiful,'' Scott, a native Philadelphian, told the girl, according to her mother.   Bell's daughter ignored Scott, only to be confronted by him again Wednesday afternoon. This time, he asked to walk her home, and the girl ran.   With Scott chasing her, the terrified girl ran to find her mother, who was minding the St. Vincent de Paul Thrift Store in Market Square.   ``Once she said no that should have been enough, but he kept chasing her,'' Bell said. ``That infuriated me even more.''   As news stories of child abductions and rapes swirled through her mind and adrenalin pumped through her veins, Bell, grabbing the bat in one hand and her daughter in the other, set out looking for Scott.   ``I only took the bat with me because I'm a woman and he's a man and I needed to make sure I was protected,'' Bell said. ``Besides, I had my daughter with me.''   When Bell caught up to Scott, she said he told her, `` `I didn't touch her. I swear to God, lady, I didn't touch her.' ''   But the 170-pound Bell had a message for the 265-pound Scott just the same.   ``I said to him, `Do you still want to walk her home? Because, when you do, I'll be there.' ''   After Scott took off, Bell flagged down a cruiser. Officers found Scott trying to hide in a dead-end alley on North Common Street.   Lynn police spokesman Lt. John Scannell said Bell ``did the right thing, but she might have called police first.''   Scott later told investigators ``he gets lonely and likes to play with kids,'' according to documents at Lynn District Court, where he was arraigned yesterday on attempted kidnapping and harassment charges.   Judge Joseph Dever ordered Scott held without bail, pending a dangerousness hearing on Monday.   ``This is the second attempt he's made at (kidnapping),'' said Steve O'Connell, spokesman for Essex District Attorney Kevin Burke. ``We intend to prove he's a danger to the community.''   Scannell said that on the morning of July 15, Scott tried to kidnap a 10-year-old girl who had just walked a sibling to the Harrington Elementary School.   ``He started asking her if she wanted to go swimming,'' Scannell said. ``At some point, he grabbed her from behind by the arms. She was able to kick him in the leg with her heel and run home.''   Scott was arraigned in that case in Salem Superior Court on Sept. 4 on charges of attempted kidnapping and assault, but when prosecutors asked he be held on $10,000 cash bail, Judge Richard Welch set it at $1,000. Scott made bail, which is set to assure a defendant will return for trial.   ``We asked for what we thought was appropriate,'' O'Connell said.   In 1996, Scott was charged in Honolulu with ``abuse of a family member,'' said O'Connell, but no other details about the incident were available yesterday.   Aside from the two attempted kidnappings, Scannell said, Lynn police have had no prior dealings with Scott.   ``I don't think he should be out on the street,'' Scannell said. ``He should be checked out for mental problems. The police arrest the criminals and it's up to the courts to do the right thing.''   Bell, relieved her daughter did not meet a worse fate, said, ``She's a phenomenal kid. Right now she's doing fine. It may take a couple of days before it all sets in.''  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Unionized strippers picket for more booty  They want S.F. club to boost pay, benefits John Koopman, Chronicle Staff Writer Tuesday, December 3, 2002  --------------------------------------------------------------------------------  San Francisco -- Seldom in the history of labor relations in union-friendly San Francisco has a group of informational pickets gotten so much attention.  It might have had something to do with their message:  "Two, four, six, eight, pay us more to gyrate," they shouted.  A couple of dozen union women at the Lusty Lady club on Kearny Street in North Beach got out their picket signs and hot-pink tops Monday afternoon to pressure management for better wages and health benefits.  "Bad girls like good contracts" was printed on their T-shirts, and some held signs saying things like, "If you want big booty, help us get fed."  Management at the Lusty Lady had no comment and told employees that reporters who wandered onto the premises were trespassing.  Not that there was any doubt where the support of the people lay. Motorists passing by made sure to honk loud and long, and passers-by stopped to stare or gawk, depending on your point of view. It was noon, after all, and there is seldom that congregation of booty shaking on the streets during daylight hours.  The slogans were sexy, but the labor issues were real. Faye Roe, field representative and negotiator for the Lusty Lady workers, said the strippers had given up $3 an hour in wage concessions 20 months ago because management pleaded economic distress.  Now, as the women's contract nears an end on Jan. 13, management is not budging on a demand to return the money, Roe said.  The women also want to keep their sick pay, have a better distribution of shifts and preserve pay levels for support workers, who take tickets, play music and clean up.  Support workers "make it so that we can work," said dancer Vivian Jones. "We'd rather be shaking our booties in there than stomping our feet out here."  The Lusty Lady employees organized in 1995 and are part of the Service Employees International Union Local 790. The union represents about 60 dancers and 15 support workers.  It is the only organized strip club in San Francisco, according to the union's office. It also is one of the nation's few remaining peep show-style clubs, where the curtain goes up on the strippers when the customer drops in a coin or token, Roe said.  Unlike strippers at other clubs in San Francisco, those at the Lusty Lady are paid hourly. Top wage had been about $21 an hour before the wage concession, Roe said.  "San Francisco is an expensive city," Jones said. "We're just getting by. We need a living wage."  Donna Delinqua, who has danced at the club for eight years, said the informational picket was designed to let management know the strippers are serious about the labor negotiations. She said the dancers have a lot of power, because no one will go into the club if the strippers are picketing.  "You go up to the club and see all the girls outside in their street clothes -- it's not very sexy," she said. "Plus, a lot of our customers are blue collar, working class. They know what we're here for, and they support us. "  No one but reporters -- all of whom, curiously, were male -- went in or out of the Lusty Lady for the first hour of the informational picket. But then, it was early in the day.  Delinqua said the strippers are not to be trifled with. They are tough, smart women, she said, and many are well-educated. A lot of them take the job because of the flexible hours and decent pay.  "It's gotten me through master's degrees and on my way to a Ph.D.," said Delinqua, who hopes to teach English literature.    
     
    
</post>

<date>20,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Dog Gives Flasher His Come-Uppance ZAGREB (Reuters) - A drunken Croat flasher got more excitement than he bargained for when he pushed his penis through a woman's fence and her dog bit it, local newspapers said on Friday.  The visibly drunk man was walking down the street and started swearing and shouting at the woman for no reason. He then shoved his penis through her fence, unaware her dog was on the other side, police said.   The bitten man himself reported the incident to the police.   The 36-year-old was taken to hospital with light injuries but later sent home. He will be charged with "insulting the moral feelings of citizens" and "violation of public order." 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Miniature Dogs Chase Off Flasher Police in the southern town of Straubing said the man, who was about 30, was naked when he surprised the 55-year-old woman with the dogs.   "He had Bermuda shorts and a T-shirt in one hand and his private parts in the other," said police spokesman Klaus Pickel.   The woman spurred the lap dogs into action, one of which bit the man on the calf before he fled through the trees. "The dog was too small to bite him anywhere else," said Pickel. The man is still on the loose. 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Ohio Teen Girl Tackles, Hogties Intruder DAYTON, Ohio (AP) - A petite 17-year-old girl awakened by intruders sprinted from her house barefoot in pajamas and tackled one trespasser, pinning and hogtying him for police.  Melissa Alexander said her experience training horses and playing soccer and softball helped her as she took down the taller and heavier 18-year-old man. Two others were arrested later, and police were looking for a fourth suspect.   "I still don't know what came over me," Alexander said Thursday. "I wasn't thinking at first, then he started making me mad."   Her mother marveled at the feat.   "She had it all under control," Vickie Stanley said of the 5-foot-3, 110-pound daughter she described as "a little bitty thing."   Police said the man Alexander tackled — Jason Burkett, of Brookville — is 5-foot-10 and 140 pounds.   Alexander told police she was asleep at 3 a.m. Tuesday in her German Township home about 15 miles southwest of Dayton when her cousin woke her, saying there were people in the yard snooping around the family's cars. The two alerted Stanley, who suggested turning the outside lights on and off a few times to scare away the intruders.   "Then I crawled back into bed," Stanley said.   But Alexander and her cousin still heard noises, so Alexander opened the garage door and saw men inside. They ran out, and she began the chase.   "I hit him pretty hard. But I think I also scared him," Alexander said.   She sat on Burkett and the other women brought her a lead line she uses to exercise horses. Alexander wrapped the lead line around Burkett's hand, then looped it around his neck and pinned him to the ground.   As he tried to wiggle free, she told him she acquired wrestling-type skills during her years of training horses.   Police arrived and were surprised at what they found.   "They shined the spotlight on the yard. I think they thought it was my stepdad who had the guy. They realized it was under control and walked up to the house. Then they saw it was me," Alexander said.   Police said that all four cars in the garage had been ransacked.   Burkett was charged with theft and criminal trespassing, police Chief W.L. Wilcox said. A 17-year-old boy and Trestan Stamps, 18, both of Brookville, who were arrested later, were charged with the same offenses, Wilcox said.   Alexander, a junior at Valley View High School, said the police asked her if she is interested in a career in law enforcement, but she said no.   "I just wanted to make sure they didn't get away," she said. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Obituary backs 'removal of Bush'  Woman 'thought he was a liar'  By Lee Sensenbrenner August 21, 2003  When Sally Baron's family wrote her obituary, they described a northern Wisconsin woman who raised six children and took care of her husband after he was crushed in a mining accident.  She had moved to Stoughton seven years ago to be closer to her children and was 71 when she died Monday after struggling to recuperate from heart surgery. Her family had come to the question of what might be a fitting tribute to her.  "My uncle asked if there was a cause," her youngest son, Pete Baron, said.  Almost in unison, what her children decided to include in the obituary was this: "Memorials in her honor can be made to any organization working for the removal of President Bush."  "She thought he was a liar," Baron's daughter, Maureen Bettilyon, said. "I think his personality, just standing there with that smirk on his face, and acting like he's this holy Christian, that's what really got her."  Bettilyon, who lives in Stoughton, said her mother didn't trifle with petty neighborhood squabbles but was attuned to significant policy-making at all levels.  "She'd always watch CNN, C-SPAN, and you know, she'd just swear at the TV and say 'Oh, Bush, he's such a whistle ass!' She'd just get so mad," Bettilyon said.   Sally Baron was born in Hurley, Wis., and spent nearly her entire life in the timber and mining country of Iron County. She worked as a factory assembly worker, a waitress, a cook and a dietician, while her husband, James "Slugger" Baron, worked deep in the iron mines.   Following a promotion, Slugger worked briefly above ground on mining machinery but in 1969 was crushed under two tons of equipment. His back and all his ribs were broken and a leg was snapped at the shin.   "We went to school and they told us our dad was dead because the accident was so bad," Bettilyon said.   Sally rushed to the scene and demanded that he be treated locally by a doctor she believed in rather than risk transporting him more than 100 miles to specialists in Duluth.   Bettilyon said the decision saved her father's life and put him in the hands of a "really old-fashioned kind of common-sense doctor."   Slugger convalesced and returned to work in carpentry, then was elected the mayor of Montreal, Wis., a post he held for over 20 years, nearly until his death seven years ago. His accomplishments included sinking new municipal water wells and establishing one of the first sewage treatment plants in the area.   Meanwhile, their children grew up. Their oldest son, Jeff, died as a college student at age 21 of leukemia. Another son joined the Navy and the rest of the children graduated from Wisconsin universities.   "She was the den mother. She was the 4-H leader. She is the lady that taught all of us how to swim, how to play softball, how to camp," said her son, Joe Baron, who owns a plumbing business in Prairie du Sac.   "Montreal isn't a big city, but it's not that small, either. It was about 850 people. And my friends used to joke that when my mom goes to the front door - when I was a kid, this is - and yells out 'Jeff, Jim, Joe!' there was no place in Montreal that she couldn't be heard.   "And it meant one of three things: It was either time to eat, it was time to do a chore, or it was time to get in a lineup to find out who did this atrocity that she perceived. Then the fury of Genghis Khan would come out."   Joe Baron said that the day his mother died he spent a lot of time waiting in the lobby, and so he sat and looked at the paper.   "I noticed that 776 years earlier to the day, Genghis Khan died. And we got quite a chuckle out of that, you know?" he laughed. "Anyhow, yeah, she was a great lady."   "She was real tough, real strong," Bettilyon said. "They never sued the mining company or anything, and my parents were so helpful to us. We're people who waste money, and they never wasted money. They helped all of us buy houses."   The decision to put the line in about Bush came easily, although after several family members thought of it, there was some "how can we really say this" kind of laughter. "It should be impeachment, not removal," Pete said, laughing. "That can mean a couple of things."   Joe Baron has no question that his mother would approve.   "She just didn't trust that a big corporate guy was going to be doing what was best for her. She just really didn't trust him," he said. 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh, and it's not just the government controlling the information you get either. It's anyone with money and power. Which is why, apparently, you can't trust anything that anyone says, including me. 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Ah - the legacy of a Republican President. I just can't hate our current administration any more than I do now. It's impossible. I think that they are evil, and I think that every single one of us has to do everything in our power to get them  out  of power in the next election cycle. If I thought God cared what happened to us, I might even pray about it.   And don't stop reading mid-way through - the important part of the article comes at the end:  As controversial as the data was the timing of its release. Typically the results of the annual survey have been released on a Tuesday in late September at the National Press Club in downtown Washington.   This year the bureau scheduled the release for a Friday, the first time it has done so, and moved the news conference from the centrally located press club to the bureau's suburban headquarters in Suitland, Md. The switch prompted some advocates and lawmakers to speculate that the government agency had been pressured by the administration to move the date and place so that that the results, which most people expected to be worse than they were last year, would generate less attention in the weekend news cycle.   I hate them. I hate them. I hate them. They lie and they cheat and they steal money from us. They give tax breaks to each others corporations while they eliminate access to preventive reproductive health care  and   abortion - ensuring that (if they have sex, the only recreation that they can afford on $9,000 a year) poor single mothers are going to STAY poor single mothers. They even force those women to go to work and leave their small children, in order to qualify for ANY benefits at all. This from the "Family Values" party. Yeah. Family Values apply only to rich, white, Republicans. The rest of us need to live in squalor, fucking like dogs and producing children we can't care for to turn violent and populate the prisons.   Argh. I can't talk about this anymore. 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I can attest to Lois' stunning description of these so-called cat hairballs. I was cat sitting for a former flopmate and, in retaliation for being left in my less than capable guardianship, the cat deposited, what looked to me at the time, as a very large crap on the dining room table. Upon further inspection, it was revealed to be a tightly bound hair turd. Of course, I left it there for the cat owner to clean up. Not only because I ain't her frickin' maid anymore, but because of the sheer mass of the expelled object. It was quite impressive and I thought she might want to save it for posterity.   On the subject of dandruff (don't let me get into the conspiracy of the hair product industry on the subject of dandruff in the first place [DANDRUFF is a medical CONDITION that can only be treated by a doctor-prescribed MEDICATION, all other flaking is DRY SKIN]) my dad was notorious for the flaky skin in his chest hair. I think Head and Shoulders should probably do as KFC did, change their name to the initials to alleviate any false advertising lawsuits, and then make H&S Body Scrub.   And there goes any desire I had to eat lunch today.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmm, that IS quite the ponderance - do they?  Is it the same thing as eyebrow crud?  Is that really  facial dandruff  but we just call it  crud, crust, flakes  because we don't want to admit that there is such a thing?    Would Head and Shoulders come out with a new name?  I mean, I guess you could still use it but it wouldn't REALLY be your head or your shoulders - maybe Face and Chest?  I throw the chest out there because if you have facial dandruff, it's going to fall straight down (unless you are in a mighty fierce wind storm) in which case it would land on your chest.    Of course, if you are flat as a pancake, it would most likely land on your feet so maybe the name would be Face and Feet.  Or, like any good marketing person would do, you create both, even though they are the same product, and sell them to people who fit each demographic.  But then we would have to look at others, like Face and Lap (for those who are in wheel chairs and such) and possibly Face and Ears, for those who are stuck on their back (because it would fall to the side, silly).  Another ponderance - why, when cats barf up a hair ball, is it called a hair ball?  I can tell you from YEARS of freakin' experience, it ain't no ball.  A ball implies that it's a nice and neat little package that you simply pick up and toss in the nearest trash receptacle.  No, the ones that I see coming out of my little beasts are long and turd like and surrounded by a puddle of whatever happened to be in their stomach.  Ugh.  They should be called something like "Hair Barf" or "Hair Turd", ya know?    =)
     
    
</post>

<date>24,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      The ponderance of the day is "Do people with beards and moustaches get face dandruff?"   Consider and discuss.   The quote of the day is from a pastor being interviwed re: the 10 Commandments debacle in Alabama.  "The removement of this monument is a crime."    Tell me Reverend, is it worse than your crimes against the English language? Or is that how they talk down in 'bammy?  Conspiracy theory of the day: Someone is trying to put the Gay Men's Reading Group at  urlLink Left Bank Books  out of commission.   This is a long-standing theory, and one to which I have never before subscribed. But in the face of overwhelming evidence, I feel that I can no longer deny its plausability.  Also, the woman in the cubicle next to mine at work seems to be moonlighting at a special effects sounds recording studio - hence her practicing all day of the "evil cackle." Even worse is the incredulous laugh with the implied "ask me what on my computer screen I am laughing at." contained therein. But I thwart this by never asking. Opening yourself to that ploy is like going to www.spamme.com and signing up for a sweepstakes.   On the plus side, our IT gal was gone this afternoon and I raided her cubicle for the compressed air. My keyboard - oh how she shine!   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Actually, that reference is more towards my idea for yours and Princess Bruiser's Halloween costumes. I think you should go as Madonna and her Chihuahua a la the "Human Nature" video. I'll even volunteer to cornrow your fabulous hair! 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey! Mademoiselle is one busy Chick! The office is crazy, not to mention the non stop love machine and boarding the S.S. Significant Other, which are taking up a lot of time as well. The computer is being hauled aboard this evening and I plan to have it set up before the day is done, which will leave me ample opportunity, barring spontaneous sex acts, to update the 'scopes in a timely manner.   Carry on. 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink The Chick Show - Current Horoscopes   Mademoiselle Julie has submitted her current weeks horoscopes to the webmistress - and all I can say is that according to the horoscope for "Leo" and Mademoiselle's commentary in the accompanying email - someone wants me to take the riding crop out of my closet and dust it off.  Well "someone" can just keep on hoping.   Acting out won't get you the discipline you crave Mademoiselle, it will only engender knowing nods and condescending smiles. 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Went to a reading tonight to commemerate  Banned Book Week . How sad is it that we have to have a banned book week to remind people that they aren't as free as they think they are? The Color Purple - banned. Heather has Two Mommies - banned. The thought police are out there in full force people. "Land of the Free" indeed. (and check out this article  urlLink http://www.themonitor.com/NewsPub/News/Stories/2003/09/22/10642896312.shtml   On another note, did anyone else hope that the UN would break out into spontaneous booing at the sight of George W.? Does the man have no shame at his own audacity?   From a Reuters story on his address:  Bush, whose approval ratings have slumped partly due to the soaring costs of the occupation, offered no apology for the chaotic security situation or the failure to find weapons of mass destruction, cited as the main reason for the war.    Ah - that's our commander in chief alright - ensuring for us the animosity of the world. Maybe after that much strenuous activity he's ready for another month of vacation. 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Tell CNN to stop acting so much like FOX - and try to focus on ALL families!   I woke up this morning and I knew I was in trouble because I was cussing at my computer screen before 8:30 a.m.   I am at the point where even reading anything that has a quote from Bush in it makes my blood pressure go up exponentially. He's such a freaking lying scumbag dirtball. Him and his whole administration. It's just too scary to face, and if we don't face it, it's only going to get scarier.     urlLink AND, check out this article on the rigged election technology we're all using now.  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Site updated with the movie review for "Underworld" by yours truly. Mademoiselle Julie swears that the horoscopes are coming tomorrow...and we mostly believe her. 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh, Susan. One of your compatriots just left my office. He yelled at me because I assumed his 2001 vehicle wasn't paid off yet. He threw my pen at me and left in a huff, then came back five minutes later and demanded I give him everything with his information on it so he could dispose of it properly and insisted he watch me delete his information off of my computer. He was sporting a less than immaculate thrift store outfit and a big scar down his left cheek. I'm sure he's heading home to polish his AK-47. 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So, I just got back from seeing Al Franken speak and read from his new book  "Lies and the Lying Liars who Tell Them: A Fair and Balanced Look at the American Right"    He is really amazing to see live. I have always loved his brand of satirical wit, and listening to him in person was great. Plus he called Anne Coulter a fucking bitch. That was worth the price of the book right there. He's extremely charismatic - which is a bit worrisome to me. I don't like to feel I am under the thrall of anyone, but like some confused Southern Baptists who must have wandered in behind me, I really did want to shout AMEN! to several of the things he had to say. Because, frankly, our government scares me. Really really it's beginning to frighten me. I fear for my freedom, my civil liberties, my right to say what I think without being wire-tapped, my home being searched, my emails being monitored.   I am also, frighteningly, starting to identify with the crazy militia people who say we all need AK-47's to protect us from the government. I think we might. And I don't want to feel that way - not just because those militia people are corn-fed, inbred retards either.  I don't want to feel scared of my country, my government, my neighbors. But I can't understand a society that would elect a man like Bush - or give a more than 50% approval rating to John Ashcroft. Are the people of this country so sedated by reality TV and Big Macs that they can't understand what's going on? Do they think that an "America - Home of the Free" bumper sticker ensures that freedom somehow?    Anyway, I digress from my original point which is that unfortunately a bunch of the people who think like me are really damn scary looking. I mean we are talking some escaped from treehouse looking hippies, with bad fashion and bad hair.   No one wants to listen to someone who looks hygiene deficient people! Take a shower before you  go out, with organic soap and recycled water if needs must, but please try to look a LITTLE more establishment, lest you turn off the crucial swing voters who are used to looking at Baywatch babes. Play the game, practice good hygiene and don't buy all your clothes at hemp festivals and swap meets. You have to earn the respect you want for your (very reasonable) views. Like the Bush administration, it's a sad reality, but it's a reality we all have to live with for now. 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      OK, updates to the site today include: Mademoiselle Julie's horoscopes. That's it. Fooled you by using the plural "updates" huh?   Mademoiselle is currently in a negative creativity vortex caused by her boss's perverse desire for her to do the work for which she is paid rather than write witty horoscopes and advice, and email incessantly with yours truly. He is evil, and he will be stopped.   On another note, I am currently on attempt #17 at downloading the update to my SBC DSL software. Oh. Joy. Nothing like the convenience and speed of DSL, especially when you have to download 17 Mbs of crap that the rest of the free world is also trying to download at the same time. 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I have always scorned webloggers and their pathetic need for attention  - as seen by their neurotic, and usually poorly spelled, posting of trivialities such as:  "I went to the store!"  "My kid did a huge poo!"  "My boss isn't nice to me!"  The question is - would a ChickShow blog, by default, be any more worthy of disk space than your average blog? Well, I guess we're about to find out. Join myself and Mademoiselle Julie, and any of the other ChickShow chicks who can find the time, to ramble on ad infinitum about our banal meaningless lives. It's gonna be a BLAST.
     
    
</post>

<date>31,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      High School Girls Pummel Man Who Exposed Himself Fri Oct 31,10:31 AM ET   PHILADELPHIA (Reuters) - A man described by authorities as a known sexual predator was chased through the streets of South Philadelphia by an angry crowd of Catholic high school girls, who kicked and punched him after he was tackled by neighbors, police said on Friday.  Rudy Susanto, 25, who had exposed himself to teen-age girls on as many as seven occasions outside St. Maria Goretti School, struck again on Thursday just as students were being dismissed, police said.  But this time, a group of girls in school uniforms angrily confronted Susanto with help from some neighbors, police said. When Susanto tried to run, more than 20 girls chased him down the block. Two men from the neighborhood caught him and the girls took their revenge.   "The girls came and started kicking him and punching him, so I wasn't going to stop them," neighbor Robert Lemons told The Philadelphia Inquirer.   Susanto was later treated for injuries at a local hospital. Police said he would be charged with 14 criminal counts including harassment, disorderly conduct, open lewdness and corrupting the morals of a minor. 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      New Horoscopes went up yesterday, and we've had a promise of "Horrorscopes" from Mademoiselle Julie by week's end. We will see if she delivers. I have heard she's much too busy looking for suitable synthetic skin to complete the look of her "Lori and Dori" costume...
     
    
</post>

<date>15,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Chick Flicks   Updated the Movie Reviews with my "Kill Bill" review, and designed a new Flash interface for the main page  urlLink  .  Otherwise not too much updated, as I am working too much on paid and unpaid projects to do more than fall into bed each night with an aching mouse shoulder. Massage? Anyone? Anyone? Bueller?
     
    
</post>

<date>10,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Does anyone else have someone in their life who is a disaster whore? The kind of person who gravitates immediately to any kind of bad situation or drama, and soaks it up like plant food to feed their sorry excuse for an undernourished soul?   You know, the kind of co-worker who rushes to "console" people who are returning from leave after the death of a relative, asking probing questions and forcing their victim to recount the last few days, and usually bust out crying? The ones who love to pick for every festering detail of your mother's bout with cancer, your father's recovery from the car crash, your state of mind after your rape?  The people who speak in hushed tones as they give meaningful, pity-laden glances to their victim, whilst they gleefully spread the miserable tidings to everyone they know?  What the HELL is with these people? It's like they are bitter little thirsty sponges of badness, and they just can't wait to soak up everyone else's angst for their own pleasure. Blech.  Mind your business  people!  If your co-worker wanted to talk to you about the intimate details of his/her life, then you would be his or her FRIEND already - if you aren't, then leave it alone and allow people some goddamned dignity, privacy, and space.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink The Chick Show - Current Horoscopes   Updates for today include new horoscopes, which I have decided should run Friday to Friday rather than Monday to Monday (just have to let Mademoiselle J in on that bit of info) and some of my new artwork is posted at  urlLink the nerdgrrl page .   By the way - I need some QUESTIONS people! Otherwise, how can I share my vast burden of knowledge?  Will try to get movie reviews up in the next few days.   NG
     
    
</post>

<date>16,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      It's been awhile since the last update hmmm? What shall we blame this on? The weather? The Republicans? Rick Santorum and his travelling man-on-dog extravaganza? (a must see!)  Nah, we just been busy. Horoscopes are new today, and by the way Mademoiselle, my neighbor and I were shopping, and for a confusing moment at a store that seems to have run out of trouser hangers we thought we'd found a pair of four-legged pants. It struck us that these would be perfect for you and YOUR new housemate, who are never without each other's company.   Remember Mademoiselle, even Barbie's best friend Skipper was an  optional  accessory...  (You know we love you, L! We just love to give J a hard time.)
     
    
</post>

<date>18,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So, I was listening to Schoolhouse Rock the other day. And I know that these songs were made in the 70's, so I can almost forgive the following misogynistic vignette from the song "Interjections"  Though Geraldine played hard to get Geraldo knew he'd woo her yet He showed his affection Despite her objections And Geraldine hollered some Interjections!  Well you've got some nerve Oh, I've never been so insulted in all my life ...hey, you're kinda cute   So, I took this pretty lightly, and just thought how times have changed for the better. People don't say that kind of thing without censure any more. They still think it I guess, but public condemnation of that kind of speech is the first step on the road to eliminating the behavior, in my opinion.   So in the shower the other day I heard the song "Fire" by the Pointer Sisters.   I'm ridin' in your car, you turn on the radio You're pullin' me close, I just say no I say I don't like it, but you know I'm a liar 'Cause when we kiss, ooh, fire  Late at night, you're takin' me home You say you wanna stay, I say I wanna be alone I say I don't love you, but you know I'm a liar 'Cause when we kiss, ooh, fire  So, that's two songs in three days, because I was listening. I bet there are more. If you spot one, let me know. I want to know how many songs out there are about women who say "No" when they  really  mean "Yes".   Got any? Let me know at nerdgrrl@thechickshow.com.    
     
    
</post>

<date>16,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Girly Beauty   Update to product reviews. Everyone want to hear about my itchy scalp or what?
     
    
</post>

<date>16,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      If you've ever been made to feel inferior by the cover of a magazine, check out  urlLink The Truth About Fashion Photography    It's what they don't want you to know.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Oxymoronville   Update to Oxymoronville. and boy is it a doozy. I haven't spotted very many Oxymorons lately, and apparently that's only because I haven't been looking. The fashion world is quite full of them.   NG
     
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I really need to check this blog more often. Don't blow your hard earned money on a pair of four-legged trousers for my Christmas present, make it a skirt. Less restricted movement that way. Restricted movement is bad, as that's how I sprained my hip during sex Sunday afternoon.   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey Hey Hey - updates to Mademoiselle's Horoscopes can be found  urlLink here , and the newest addition (just in time for Christmas) is Chick Show Merchandise. Yes, now you too can have The Chick Show logo emblazoned on your jiggly bits! Check it out,  urlLink here .   Also, the current administration still sucks, and we're all still hating on George Bush. But, is Howard Dean dying his hair? NO Dean, NO! Put the Grecian Formula DOWN.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink The Chick Show - Current Horoscopes   OK so there are UPDATES! And when I say updates, I mean a whole shitload of 'em! First of all, let the link above take you to MJ's latest round of faux horoscopes and predictions. Don't forget to contact her for genuine fake psychic advice.  Next,  urlLink the ChickShow shops  have a TON of new merchandise! We've added the long-requested "Make Your Own Damn Dinner" t-shirt, and a new "Out of Your League" design - and several items are on sale! Check it out!  
     
    
</post>

<date>06,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink http://sfgate.com/cgi-bin/article.cgi?f=/c/a/2003/12/12/MNGRE3KKJT1.DTL   Do you think that forcing President Bush, John Ashcroft and Tom Delay to go to an African hut and watch a 14 year old girl bleed to death from an illegal abortion would change their mind about the global gag rule?   Yeah, me neither.   Anything to ensure that right wing zealot voter base! Don't alienate the right-to-lifers by caring about something as trivial as a life. After all, it's just a poor African girl that you will never have to see - whose mother won't have a chance to vote for you or not vote for you. Of what value is that life anyway?
     
    
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Kent police field complaint about busty snow woman  Artistic housewife feared she would be arrested   By Carol Biliczky Beacon Journal staff writer AP    The last turned out to be a no-no, as someone complained to Kent police about what he called an indecent snow figure.  And a police officer showed up at her apartment door minutes after she completed her work.  ``He said that I should cut off her breasts, but I said no woman wants that,'' Lynn, 35, said.  She didn't want to knock down the snow woman. And the figure was too busty to be covered by a shirt. So Lynn opted to drape a ruffled maroon tablecloth around her shoulders.  ``She looked really good, like she was getting ready to go to a party,'' she said.  Kent Capt. James Goodlet said the incident began at 7:30 p.m. Wednesday with an anonymous call from a man about the ``inappropriate snow figure'' on First Avenue.  Goodlet said the officer didn't demand that Lynn alter her artwork, but she left the conversation thinking she would be arrested for disorderly conduct if she didn't comply.  ``We would have had to have someone file a complaint,'' Goodlet said. ``We wouldn't have charged at that. We were treating it almost as a neighborhood domestic situation.''  He said the dispatcher considered the call to be serious -- not a prank call.  But Lynn was flabbergasted.  ``I didn't think there was anything inappropriate about it,'' said the self-described housewife. ``I just wanted to play in the snow.''  She said she called the police after the officer left. When she realized the officer was just passing on a caller's complaint, she took matters into her own hands, stripping the tablecloth off the snow woman so that she could be exposed in all her glory.  Goodlet said this may be the first time he's fielded a complaint about an indecent snow figure in his 26 years of police work. ``They aren't one of our higher priorities,'' he said.  Lynn said she was insulted by the whole mess.  ``It's just snow,'' she said.    Crystal Lynn of Kent, Ohio, poses Thursday, Feb. 20, 2003, in front of a snow woman she made. After receiving an anonymous call of an "inappropriate snow figure," Lynn was told by a Kent police officer to remove the breast of the snow woman or face possible disorderly conduct charges. Lynn decided to cover the breast of her snow woman with a cloth, a decision that satisfied the police officer.  Crystal Lynn went for realism when she built her snow woman -- celery for the eyes, a carrot for the nose and two blobs of snow for the breasts. 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink STLtoday - News - Story   Oh for fucks's sake. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink TV Watch | Super Bowl: After Flash of Flesh, CBS Again Is in Denial   The best article I have read about Janet's tacky flesh baring. I can't decide which of the two is more talentless, her or Timberlake. What a pathetic stunt. 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink GRAND THEFT AMERICA   Scary - and yet very true. Why do the majority of the sheep in America not care about this issue? Apparently Katherine Harris wants to run for Senate too - and the GOP is trying to dissuade her, afraid that having her running at the same time as dubya would cause controversy (more like, remind people what scum-sucking crooked lying cheats the current adminstration is filled with)
     
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Body Politics (washingtonpost.com)   Wonderful article about the April 25th March for Women's Lives in Washington. I love that a man gets that the new wave of feminists can incorporate standing up for our rights and being happy, strong women with senses of humor and the ability to say the "C" word. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Updates to the Music Reviews and Beauty Reviews section - new forum is still going strong!  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      How fucked up is this? Really? Is ANYONE in the world stupid enough to have one shred of faith left in the Catholic church? No pun intended there. I mean, they are really pure, unadulterated, money grubbing, power hungry evil. Is there anyone but me who sees that? That they are a anti-woman, anti-child, anti-life lived by rules which they have proscribed, jackasses? That the teachings of the man they profess to believe in (Jesus - remember him?) are all about love and forgiveness and charity and peace and helping others?   Do you think Jesus would have refused communion to  anyone ?  Anyway, their obvious ploy to interfere in the US presidential race and keep Bush in office makes me ill. But then again, what have I read or seen or heard in the media in the last year that hasn't made me ill? I think there's a hell, and I think it's watching something you love be slowly destroyed while no one around you does anything or even notices it's happening.    Cardinal: Politicians Need Follow Church on Abortion Fri Apr 23, 1:41 PM ET     By Philip Pullella   VATICAN CITY (Reuters) - In remarks that could influence the U.S. presidential race, a top Vatican (news - web sites) cardinal said Friday that a Roman Catholic politician who unambiguously supports abortion rights should be denied Holy Communion at Mass.   Cardinal Francis Arinze spoke amid a debate over whether Democrat John Kerry (news - web sites) should be denied communion, which Catholics believe is the body of Christ, because he supports abortion rights.    At a news conference presenting a Vatican document restating standing rules about the celebration of Mass, Arinze was reminded of the Kerry case and asked if a priest should refuse communion to a politician who unambiguously supports a woman's right to choose abortion.    "Yes," he answered. "If the person should not receive it, then it should not be given. Objectively, the answer is there."    Kerry supports abortion rights and has said he would nominate only Supreme Court justices who support his position. Anti-abortion groups in the United States, which is about 23 percent Catholic, say Kerry has what they have called a "perfect record" of voting for legislation that allows abortion.    He is due to be endorsed by Planned Parenthood (news - web sites) Action Group, a pro-choice group.    Some members of the Church hierarchy in the United States have said they would deny communion to Kerry, who, if elected, will become the first Roman Catholic president since John F. Kennedy in 1960.    The Church teaches that abortion is murder and debate over Kerry's eligibility for communion arose after Archbishop Raymond Burke of St. Louis told him not to present himself for communion in the city. Other bishops have given similar warnings.    CHARGED DEBATE    Frances Kissling, president of the Washington-based Catholics for a Free Choice group, accused the Vatican of not understanding the separation of church and state.    "It is time for Church leaders to acknowledge that the threat of denying the sacraments to Catholics who disagree with their positions has no basis in Church law. It is both bad politics and bad religion," she said.    Arinze, a Nigerian who is head of the Vatican department that establishes regulations on the way the sacraments should be practiced, spoke at a news conference presenting the Vatican document which itself is likely to charge debate over Kerry.    The 70-page document makes no specific reference to politicians but turns the screws on practices that have become common in some local churches, such as joint communion services with non-Catholic Christians.    The section on communion which, in the Church's view, could apply to Kerry says: "The Church's custom shows that it is necessary for each person to examine himself at depth and that anyone who is conscious of grave sin should not celebrate or receive the Body of the Lord without prior sacramental confession."    Cardinal Theodore McCarrick of Washington, who heads a panel studying how to handle politicians with views that diverge from doctrine, has said Kerry should follow Church teachings.    Kerry did take the sacrament during a Mass at Boston's Paulist Center on Easter Sunday.    A practicing Catholic and a former altar boy, Kerry also supports stem cell research and civil unions for gays and lesbians, issues he calls matters of conscience.          Kerry has said he keeps his religion separate from his public life. President Bush (news - web sites), a Methodist, approves of abortion only in cases of rape or incest or when the pregnancy endangers a woman's life.     Kerry Affirms Support for Abortion Rights    By NANCY BENAC, Associated Press Writer   WASHINGTON - Democratic presidential candidate John Kerry (news - web sites) delivered an unabashed defense of abortion rights on Friday just hours after a top Vatican (news - web sites) cardinal said that priests must deny Communion to Catholic politicians who support abortion rights.    Several other Catholic politicians said they, too, had no intention of altering the way they practice their religion or their politics.    With hundreds of Catholic politicians in the United States supporting abortion rights, the trans-Atlantic counterpoint was only the latest sign that the issue promises to be a recurrent one on the U.S. campaign trail this year.    "I believe that in the year 2004 we deserve a president who understands that a stronger America is where women's rights are just that: rights, not political weapons to be used by politicians of this nation," Kerry declared at a rally with leaders of pro-choice groups that are mobilizing in Washington for a big march on Sunday. "We are going to have a change in leadership in this country to protect the right of choice,"    Speaking earlier from Vatican City, Cardinal Francis Arinze stopped short of saying whether it was right for Kerry to receive Communion, but said a Catholic politician who supports abortion rights "is not fit" to receive the Eucharist. U.S. bishops have discretion in deciding who should receive Communion, but the cardinal's comments could put more pressure on them to sanction Catholic politicians whose positions are at odds with church teachings.    Kerry says he personally opposes abortion but supports a woman's right to choose. He did not directly respond to Arinze's comments, but campaign spokesman David Wade said Kerry believes the separation of church and state "helped make religious affiliation a non-issue in American politics."    Bush campaign spokesman Steve Schmidt countered that Kerry's views on abortion were "outside the mainstream" and said the president "supports a culture of life."    Judie Brown, president of the anti-abortion American Life League, said it was perfectly appropriate for voters to consider a candidate's religion and the way he or she practices it in deciding how to vote. She said the group is keeping tabs on 500 Catholic politicians at the state and national level who support abortion rights.    "If you are elected to public office as a Catholic, then your fellow Catholics expect you to be Catholic," she said, calling it "hypocrisy" for Kerry to say he is personally opposed to abortion while supporting wider access to the procedure.    But Frances Kissling, president of Catholics for a Free Choice, USA, said statements such as Arinze's "debase the political campaign" and would only isolate the church from its U.S. members, most of whom she said support abortion rights.    "Every time Catholic church leaders have attacked Catholic politicians for their view on abortion, the Catholic politicians have become more popular and the church has become more marginalized," she said. "It's a very foolish strategy relative to political influence."    She added: "Do they really want to tell Senators (Edward) Kennedy, (Barbara) Mikulski, (Patrick) Leahy and 70 other members of the U.S. Congress that they can't receive Communion? Because they can't just tell this to Senator Kerry."    Sen. Edward Kennedy, the Massachusetts Democrat whose brother was the nation's first Catholic president, stressed that Arinze was speaking for himself, not the pope, and said he did not expect to be denied Communion despite supporting abortion rights.    "I'm a very strong believer in the separation of church and state, as President Kennedy spoke to, and I continue to follow my own beliefs and will continue to serve the people of Massachusetts," he said.    Among American Catholics, 56 percent of non-Hispanic Catholics and 59 percent of Hispanic Catholics oppose making it harder for a woman to get an abortion, according to the Pew Research Center. Support for additional restrictions increases among Catholics who attend church at least once a week, with 50 percent of non-Hispanic Catholics favoring further restrictions and 43 percent of Hispanic Catholics.    Rep. Nick Lampson, D-Texas, was criticized by Republicans recently for keeping track of the votes of Catholic members of Congress and whether they are in keeping with church doctrine. He said the vote tallies grew out of meetings by a group of lawmakers exploring their own beliefs, "knowing many of us want to bring as much of our faith as we can to our action in Congress."    "We are trying to live the teachings of our church and we try to bring that to work," he said. At the same time, he added, Catholic congressional members struggle with adhering to their faith while representing people of many religions.          "I am not here to represent the Catholic church," he said.   Last week, Kerry met privately with Cardinal Theodore McCarrick, the Washington archbishop heading a task force examining whether there should be church sanctions for Catholic politicians who vote and support positions at odds with church teachings.   Bishop Raymond Burke, the archbishop of St. Louis, has said he would refuse to give Kerry Communion.    
     
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Some moron with too much time on his or her hands deleted our ChickChat Forum. Twice.   Anyway, I upgraded us to the newest version of our forum software, which will hopefully be a bit more hacker-proof than the old one, and I managed to save everyone's name/log-on info (I think) so sorry for any inconvenience that's been caused by pimply dorks in their parent's basements with too much time and not enough sexual contact.   NG
     
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The following letter was read by the author at this year’s  In Celebration of the Muse , Cabrillo College.   AN OPEN LETTER TO JOHN ASHCROFT, ATTORNEY GENERAL OF THE UNITED STATES    On January 28, 2002, Attorney General John Ashcroft announced that he spent $8,000 of taxpayer’s money for drapes to cover up the exposed breast of The Spirit of Justice, an 18-foot aluminum statue of a woman that stands in the Department of Justice’s Hall of Justice.   John, John, John, you’ve got your priorities all wrong. While men fly airplanes into skyscrapers, dive-bomb the Pentagon, while they stick explosives into their shoes and then book a seat right next to us, while they hide knives in their luggage, steal kids on school buses, take little girls from their beds at night, drive trucks into our state capital buildings, while our president calls dangerous men all over the world evildoers and devils, while we live in the threat of biological warfare, nuclear destruction, annihilation, you are out buying yardage to save Americans from the appalling, alarming, abominable aluminum alloy of evil, that terrible ten foot tin tittie.    You might not be able to find Bin Laden, but you sure as hell found the hooter in the hall of justice. It’s not that we aren’t grateful.  But while we were begging the women of Afghanistan to not cover up their faces, you are begging your staff members to just cover up that nipple to save the American people from that monstrous metal mammary.  How can we ever thank you?   So, in your office every morning, in your secret prayer meeting, while an American woman is sexually assaulted every 6 seconds, while anthrax floats around the post office and settles in the chest of senior citizens, you’ve got another chest on your mind.  While American sons arrive home in body bags and heat-seeking missiles fly around a foreign country looking for any warm body, you think of another body. And you pray for the biggest bra in the world, John, because you see that breast on the Spirit of Justice in the spirit of your own inhibited sexuality.     And when we women see our grandmothers, our mothers, our daughters, our granddaughters, our sisters, ourselves, when we women see that statue the Spirit of Justice, we see the spirit of strength, the spirit of survival.  While every day we view innocent bodies dragged out of rubble and women and children laid out like thin, limp dolls and baptized into death as collateral damage, and the hollow-eyed Afghani mother’s milk has dried up underneath her burka in famine, in shame, and her children are dead at her breast. While you look at that breast, John, that jug on the Spirit of Justice, and deal with your thoughts of lust and sex and nakedness, we see it as a testimony to motherhood.  And you see it as a tit.   It’s not the money it cost.  It’s the message you send.  We’ve got the right to live in freedom. We’ve got the right to cheat Americans out of millions of dollars and then just not want to tell Congress about it. We’ve got the right to drop bombs night and day on a small country that has no army, no navy, no military at all, because we’ve got the right to bear arms, but we just better not even think about the right to bare breasts.  So now, John, you can be photographed while you stand there and talk about guns and bombs and poisons, without the breast appearing over your right shoulder, without that bodacious bosom bothering you, and we just wanted to tell you, in the spirit of justice, in the spirit of truth, John, there is still one very big boob left standing there in that picture.    -- Claire Braz-Valentine
     
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have at least one conviction for drunk driving in Maine. My Texas driving record has been erased and is not available.  I was AWOL from the National Guard.  I refuse to take a drug test or even answer any questions about drug use  All records of my tenure as Governor of Texas are now in my father's library, sealed, and unavailable for public view.  All records of SEC investigations into insider trading or bankrupt companies are sealed in secrecy and unavailable for public view.  All records or minutes from meetings that I, or my Vice-President, attended regarding public energy policy are sealed in secrecy and unavailable for public review.   Accomplishments:   I attacked and overtook two countries.  I spent the U.S. surplus and effectively bankrupted the U.S. Treasury.  I shattered the record for the largest annual deficit in U.S. history.  I set an economic record for most private bankruptcies filed in any 12-month period.  I set the all-time record for the biggest drop in the history of the U.S. stock market.  My record for environmental issues is the least of my concerns.  I am the first president in U.S. history to enter office with a criminal record.  I set the the all-time record for most days on vacation in any one year period.  After taking-off the entire month of August, I then presided over the worst security failure in U.S. history.  I am supporting development of a "Tactical Bunker Buster" nuke, a WMD.  I am getting our troops killed, under the lie of Sadam's procurement of Yellow Cake Nuke WMD components, then blaming the lie on our British friends.  I set the record for most campaign fund-raising trips by a U.S. president.  In my first year in office over 2-million Americans lost their jobs and that trend continues every month.  I set the all-time record for most foreclosures in a 12-month period.  I appointed more convicted criminals to administration than any president in U.S. history.  I set the record for smallest number of press conferences of any president since the advent of television.  I signed more laws and executive orders effectively amending or ignoring the Constitution than any president in history.  I presided over the biggest energy crisis in U.S. history and refused to intervene when corruption involving the oil industry was revealed.  I presided over the highest gasoline prices in U.S. history and refused to use national reserves as past presidents have done.  I have cut health care benefits for war veterans and support a cut in duty benefits for active duty troops and their families -- in war time.  I have set the all-time record for most people worldwide to simultaneously protest me in public venues (15 million people) shattering the record for protest against any person in the history of mankind.  I've dissolved more international treaties than any president in U.S. history.  I've made my presidency the most secretive and unaccountable of any in U.S.. history.  I'm proud that the members of my cabinet are the richest of any administration in U.S. history.  My "poorest millionaire," Condoleeza Rice, has a Chevron oil tanker named after her.  I am the first president in U.S. history to have almost all 50 states of the Union simultaneously suffer massive financial crisis.  I presided over the biggest corporate stock market fraud of any market in any country in history.  I am the first president in U.S. history to order a pre-emptive attack and the military occupation of a sovereign nation, and I did so against the will of the United Nations and the world community.  I created the largest government department bureaucracy in the history of the United States.  I set the all-time record for biggest annual budget spending increases, more than any president in history.  I am the first president in U.S. history to have the United Nations remove the U.S. from the Human Rights Commission.  I am the first president in U.S. history to have the United Nations remove the U.S. from the E Elections Monitoring Board.  I removed more checks and balances, and have the least amount of congressional oversight than any presidential administration in U.S. history.  I rendered the entire United Nations viewpoints irrelevant. I withdrew the U.S. from the World Court of Law.  I refused to allow inspectors access to U.S. "prisoners of war" (detainees) and thereby have refused to abide by the Geneva Convention.  I am the first president in history to refuse United Nations election inspectors (during the 2002 U.S. election).  I am the all-time U.S. and world record-holder for receiving the most corporate campaign donations.  My largest lifetime campaign contributor, and one of my best friends, (Kenneth Lay, former CEO of Enron Corporation) presided over the largest corporate bankruptcy fraud in U.S. history. My political party used the Enron private jets and corporate attorneys to assure my success with the U.S. Supreme Court during my election decision.  I have spent more money on polls and focus groups than any president in U.S. history.  I garnered the most sympathy for the U.S. after the World Trade Center attacks and less than a year later made the U.S. the most resented country in the world, possibly the largest failure of diplomacy in World history.  I am actively working on a policy of "disengagement" creating the most hostile of Israel-Palestine relations in at least 30 years.  I am first president in history to have a majority of Europeans (71%) view my presidency as the biggest threat to world peace and security.  I am the first U.S. president in history to have the people of South Korea more threatened by the U.S. than by their immediate neighbor, North Korea.  I changed the U.S. policy to allow convicted criminals to be awarded government contracts.  I set an all-time record for the number of administration appointees who violated U.S. law by not selling their huge personal investments in corporations bidding for U.S. contracts.  I failed to fulfill my pledge to capture Osama Bin Laden, dead or alive.  I failed to capture the anthrax killer who tried to murder the leaders of our country at the U.S. Capitol Building. Even after 18 months I have no leads and no credible suspects.  I have successfully prevented any public investigation into the biggest security failure in the history of the United States.  I removed more freedoms and civil liberties for Americans than any president in U.S. history.  In a little over two years, I created the most divided country in decades, possibly the most divided since the Civil War.  I entered my office with the strongest economy in U.S. history and have turned every single economic category downward.   Please consider my experience when voting in 2004. 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This post is chock full of really cool information. First! Dave Eggers, author of  A Heartbreaking Work of Staggering Genius , is partial owner of the book store chain McSweeney's, affiliated with a most excellent  urlLink website  which, incidentally, regretfully rejected my  urlLink sestina  after praising it all to hell (the whole editing staff couldn't agree, which sounds like there was a mysogynist holdout, to me, but I digress), has collaborated with Michael Hearst of the band One Ring Zero to produce a most interesting book released on May 1st titled  As Smart As We Are . Said book contains essays by musicians like David Byrne and a CD with songs written by such award-winning authors as Neil Gaiman, Jonathan Letham and Margaret Atwood. Fuck yes, you want this book. Barry doesn't have it in stock yet at Left Bank Books and Powell's is sold out, but booksense.com has them and will deliver to the indie bookstore of your choice in 1-5 days. Go  urlLink here  to read a full Salon.com review of the book and CD.   Second!  Mademoiselle Julie's new horoscopes should be up by the end of the week.  I sleep now!
     
    
</post>

<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Yahoo! News - Woman Bites Off Attacker's Lip   Oh Kick Ass! This is "Kill Bill" come to life, and this is absolutely a chick whose hand I want to shake. Power to the Matriarchy!
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink The New York Times > Health > In New Tests for Fetal Defects, Agonizing Choices   This article totally pisses me off - but not for the reasons you might think.   My total support of reproductive freedom encompasses reasons for termination including "because the fetus had an extra finger" or "because the fetus was the wrong sex." What I really really really hate is people like this guy:   "He and his wife, who have three other children, were reared Roman Catholic and had never considered terminating a pregnancy. Yet even his father, Mr. Horan said, who had long been opposed to abortion, supported their decision to end the pregnancy.   "Confronted with this question and knowing what we knew, it changed his mind," Mr. Horan said. "It's not just a question of right and wrong; it introduces all sorts of other questions that one has to consider, whether it is the survivability of the child, quality of life of parents, quality of life of siblings, social needs. And it becomes much more real when you're confronted with an actual situation."   WHO SOMEHOW NEVER GOT THE POINT of the reproductive rights movement, that reproductive choice is about respecting INDIVIDUAL situations, and not legislating blanket solutions for personal medical decisions.   There's a saying in the pro-choice movement, that your general anti-choice person supports abortion in three cases:  Rape ,  Incest , and  Me .  Somehow, these people feel themselves qualified to judge, not only for themselves, but for other people as well, what is a correct and incorrect termination. What the fuck, people?    Before you take an anti-choice stance, or a stance on anything for that matter, isn't it your duty to think about things from the "What if it was me?" viewpoint? Have these "women" (I hesitate to use this word for those betrayers of the female half of the human race) who stand outside abortion clinics, moralizing and proselytizing actually never stopped to think "What if I was carrying a severely deformed fetus, who had no chance at a normal life?" or "What if my husband of 9 years had just left me and my 3 kids, and I was unemployed?" or "What if I was a 15 year old girl who made a mistake, and wanted a decent chance at an education & successful life anyway?"  I don't understand it. Is the anti-choice lobby's primary defining characteristic an inability to empathize? I get that from white men - those born into privilege have never been able to spout anything other than the American equivalent of "Let them eat cake." But the women? And especially the holier-than-thou women in this article who claim that they've "always been pro-life" but had a sudden change of heart when the choice was suddenly  their  choice? I really want to barf on their cloak of self-righteousness. 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, according to the link above, George W. has the nerve to start a campaign in which he claims the "W" in his name stands for "Women."  I can see how that would be true - if he means it stands for the  Women  he's let die in Africa because he wouldn't turn over the  urlLink United Nations Population Fund's $34 million  to prevent  Women  dying of AIDS and  urlLink fistula  and in childbirth and due to illegal and unsanitary abortions. It might stand for  those   Women .   It might stand for the millions of American  Women  he's betrayed, by rolling reproductive rights back to the 14th century, restricting access to abortion and emergency contraception, telling Women that abortion causes breast cancer, which the American Cancer Society's Data proves is an outright lie.   How about the young Women, who he has decided are too young to take a pill to prevent pregnancy - but are apparently old enough to be mothers. Or the ones subjected to his "abstinence only" sex education, whose teachers aren't allowed to tell them anything about birth control except its failure rate.   And don't lets forget the thousands of  Women  whose brothers and sons and husbands are dying in Iraq in a stupid war that he lied to us about and based on fictional Weapons of Mass Destruction. Oh yeah - there are  Women  over there too, dying in that war, and now facing the possibilty of being captured and sexually tortured in retaliation for Abu Ghraib.   Oh yeah, the "W" stands for those  Women.    I don't know about you, but hearing about this makes me want to become a "WMD" - a  Woman of Mass Destruction . If by "Mass" you mean the millions of us who are outrageously pissed at his balls in starting this campaign, and by "Destruction" you mean the total, resounding and humiliating defeat of "W" at the polls in November (always assuming that he and his friends haven't  urlLink banned us from the registered voter list , or hijacked the  urlLink e-voting )  You with me? 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Yahoo! News - Unhappy Workers Should Take Prozac --Bush Campaigner   Yeah, so they can't get a new job, cuz there aren't any, and they can't take the Prozac because their health insurance either doesn't exist or doesn't cover it. So, let them eat cake I guess, huh?
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink www.bodyasbillboard.com   Dear bodyasbillboard,  I saw your t-shirt in Ms. magazine and visited your site the same day because I wanted to buy one. Obviously you're a feminist organization, all about empowering women. Great. But WHY OH WHY (like so many other sites which are supposedly "pro-woman") are you only about empowering women in sizes S-M-L? I am a large woman - I need  at least  an XL.   I want you to hear me.    ****I EXIST****    So do a lot of other women like me who are unable to take part in your campaign.   Please try to empower and include ALL women. Not just the dinky ones.   Fed well and fed up,   Nerdgrrl
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Argh. Just argh.   I hate the world sometimes.   Most of the time.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>