<Blog>

<date>29,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Visit my website:  urlLink http://home.earthlink.net/~feudal1/     It's pretty simple, but I hope to make it better!!!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>28,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I've been lazy, and I don't feel a bit guilty for it.  With classes and my job, I just wanted to rest my nerves.  I did get the rest, had pizza, and watched some not so great movies, but the point was I enjoyed my free time.  LOL.  I did have the pesky task of mowing my lawn before any chilling could begin.   The front lawn is always the hardest.  The worst part is between the bushes and the ditch.  Not enough room to manuver.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Wanted to write something today.  I'm at a loss for words.  Visit my forum  urlLink The Art of Chill .
     

    
</post>

<date>24,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm glad this day is almost over.  It feels so blah.  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Feeling like I'm in a funk.  Its put a cloud on things.  Need to rest.  Will be able to soon.  Novel writing moving at snail's pace.  At least its still moving.  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Just had some nachos for lunch.  Couldn't eat all.  LOL.  I'll eat them later.  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Rome was not built in a day.  Why do I feel a need to rush myself.  i should Pace myself, as to not burn out.  I'm positive when the spirit moves me, I'll be writing again!
     

    
</post>

<date>21,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Creativity is doing that off/on thing.  LOL.  All I wanted to do is organize some of my thoughts.  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Working on novel again.  I got an idea for the title.  Came up  with the idea while walking to my car from class.  Jotted it down on a peice of paper.    I'll post the title one day.  LOL.  Not to be mysterious, but its not copywrited, so I don't want to give it away without protection.  As soon as I get it together, I'll be proud to show it.    Took Photshop class today.  Got a little confused, but I think I'll todays lesson is under control.  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I met a friend yesterday I hadn't seen in a while.  She's doing fine.  I was happy to see her.  Its nice to see someone who you have good memories of, 'cause she's an angel.   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hmmmm.  I'm at work, and I'm still not fully awake.  Proud of the work I did yesterday for my novel.  I worked on charcters, so now I have a list of them, with their motives, and their relations to other characters.  Mind you. I also have the first ten pages typewritten, and at least five more handwritten.  I hope to produce some work later, when I go home.  Have to remember to make a back-up copy of my work on disk, so I have spare to work on.  Also need a print version of it, so I can edit directly on the text.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Ideas are looking good!!!!!!  Will work more on them.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      So far, so good witht the ideas for my novel.  Still working on it.  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Got some good ideas for my novel.  Jotted them down quickly, will be tying up results ASAP!!!!!  :-)
     

    
</post>

<date>18,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Guy cut his foot outside the library.  He like "its no big deal," but there's blood all on the pattio.  Yuck, yuck, yuck.  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hmmm.  I'm filling in for my co-worker, so I'm here on a Satuday.  I should have been mowing my lawn, and trying to relax, then working on my novel.  Took baby steps with the writing.  I can do some research now that I'm at work.  Thank goodness for that. 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Fave site:   urlLink E Online .  Nothing beats Entertainment news.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I just wanted to start my journal, so here goes.   I've been busy.  Real busy, so I have to slow down.  Forunately, I have the day off tomorrow.  I may finish up some things like my novel that I swear I'll have a chapter down by the end of the month.  Did all the homework I need to do, so I'll have a quiet Friday.  :-)
     

    
</post>

<date>18,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hello all.  i'm working to create a good blogg for you.  it's gonna take some time, and a lotta work, but I love a challenge.  ;-)
     

    
</post>

<date>18,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Check out  urlLink Delphi Forums 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Added link for my forum.  I will be doing more of that soon.  I want to get my ducks lined up in a row.  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Working on Bloggsite.  I just think I'll start slow.  LOL  My ambition led me to believe that I could dmake the site a little more spunkier.  I just need to pace myself.  LOL.  This is hard work to maintian, but well worth it. I'm glad I spent this time working on this.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Oh yeah, Happy Halloween!!!!!!!!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I have been working on my image project for my web design class.  I have a lot of little mistakes that I hope to fix this week-end.  I am very pleased with the progress I'm making.  Yesterday I felt really giving and good.  I don't know what came over me, but a sense of peace came over me, as I helped many people, and tried my best to be a good person.  I guess  that's a wonderful quality I wanted to write about.  For one day I had a truly pleasurable experience, and it felt AWESOME.    Let me tell you how good this experience was.  When my "friend" called me at 4:30 PM at my job (walked in at 4:00), and preceded to tell me about her day, like I'm supposed to sit there and take it, I calmly reminded her that her call was inappropriate for the time, and said goodbye.   Truth is, that was the LAST straw.  If it were any other day I would have bitten her head off for calling me after I told her for some time now to limit calls to important situations, not casual calls.  Like I have time for personal calls with my boss right next to me.    I don't like being mean, but it seems like that's my only option.  I'm going to do it calmly, because I feel like it.  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Been very lazy.  Here is yesterday's entry:  Co-worker still sick.  She has the flu B-A-D.  No offense to her, but I hope she stays home.  I don't want what she's got.  LOL.  Don't need it either.  I do hope she gets better, and has a swift recovery-just at her home.   I was late for class this moning.  I was doing fine until I turned on my TV while getting dressed.  I hadn't peeped Rikki Lake in ages, but I did today.  A guest called her "Jenny."  Was that a faux pas or what?  I laughed and laughed and laughed.  I didn't get dressed.  I left home, got into some so-so traffic, and barely made it to class with about 20 seconds or so to spare.  I was psoitive I wasn't going to get a computer to use comming in so late.  That'll learn me.    Finished my project.  I'm proud of that.  Library's busy again.  I'm taking a break for some food.   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Had a good day so far.  Went to class, and talked to instructor about what I can expect from the Commercial graphics program.  Frankly, I didn't know the difference between the graphic design program, and the digital media program.  She told me that the difference is that in SC the graphic design program is more helpful for doing print jobs.  I could do brochures, and posters.  All that type of fun stuff.   With the digital media I could go into multimedia and design more internet content.  She also told me the pay is better for multimedia, and the jobs are better outside of SC.  I can expect better pay, a deeper challenge, and a lot more money.  :-)  Now that I do have a stronger focus on the digital media program, I can focus a lot stronger on it, and make my primary goal to graduate on time, and get me a good job!!!!!  I was coasting through the program, trying to feel my way through, but now that's over.  I'm sticking with the program, and I'm gonna do better for myself!!!  I can see myself finishing and challenging myself to come up with new ideas.  The world is open to me.  I can go into game development, or educational programming.  I'm heading down the right track!!!!  The Lord does deliver clarity to those who ask for it.  :-)  Co-worked absent today.  She's under the weather.  She sounded fine last night, but that's all it takes is overnight stuff.  Flu's going around.  I hate that.  I manage to get sick every semester.  Can't let that happen this time around.  I hope she feels better.    A friend decided that she wanted to purchase Dreamweaver/Fireworks even though she has no idea how the programs work.  I think she may be feeling left out 'cause she's not taking classes.   I have a sneaky feeling that she'll be asking me a lot of questions on how to operate it.  I also think she tried to rub it in my face that she was buying the software.  It's the way it came out of the blue, and was mentioned.  I'm feeling waaaaaayyy to good to let her disposition to affect me.  I'm not answering her questions though.  LOL.  She's not popping up to ask/show me her Dreamweaver/Fireworks problems either.  LOL. 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      This is what I should have posted yesterday:  I'm finishing up my homework, which is due on Tuesday.  I'm making web pages, which turns out to be harder than one expects, as a novice.  I have pratical knowldge, but I'm getting better.  Had to e-mail professor as to a question about codes.  I'll make arrangements to finish the work if I get a response by tomorrow, or Monday.    Have to go to grocery store.  I have to cook tonight.  I really don't want to, but what chjoice do I have I want to eat, after all.  LOL.  I also gotta put gas in the car.  It's on a quarter tank, but I'd like for it to be a little higher.  You know what I mean? 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Came to work, and have so little to do.  Most people want reference help today.  Of course the librarian doesn't come in until 1:00 PM today.  When he/she gets in, they'll have their work cut out for them.  When I worked on Friday, I didn't realize that reference bailed out on us before we closed the place.  People were asking me all sorts of questions I couldn't answer.  I did my best, but it was clear that they needed the librarian.    Almost forgot about daylight savings time.  Would have came to work an hour earlier if left to my own devices.  Yet I still managed to go to bed late.  LOL  Finished most of my homework.  I still have another day to fix my web pages for a grade.  I'm getting nervous.  I had hoped to be done by Saturday.  After class, went to grocery store.  Bought ingredients for beef stew.  Somebody has to cook the rice today, 'cause I did the stew last night.  I got home after 6:00 pm to cook.  Didn't finish until 11:30 PM.  I took my time.  I wanted the meat tender before I added the vegetables.  I may have put in too much veggies, but it will make it more filling IMHO.  I get this feeling my brother won't make the rice.  I'll do it when I get home (around 5:30 today).  Bought my niece the Lion King DVD last week-end.  She's such a cutie.  I'd love to get her more gifts.  Maybe something she can learn from.  I'll have to put thought into that one.  I'd like to make sure she gets family support in addition to her parental support. :-)  It makes me feel good knowing she's getting proper love and attention.  I've never been an uncle before, so I'm leaning and growing.  That is just the most precious moment I think I've had in a long time.   I'm savoring that one.  My novel.  LOL  Hadn't touched on it in a while.  I was writing an essay on the direction I wanted to take when I was so interrupted by a phone call (several phone calls). I'm like "hey this is my time," and people are like "but I need."  sigh, nobody listens, but they want me to pay attention.  LOL.  When I get home I'm making all the time I need for my essay.  it's long overdue.    
     

    
</post>

<date>24,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm at work today, and boy is the library slow.  No student wants to be caught in this place on a Friday.  It's like they're embarrased to study and what not.  LOL.  The people I've seen have some interesting clothing on.  Some of the people are casual, and some are wearing stuff like, "did you see yourself before you left your house?"  LOL  Nothing like a college campus to wake your senses.  Had a boring (cheap) lunch of chicken nuggets and waffle fries.  Wish it was better, but beggars can't be chooser, you know?    Paid for parking today, and it cost me $4.50 for 3 hours.  Man, It's crazy downtown.  Had to move my car closer to the library, so that helps some, but not much by the way of time (I still had to wait for time to allow me to park freely)   We're talking about the new libray being built.  Nobody knows what's going to happen to the old one, so when people ask me, I can't tell them anything.   
     

    
</post>

<date>23,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Worked on project for web design class today.  I asked the professor if the second web design class uses the same book.  She said that she didn't know because the Marcomedia software is upgrading, which means that there will be new books on that.   I don't know how good that is, but it means I will have to buy new books.  I was going to buy the macromedi software, but that won't happen until January 2004.  I will be working on a Friday (How I hate that), so I'll do what I have to do.  This is a wrinkle in my plans.  LOL.  I wanted to rest more.  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Should have posted sooner.  I'm such a slowpoke.  LOL  I have much to do.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      It's been a long time.  Not!!!  LOL.  I've been doing evertything from cleaning my room, to doing my homework.  Man am I tired.  LOL  Went to class, and one classmate is like asking all the time for answers.  I don't have them, how could she ask for them?  I did notce she played dumb, and letothers finish her work.  Imagine, her grade came form two other people.  It would have been three, if I didn't keep my mouth shut. 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Not too busy today.  It's nearing fall break for the college students.  I have the dubious task of being here tonight.  Most of the students have cleared out.  I have been getting some dumb and drawn out phone calls.  it seems nobody can form a sentance today.  LOL  Today in class I had to finish my web pages for the imahe project.  I did a lot of hustling.  LOL.  Editing is not as easy as it seems.  I needed to align my tables proper, and take care of all of the bugs.  I did it.  I got a 92, and 96 on the pages I turned in.    One of my classmates doesn't understand anything in the class.  She keeps asking questions, and sometimes I can't answer them.  I think she wants others to do the work for her, since she didn't even define her site (something we learned in August).  She says she's scatterebrained, but she needs to get it together.  Maybe she could BS her way through a web design, but I think she's cheating herslef, and the client, if she ever takes up web design as a career.    Some people helped her in class.  Poor people did all of her work for her.  She said it was a nightmare to complete, but it had to be a dream, since she didn't do too much.  LOL  I know one thing, I will not do her work for her.  She's gonna have to learn the work. 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Visit  urlLink Blogskins  to spiff up your blogg
     

    
</post>

<date>14,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm working on changes for The Comfort Zone.  Bear with me please.  It's a work in progress.  
     

    
</post>

<date>14,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Today I got a letter in the mail telling me I didn't get the job.  Boy that smarts so bad.  I really wanted to break into a new position.  I suppose I will have to bide my time.  I know there is something better out there for me, so I won't give up.  I do however feel like I'm chasing my tail.  If  a job won't come to me, I'll guess I'll have to make one of my own.  Something's gotta come my way.  On a good note, I don't feel like I'm in a funk.  I'm not angry or upset.  It must have something to do with the fact that I prayed a lot about this interview, and promised myself that I would make the best impression I could.  That way if I didn't get the job, it wouldn't be due to any deficiencies I had at the time.  I did make an impression, just one they wanted.    I'm going to pray that I become a better writer, and that I start selling some of my short stories, so I can have something on the side that keeps me going.  Because at the end of the day, I need to feel like heading somewhere other than nowhere.  
     

    
</post>

<date>14,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm in a funk again.  It's because I need some rest.  LOL.  I'm tired.  Completed most of my project for my web design class.  There's a student in my class that always asks me questions.  She's a little too much, and she doesn't seem to grasp a thing we've learned.  I can't help her much, even though she thinks I'm like efficent in the class.  I'm like I'm reading the same book as you, and all I ever do to remember my steps is go over the pratice exercise.  LOL.  I guess she doesn't want to go that route.    I like the progress I'm making, and I need to feel that way about my photoshop class.  I kinda hated that last project.  I got fustrated, and upset.  I turned in what I had, but I don't know if that is good enough.  That makes me feel sad.  maybe I wasn't going to learn ALL of the material, but the majority of it.  Classses are tough sometimes.  I do want to rest my nerves, and go to sleep.  I forgot Law and Order now comes on Tuesdays, so I'm missing that.  Life's full of twists.   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Can't remember anything I did this week-end.  It's all a blur.  LOL.  Seriously, I rested.  That was good enough for me.   Gave one of my stories to an editor to read.  Began to think about ways to make my writing less sterile, and more poetic.  We shall see how that works out tonight.  Co-worker asked if I'd take her Sunday shift (4pm to Midnight)   I replied that I hate those hours.  I LOVE my free evenings, I don't want to do them.  Usually I don't say no, but I had to.  LOL  I hate those hours on Sundays.  If it were an emergency I might consider doing it, but its not.  Other co-worker has lost her mind.  She's cursed our supervisor and students.  On top of that she stormed  out in the middle of the conversation.  She should have gotten a pink slip.  I know I couldn't do that (and don't want to).  Some of the students saw that mess, and lost a lot of respect for the staff.  I think something's in the air during the day that makes people fool in here.  There's no excuse for insulting people (especially good students who do their job).  It will go on  and on, until somebody's mouth falls off.    Worked on image project for web design class.  I tired to get my table set proper.  Boy was it all wrong.  It was so misalligned, I had to delete ti, and start all over again.  I got it better the second go 'round.  I did forget to add all the alt text for the images.  I remembered after I got back home form the computer lab.  LOL.  So if I have some spare time that's what I'll do tomorrow, since I can't edit from here.  Booooooo 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Did the regulars today.  I went to work, and I went to class.  In class theI had to tun in my outline/flowchart for my fianl project.  I almost forgot about it.  LOL I would have been in trouble.  
     

    
</post>

<date>08,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Thought about something.  I need to not look at my novel for a week or to, to divorce my mind from it, so I can look at it with new eyes when i return.  Just a thought.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      This is what I wrote in my jounal:  Had my interview today.  Man was I nervous.  LOL  I took the nervousness as a good sign, since I knew I was taking everything seriously.  I demonstrated some serious communication skills, and my background served me well.  I hope to hear from them soon.     I did think I'd miss working with some of my co-workers, but the better pay offsets any sad feelings.  Also, I need a new challenge to lift me up.  I'm way too young to be caught up in a dead-end job.   My life outside of work is a soap opera.  A freind suggested that my annoying friend was attracted to me, since she's on the clingly side.  I'm  like nothing's going to happen, but the this woman's clinging more and more.  She's forgetting her boundaries, and I can't tolerate that.   The drama unfolds in "Stacy's Life."  LOL.  She's gonna get her feelings hurt if she does that dissrespect thing again.  
     

    
</post>

<date>06,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I got 52 pages of my novel!!!!  Now all I have to do is revise that sucker.  LOL.  The easy part is over.    Also revised a short story.  Yayyyyy!!!!!!!!  It's all good.  I love well spent time!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>05,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I am getting back into my drawings and paintings.  It seems aburden has lifted, and creativity is pouring back into me.  I have been in a creative slump, and now that's over with.  I'm riting ideas down, and will have to remember to bring my sketchbook with me, so I can put images down from my head.  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Went to class, then Wal-Mart.  Love to shop, but I was tired and hungry.  I felt a little light-headed.  Not a good way to do any purchasing.  Got some waffle fries and a soda to offset the hunger.  At work bought some wings (Italian, and Oriental) and celery sticks to fend off hunger.  Drank some tea, but am now chasing down water, which i also need to keep up with.  Will visit family member tomorrow, whom I haven't seen in a while.  I'm looking forward to the meeting.  Remember how some relatives you absolutely dread visiting.  LOL.  Mercifully, that's not the case!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>01,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Happy birthday to me!!!!!!!!!!   LOL  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm still busy.  LOL.  Holidays got me running in circles at work.  Also finals still due.  I worked real had on the web page class material.  I want this done sooner, since I have to create ten pages.  I love my work.  I did image maps, slicing, exporting of Gifs and Jpgs to keep thins going well.  Man have I suffered, but in the best way.   It was all to get my material done.  I'm proud to say I'm ahead of the game.    All that was needed for Tuesday's class, was me having my layout page completed.  I did that and then some.  I feel good.  Today I said I wouldn't do anything for the page, to give my mind and body rest from the page.  I was right to do so.  I have an hour left at work.  It got busy in here.  Too busy.  In fact, I think I'm going to buy my dinner, and go home.  I'll rest for the end of my day.   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Working on web final project tonight.  Am very busy, but wanted write at least something.   Heard about Michael Jackson?  He's all over CNN, Court TV, and Fox News.  I hope he's telling the truth, for his sake.  
     

    
</post>

<date>19,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Professor not well today, so I'm in class typying something for this journal.  Will go home and rest nerves.  A thunderstorm is comming, so I want to be done with the computer when I leave the campus.  I was tired this morning, and it seemed to trickle down to class time.  I'm getting something to eat, then I'm going home, then onto work later.  The good news is that its the "hump" day, so once it's over, I can breathe again.  My nose is running like a leaky facuett.  When I excuse myself to blow it, it dries up.  Go figure.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Did some more links to the page.  I think they're well done, if I say so myself.  LOL
     

    
</post>

<date>16,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm so busy with projects.  Finals are stressful.  I did want to write something though.  I like writing.  it releaves my stress some.    Tried the iced tea from Starbucks.  It tastes  NASTY!!!!   LOL.  Thank God I bought the tall, instead of the grande.  This thing is awful.  I've tasted bad tea before.  I don't like this one.  I know it's only my opinion, but it is what it is.    Didn't want to do anything but rest today, but I had to press on.  I have things to do.  Got myself though my image project.  I have a big test on Thursday, and after than I still have two fianals to finish.  I'd love to add better links to this page, seeing as how I have started editing the code.  It's a pity, cause I end up being pulled in so many directions.  I don't want "Comfort Zone" to be a casualty.    Oh, I promised myself that after I finish my classes for the semester, I'm make a better homepage.  LOL  I want it to look good.  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      It's been a while since I wrote something meaningful, that I personally found satisfying.  I've been contemplating ideas, plus having little adventures like you wouldn't believe.  LOL.  I stay busy.  My mother asked me to help her with her new insurance forms.  She wanted to apply online, and I was ready to help.  She kept changing her mind as to the selections.  That made it frustrating to help her with things.  We got it done though, thank goodness.  Been having late night creative urges, that may be in part due to my large consumption of water during the week-days.  I flushed all that Cola off my brain.  LOL    Class work's gotten tougher, but I'm working through that.  Did work for my web-page final, and found myself wishing I didn't start earlier.  One of the challenges of my classwork is that I have to find a decent solution, which I have.  It was one of those day at the computer lab when the supervisor was like he may have to close early, and I felt 100% rushed.  I HATE being rushed.  I'm not that good when doing creative things rushed.    Thought I owed the IRS money, when in fact, I didn't.  I had to return a notice to them, which I will do promptly.    I'm hungry.  I may go to the grocery store, so I can get some good eats.  I'm in the mood for some Mexican-style food.   
     

    
</post>

<date>14,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hello,  been busy, and I wanteded to write something.  I'm bored with television on my day off.  I am going to be up to my neck in projects.  I was a creative whirlwind last night.  I was up until 2:00 Am writng down Ideas.  I may start writing again.  I have so many ideas.    I'm being distracted by family members.  I won't get anything done.  :-(
     

    
</post>

<date>09,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hello, Working on my creativity.  I seem to be lacking the proper focus.  I'm all energy, and I'm feeling a need to direct my energies into something positive.  I suppose I can call this a mature move on my part, because I really am desiring to have a purpose in writing I want to see a positive output of talent.  Creativity is a gift, and I want to pool my resources, because I know I can be a success with my gift.  That is someting I have always neglected.  My success depends on how I conduct myself, and if I shy away from my ideas, then I have nothing.  I'm still in the process of developing ideas proper.  I don't want to play it "safe" and try to second guess myself.  I want to take some risks, and work at my crafts.    
     

    
</post>

<date>07,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I had too much caffene.  As a result, I was up late, and couldn't go to sleep.  I think I may have dozed off around 6:00 AM.  That sucked, and I'm still not sleepy.    Went to See Matrix Revolutions today.  It was ok.  I didn't like the ending, whic I won't spoil for anyone.   How cool would that be?  Yesterday I worked on improving pages for my image project.  We'll see how that  goes.  I'd like to see it completed.  I could then move onto my final project.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Been way too lazy.  Good to write something fresh tonight.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      My life's a soap opera.  I have one friend who is having a crisis with her aunt.  She want to rollover and let things happen to her.  I hate talking to people like that.  What makes it worse, is that she complained that she has no rights.  WTF???  You gave them away.  Enough about her.  I've purged her from my mind for today.  Did lotsa homework for Photoshp class.  For two assignments, I missed some important details.  My instructor alerted me to it, and I got to spend an hour after class trying to fix my projects.  I only have 2 projects left before the final.  The instructor said there was a writing component to the final.  I wonder how much writing is there.    I have open lab for my web design class tomorrow.  I'll talk more on that tomorrow.  Work was ok.  A little busy at times, and a little noisy.  This is the only library that I've been at that encourages the students to talk loudly.  LOL.  Go figure.  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Merry Crhistmas to all!!!!!  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Oh,  I've been so lazy, but with good reason.  I took some time off to rest.  My holiday time at work has started, and I feel relaxed.  I wanted to write something that is not on paper.  LOL  I hope to write more frequent.    I downloaded Netscape from a disk that gave me demos for dremweaver and fireworks.  Hopefully I'll redo my hompage, cause it looks crappy.  LOL
     

    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Today is the last day of class.  All I have to do is turn in my project folder, and I'm done.  Yes!!!!!!!!!!!  I've spent some time burning copies of my work to cd's so I can use them at home.  I'm in the computer lab waiting for my instructor to arrive.  Life, is good. Mom had a flat tire and didn't even realize.  She drove home on a flat.  I worked late last night (didn't get off until 2:00 AM).  I didn't go to sleep until like 3:30 AM.  I got up around 11:00 this morning, so I could put gas in my car, and take care of biz, before I stopped by my class.  Now all I have to do is go to work.  LOL.  That's later today.  I hope to write more, now that I have some free time.  LOL
     

    
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm glad I'm back to writing regularly.  I needed to clear the air first.  Makes me feel good.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Yahooooooo!  I completed BOTH my final projects!!!!!!!!!!!!!  Now all I have to do is go to class on Monday and Tuesday and turn them in.  I feel wonderful!!!!!!!  It took me some doing, but I finished them in time, and I can rest my nerves.  I do have to go to work, and deal with other student's nerves who have yet to start their finals, but I don't care, I've done something good for myself.    My cat has been trying to lay on the table.  That's not good.  He's been trying to find places to curl up on that's not the floor.  He's been on my bed, my mom's, and my brother's bed.  We got him a pillow.  The moment he saw it, he was in heaven.  It was his little space where he could rest.  LOL.  I couldn't take him on my table.   I am pleased he has a space he can rest on without getting himself in trouble.    Classes are almost over, since I have two days left.  I really am happy I stuck with the digital media program.  I foolishly thought I was in over my head during the first semester, but now I realize that if I take it one step at a time, I don't have to worry.    I promised myself that I would re-design my own website over the break.  I'm thinking of new images.  I may use some from my project, because I loved what I did, and that is my goal.  Also I have been working on new short stories.  I want to compile the stories, as to get several to choose from, and to have a body of work.  Go me!!!!!!  (((((((((pats self on back)))))))))  I'm very happy now.  :-) 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I have to put in an appearence, because I love to write.  As mentioned earlier, I had a lot to do with my finals.  Man am I tired.  LOL.  Here's what I wrote for my entry:  Finals are nowhere finished.  I'm about 95% done with my final web page project, and 65% done with my Photoshop final.  Progress is good.  I also had a creative burst, so I've been a writing fool.  I hope to do more writing before the night's out, but the library's busy, so I may not.  If I take a break, I may scribble down some ideas.  I'd like to wait 'till I'm off work, so I won't be so distracted.  Bye.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's a pity, I don't write frequent enough.  I am to fix that.  I will handwrite at least one paragraph per day, and type it out here.  At least my journal will have some infomation.  I suppose it looks pretty dead at some point, but it can be better.  I did get a vist from my angellic neice yesterday.  She's so sweet.  I love when she visits.  Also bought a digital camera, so I'm trying to get all the kinks out.  
     

    
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Time flies, and I forget to post, or at least get caugut up in some mad ish.    I am so late or an entry.  it looks like I've abandoned all entries.  No, just working on a writing project that is not done, will be worked on tonight, and I'll have it completed by the 20th.  That is my projected date to submit the writing.  Who knew it would be so detailed, and I would be so wrapped up in the material.    I'm on abbreviated time, so I have to close up in about ten minutes.  I did want to post, and will post again soon.   
     

    
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ah, how the lazy have fallen.  LOL.  I have been busy, and classes are no help.  Iwanted things to slow down, so I can make better use of my time, and not waste any.  Well, as you can see, January 18th was my last entry.  I've failed myself, but I havn't given up.  I have a photography assignemnt to finish, and some other ish to made due wit.  Tried a new game, Beyond Good and Evil for Gamecube.  Normaly I hate adventure games, but I like this one.  I get all confused, and lost.  It does make me think a lot.  LOL
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm washing laundry.  It's a necessity.  I should not have put it off so much so much.  So it's everything from light clothes to the darks.  I didn't realize I had so much socks.  They nearly took up a whole full load.  LOL.     Classes start tomorrow.  I said I'm getting an "A" in both of them.  What can I say, I know I can keep things together enough to pass my c;lasses.  I want back on that Dean's list also.  The classes are Computer Imagery (Adobe Illustrator), and Multimedia Presentations (Powerpoint).  I'm going to enjoy both of them.  :-)  I'm not cooking today.  I'm going ton relax as much as possible.    
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Oh, Special thanks to Berry, for kicking me in the pants about keeping the writing up.  Now that I have free time, might as well put it to good use.  LOL  My co-worker allowerd her son to have a copy of Anne Rice's "Queen of the Damned."  Her son's like 12.  I didn't think that was a book for kids.  It was far too mature.  She looked shocked by that, but I had this feeling that she didn't want to take too much responsiblity for him having the book.  That's just my opinion though.  I could be wrong.  
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hello, again.  I've made so many changes, and I hope to keep the Blog going.  It's my fault.  I should have posted onece a week.  it would have kept me sane.  No more excuses though, lets get onto fome fun things.  Classes start next week Tuesday for summer.  After that I have three more semesters to endure all the fun things Trident Tech has to offer.  After that, It's on to grad school.  That will take me year to complete.  I don't think my mom likes the year part, but I gotta get myself going.  I don;t want to be one of those peole whose life begins and ends at a dead end job.  What's that?    I have to get some opinions on my work.  I'll have to ask my instructors wht they then of my portfolio website I hope to have smething for them soon.  Also working on my statement of purpose, and the application for grad school, whic is due by January.  It should be done by then.  No?  LOL  
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Tonight and tomorrow I will work on my new web sites.  I was going to call my homepage "Stacy's House," or something like that, but the page is not just about my name.  It's about me, and not naming  everything  after me.  I did think of a nifty logo for "Stacy's House" I may use, but as a signature.  I want the homepage to be original and raw.  Y'know get the best of me in there, and let you know it's all good.    The rain subsided, and I went to lunch.  Downtown floods so easily, and wcars slached water all over the side walk.  If they wern't racing through the water, it wouldn't be so bad, but those bastards did, and I nearly got soaked several times.    I got some nachos, and a Sprite, and called that an evening.  I tried out the Yahoo radio.  The one where you customise the music.  My taste is so eclectic, that I didn't know half the selections the radio was selecting for me.  I got over that real fast.  LOL  I've written three times today.  That's a great thing.  I feel great when i write, and I like that feeling.     Song of the Evening:     Fall   by Cree Summer.  Why: It's a rock flavored tune that I like.  It also represents my ecleticism well.      Thought of the Evening:    Do not question everything.  Somethings must be accepted as is.  Be well people, be well.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It looks ugly outside.  There's a storm on the horizon.  It looks so dark outside, I'd swear it was 9:00 PM already. I hate it when a storm brews, and I'm not home.  It makes me a little nervous, 'cause a lot of people drive poorly in the rain.  They speed like crazy. Caution gets thrown to the wind.    I got an  offer for an interview.  Don't want to jinx it, and I have yet to confirm the date, but needless to say it would allow me to take my late night classes if the opportunity presents itself.  Also more pay would be fine, if possible.  I'm praying for success.  Did some data entry for today.  I mainly went over other people's work, as someone haphazzardly placed the info in the system.  I checke and redid the info when necessary.  it wasn't so bad.  I liked it.    I wanted to buy Brandy's new CD, but decide to put that money elsewhgere.  I may purchase a few tunes from itunes later next week, if time and money permits.     Song of the Evening:    Friend of Mine   by Kelly Price.  I love to hear both the album and R. Kelly remix.  Bad friends are the worst, and hearing songs about them is even better.  Peace y'all.   
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hello,  I'm in class.  I like to take this time to reflect on the day.  It's soooo early.  I'm going to go home soon.  I may go to sleep.  While yesterday, I avoided caffine, I still didn't get much sleep.  That's a shame.  I need a latte.  It'll keep me awake. Turned in my homework assignment for today, which I did last night. Filled my car with gass today.  I spent $15.05, but it's full.  It should last me a week or so.  Eveybody else pays like much much more.  I guess their tank is huge.   Song of the Morning:     This Love   by Maroon 5.  Why:  I listened to it on the raido on my way to class.  It was a good song to drive to.  
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      People are paying me compliments on my shirt and hat today.  Makes me feel good.   I have a Superman logo on my shirt.  Guess that makes me the man.  LOL.   Somebody didn't like the fact that I got comments, and started hating, and quite frankly it turned me off.  I'm getting over that.  I should get some more cool shirts, and let them hate harder.   If I think about it what should I do anything different from today.  I need to treat myself better than before.  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have decided that i should not allow other factors in life to constrain me.  This means taking control of my life, time, and energies.  I want to be able to project the right amount of energies into my talents.  There should be no excuses, no explanations or justifications to others about what I do.    In the past I felt a need to please others, and I'm not happy.  I'd like to get to a point where my happiness and life come first, and not last.  I getting there.  Of course things don't happen overnight, and if I rememeber to do things the right way (put my needs and well-being first), then I can't possibly fail.  It shall all work itself out, if I maintain the right course.  I'm developing two new websites.  The first is my official home site.  This site will contain photos, poetry, and liks galore.  LOL.  I want it to be my special site.  The one I would want to design if I went to a professional and asked them to work on it.   The second will be a labor of love.  It's a site dedicated to fine art.  The details are still in the wash, but my background in art is my first love.     Song of the Day:     Talk About Love  by Brandy.  It is really a cool song, and is right for the summer.  If the opportunity presents itself, I'll purchase her new CD.  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My Mom and Grandmother just had birthdays this week-end.  I know they're happy.   My got herslef a new counter top stove to celebrate her victory.  LOL.  I'm so proud of her.   It was what she needed to complete her kitchen.    Talked with someone who was having some obcession/stalking problms.  I know a little about people who don't know how to respect boundaries.  They force you to be more agressive in responses.  You can't be nice to some people, 'cause they seem to want to run all over you.    Have to tell my friend she's being to nice to the obcessed person.  Let them know showing up on the job is not healthy at all.  Respect is key to all friendships.     Album of the Week:   Belly of the Sun , by Cassandra Wilson.  While this moves me out of R & B, and into jazz, we can all use a change of pace, and Wilson's music is great, and has a mellower vibe.  Also the live instruments are so cool to hear.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Where to start today.  I have freinds problems.  One friend is not speaking to the rest, and creating a rift in our group.  Needless to say some are taking it more personal than others.  That's to be expected.  It's pretty upsetting to see someone you know going through things, and they won't let you in at all.  What's the deal with that?  Attempted to use the campus computer lab , but their Dreamweaver software kept crashing.  I really went there because their computers have much more power than my laptop, but I might as well as stayed home.  I did get to talk to a friend who had this crazy story of someone stalking someone else.  I know the person doing the harrassing.  It  will  get worse, that I know.    I attempted to listen to the "Damita Jo" cd a friend loaned me.  I couldn't get into it.  It's not Janet's best.  Oh well.  It doesn't make album of the week.  LOL   Song of the day:  My choice is "Golden Boys" by Res.  If you listen to the lyrics, she sounds so disillusioned by people in high places.  The beat kicks too.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yesterday I didn't wear a t-shirt under my main shirt.  I felt funny, like I was walking around with no undies on.  LOL.  I know that may sound silly, but I am used to an undershirt beneath the shirt.  It felt naughty, almost.  I'm so old-fashioned.  LOLOL!!!!  I'll get myself out of that.    I'm still trying to figure out a solution to my class scheldue.  It's not so successful.  The only salvageable news is that I'll be done with the core classes this semester, and I may take my QuarkExpress class sooner.   The Library's louder than usual, for the summer that is.  It's ok.     Song of the Day:  Angel in Disguise by Brandy.  Why?  It's what's playing in my car.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I didn't write yesterday.  I'm such a slacker.  I know I'm writing today.  LOL.  Nonethelss the day was filled with some pretty blah moments and I had cabbage and rice on my break as food.  I'm outta cash this week, so whatever's home will have to do for me.  These weeks can be limiting, when the funds are low.  A friend gave me an apple.  I'll snack on that later.  I've also been munching on some crackers.  I can't say I'm starving, or hungry lol.  I got what I needed.  :-)   Song of the Day:   Golden Boys by Res.  Why, 'cause The lyrics are deeper than I thought, and the beat brings it on home.  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I didn't write yesterday.  I was real lazy.  So lazy that I didn't do much of anything constructive.  I am fustrated still that the hours for Fall semseter's classes are late in the evening.  I'm at the mercy of somebody playing with the admin system.  LOL.  I'm very pissed.    This is a skimpy post, and I don't feel muck like writing anything, but I musn't miss two days, 'cause that's when it becomes three, four and five days.  Such a sad cycle of nothiness.  I did want to work on a writing project, and may do so later in the evening.     Song of the Day:   I did have  something  to write about today.   "The Beautiful Ones" by Prince.  Why, cause it's on heavy rotation on my iTunes, and old school Prince is great Prince.  
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm working on my portfolio web page.  I wanted a link to my blogg, but I forgot the address.  Since I had to visit my sitre, I might as well write something.  Cooked stir-fdry today.  It didn't get as involved as I thought.  It was neat, (mostly) clean, and painless.  I love that in a meal.  I cooked enough for two days, so we'll see how long it lasts.    For breakfast I ate the last two slices of leftover pizza.  It was good.  The crust was a little tough as I mic'ed it too long.  Later on I have to get my cat some food, as he is already out of the bag I bought a couple of weeks ago.    It's obnoxiously hot outside, but I gotta get stuff done, then I gotta take some asprin 'cause my head's hurtin' somthing fierce.     Chill, Y'all     Album of the Week:   "Secrets" By Toni Braxton.  Why?  Because it's her best work.  There are a lot of great songs on there, and the way I'm playing the CD, you'd think I never heard the songs before.  LOL.  Seriously, Toni lays down a lot of hot tracks on this CD, and she has a great voice.  The qualty of music, lyrics, and voice are the best.   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      What's up all.  I had the best sleep last night.  I actually got to sleep  LATE .  Can you beleive it?  I had a day to sleep until 11:00 AM.  I'm so satisfied.  LOL  I also started writing ideas for a new story i can't tell y'all 'bout 'cause I really just have random thoughts about.  If I ever work it out, I'll share.  Tomorrow I have an early class, but I'll go to bed early tonight to offset that miserable I don't wanna get outta bed feelings I get in the morning.  I just hate rolling out of bed.  I'm still a night person.    Song of the Day:   "Naughty Girl" By Beyonce.  It has the right beat to pump in my ride.  Love to hear it.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I had a topic, but then I forgot it while driving aroud.  LOL  Got a haircut today.  Boy did I need it.  My hair looked a mess.  LOL.  My beard was outta control.  It got cut proper, and looks good.  I love that.     Song of the day:   "Let It Flow" by Toni Braxton, cause the song says what I need to hear, which is to let all the negative pass me by.  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Once again, I feel lazy, which means I must write something.  LOL  Amazing how inspiration can change at certian moments.    They've posted the hours for fall classes.  Don't you know every class I want is in the evenings.  I'm a little saddned by this, since I wanted all day classes, it would work well with my evening job.  So now I have to find a way to work with this, so I can make some money, and advance my edu.  I feel so conflicted.  That sucks.  I paid for my cat to get his shots and a bath.  I paid waaaaay too much money.  If he wasn't loved, I wouldn't do it, so I don't mind doing it, but it did put a dent in my wallet.  Fortunately, I have most of my bills paid already, and one heafty car note.  Can't do without the ride, especially sinces it's a good ride.  LOL.  
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Have you noticed that some people settle for less,never hoping to rise above their current situation?  After hearing some people say how we should be grateful to have a job, and more along the same lines.  What I got from that was that if I'm working a dead-end job, I should be happy with that.  If I don't like the relationship I'm in, I should be happy I have someone I'm with.  What is that?  Nowhere did anyone mention that there is room for improvement.  That you don't have to settle.  Use the dead end job as a stepping stone.  If the relationship is not healthy, then leave.  I don't want to have crumbs on the table, I want a whole dinner.  I don't have a fixed "place" at the bottom of the barrell.  I should be rising to the top.  My goal is to remember that I must improve my living and finical status. I will grow, I shall rise, and take my place as a leader, not a follower.  We gotta do for ourselves, 'cause too many people are treating us like we're not supposed to have feelings or desire.  Besides, why waste God given talent and drive.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Saw Terminator 3 last night.  It was ok.  The audi for my HBO is horrible though.  Why am I paying for this thing if tt doesn't work?  I'm getting hungry.  What to make for dinner, I wonder.  I'll think about it more.  Yesterday me and my friends were talking about people in sucky relationships.  we've come to the realization that it's all about denial, and beleiving that things will be different for someone dating an asshole.  Go figure.  Little bits of life, eh.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I don't wanna write, which means I have to write at least five sentences.  I have some ideas for a project, which I have been hand writing, and I have homework that needs to be completed.  As I write this, I'm trying to not look at the keys.  It's tricky, but I can do this.  LOL.  Man you just gotta love praticing, cause it can only make me better.  I wrote this journal entry.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My boss just shushed us.  LOL.  Now I have to find something quiet to do.  Namely I decide that it was time for today's entry.  Aftewords during lunch I can sing "Swing Low, Sweet Chariot."  It may take the edge off of massa's commands.    I woke up the morning with my eye burning.  I got allergies bad this week.  Man, it was hurting something crazy.  My intention was to call my professor, so I could get her help on a particular topic.  I found out my e-mail never reached her, so I sent it again.  e-mails are crazy sometimes, aren't they.  I get they get lost like some letters do in the mail.  I tried the "Java Chip" at Starbucks today.  Not my usual vanilla latte, but it's different.  I've been doing coffee all this week.  Better slow it down 'fore I become wired and nervous.  All I need to be is a mess by tomorrow.  I'm going to have Chinese for lunch, or at least that what I'm thinking about.  General Tso's chicken from Chopsticks is the best I've had.  Wore my straw hat today.  People love this hat.  i get the best reaction from thius hat.  I should get my hair cut, so I can stop wearing hats all day.  Straw is more comrotable, but useless when it rains, like it did an hour ago.  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I wasn't going to write today, since I have so tired, but after sufin' the net a little, I decided to get off my lazy duff and write something.  I should forewarn that I may skip Fridays, and some Saturdays for personal reasons.  Really, on those days if I touch the computer and go online, I just may have to write, but on those days I'm resting from work and classes.  I don't wanna see a damn machine.  Yesterday, a co-worker said she had to go home 'cause she left her dog in the house.  I suppose if a rainbow had hit the sky she might have to leave us today.  Alas, no rainbow, no retreat.  The libray is obnoxiously silent.  It's too quiet.  The only real sound I hear is the tapping of the keys.  I wondering if I'm typing too loud for the patrons?  Circulation is almost capable of running itself when it's this inactive.  All I do is answer questions about times open/close, and computer lab locations.  Phone hasn't rung in a while.  I take it that's good.  Took a test today in my computer graphics class.  I still think multiple choice is a bad way to desmostrate knowledge of software.  Weshould have projects to complete, and be judged on that, but I got an "A," so I shan't bitch too much about that. 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I' m at home resting my nevers before I go to work.  Spoke to a friend last night.  She was doing fine.  I was happy to get in touch with her, since I hadn't seen her in a while, and I like talking with her.   Have another project to work on, so I need to get on the stick about it.  We'll see. 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's me again.  Went to dinner with my family yesterday.  We went to a stakehouse.  It was sooooo good.  LOL.  I was stuffed.  Of course, I ordered steak.  I got a big one.  Man, I enjoyed myself.  I won't do that for a while.  LOL  When coming from work, yesterday, I saw the damnedest thing.  This guy was on the street with an erection going.  He looked like he was going to pop outta his pants.  I suppose it's pervert season near/at the library.  He really should go home with all that. I kept walking.  I didn't need to see any more.    I've seen and heard worse on the job.  Guys exposing themselves to library patrons.  This seems to come with the summer time.    I remember last year  when a guy exposed himself upstairs, and I asked the young woman if she wanted to call public saftey.  She said "no," but I had to insit she call. because she saw the incident, not me.  My boss took the conversation over, and afterwards tried to chastise me and my co-worker for not reacting "quick enough."  He also insisted that we were laughing at the woman (which was very untrue).     God, he was so out of line.  I let him know I did what was required, and I think he was mad at me for doing my job and standing up for myself.  THAT is why sometimes my job sucks.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yesterday, there was some rennovating about the house.  I was so sleepey when the people came to work, that I slept through their time here.  I got up, and they were ready to work on the windows.  Lord, my room looked a mess.  I had to scramble and make things look neater, so they could get though and finish the  windows.  The windows look nice now.  LOL  :-)  Bought new blinds for the windows.  One of them doesn't fit my window.  Have to take it back today, and get a larger one.  Talk about anti-climatic.  LOL  Still working on my porfolio for graduate school.  I also want to take more photography classes, so I can expand upon some ideas I have about creativity.    An  ex-friend called me recently, but I don't think I want to talk to her anymore.  A lot of things have changed between us.  Namely the fact that she tried to start a conversation as if nothing has happened between us to make us stop speaking to each other.  What does she really want?  I don't thin I'll ever ask.  I don't want to know.  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My life as a Graphic Designer  How many goals are there in life?  How can one flourish or fail?  I'm thinking of adding some additional skills to my roster.  True to form, I'm paninking about how I can fit all of the things I want to fit into my schedule.  I know, however that if I allow myself to think about my ideas over a week or two, a solution will emerge.    It's funny, but moment I wrote about my crisis, the panic faded away.  Life is good.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hello,  My home's in the process of being repaired.  It's been getting me up early.  Boy am I tired.  LOL.  I just need to get my bearings.  I'm also hoping to get myself working on some new theories.  I wrote them down, and we'll see what I can work with in the future.    They're cleaning the carpet at work today.  It's slippery.  I hope not to fall down.  I'll stay in one spot.  LOL  That's it.  One spot.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Went to class today.  Boy was I sleepy.  LOL  I got up at 7:00 AM (BTW did I mention that I'm a night person?), and dragged my way to my college.  I need to buy a book for the class.  It costs $40.00.  Everything's expensive.  It'll be orth it though cause I really want to learn Illustrator.  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm at work.  Nothing new.  Last night I worked on my HTML portfolio.  the work is slow, but steady.  Classes start today.  My Mpowepoint class is online, so I didn't have to get up early.  Tomorrow is my Illustrator class.  I do have to be up early for that.  LOL.  I'm such a night person.  How do I get into thes ethings?  It's for a good cause, so I shan't whine too much about it.    atched CSI Miami last night.  I love that show.  Also got to watch some reruns of Law and Order.  Stayed up late watching the history of barbarians on History Chanel.  It was so goo, and I should have wnet to bed.  
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's about that time to put the finishing touches on a few assignments, so I better get cracking again. Of course, I've been so busy with some things, like assembling a graduate portfolio.&nbsp;&nbsp; It's one of those weeks where timee can be both friend and enemy.  Met with one of my instructors to view my portfolio.&nbsp; She was impressed.&nbsp; :-)&nbsp; I'm glad I was able to get feedback from her.&nbsp; I now have to create a resume proper.&nbsp; Man, I'm going to be pooped from all the work.&nbsp; LOL    Song of the Day:   "   Closer   "   by Tracie Spencer.&nbsp; Why?&nbsp; It's not that well known, and I doubt it even had airplay, but I love to hear it&nbsp; it always reminds me of Christmas 1999, whene I worked for Disney.&nbsp; Good memories, crazy times.&nbsp; I was sober through all of it, I swear.&nbsp; LOL 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hello,   I'm knee deep in mock-up sketches for a cd design.&nbsp; As usuall, I'm never staisfied with the first version, so I go on and create some more.&nbsp; I took a break to remind myself that I wrote nothing for my blogg today.&nbsp; It was the perfect break moment, as I began to get tired of my rather poor sketches.   I wrote up an inventory of my skills, and quite frankly, I have a whole lot of software and artistic skills.&nbsp; Sometimes you can loose sight of who you are trying to catch up with others, when all that time you have the tools necessary to take you to first place, and hold your own.&nbsp; I can do whatever, can't I?&nbsp; It's all a state of mind.   I will write more of my work day later, possibly tomorrow, since this is a quick break.&nbsp; For those who read this,&nbsp;  "believe in yourself, and take stock in your skills.&nbsp; You will be amazed at who you are, and what you can do."  &nbsp; That is my   Tip of the Day.        &nbsp;    
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yesterday, my co-worker got me a vanilla latte.&nbsp; She's so sweet.&nbsp; She didn't have to do that.&nbsp; It kept me awake longer than I expected, but that's OK.&nbsp; LOL.&nbsp; Good intentions, and desires for thing can come with a price.&nbsp; Latte's are dangerous.&nbsp; They placed a spell on me, and that Starbucks has me hook, line & sinker.&nbsp;   Today I tried to put in my contacts when it seemed everyone was content with bothering me, and insisting on answers.&nbsp; To make matters worse, I lost the left eye contact.&nbsp; I am so pissed!!!!!!&nbsp; The good news was that the lenses were disposable, and it is the last week for them, as I have a fresh pair ready to go.&nbsp; What makes me upset is that I was in the batroom with the door closed.&nbsp; Why the hell would&nbsp;anyone want to bother me then?&nbsp; As I ask that question, I realize that people feel a strong need to feel secure, and I happened to to be the blanket to their Linus.&nbsp; &nbsp;No use crying over spoiled milk, so I grabbed my glasses and went to work.   I did leave a soda in the fridge, and had to call back home for someone to remove it.&nbsp;&nbsp; I totally forgot, and was glad it hit me when it did.   I had a meeting about the new format for the e-res pages.&nbsp; Boy, that meeting was&nbsp;45 mins.&nbsp;too long.&nbsp; It lasted an hour.&nbsp; It was so dry, that I started drawing all over the pages I was supposed to be taking notes on.&nbsp;&nbsp; I've been doing e-res stuff for 3 1/2 years now.&nbsp; I had the basics down.&nbsp; The updated version simply looks different.&nbsp; I told my boss it was too long, and he agreed.&nbsp;   Have to meet with one of my instructors on a review of my portfolio.&nbsp; It's a step in the right direction, so I want the best feedback.&nbsp; I will get this portfolio launced soon!   Burgers and fries were on the menu today, as I ate them.&nbsp; I was luck I was in a room by myself, as I belched so loud, I felt that in my chest.&nbsp; Lord, it was a relief.&nbsp; LOL.&nbsp; Thankfully nobody heard me (or so I think).&nbsp; I said "excuse me" politely.&nbsp; Pratice makes perfect.&nbsp; &nbsp;      Tip of the Day:  "Don't add sugar to your lattes."  &nbsp; It will only agitate you more than usual.&nbsp; LOL      Song of the Day: &nbsp; " Happiness "   by Vanessa Williams.&nbsp; It's such a bubbly song, and so cheerful.&nbsp; It stays with you for some time.   
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's almost time to close this place up.&nbsp; On top of that I've been having a swell day.&nbsp;&nbsp; Nobody complained.&nbsp; LOL.&nbsp; No backackes, and talk of "mucus in one's chest."&nbsp;&nbsp; LOL.&nbsp; Praise the Lord.&nbsp; Nobody knows how annoying and digusting it is to hear that mess, in addition to all the camel noises&nbsp;this co-worker makes.&nbsp; I've  never  met any woman who was willing to belckh or fart in front of other people.&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;   The Ball and Mirror project didn't go so well.&nbsp; it looks like crap to me.&nbsp; I suppose that's my own fault for waiting so late.&nbsp; next time I'll have to do much better.&nbsp; I have two projects left in my Illustrator.&nbsp; Don't you know my animation project file got corrupted, again!&nbsp;&nbsp; I'm so pissed.&nbsp; I worked on that sucker.&nbsp; I wanted it to shine!&nbsp; This time around I made multiple copies, so if something went wrong, I had another back-up.&nbsp; Good thing too.&nbsp; I would have lost my mind as a few weeks of work goes down the toilet.&nbsp; A classmate of mine lost  ALL  of her current work.&nbsp; it wasn't pretty.  I have a final presnetation.&nbsp; I'm doing it on American Realist Thomas Eakins.&nbsp; Eakins broke rules and conventions.&nbsp; Also I know a lot about his work.&nbsp; it makes the research much more easier, as I sort and tease through the information.    Song of the Day:&nbsp; "The Greatest Romance That's Ever Been Sold"   by Prince.&nbsp; Why?&nbsp; That son't been in my head all week.&nbsp; I find myself humming it and singing the lines aloud.&nbsp; How did it get there?&nbsp; Not that it's a bad song, but it seem to come from out of the blue.&nbsp; Thank God I didn't listen to any boy bands or tten pop acts.&nbsp; Lord I'd be so regretting it now.&nbsp;&nbsp; LOL  &nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Went from the computer lab to Wal-Mart, and bought some bread, ham, and cheese.&nbsp; The store clerk joked about me making some sandwiches.&nbsp; he was right.&nbsp; I wanted them.&nbsp; Made some for lunch today.&nbsp; Alrady ate them.&nbsp; LOL&nbsp; Breakfast is good for the day.&nbsp; LOL  There may be a duty expantion for me at work.&nbsp; I will find out on Wednesday if I have new duties, as we prepare (yet again,&nbsp;I swear the delays are endless) to move into our new library.&nbsp; I talked with another co-worker from a diffent dept.&nbsp; He thinks we're going to have a lot of extra duties, for the same amount of pay as well.&nbsp; LOL.&nbsp; This expantion is a mixed blessing.&nbsp; I'm sure it means I will now have tacked on duties of other departments.&nbsp; I could be wrong, so I keep that in mind.&nbsp;   I don't want to do my Illustrator project.&nbsp; I find it rather cumbersome, and annoying.&nbsp;&nbsp; This stupid ball and mirror thingie.&nbsp; I have two finals in the class, and would love to dedicate time to them, and not be in such a jam&nbsp; later on.&nbsp; One day I'll have to post the projects, so all can see.    Song of the Day:&nbsp;  "Automatic"    by the Pointer Sisters.&nbsp; Why? It's one of my favorite 80's songs.&nbsp; I decided I wanted to purchase it from iTunes, and now I can can hear it all I want.&nbsp;  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Worked on the lawn this moring.&nbsp; I overslept, and the sun got me just right.&nbsp; All that water I drank yesterday went to good use, as I sweated it out.&nbsp; It was too hot, and I ended trimming bushes, and raking up the brances.&nbsp; It's was all good.   It's raining now, and I wonder if I'm gonna go to Wal-Mart like I said, and get some groceries.&nbsp; I hate driving in the rain.&nbsp; At least I don't have to go downtown today, where people drive even worse&nbsp;(I think with their eyes closed).&nbsp;   Talked to a friend today who is having the best time learing Macromedia Director.&nbsp; After seeing her work, I have to say, I&nbsp;can't blame her.&nbsp; She's doing a fantastic job.&nbsp; If my plate wasn't full, I'd take Director now.&nbsp; LOL.&nbsp; Good programs are great to get into.&nbsp; I have a couple of flash books to do work on, so I'll add those to my "to do" list.   Somebody from work called my home earlier.&nbsp; I'm sure it wasn't a call I wanted to hear.&nbsp; Nonetheless, I was way to busy in the yard to answer.&nbsp; "sides, I got sh*t to do, and places to be.&nbsp;&nbsp; If I didn't go to Wal-Mart yet, I'll be darned if I go downtown.&nbsp;&nbsp; LOL     Song of the Day: &nbsp;   "Yeah."    by Usher.&nbsp; I like the song, and I'm not a big Usher fan.&nbsp; He won me over.&nbsp; I can't front on that.&nbsp; LOL&nbsp;     Thought of the Day: &nbsp;   "What have you got to lose by doing something new?"   &nbsp; The answer is absolutely nothing, although that nothing sometimes holds us back some.&nbsp; Makes you think.&nbsp; No?&nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's summer movie time, and I got a few recoomedations from friends, so I have to take the time to go see them.&nbsp; Everybody who saw Spider Man 2 loved it, and says go see it.&nbsp; I Robot got some buzz too.&nbsp; Catwoman is a mix.&nbsp; Most forum people I spoke to were like "no way" (especially comic book fans, but understandable since the character veers from the comics).&nbsp; I peeped the trailers, I hope it's good.&nbsp; I'm a little curious.&nbsp; I like Halle, so I hope she can pull something off with this series.&nbsp; Besides, it would be good to see a kick-butt woman of color on the screen.&nbsp;   I want to buy the last Lord of The Rings DVD, but the budget won't allow it yet.&nbsp; I have devised a plan to obtain a second job, so all is not lost.&nbsp; I'll be likely too tired to see it.&nbsp; LOL.&nbsp;&nbsp; I will pray for endurance, and peace of mind.   Convinced my supervisor that we needed an online page for the Circulation.&nbsp; I'm all ecitied about that.&nbsp; I want all my co-worker's opinions, and I'll design it, and the rest will be history.&nbsp; :-)&nbsp; So far this day has been well.  &nbsp;    Thought of the Day:&nbsp;  "If you're really sick, then why don't you do something about it other than complaining."   &nbsp; I have a co-worker who complains about her life all the time, but doesn't do anything to heal herself.&nbsp; I thought it was worthsharing.&nbsp;    Be Well,     ---Stacy     
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey, it's another day, and life is great.&nbsp; Last night went fine.&nbsp; Today was an "I can get up late day," as 11:10 AM came by with me in bed.&nbsp; I made myself get up, so I can get dressed, and eat.&nbsp; As it turned out, I didn't eat breakfast, and went to work.&nbsp; Brought steak&nbsp;& rice for dinner.&nbsp; :-)&nbsp;&nbsp; I love a good meal.&nbsp;   Currently, I'm sleepy, and thoguht about going home early.&nbsp; I have some compensatory hours to take, and just may do so.&nbsp; I want to go to bed.&nbsp;     Song of The Day:    "To Your Love"    by Fionna Apple.&nbsp; Why?&nbsp; I love the song.&nbsp;&nbsp;Fionna's got a way of making beautiful music and cautionary lyrics blend.&nbsp; If you don't listen,&nbsp;you won't figure out that she's deliving a warning.&nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       The day has gone fine, and I can say that the&nbsp;world looks good.&nbsp; I finished a couple of PowerPoint projects earlier.&nbsp; I had&nbsp;no idea of what I was doing.&nbsp; I followed the instructions,&nbsp;but some things didn't make sense.&nbsp; If I don't get an "A" on these two projects I won't be&nbsp;upset at all.&nbsp;&nbsp;     &nbsp;   Met my co-worker's daughter for the first time.&nbsp; We've only like spoke on the phone for like 2 years.&nbsp; LOL.&nbsp; She'd call for her mom, and I'd&nbsp;end up speaking to her.&nbsp; She's a nice young lady.&nbsp; Takes right after her mother.&nbsp; Has a wicked sense of humor.&nbsp;     I'm working solo tonight, but that's ok, since I had to finish my work.&nbsp; Now that I'm done, I can write more.&nbsp; :-)&nbsp; Y'know, I panicked 'cause I didn't think I could get the work done, but I did, so I'm very happy with myself.&nbsp;&nbsp; I feel so good about now. so I'm loving this moment.&nbsp; :-)      Thought of the Day:  &nbsp;    "You don't win friends with salad."   &nbsp;&nbsp; I got that from the  Simpsons .&nbsp; It's true.    
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       My allergies finally stopped bothering me.&nbsp; It was just in time as my follow-up eye exam to see how well the contacts work.&nbsp; Their fine.&nbsp; It's getting better to stick thse things in my eyes, although the left one gives me some grief.&nbsp;&nbsp; I got it in there though.&nbsp; LOLOL.    &nbsp;  I was wired off of a Vanilla Latte last night , and went to bed at 3:30 AM.&nbsp; I was also wired, because I thought I lost my wallet.&nbsp; As ususal, I put things down, when I'm home, and forget where I place items.&nbsp; Fortunately, the walled was safe and sound, so I was ok this moring, but late for my computer graphics class.&nbsp;     &nbsp;  Watched SVU last night.&nbsp; I was saddende to see that a mother would use her foster children for a check, muder one of them, and pin the murder on her husband and her other foster child.&nbsp; That's low, but her ass got busted proper in the end.&nbsp; One happy ending, at minimum.    &nbsp;    Song of The Day:&nbsp;  "Heartburn"     by   Alicia Keys.&nbsp; Why?&nbsp; I needed to hear something upbeat anf enjoyable, and I can't reccoment "You Don't Know My Name" without laughing and imitaing that long ass message she left on that guys phone.&nbsp; "Hello, is This Michael?"&nbsp; LOLOL   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Xerox instructor showed us a new model Xerox that works like the older one, but looks different.&nbsp; It has a few funky features, but I wasn't as impressed as I wanted to be.&nbsp;&nbsp; She was a good instructor and nice, so I can't hate on that.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Today  must  be a full moon, as a couple of library patrons have had nasty attitudes.&nbsp; perhaps they were having bad days, and tried to give me thier ill will.&nbsp; Either way, I have to shrug it off, as I do not have the proper time to wallow in someone else's self-pity.&nbsp; One woman was all tearful and pissy at the same time.&nbsp; She didn't want a lecture, she just wanted me to break all of the library's policies for her.&nbsp; Like that was going to happen.&nbsp; The next had an attitude, not worth going into detail about.&nbsp; She's so done.&nbsp; They did scare off my student worker.&nbsp; I was not pleased with that.  &nbsp;  I was late to work, due to bad traffic.&nbsp; I have to change that, as I like to be palces on time.&nbsp; My boss really wants eveyone to be on time.&nbsp; The person who was chronicly late was acting like I was in big trouble, but she was full of it.&nbsp; Honey, one day doth not make you exempt from your tardiness.&nbsp; LOL&nbsp; She's gonna get burned when she walks in with her usual hour late routine.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Ran plenty of errands this morning.&nbsp; From mailing off my car payment to purchasing Frontline for my cat.&nbsp;&nbsp; I had to archive a lot of files today.&nbsp; I'm not nearly as finished as I like to be, but I did a great chunk this morning.&nbsp; :-)&nbsp;&nbsp; Later I just had to have Starbucks' Vanilla Latte.&nbsp;  Why  I didn't get the small is beyond me.&nbsp; $5.00 for a cup of latte.&nbsp; I should have known better.&nbsp; I need to gas my car, I may do that later on this week.&nbsp;&nbsp;Gotta have gas.  &nbsp;    Song of The Day:  &nbsp;    "Heaven Must Be Near"    by Ingrid Chavez.&nbsp; Why?&nbsp; Because when I hear the song, it lifts my spirits, and I can use that after this full-moonish day.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;    
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey, I missed a couple of days, but that's ok.&nbsp; I've been working on a Powerpoint presentation.&nbsp; The "Me" project for one of my classes.&nbsp; It took up a lot of my time, and energy.&nbsp; Boy was I exausted.&nbsp; I maxed out two solid days of making this project shine.&nbsp; It looks pretty great.&nbsp; Design wise I get stronger each day with how to make things look better.&nbsp;&nbsp; I am pleased with my progress.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Since we last met, I worked on my lawn, and started my allergies up.&nbsp; My eyes watered so bad, I didn't put my contacts in.&nbsp; Then the sneezing and sniffling began.&nbsp; Sigh.&nbsp; I'm back to glasses.&nbsp;&nbsp; I'll write more when time becomes available.&nbsp; Now a have a  tepid  Xerox tranning session to attend, in spite of the fact that i train people to use the damn machine all the time.&nbsp; Call it a management issue.&nbsp; With luck I will learn something new to report back about.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Sincerely, Stacy 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I suppose it's another Sunday, but as usuall, the drama twists and turns. My boss sent me a very passive-aggressive email, which tries to berate me. Since I know better, I won't take the bait. I could care less about him being mean-spirited, but he seems to flip out from time to time. Not even he can ruin my good day.   I have some work to do on a project I should have started Friday, but I goofed around, and lost some time. Typical me. If this power point class wasn't necessary, I don't think I'd take it. Enough whinning about it though. The work is do, so its do or don't time.     Song of the Day:      "This Love"    by Maroon 5. Why? I just downloaded the song from iTunes, and it's fresh in my ears. :-)     Thought of the Day:   If people are testing your patience, then 'ef them. They have no power over your life whatsoever.  That, and the best revenge is living a good, productive life that can't be beaten by callous people.    Peace Y'all    
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I wish I wrote yesterday, but I was knee-deep in editing a videotape for my class presentation.  With that being said, I also got my self some contact lenses.  My God, I had no concept of how these things work.  I also did't concieve of how I would blink so much.  I am somewhat annoyed by the process, but the chance to see a whole lot better iwas too appealing to let go of.  It's real nice.  Everything seems much brightere, even at night.  LOL.  Was I missing out on everything?  I know most people can take their vision for granted, but since I am usually as blind as a bat, it made for a better triumph.  It's so nice to see all around.  :-)   Song of the Day:     "Pink Casmere"   by Prince.  It's highly underrated, but a sexy Prince song nonetheless.  it's always good to listen to.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Feeling a little down today, as I desperately search for alternate classes.  I did have plans on leaning new software programs in the fall, but alsa that dream hass been dashed.  After yesterday's post, I should be happier , however, it ain't easy.  :-(  Didn't do much of anything.  I don't feel like it.  I need a day to mope about.    One co-worker didn't show up to work.  She's a mess.  She really needs to get her act together cause she's all no work, and all play.  Must be nice.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hello all,  I was knee deep into a Powerpoint project, however, I should have taken to this task this week-end.  It would have made it smoother to finish.  The project's due on Thursday, so I believe I have the drop on this.  Ha!  Of course there's another project on the way for next week.  It all but assures that I stay in front of the computer working.  I just got an e-mail about the interview I had two weeks ago.  The job opening was "cancelled."  The band for the job had been changed.  I can re-apply when the job is up for grabs again.  That sucks.  I feel like life's trying to hold me hostage.  Perhaps things are happening in a vacumm.  The world is not out to get me.  Not as long as I have the power to create, and the power to know love.  I am invincible.  Truth is, I cannot allow myself to feel defeated because of some setbacks.  Mind you, it's rough sometimes.     Song of the Day:     "Paradise"   by Sade.  Why?  Sade has some of the best songs with the right mix of mellowness and sadness that can push you to feel something good.  Paradise is where I'd love to be if I could.    
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hello all,  I broke my glasses.  I'm so upset!  I'll have to make an appointment for Thursday top get my eyes examined, and a new pair.  Right now I tried using some glue, but that didn't work.  When the opportunity presents itself, I'm getting some contacts, so if I run into problems, I can switch out.    A friend told me that she's having a bad spot with another friend.  She has a solution, and I hope it works out.  Let's hope things stay calm.  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm at work today, contemplating why I didn't use my sick leave today (It's cause I'd waste it).  The library's all silent.  Earlier this girl came in, on a cell phone, and blabbed  ALL  her business.  He man was dumping her for someone else, and she didn't have the sense to carry that conversation elsewhere.  She kept raising her voice, and getting upset.  She'd excuse herself, come back in calm, then raise her voice again.  She did this a few times, until she lfet for good.    I wonder about people who patron the library sometimes.  It's like a bad mood day.  LOL  It is  H-O-T  oustside.  It's so hot I saw the devil outside hailing a cab.  LOLOL!!!!!   Song of This Hot Sweatty Evening:     "Take Me Out"   by Franz Ferdinand.  Why?  The song , while not R & B, is slamming.  I love to hear it.  I've got to get that one for my iTunes collection.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's early.  it's a class day.  Learned about creating business cards today.  I need to get up and walk.  My legs are stiff.  I have to go to work today, to make up for the library being closed on Sunday.  Boy is that fun.  My only consolation is that the library is going to close at 6:00 PM tonight.  I'll more than likely write another entry at work, 'cause nobody wants to be seen at the library on Fridays.  LOL  Misplaced my ring today.  I'll stop by the house before I run to work, and reclaim it.  
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today, I got to play with the color printer.  This was to test it out.  We may not keep it in the library, but it sure is great.  Love it.  I may have to quit my job in order to fulfill my college obligations.  I was was hoping FA would give me more loans, but they gave me work-study instead.  I'll get a job on campus, but I'll more than likely have to get a second job, if they don't add something to the plate.  Sent a letter to the department head of the visual arts dept.  Quite frankly they said my classes would be during the day in the fall, and that's n longer true.  I hope she has a good explanation, 'cause I don't take quitting my job lightly.  I may get irritated at work, but it's still my job, and I'd like to leave because I'm ready to, not because my had is forced.  The students at work don't have the proper paperwork to be on the job, so we had to send the home.  the person who files the paperwork is conviently sick today.  Even worse, I was told she had three weeks to get things straight.  Now I have some students who may be peeved thay may not get their check as planeed.  I hate when that happens.  It puts me in a bad position.  Saw one of my fomer student workers.  He's all tanned and shit from the sun.  He's happy, which is good, and he went about his merry way.  Another SA got an internship, so she won't be hanging around us for a while.  I'm proud of both of them.  Another of my SA, whom I'll call "Drama Mamma," was loafing about.  I spotted her yesterday.  She looked sleepy, and appeared out of sorts.  Gotta get that girl some No-Doze 'fore she falls on her face.  Hopefully she's not in more drama.  She's a sweet girl, I just like to see my students well.     Song of the Day:     "Don't You Want Me?"   by Jody Watley.  It's 80's chic, and brings back memories of teen years.  LOL.  I'm getting up there, and I hope to get to grad scholl next fall.  if I'm bitching about not being there around this time next year, y'all will know I'm pissed.   
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I wrote so little earlier.  There was nothing to say.  i did have to got to the FA office to straighten out any potential mess I may be in, only to learn I don't know how much aid I'm getting for the fall.  it's like a top secret thing where I keep having to guess where thing lie.  I am so tired of these classes messing with me.  It's like a broad conspiricy to make me quit.  Played Powerball today.  I got the numbers from a dream.  LOL sounds silly?  Why not.  Those numers are as random as others.  LOL.  Sides it's fun, for all of five seconds.   Song of the Day:     "How Can I Ease the Pain"   by Lisa Fischer.  I think this song is very sexual, and beautiful.  I wonder if that was intentional?
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm pissed.  I can only pick two classes for the fall semester.  I wanted to take three!  Damn this schelduing.  LOL.  I have to keep my humor up, or else I'd climb the wall.  I don't have much to say right now other than I feel like I've been beaten out of the college system.   
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I took a few days off.  But I guess you could tell by the silenece of my posts.  The holidays were here, and I had a few days off from classes and working.  It felt soooo good.  I slept late, and loafed about.  I planned a cook-out for the fourth, which I did.  I marinated some steaks, and ribs the day before.  I never used a grill before.  I was so naive, I followed the instructions for the charcol, and used only  40 peices .  LOL  I nearly screwed myself BTW that coal burns far faster than I anticipated.    Anyways my mom inisted that my older bro to do something, so he took the cooking aspect away from me, and charred all the meats (even the hotdogs felt the sting of his grilling).  All I did afterwards is make a real a real great pitcher of tea.  It had the right blend of lemon, it was my best tea yet.  Some family members came over and stayed a long long time.  It as nice to see them, and nice to see them gotoo.  LOL   Had a discussion with my Aunt about who to vote for in the comming election.  She doesn't like Kerry 'cause he's for same-sex marriages.  So I'm like you'll vote for Bush.  She's like yeah.  I was turned off by that, but she's entitled to her choices.  I do think she was being willfully ignorant though.  She says same-sex relationships are wrong, but she put an equity on this "sin."  I felt she was not representin.     Song of the Day:     "Crush"   by Zhane.  I love this song because its smooth and elegant.  It also happens to be true for many people.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I took a few days off.  But I guess you could tell by the silenece of my posts.  The holidays were here, and I had a few days off from classes and working.  It felt soooo good.  I slept late, and loafed about.  I planned a cook-out for the fourth, which I did.  I marinated some steaks, and ribs the day before.  I never used a grill before.  I was so naive, I followed the instructions for the charcol, and used only  40 peices .  LOL  I nearly screwed myself BTW that coal burns far faster than I anticipated.    Anyways my mom inisted that my older bro to do something, so he took the cooking aspect away from me, and charred all the meats (even the hotdogs felt the sting of his grilling).  All I did afterwards is make a real a real great pitcher of tea.  It had the right blend of lemon, it was my best tea yet.  Some family members came over and stayed a long long time.  It as nice to see them, and nice to see them gotoo.  LOL   Had a discussion with my Aunt about who to vote for in the comming election.  She doesn't like Kerry 'cause he's for same-sex marriages.  So I'm like you'll vote for Bush.  She's like yeah.  I was turned off by that, but she's entitled to her choices.  I do think she was being willfully ignorant though.  She says same-sex relationships are wrong, but she put an equity on this "sin."  I felt she was not representin.     Song of the Day:     "Crush"   by Zhane.  I love this song because its smooth and elegant.  It also happens to be true for many people.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hello,  Almost didn't write anything, but between switching channels between Iron Chef and Road Rules, I thought I needed to do something positive.  Went grocery shopping today.  Bought things for cooking on the grill tomorrow.  I marinated some steaks, and ribs.  I bout some marinade that is really spicy.  I didn't realize that untl I tasted it.  LOL.    Caught up with a good friennd via phone.  We joked for a while, then went on our seperate ways.     Song of the Day:   Where My Girls At? by 702.  Why?  I just saw the vidoe, and I wanted to hear something that wasn't sad sounding.  LOL 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hello all,  I haven't been myself lately, and at last finals are done.  Last Friday, while driving home, someone started shooting.   A bullet hit my car.  Thankfully I was not shot, but My car was hit.  Called 911, filed a report, called the insurance company.  All this time finals are going on.   Well, I was shaken, but not destroyed.   I finished my last final yesterday.  When I checked my grades this evening, I got a big fat  98 .  Yes!!!!!!  I'll post more later, but for now I gotta go.   ---Stacy  P.S.  Special thnks to Nicole for posting a comment.  I've been away a few days, but I still love reading responses.  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I don't know what came over me today.  I just wanted a latte.  I felt the need for one, and scapped together four bucks for a tall, iced latte with soy milk.  It tastes great.  LOL.  Thnakfully I have my tank gassed, so I don't have to worry about it.    If only Latte's were fuel.  I have a quiz to take, one I'm so not prepared for, so I might as well get that misery over.  Completed one of my finals, now I have a couple more to go, and that's just crazy!!!!   I'm tired, and someone who is not handicapped keeps buzzing to be let through the handicapped doors.  That's just lazy.  I'm spent.  Let me take my test. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The title's a lie, but it was sure funny.  LOL.  I did watch a lot of the Food Network a lot this week-end.  I should have got some extra calories from watching it.  Guilty pleasueres are so funny.  I watched a clam chowder contest, a BBQ contest, and a resturant that uses charcoal grills only to cook its food.  Some of the chowder looked so rich.  They used heavy cream and stuff.  Pretty cool.  You have to love your chowder to go there though.  LOL  Today it rained.  Lightly at first, then it rained some more, this time a little more rushed.    I hate driving in the rain.  Makes me nervous.  'sides I drive like an old man when the weather gets on the wet side.  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hello,  It looks a little stormy outside.  In fact, a tropical depression is off the coast of SC.  It's not supposed to hit us, but it's close enough to give SC some rain, wind, and whatever else it could drop on us.  The library's freezing, but this time I brought a sweater.  Clever me.  I went to the kitchen in this dump, to add some more water in my cup, and there was this inscet in the sink.  It looked like a spiny caterpillar.  Needless to say, I went for bottled water.     Today is ok, because Sundays are the easiest to start.  It's just me and a student holding down the fort.  It is also finals time, and I said I was doing my final on Thomas Eakins.  That meant scanning multiple iamgeas out of these big annoying art books.  The scanner is so petit compared to the book, so It took some considerable time to get things done proper.  Nonetheless, I have multiple images to work with.  I would still have to find some images from Henry O. Tanner, and Winslow Homer, since bopth artists were Eakins' contemporaries.  I'll do those via web.  I'm bound to hit something.   Aside from my finals, the job is even tempered this week.   Same old drama goin on.  One co-worker called to say she was "in transit," meaning she's show up.  We never saw her.  That was Monday.  LOL  I suppose she's having fun somewhere, or thowing herself a pity party.  So long as the day remains quiet.   I did, however have a dog of a time with the FA office.  All I needed to know is when was my aid going to be posted to my account.  I got a song and dance about I won't know until the semester starts, which is beyond reasoning.  The classes needed to be paid now, since I had the cash, and the deadline is Aug 6th to settle up your bill, or you will be bounced out of the classes you signed up for.    Sometimes the fact that you're at a higher learning institutionis ironic, becasue so many people there seem to be lacking any knowldge.  Did I mention that those of us who applied for scholarships, will not be notified as to whether we've recieved them or not  until the 6th.  It's a pretty shitty postion to be in.  I buckled down, and paid for any expenses I needed to.  It means no Lattes for some time, since I am, in effect, without some cash to carry myself around.  Thank God I can lan on my family.  It's times like this that you need people around you.     Song of The Day:     "I'm So Lonesome I Could Cry"    By Cassandra Wilson.  Why?  It's a remake done in a great way.  You can feel the sadness in the song.   Good rainiy day song.  Be well,  ---Stacy   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>