<Blog>

<date>28,February,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Still horribly fat. Done absolutely nothing about it .. more excuses why I didn't do it. I'm kinda like not caring anymore about how I look but then when I go out .. I feel so bad because I'm SOOOOOOOOOO FAT!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! and everyone else is so tiny and beautiful .. and they have a guy or guys look at them. I look like a mom (a 30 - 40 year old mom who's had like 5 kids). I'm only 25 and look like this already .. what happens when I get there? Well I won't be a mom because no man will ever want me .. right .. who would want to sleep with something like this, case in point my ex boyfriend. So yeah I think there's no reason for me to lose weight. If I DO lose weight that would mean I'm changing who I am and i don't want to do that. What if I meet a guy and i'm all tiny and nice but then when my weight goes up, he'll dump me (because real love like in the movies does not exist). I am so sick of living like this. I am so sick of life. 

						
</post>

<date>15,February,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   My first entry into my weight loss journal. Woo hoo!  Anyway it's really early in the morning, and I guess I've been 3 or 4 days into my latest 'start'. I had a few mis-starts (okay, more than a few!). I usually restart everything when I do something 'bad' - like not exercise for more than a week, or eat way too much for a few days in a row. I guess that might be sabotaging my progress but I'd like a really clean start. I've been doing great for the past few days though.  So now I'm at 165lbs, again. I was 155lbs about 6 months ago but because of a few dozen things which went wrong from July 2003, I've started piling on the pounds. I won't explain what those are because it really is for a whole different blog. Ideally I'd like to get to 135lbs, but I've not been that weight since I was 15. I'd be happy with 145lbs which was where I was about 5 years ago. You can actually chart my weight like that. It goes up and down between the periods but every 5 years I put on 5 more pounds, not a good sign I'm sure.   So what's my plan? Basically it's like this ..   Meal plan  Breakfast - Special K with milk, some fruit Snack - fruit or Power Bar/granola bar Lunch - as usual Snack - same as above Dinner - protein shake or Special K ** Special - one 'bad' item (ice cream, choc, cookies)   Workouts      - 45 min treadmill (with 10min warmup/cooldown) .. 4 - 6x per week    - toning (arms, legs) - 3 - 4x per week  Not a very good plan I'm sure. The main problem I'm having is that my mom is a spectacular cook and she loves to cook so there's always a huge quantity of food around. So that's why I have lunch (or dinner) where I can have what she cooks .. but only one meal. On top of that I have a really thin sister who just loves to buy and eat chocolates and junk food. I hang out with her a lot and as such .. I eat them too! I'm looking to lose 5lbs every 5 weeks, and to get to 155lbs by the end of 10 weeks .. although I think with some effort I can do that sooner.  

						
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Today was a good day .. I've only eaten some sushi for lunch .. and if I don't break down and eat lots of bad things for the rest of the evening, I will have a 'good' day.   I'm not feeling well today, cramps & stomachache ... but i guess it'll help motivate me to do better.   I do not like what I see in the mirror, or when I put on my clothes to go out. Nothing appealing or non-depressive.  

						
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   My actual weight is around 78 kg (approx. 172lbs) .. and 40 - 41% body fat, 40% body water.  I did pretty well today .. did not eat anything bad and had really small portions. Munched on some pistachios though (although def. not more than a handful incl. shells). My only one 'bad' thing of the day was a chocolate shortbread biscuit a couple of minutes ago.   Small progress, but it is still some progress in the right direction. I WILL lose at least 20lbs. by the end of July.  

						
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I can't believe that I MADE myself get this DIGUSTINGLY FAT sooooooooo fast! 6 months and 20lbs. .... wow!!!! That's got to be a record .. now it'll take me .. hmm ... 12 - 18 months to get it off. I DO NOT like this weight gain, then weight loss ... then all over again. It's not healthy and it's horrible for the body (plus when you put it back on, it's actually MORE fat than before .. how this works, i don't know). I need to change my behaviour, I need to have a point where I go STOP and re-evaluate my weight when that happens. Like say if I gain 5lbs. I can go, okay .. now I need to lay off the sweets and step up the exercise. And not just let myself gooooooooooooooooooo for like half a year. Bloody irreversible damage to my body!   I need to buck up NOW. I am so not going to be the fat girl anymore. The fat girl DOES NOT get anything. The fat girl IS NEVER happy (truly, completely 100% happy). The fat girl never gets the guy. The fat girl never has an exciting life. The fat girl NEVER wins!   So right now I'm 80kg, 177lbs, 12.5 stones, Size 16 UK. I'm going on a super crash diet tomorrow. No sweets/crisps AT ALL (if you have one, you just have to have more!), NO meals for 1 week (only have protein shakes or bars .. breakfast as usual - cereal or yogurt), no snacking AT ALL (again, do not start even ONE), LOTS of exercise (interval training .. 30 min at least .. every single day; toning .. every single day).   I AM OBESE! I AM SO FAT IT'S UNHEALTHY. NO MORE LIVING IN DENIAL! Almost half of me is composed of fat, how disgusting! I am most definitely a thin person (I have a small frame, NOT a big boned girl like everyone used to say ALL MY LIFE!) .. so I will get thin by July 2004. I'll lose 15kg, 33lbs, 2.5 stones and 2 - 3 dress sizes ... 65kg, 144lbs, 10 stones, Size 10 - 12 UK!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! 5 kg a month? Okay then ... it's a do or die thing. I cannot live like this for the rest of my life. I do not ever want to be the fat, insecure person anymore. I don't want to be the girl who'll always be ignored by guys. I don't want to be the girl with the pretty face but horrible, fat, ugly body. I don't want to be insecure. I don't want to wear Size 16 clothes.  

						
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I finally bought the digital scale & BF/BW monitor. It's sooooo cool. No more standing on the scale, adjusting my stance .. and seeing different values at different times of the day (5lbs. difference? puhleeze).   Unfortunately I'm now at 80kg and 44% bodyfat (i think .. well, it's above 40%) which is SO not good. My sis is at 55kg and 19%, which is perfect. Ouch .. so so horrible. I don't want to be this fat anymore.  I've been so depressed lately .. i have an issue with a certain part of my body and it's consuming all my thoughts. I want to go back 6 months ago and change it, or not make such a stupid decision.  

						
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I've been progressing. Eating less but I'm still eating 'bad' foods. I'm cutting them out slowly.   Anyway I can actually fit into my 33" hip hugger jeans .. which is a great thing! I mean that means I MUST be less than the dreaded 35" at my actual waist, over the belly button .. and should be even smaller at my natural waist, when you bend to one side there's a crease .. that's your natural waist. It wasn't super tight, I could breathe but there isn't much space in the waist band to put like a couple of fingers in :)   I'm still at 175lbs according to this really buggy scale, will get new scale by next week - digital with BF calc. I have a really bloated tummy nowadays .. all fat, probably .. but I haven't had my period .. coming to 3 months now. And NO I am not pregnant.   Have to work even harder! I need to get to 150lbs (25lbs!!!!!!!!!!) in 4 months. I'll be happy losing 4lbs. a month (1lbs. a week, total loss 16lbs. to 159lbs) ... will fall short of target but who cares as long as I'm never this fat again.  

						
</post>

<date>19,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Make that 175lbs. I am ACTUALLY 175lbs. How horrible!!!! I have a long(er) way to go.  I'm doing kinda good today. Did not eat excessively just yet. Will do my workout in the evening, not such a good thing .. compared to a.m. workouts, but it's better than nothing. I'll try to do 60min treadmill + 15min bike + 15min bike .. plus some easy toning for arms & abs.   I have my eye on a digital scale with bodyfat calculator. The price is a little steep $350, so I will have to forgo my DVDs next month. Sacrifice for my health/weight :) Should be cool to track my weight, bodyfat .. although I bet it'll be discouraging at the moment. The last time I measured my bodyfat I was 33% (at 150lbs.) .. and then 44% (at 160 - 180lbs) .. so now I could possibly be 50% bodyfat .. WOWZA!!! Although through the HealthCentral tool (which uses your height, weight and body measurements) my bodyfat is only 23%. I wish!   I was reading my old posts from a diet forum, from 1998 - 1999, and boy .. wish I could go back and kick myself in the head/ass. Because I was 140 - 147lbs, 38-27-38 and I thought I needed to get down to 125lbs!!! Stupid, stupid, stupid! But there were lots & lots of external/environmental factors then that contributed to that really distorted body image.  

						
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I thought I did really well today. I'm not doing great with the sleep on time thing though .. I prefer to stay up at night when I can have all the peace and quiet I need (to do work, watch DVDs, workout). So I've been sleeping at about 4 - 6 am and waking up at about 12 - 2 pm for the past two or three days.   My diet has been horrible. I still eat a little chocolate or cookies or chips or ice-cream each day. It's not only just one each day .. it's like a few of them at once! I mean I should  be cutting each and every single one of them out of my diet .. but no, I'm still at it. I feel so bad about that. A new day tomorrow and we'll see. I think I should just cut it all off .. completely, so I won't be tempted. When you reach for one .. you just have to go for another & another & another. Argh!   Today I did an amazing workout. I did 60 minutes on the treadmill (5 min warmup, 5 min cooldown). Then later did about 15 minutes on the bike, very high rpms .. so burned about 150 cals. I don't know why but the bike makes me feel like I work harder .. I'm hitting my THR totally. While on the treadmill, that 60 minutes I only burned 200 calories!!! The bike was like quarter that and almost the same cals. Maybe it's not accurate? Although not sure which one. I use the treadmill on an incline and I can feel myself working it .. but it's so discouraging to look at the cals and just see 200 in one whole hour! Tomorrow I hope to continue with the cardio like today and do some toning with the tapes/VCDs I have.   I'm STILL 170lbs. Stuck at it for the moment, which is really really horrible. I mean about a week ago I was 165 and moaning about it and now I'm 170 (and above) and ... it's so depressive to think about. I'm back to this point where I said I would never be again (because of ANY man) and sure enough ... it happened yet again, for basically the same reason!   I'm so tempted to start hitting the laxatives (Epsom Salts) again. I used to do that A LOT because I really thought it made me lose weight ... and it did work. I got down to about 155 the past year.    

						
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I can't believe that I could be 175lbs now! I mean 165 was reasonable, by the fit of my clothes .. but then in a matter of days it went to 170 then finally 175. When I wake up & weigh myself it's about 170 - 173lbs .. and then later in the day it'll be 175. How does a person put on 10lbs. in a week .. or in like 3 days?! What is going on?  I need to get a new scale but this scale is accurate (my sis is consistently 110 - 115lbs so I use her to test it). I wish I could be closer to that .... 120lbs - 125lbs. is THE perfect weight for my height but I'm trying to be realistic here.  This is what I ate today .. wasn't much, I'd think Breakfast - pancakes, small (3/4) with maple syrup (little), ice cream (1/4 cup) Lunch - protein shake Tea - stir fry Chinese noodles (1 cup, max) Dinner - chicken sandwich (using white bread & sandwich meat), some mayo & lettuce (1 sandwich) Snacks - Viennese butter cookies (3 x 40cals), raisins (1 tiny/small box), satay fish (3/4 pkt)  No workouts but did make a little hike at the building site of the house. I'll probably do some weight training (arms) in awhile. My legs still ache from the workout I did 2 days ago.   I need to improve on my diet. Absolutely NO cookies anymore! And drink more protein shakes .. like replace both lunch & dinner. I really don't need all those calories.     

						
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I thought I did pretty well today  1. Slept at 3 a.m 2. Woke up at 10:30am 3. Workout (am) at 10:45am, treadmill for 30 minutes 4. Breakfast right after workout - cereal (1 cup) w/raisins 5. Lunch (at 4pm though) - usual 6. Snacks - cookies (4 .. 40cals each), fruits - mango, fruit juice, chips (1 small bag), choc (Wispa 1/3bar) .... throughout the day. 7. Workout (pm, after 5pm) - Cindy Crawford's Shape Your Body, Workout 1 (did about 3/4 of it though, the legwork totally killed me!) 8. Dinner - average, less than usual .. at about 8pm  So .. hmm a good start I would have to say. I think I know where my exact problem is .. towards the end of the day, I get these cravings or I just eat because I'm bored (or eat while I watch TV). So I have to keep watching that. But truly, my snacking today was really on the low side .. I'm usually way way way overboard .. so i am super happy about today.   The only bad news is that I stepped on the scale and I'm actually 170lbs (in the morning). Gross!!!! Then when I stepped on it later in the day .. i was over 170. Dammit, how can I put on so much weight in less than a couple of days? I have like this huge Buddha belly nowadays .. it's not funny .. it's so distended, probably bloated with water or something.  I want to go on a juice/liquid fast .. but .. i never have the motivation to do that! Argh! I think I need to take some drastic action soon.   

						
</post>

<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   My mom has been on my case A LOT lately about losing weight - she keeps on giving me these looks when I walk past (kinda like a scrunched up, scruntinizing gaze .. without saying anything!) and talks about losing weight by using all these fad products. I don't want to do that, I know that I just need to exercise and watch (a little) of what I eat. She is right about one thing though .. and that is cutting out sugars, sweets. So .. I told her, instead of buying those things for me (which would never work, we're talking infomercials here) .. give me the money at the end of a certain period if I hit a certain weight. So we agreed, that by my 26th birthday at the end of July, if I'm 150lbs .. I win a reward from her which is about $500. If not, I have to give $500 to her. It's not a huge amount and I don't need the money but it's something .. for someone like me who has absolutely no motivation at all. I needed a challenge .. so here it is. This is going to be an interesting 4 months/16 weeks .. I think I can hit 150lbs by the end of June, 1lbs per week (3,500 calories less per week, 500 calories less per day).   My plan 1. Sleep every night - 1 to 2 am latest 2. Wake up - 9 - 10am 3. Workout (am) once you wake up (10 min, 20 min, 30 min .. whatever, just workout .. cardio preferable) 4. Breakfast - after workout (before 11am), complete breakfast .. cereal, milk, fruit 5. Lunch - as usual  6. Snacks - 1 or 2 'bad' items only, as a reward. Protein shakes. Fruits. 7. Workout (pm) - toning if done cardio in morning (arms, legs .. alternate every day) 8. Dinner - BEFORE 7 or 8pm. Absolutely nothing after that time.  9. Cut out the constant chips & chocs, no more goodie drawer to fill up every time you go out.  10. Go by the fit of your clothes NOT the weight on the scale. Only step on it once a week.   Wish me luck! 

						
</post>

<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   To some people that must be horrifying but to me .. that's a safe zone. if I ever hit a Size 16 UK (bottom) then I know that I'm in trouble.  I'm 165lbs now .. it's stagnating thank god. I guess this will always be my weight whenever I never really watch what I eat or exercise. It's my natural weight.   I went to Dorothy Perkins today (it's a British clothing store) and decided to try on some clothes. I took a pair of pants in Size 14, then a pair of jeans in Size 16 because I thought I'd be that big ...  Was I surprised to discover, that I'm really not that big. The Size 16 jeans were hanging way too loose, and they were hip huggers. Very good news for someone who has an hourglass figure - boobs, hips in proportion .. relatively smaller waist. Hip huggers are never good IF you have hips.   The Size 14 fit just right. I'm probably at the mid to high end range of Size 14, so within the month or two would like to get down to the low-end of Size 14 (155lbs?)  Then finally .. get down to a Size 12, my perfect size at about 145 - 148lbs.   Btw US sizes are either 2 or 4 down from UK sizes, depending on who you talk to. So .. a Size 14 UK is a Size 12 or 10 US. 

						
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Hmm .. feel a little better today than when I posted that last one! I updated my website today, with my progress details and pictures. I'm getting there with the diet, but I have to add in the exercise.  The weight is creeping up on me though, I'm about 168lbs if I readily admit it .. but sometimes I get on the scale and it reads about 164lbs .. so I'll say about 165 - 168lbs to be safe. I do not want to be 170lbs again. Actually I do not want to be this big anymore. Sometimes I wonder how the hell I could just put on 10lbs and not notice it!   I will work out today. Do something about it. Don't just sit on your a** anymore.  

						
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Umm .. my weight is now 167 - 168 lbs in the morning, and tapers off to 169 - 170 throughout the day. I caught a glimpse of myself in the mirror and I look so .. disgusting. Really, honestly, disgusting. I always thought I looked okay but today I took a good look at myself .. and I'm not okay. I never quite stood in front of the mirror and took a good look, i haven't done that in awhile ... and wow, I am back to being such a big gross fat girl.   I have not been working out, at all. I keep on saying, I'm too tired from a long day at work .. and put it off for another day when 'I've got enough sleep' (or something). How pathetic. I know that once I start working out, even 3x a week .. it'll help. I'm now about 40% - 41% bodyfat which is really truly gross. Although I have always been chunky as hell - even when I was at 145lbs I was 30% or so. So .. hmm .. i don't know what to do with myself. I am so sick of being fat and it's such an easy solution. Eat less (which is working btw) and exercise.    Plus I find out that a Size 12 US is NOT a good thing. It's sometimes a Size 14 UK but usually it's a Size 16 .. which is so not right. When my lingerie arrives, I doubt I'll be able to fit and that'll be depressive as hell.  My bum and upper thighs, back of my thighs .. are like THE most horrible things I have ever ever seen. They're gargantuan. Not to mention my almost bat-wings. I keep on torturing my body like this .. put it on, take it off, put in on but even worse (fat distribution) .. repeat.   I don't know where my energy went. When I lost it the first time, all I did was work out every single day - walk throughout the neighbourhood .. at least 20 - 30 minutes. Then later in the afternoon do my old staple of Cindy C's Shape Your Body (the first one which is not a favorite of most). And I lost it all, which is all this right now in about 2 months.   The next milestone is 165lbs .. I'll try to reach that by mid-May .. solidly hit 165lbs. Then on to the next 4 or 5lbs. I am so discouraged and inspired in a way .. I saw this woman's blog .. and she went from 165lbs to 128lbs in 8 weeks .. 35% bodyfat to 18%! Wowza. That's 5lbs per week .. is that even possible?!  

						
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Hmm .. am down to 165 - 166lbs on the old scale. Did not use the digital scale .. how odd that i get different results with the digital one - according to where I put it on the floor or in the bathroom. I've been eating well. Am so proud of myself. I haven't been binge-ing on stuff at all. Just two - three meals plus little snacks (healthful snacks) in between .. I do treat myself to a little something from time to time, but it's not excessive.  I tried on some of my old clothes. I have a Size 10 (UK) pants, that I used to love to wear and now I can't fit it past my upper thighs. I have a beautiful black shift dress, the perfect black dress which I could fit in last when I was about 145 - 150lbs in 1998 (when I went to Paris) .. and now I can't fit it around my butt and boobs. Finally, a pair of Size 12 UK pants that I can't zip up .. I can get it past my thighs, hips but it just won't close! Maybe another 10lbs for that one.   So okay .. now I'm 165 - 170lbs, Size 12 US, Size 14 UK. My waist size is either 34" (ugh!) or  33" .. gross, I know. My hips and top are 42" or so. I have to face the facts that I AM a fat girl, obese, unhealthy .. I keep on justifying it you know .. like at least my guy (then) finds me attractive even like this or it's not so bad unlike some people or I don't really want it enough. But I am that bad, that far along .. I am so heading for an early grave if I keep on putting weight like this.   Next milestone, in 2 months - June .. that sounds reasonable, would be 155lbs, 32" waist, 40" hips/top. Hopefully a Size 10 US & Size 12 UK. I am supposed to be able to fit into those clothes - 12 UK pants and shift dress but I think as I kept on putting on weight (yo-yo) my body composition gets worse .. so more fat. Will need a little more time to tone up. Now is the time to step up with the workouts.    Third milestone in another 2 months - August 2004 .. would be 145lbs, 30 - 31" waist, 38 - 39" hips/top. That's where I was before. And by then I should be able to fit into all my OLD clothes .. Size 12 UK just nicely and perfectly. I think at that time I could fit into a Size 10 UK but it would be a little snug.   The FINAL 10lbs, will take 4 months .. to really really tone it all up. So by the end of the year I'll have my perfect body. I didn't like the feeling of NOT being able to fit into all those clothes. I look at it and I go .. was I really that small? And when I was at that point I was always thinking I was SO fat and ugly and needed to lose another 10lbs to be 'perfect' .. how stupid.   Then .. then .. the most important part is maintaining my weight. No more overeating when I hit a crisis and 6 months down the line find out that I'm fat AGAIN! Never never never never again.   I am so glad to be seeing some progress. Yaay! Imagine if I actually did put in more effort with the workouts .. then there would be more results.  

						
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Day three and I ate a tad more .. 3 meals, not much snacking although there was choc in it (broke my promise again). I feel better about myself since I'm not snacking all the time on junk food or whatever. Although the meals today make me feel like a bad day, they are normal by everyone else's standards but I don't feel right eating 'so much'.   Lunch (4pm)  - rice (1 cup max) with sambal, 1/4 egg + choc milk  Tea (5 - 6pm)  - roti canai with kurma  Dinner (9 pm)  - pizza, 9" or 12" thin/homemade crust .. chicken & garlic (3 slices of varying size) - Coke (1 can)  Snacks (after 10pm)  - chocolates (4 cubes of Swedish choc) - Mentos (some) - Digestives biscuit (1)  The pizza thing at the end of the day was a little overboard .. 3 slices but at the very least they were NOT Pizza Hut sized. And the chocolates .. hmm ...   I weighed myself this morning and the old scale said 167 - 168lbs which is amazing. The digital scale says 77.1 - 77.2kg which is around there or 170lbs (depends whether it's 2.14 lbs or 2.2 lbs per 1 kg). I am so happy to be BELOW 170! Now my next mini goal is 160lbs by the end of May. It's quite a lot, but I think I can do it!  

						
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Day two on being serious about losing weight (finally!). I've had a motivational burst because I've recently bought some new lingerie and want to look amazing in it. They're supposed to be one-size fits all but according to the measurements, I'm either at the higher end of it or I won't fit into it! So yes, I DO have to lose weight and at least get back to 155 which was where I was about 8 months ago, then we'll work it out as we go along.   My weight fluctuates between 77.1 to 77.5kg, but yesterday it was a little over 78kg after lunch. So about 170 - 173lbs. Way too much! I'm always like this .. I gain 15 - 20lbs in like nothing, then I go .. wow, where did it come from? It's so unimaginable sometimes.    My diet has improved. I read an article in Oxygen magazine, which has way too buff women .. but it is right the way they eat. They eat every couple of hours - 9 am, 12 pm, 3 pm, 6 pm, 9 pm. Small meals and snacks. I'm trying that .. and hopefully will stick to drinking protein shakes for my snacks. So far so good, they fill me up.   I'll focus on the diet first and then incorporate a little exercise. So far nothing actually .. wow, I haven't exercised in a while. I do some toning for my arms and legs once in awhile, but it's really not enough. I need to do more cardio and interval training, I see great results with that.  

						
</post>

<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   hmm .. not that much progress, but I am now hovering between 76.9 - 77.2 kg in the mornings. That's about 1 kg from the late March or early April. So it is progress. I NEED to get to 165lbs in 2 weeks at the most, not too far off .. about 3 - 4 lbs.   No workouts though .. horrible! Trouble sleeping lately but then I guess I should workout at night when I can't sleep, like I used to before?  Eating is so-so .. still have some junk food but reaching for healthier alternatives most of the time. Snack on pistachios, pumpkin seeds, almonds (never more than a half a handful), a smidgen of chocolate, granola bars .. what not.   My goal body .. is oddly a video game character. I play it a lot .. SSX Tricky, snowboarding .. and there's a character Zoe who's 5'5" and 135lbs and nicely muscled. That's the image I have in my mind as my goal body because it is acceptable, same height and all ... and that was a weight when I felt 'my best'.     

						
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I am now, actually 170lbs. How amazing! I guess it's because I'm not so bloated anymore with water retention or whatever after not having my period for 2 - 3 months! So I'm on the right track, I'll get down to 150 no problem. I've been eating pretty well .. although I have not cut out all the junk food 100%. Instead of eating a couple of dozen, I take one and enjoy/savour it. Not such a bad plan at the moment. No workouts though .. which is just ugh!  

						
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I haven't posted here in awhile.  The lowest weight I got down to was 163lbs. last weekend, because I was sleeping too much and eating too little - heartbreak, literally. The lowest of lows. I need more weeks like that, just so I can get down to a lower weight. But it's progress and at least now I know I can do it. I'm hovering about 163 - 165lbs right now. On the digital scale it's reading about 76kg and 39% BF. Lovely.   But .. the past two days, I have been horrible. Eating 'right' again meaning 3 meals a day and an ice cream cone, chocs as treats. Gotta stop.   I was looking through MY old pictures. From my trips and such .. and I was struck with  how stupid  I completely was. There was this one time we took a trip to Bali, I can't recall the year but I did write at the back of the picture - 137lbs. and in all the pictures I fuzzed out my face with a pen, totally blacked it out. And also did these huge circles over my breasts, stomach and thighs and labelling them  fat, sausage thighs  or  huge thick stomach roll, gross!  and such things. I had such animosity for my body, it was unbelievable and when I look at that picture now .. I look so healthy and small. Although I think even though I am older, my face does look better now for some reason. Maybe I AM more comfortable with myself right now overall compared to then and it comes out.   But yes, I  want  to get back down to that weight and be able to fit into those short shorts. I need to wake up. I've been fat (above 150lbs) for the past 4 years. Coming up to 5 years. My highest weight was 175 (this January) and the lowest was 155 (early 2003), not counting the 145 that I started from back in late 2000. So yeah I don't want to be the fat girl any longer.   Time to take absolute drastic action. I think if I really hit it I CAN hit 150lbs (my goal for my challenge with my mom) by the end of July. And to definitely continue on after that until I get down to 145lbs, where I was before. Wish me luck.   

						
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Failing at .. everything.  Today on waking up, weigh 78.1kg (digital in bathroom, twice) with BF% of 41.3%.  On old scale, weigh 170lbs-ish. Twice, as well.  Not good. Where did 5lbs come from? Where did 1kg come from?! Do not look good at all. I don't like how I look anymore. I thought I look & felt so great this weekend but apparently it was all just in my head. Disappointing.  

						
</post>

<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I am now back to 165lbs, on the old scale. Completely dead center on 165! I'm ecstatic. Although on the damned digital scale it still reads 77.2kg on the bathroom tile. I feel better about myself, about how things fit .. and I can see the curve of my waist vs my hips REALLY coming back.   So not sure what's up with the digi scale, maybe it uses a different calculation for kgs vs lbs? I doubt it. . I mean it must be progress since that old scale, in the same spot, used to read 175 a few weeks/months ago. And my sister, who's the yardstick because she has a constant weight always tests it out and it reads the same for her ... so .. okay I AM 165lbs!  I think it's good progress to see that I've gone from 175lbs to 165lbs pretty quickly (i think). Imagine how fast it'll all go if I start working out properly? So 155lbs here I come in about 2 months!    I've been eating great, although at night I get the munchies. Nowadays I reach from some wheat crackers, instead of chips or chocolates .. so that's good. I only give myself one chocolate item a day .. which is either a snack size Snickers bar or a choc pudding handi-pack. And I only eat one - two meals a day, no dinner .. not really. Maybe that's why I've been snacking late at night? I'll have to watch that.   Btw I haven't posted in my weight loss blog for quite awhile, but since the last post .. my lingerie arrived in the post about a week ago. And I look AMAZING in it! Even the one-size fits all one. I didn't think I could look that good honestly. I think all women should get some sexy lingerie .. just for themselves because it's so wonderful to know that you CAN be sexy no matter what your weight is.  

						
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I went out and finally tried on some swimsuits .. and boy, was it disappointing. There were only Speedos and now apparently we have bikinis Speedos .. they weren't around a couple of years ago! Obviously I didn't even touch those and went for the one piece suits .. which umm .. were ugh. The one I fit best in was a 38 but it then was baggy in the bottom and my top was all squished up. Plus it had this whole shorts thing going on instead of a high leg cut, and .. it made me look like a beach ball. Not kidding. Another one I tried, to get more coverage supposedly is something one would wear when they want to boogie board .. you know .. black suit .. covers from neck to knees. But .. I look like a whale in that one. So I don't know. Right now I feel so icky and don't think I'll get a swimsuit until I lose weight, which most definitely will not be within the next 2 weeks. Why aren't there anything classic, flattering to someone who's curvy .. or fat, okay I'm fat .. I admit it. I mean what do people who are really fat do? Where do they find suits? Where are they hiding? I wanna join up.   And went shopping for shorts and stuff and I love those boarder shorts, which are so cute with their prints and such .. but umm .. not very nice on me at the moment. My thighs are horrendous. And I can't fit into any kind of normal thing. I tried on a LARGE Jill Stuart tiny t .. and .. it was obscene, to say the least. LARGE!!! Went to this little store that sells all these casual stuff and tried on their largest size - a "9" which was supposed to either be a 10 or 12 UK (8 or 10 US) .. which is SO laughable .. the largest! And hah .. the good thing is that i fit in the pants - my waist does .. but my hips & butt .. nada, so we know what the problem area is :) Btw it does work, that thing where you put the waistband of the pants around your neck .. basically your neck circumference is equal to the length of the pants, flat .. if you don't want to try the pants on - got that from Queer Eye! So in the end went and grabbed some shorts from the "men's" side .. i put that in quotes because I can't believe men can be that small. I tried an xl and then a large and the large fit me kinda right except in the areas where men differ from women .. the waist doesn't cut in and it's all baggy and whatever. But nah, I'm not gonna wear a men's large!!!   You know what, I honestly hope that when I lose weight I'll go down a cup size or a band size or something .. because big boobs are SUCH A BANE! They're worse than big thighs. I mean I know my thighs are huge but I have no problems pulling the suits past my hips and thighs .. but never the boobs. Ugh!! And when my boobs go down .. the hips follow .. it's so freakin' consistent. If I'm a 42", like now .. hips are exactly that as well. My "normal" measurement is about 38" .. it's like 4" down but what a difference that makes apparently. And my waist is about 8 - 10" less than either one, which is a good thing I think .. but could I just not be a larger scale of what I want to be?   So .. hmm .. I have to scrap plans of actually going in the water at the moment. I'll see in 2 weeks whether I've lost weight enough or whatever. If not, I'll be stuck in the sauna or the spa all day instead of by the pool.   I'm now 170lbs btw .. about 77 - 77.5 kg. Very very very large and heavy. I'm working on a three month plan now, totally go for broke like I did last time. Three months, as planned to get down to 150 at least.  

						
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Hmm .. am still horribly overweight 168 - 172 lbs. And .. I have that vacation coming up where I have to be in a swimsuit .. because what else are you supposed to do at a seaside resort? No swimsuit yet but I am dreading shopping for it totally. I know I'm huge and plus size by any standard, and here .. pfft .. it's worse since the sizes run so small anyways. My hips are at the very least 40 - 41" which is HUGE .. and let's not mention my thighs or my waist or whatever. I mean no matter how proportionate I am, it doesn't matter .. I'm big. Look at how shopping for undies went .. I just couldn't find something that would fit me right and hopefully the stuff I got off eBay would work better (and cheaper too). So what chances would I have with a swimsuit? I want to swim and windsurf and kayak and parasail and all that fun stuff you do half naked (which I LOVE to do, am such a water baby) but .. I'll keep on thinking about my gross thighs exposed and stuff like that! Argh! I think I'd look amazing in one of those classic suits like 50s style, Marilyn Monroe style .. don't you think? :)   I was reading a magazine earlier today and there was these stats of how Australian women changed over the years - an Aussie mag. And of course, there was one about their weights and stats and such. So the 'average' Aussie woman is 68kg and has so & so centimetres for their waist or hips. But, I'm 10 kgs over average .. does that NOT tell me something? Also the US has this the average American woman is 5'4" and 145lbs. I'm like 20 lbs over that! Ouch! So ... is there ever proof that I'm overweight, then all that is it. I WAS average but now I'm not anymore.   But .. it's wonderful that I've heard of these girls who lose 50 lbs. and look AMAZING. One major case in point was this girl who lost 50 lbs. and in the end won the latest America's Next Top Model II. And you know I'm not past that point where I can't do anything about it or change it. The body is a wonderful thing and it CAN bounce back. So yup, will try to get down 50 lbs, as these people have done. A year will do for that, don't you think?   

						
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I didn't think swimsuit season would be coming so soon! Suddenly today all plans were made, flights were booked and we'll be off in mid July for a vacation. It's not too long, but long enough .. 4 nights, 3 days in a beautiful resort. So I have to go shopping for a new swimsuit and hopefully will not look that horrible in it!   My weight has stagnated to about 165 - 170lbs. which is not good. I have 22 days to lose 22 lbs .. hah .. i wish! 1 lbs. a day would be such a miracle and something I so need but it's so unrealistic. I'd settle for 5 - 10 lbs. so get working! No kidding .. I want to lounge by the pool and swim as much as I want.  Eating has going pretty well. Not too much of anything, but I need to work out to tone up a whole lot. Wish me luck!  

						
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Back to 78.6kg .. this morning. Yuck! 1 - 2 kgs in about 2 weeks. Amazing aren't I? Too bad it's a gain and not a loss. Back to crash dieting.  

						
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Woke up this morning, stepped on the scale and it was 169 - 170lbs and 78kg on digital scale. Yuck! I'm supposed to be at least 68kg (which is fat as well) .. and really should only be 45 - 55 kg! I can't imagine that. I have an extra one half of a whole person. I weigh more than a man, a man who's much taller than me.    At least it scared me into really moving my butt. I've been exercising pretty regularly and upping the duration and intensity for the past 3 days. So today I hit 45 minutes on the treadmill, did some crunches and very light arms, legs. And I did it in the morning! Which is such a miracle. The doing at least 10min per day thing works. In the end I don't only do 10 minutes, by the time I hit that mark .. I think it's more worth it to go to 15 .. then 20 .. then 25 .. then 30 .. and on & on! So yeah it's a good plan, tricking myself that way :)   Now, I have to watch what I eat. Honestly once you exercise, you rethink it before you put something in your mouth. You go .. I just worked my a** off on the treadmill for about an hour and if I eat this or this, it'll negate all that. At least that's how it is for me :) I need to make a habit of this.   Back to 155lbs within 2 months. I did it last year so should be a snap. Then .. 4 lbs each month, and voila .. by the end of 2004, you can have a new start with your new body.      And I so want a buff body. I keep on mentioning this but i am so sick (with myself) when I see people who can wear whatever they want and look soooooooo good. I want to be one of those women who can bounce quarters off my stomach & my butt, have thighs that don't touch, arms that don't jiggle. I don't think I should be satisfied with just being a healthy weight. At least once in my life, I'd like to unveil the smokin' body I know I have under all the fat. 

						
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I've been working out .. for .. 2 days now. I did my 'complete' workout today - one that I can feel 'proud' of :) I feel much better and it's so not difficult at all. The first workout is always the hardest .. to get you right off you a**.   Eating is still horrible! Dinner plan didn't work for yesterday but we'll see about tomorrow.  I am so disheartened about my weight. I'm SEVENTY SEVEN kilograms. I look in the newspapers and I see these ads for these slimming salons and their great results .. and the biggest woman on there is 67 kgs and she looks pretty hefty. So what do I REALLY look like? Not what I think in my mind, eyes .. most definitely. Just made me .. feel horrible, because I am horribly big. No more excuses .. no more 'I carry it well' or 'it looks better on me' or 'i have a big frame'  

						
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Ugh .. am back to around 170lbs. I have been binge eating like mad, at least I think that's what it's called. Or I just am eating 3 normal meals per day and because I'm not normal I can't do that. I have to go back to my protein shakes and absolutely nothing else. Will try that for dinner today. I can eat breakfast or lunch, like a normal person .. but dinner .. or after 7pm absolutely nothing.   Still have not completely phased out junk food, in fact .. it's been cropping up all over the place. I'll have one or two "cubes" of Cadbury choc (one of those huge bars, they segment it into cubes of 4x across). And maybe an ice-cream cone once every two - three days, because it's so hot. Other than that .. some kind of chewy sweet, I think .. and nothing much. No soda, besides sips. No chips, 2 weeks once perhaps.   I don't get it. Am I just destined to exercise like mad every single day? I eat such small portions compared to other people. Yeah I guess so, I need to make sure I work out every single day.   I'm trying to motivate myself by doing these 10 - 20 min segments throughout the day. Instead of allocating 45 - 60 minutes, which .. just thinking about it makes me feel so tired .. I'll do short bursts of 10 - 20 min high intensity workouts. I'll TRY to do them 2 - 3 times a day, or more .. as much as I can. I think that's a better way to go around it since it does not feel so tedious to do.   I watched Fear Factor Couples the other day and the women had THE most amazingly buff, perfect bodies. I want one of those. I don't want to be stuck as a fat woman for the rest of my life and not be able to enjoy the final days in my 20s as a 'normal' 20-ish woman. I don't like looking in the mirror and seeing my stomach .. bulge out. Or looking at my face and seeing how fat & pudgy I look. Or my thick thighs. Or my horrible upper arms. Or .. all the cellulite, stretch marks, whatever else that befalls me as a fat person.  

						
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   .... not on the weight front, but on the lifestyle front :)    Been working out loads this week. Swimming for about 45 minutes, twice - three times a week (so far) and feeling a nice burn. I haven't drawn up a fixed program just yet but I've been consistent. Did some sprints today. I haven't hit my 10,000 steps per day .. more like 6,000 to 8,000 instead. Some days more .. when I go shopping so I think each week I definitely hit 70,000 steps .      Eating has been okay as well. Just yesterday my mom handed me some Xenical. I was asking her to try those instead of all those other shady things .. and in the end she got them, handed them to me and said that'll be $130! I'm like whoa .. they cost that much for 2 strips? I only take them if I have a binge-fest of fat .. which isn't often. Like .. say, this evening I had some McD's .. so took one. None of the dreaded side effects yet though .. so we'll see in 48 hours after this meal. It's not a miracle pill but if you're eating high fat food constantly .. like for breakfast, lunch, dinner plus snacks .. then you pop this pill and it cuts 30% of the fat .. so I understand why it would work for a really overweight person. I'm not sure whether it'll work for me but at least I have a .. panic button .. so to speak, when I eat something horrible like pizza or fast food. Cutting back on the 'junk' food but still not 0% which I think is what I need to hit .. even if I have a bite of something 'bad' the day is a bad day .. not healthy, huh?     My weight is still ugh .. 77 kg .. 168 - 170 lbs. Feel constantly .. bloated. Ugh. Too much info ... :)  But I kinda like how I look .. don't know why. I know I'm heavier than I was before and I probably look real tubby and have a chubby face or whatever .. but I like how I look. I even like how I look in my swimsuit! So I don't know .. my eyes are tricking me or some such thing.     

						
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The other day I over-reacted but honestly, it was 79+ kg .. close to 80! By the next I was down to 77ish and then back to normal and losing weight. So it was all .. water retention or dehydration or whatever travelling does.     Yup ... I'm losing weight .. yippee! I guess the run up to the vacation plus those few days away was a nice jumpstart I needed! Heh! Clothes fit much better and the scale reflects it .. down to 165, which isn't much but come on. .. progress! :) Down to 160 by the end of August. I'm taking it real leisurely, which is a good way to go I think.     Lotsa exercise (cardio plus 10,000 steps a day) and watching what I eat .. but not actually dieting. It's been working out fine.     I don't feel too great these past few days .. fever-ish, constant headaches, feel very achy &amp; lightheaded .. and what not. So taking it slow.   

						
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   All throughout the vacation I just had, a short break .. earlier this week .. I've consistently been 165 - 168 (am to pm). Then I come home and this evening, the 'normal' scale hits 170 (okay) but the digital scale reads .. SEVENTY NINE point SEVEN! Can you believe that? And my body fat is almost 43% and my body water is 39%! How can that be?!   I know I ate .. consistently, I would have to say. A big breakfast, not with every single thing I can gorge myself but portions here and there AND I was watching what I ate. No lunch, because of big breakfast. Then dinner later on - seafood, no cream sauces or fattening stuff. And I walked miles every single day and swam and kayaked. So what gives? Argh .. I'm EIGHTY freaking kilograms! OMG!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  I mean it's so not possible that just because I ate for the day and was on the plane, that I'm bloated and dehydrated. It was hours ago. So what gives? If the scale reads 80 kg or 90 kg or 100 kg .. I am that weight. So freakin gross.   If I'm 80 kg that means I'm 80 x 2.2 = 176 lbs. Back to 175 lbs AGAIN?! Geez .. no wonder I looked so horrible in everything. I thought the pictures I took turned out okay, but argh .. apparently NOT!!!!   I feel like hiding out in my house and never going out .. honestly. I sometimes look in the mirror and really think that what I see doesn't correspond with what I really look like i.e. what people really see.    It's disappointing to go by the pool and see these healthy women wearing bikinis .. I say healthy because they're not skinny but nicely shaped, womanly (true ones, not me .. I'm just fat but womanly sounds nicer eh? instead of obese) .. and they look amazing. Why couldn't I have thought I was okay when I was that weight? Or more importantly why didn't anyone think I was OKAY at that weight?   I am so screwed .. in life .. in everything. 

						
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   And I still feel very very very (x infinity) ... icky. I won't get into that but .. ugh, I'm at the point where I'm going "HOW DID I GET HERE?".   My mom wants me to lose lots of weight. She's always giving me these diet teas, every single day .. and when there's an infomercial on, she'll ask me to get the stuff no matter how crap it looks. Today she got me this slimming belt, this thing you wear around your waist that supposedly trims your tummy. I know it's crap but I'm wearing it to appease her. She also gives me this 'look' that she thinks I don't notice .. looking at my body (thighs, stomach, whatever) and saying to herself how fat I look - it comes out in a minimal way like .. drink this, or buy that, or use this .. and not YOU ARE FAT, DO SOMETHING! which she so wants to say.   It's unimaginable .. how I've always been fat, to her and everyone else in my life. Ever since I was 12 when I grew into my hips & breasts & my full height .. everyone has told me that I'm big-boned i.e. fat. I'm not blaming them .. but no matter what it's just not thin enough. I was 130 lbs and swimming miles a day, I'd always get the "Are you gaining weight? oh .. you should watch what you eat. you don't want to get fat". On to 145 lbs, and all the pushing me to go to the gym and workout and the same comments - your butt is widening etc. I remember once, we went out to lunch for my sister's birthday .. and she was all .. oh your buttons are gaping at the chest, you shouldn't eat so much and gesturing to me to not flash the waiter who was serving me. Then my dad went 'Oh did you gain weight?' and that was the last straw. My breasts got bigger, so sue me. One such incident out of zillions, and that was just from them. On to 165 lbs, it gets worse. On to 175 lbs. it gets worse. So what is it? If I'm NOT 120 lbs and flat chested and flat stomached and have stick thin thighs where they're as big as my calves and you have a canyon in between the thighs so they don't touch .. then I'm NOT THIN ENOUGH?! Not just to my mom but to everyone out there?!   I don't want to be super thin, but I don't want to feel like this all the time. To feel so inadequate just because I happen to weigh a certain number .. and have my mom basically badger me all the time about how big I am. I know she worries all the time that I will 'never find a guy' to love me .. because it's such a known 'fact' that fat girls NEVER get guys as much as their thin counterparts (right!). It's annoying the living crap out of me .. and yes, in a way she is true .. I don't have that many chances as a thin girl my age. Being thin is SUCH a commodity in the world today.   So ahh .. I want to lose 50 lbs. Not 30 lbs to get down to where I'm safe & happy .. but no, 50lbs. I'm so absolutely going to do this! By December! 5 months to lose 50 lbs! It can be done! Just eat .. freakin' watermelons all the time then. I need to give up chocolates .. my hugest vice. Ack! I'm ONE HUNDRED SEVENTY POUNDS, my sister iS ONE HUNDRED TWENTY POUNDS, same height .. there's something SO wrong there don't you think?!   MONTH(End)-  5 August    - 160, 165, 175  September - 150, 160, 180  October   - 140, 155, 185 November  - 130, 150, 190 December  - 120, 145, 195  So do you want to lose .. 10 lbs per month or 5 lbs per month (which is more realistic, I admit) OR do you want to gain more weight and just go past the point of no return?!   I don't even feel like wearing my lovely swimsuit .. I got 3 for good measure. One I got because it was cheap & held me in, another I got today because it was a nice racing suit and the final one was a lovely red halter, more for lounging than anything. But it's too bad .. because I can't bloody wear any of them. I won't go out in public with them .. or do things I so absolutely want to do .. like swim, or sail, or kayak, or anything. Because i'm FAT and don't want to 'impose' it on people.   I'm ashamed of myself, honestly .. 100% I am ashamed of my body .. of myself.  I was watching the Laureus Sports Awards and there was this 40-year-old man who still surfs these humongous waves every single day and a 67-year-old guy who climbs mountains and a woman who lost her leg but still swims competitively and here I am a 26-year-old girl .. not being able to do barely anything, because my fear holds me back. It's not technically my weight that holds me back .. but my fear of that weight, for the most part. How shameful.  

						
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I haven't been spectacular at (not) eating but have been eating less. I guess if you aim for  a higher goal, when you fall short then it's not so bad.   No workouts besides the daily squats and kicks. Yuck, need more cardio.  Weight this morning was 77.7 kg (digital) and 165 - 166 (normal/old scale) .. even got my sis to check that. I have to stop weighing myself every single day, I'll only weigh myself next week. Once a week from now on.   Off to do a little more shopping for the trip, didn't know it was so soon! Have to start packing and I still don't have some of the stuff I need. 

						
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Day Four .. was a bust.  Did not eat lunch .. but ate a late dinner. And then .. some snacking, as per usual in front of the TV. Had a very tiring day at work but it's just a horrible excuse.   Back on the horse again, tomorrow. If I don't cut back on the food .. I'll really suffer on Thursday or Friday when I really hit the liquid diet.   Of course more workouts, will not justify that with any more excuses. Will do some squats and such before bed.  Good news - got a swimsuit, that fits beautifully and I look good - from the front. The back is a little icky - no backfat but I have a huge back. And of course from the side .. I don't have the nice curving in at the stomach. I guess I can say I have a womanly body, but .. that's not any kind of consolation. 

						
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It has been an absolute .. bust, day three that is. I ate way too much of so many things .. and no exercise. What I mean by too much is basically .. anything, because it was only supposed to be a liquid diet - only protein shakes at the most. And of course, still have a couple of 'junk' items .. small quantities but they're still there. So what the hell .. I keep on making excuses. Junk is junk no matter how little I have. And food is still a bad thing to have on this diet. Will do better tomorrow.  No workouts either. Totally lethargic. The only exercise I did today was a couple of jumps up the stairs - two legged, sideways ... and some 'showgirl' kicks - 100 reps x 2 ... and some arm exercises (25 reps each of 5 different types). Not enough for whatever I consumed today.  I have a HUGE craving for a BK Whopper Jr. I think I'll have that tomorrow and not eat anything else (besides shakes or fruits) .. so it would be fine right?  

						
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Which conversion is correct for kg to lbs? Is it 1 kg = 2.2 lbs  or  2.142 lbs? Did someone round it up to make it easier to calculate on the fly?   There's a discrepancy in those scales - digital vs. non digital/basic. I'm not saying that I'm not that weight when it's 2.2 or 2.142, but was wondering why there's a difference.   First - 77.6 kg x 2.2 = 170.72 lbs Second - 77.6 kg x 2.142 = 166 lbs - exact numbers on the scale (both)  Are the British more exact in their measurements then?   I know that the digital scale is the most accurate measurement. But why is there a huge difference - 4 lbs. in the calculation?  

						
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Starting off well. The digital scale reads 77.6 (0.2 down from yesterday) while the normal scale reads way below 170 - about 166 to 167lbs. I do so wish I could be around that weight again, would be wonderful.   Have eaten nothing so far, which is great. But will go down in awhile and have some cereal and fruit. And do a workout .. or maybe I should eat after I have a workout? I think it's better before since I need the energy.  Will update this later and see whether I've stuck to the plan.  

						
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I haven't been as good on day two. I didn't eat a whole lot, but the snacking did get out of hand (nibbling little things at intervals). No meals though, so that was good .. and plenty of water.   I don't feel too well. Am feeling a little dizzy so will turn in early today. Maybe because I didn't eat much?  And of course, did not feel up to it to get on the treadmill. I have this huge fear of twisting my knee out of it's socket (which happens often) while on the treadmill and fall off. I know the treadmill has this safety key but if it's real fast, which I do go at my highest intensity .. then .. there wouldn't be time to react and my leg would buckle because it would be useless from knee down. But ah .. no need to explain that :) I'll wake up early tomorrow and do a workout of some kind - toning vid, perhaps.   And will working on the liquid diet tomorrow. Wish me luck! 

						
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Day one has been a resounding success! I didn't eat a lot of anything at all .. not even meals. And did a great workout for 40 minutes total, plus some quick interval training right after - sprints, running up & down stairs etc. Lots of good sweat but thankfully I am definitely not as unfit as I look, I could really push myself at everything.    Saw something on Discovery called 'Faking It' where this guy who worked in the junkyard was supposed to fake it as a male model. So he had to lose 30 lbs. in  3 weeks  and he did it by having a really high protein diet, combined with 3 hours of workouts 5 days a week. Well he lost 24 lbs. in 3 weeks, then the final 6 lbs. came off after he did a colonic. I know guys lose weight faster than women but it just shows that it can be done. Lots of examples of people who  have  lost weight in a matter of weeks - the Body Challenge on Discovery, people on Body For Life, any Fitness or Shape magazine you pick up from the newstand.  It's simple, sacrifice a little these few weeks (4 - 16 weeks) then I'll be thin enough. 16 weeks x 2 lbs. a week .. that'll be 36 lbs. which is just about what I need to reach 140 and below. It's easy for me to maintain my weight, as it is right now .. it's so stagnant when I do nothing and eat however I eat - no matter whether I was 145, 155, 165 or now at 170.   I'd like to see how fast I can take it all off, and seeing as how good I did today .. I'm going to take my diet up a notch and really not do that grazing thing I did today - I took half tablespoons of things here and there, instead of eating full meals. I need to cut that out, and some of the snacking .. it's healthy stuff but not so much. It was supposed to be a liquid diet, which I didn't keep to just yet. I'll try phasing the food out and do a total liquid diet in a couple of days when I get a handle of my hunger, or especially the impulse to eat when I'm  not  hungry.  And of course the workouts, today's cardio needs to be maintained .. at least that 40 min of cardio EVERY SINGLE DAY. Then add in the interval training, to extend it to about 20 minutes and beyond .. plus a toning vid. I've had major success with Cindy Crawford's Shape Your Body .. which is kinda old and people say that some of the moves can injure you .. like the abs, where she goes too fast. But I pause it and take my time with it, so it's fine.     I'll incorporate that into my workout next week or .. maybe I'll do it later, in an hour or so.    Mini goal for the week ending Friday, 9 July 2004 is  1 - cardio 30 to 60 min, 4x minimum for the week 2 - toning vid, 2x minimum for week 3 - diet, keep at it but by next Thurs or Fri .. totally liquid diet 4 - weight goal is 168 lbs. or I want to see it dip below 170 (clearly)   

						
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I am fat, still. ugh! I hate it! I weighed myself this morning and I am .. about 77.8kg still, which is horrible. That's approximately 171 - 172lbs. so I really didn't lose all that much. I'm still as fat as I was months ago.   Do you know that I am closer to 200 lbs. than I am to 100 lbs.? Most women are 105 - 120 lbs. and here I am coming in at 50 lbs over that. If I gain another 30lbs. I'll be over 200lbs! Depressive to think isn't it?  I have a waist that is 34", seriously. My hips used to be only 2" more that when I was thinner, heh .. so horrible to think about. It's where my belly button is, but my natural waist is only 32" - 33", so I have that curvy hourglass look still. Although I want to be able to say .. my waist is 28", and not have to put a clause there and say .. oh yeah, but only at my natural waist (the smallest point of your torso). One does not wear pants there, and if it goes by where you wear your hip huggers then I think my 'waist' would be 42". That's how big my hips are.  Something has to be done. I've been on a drastic kinda diet for the past few days, but have not been able to cut out the junk totally (in moderation) .. but I am proud of my ability to eat small meals. Today I'm going cold turkey, I hope .. just a liquid diet. Or replace most meals & snacks with protein shakes. And working out. I've read that most Hollywood moms lose about 50 - 75lbs in 2 - 3 months, by working out up to 3 hours a day (2 hours cardio, 1 hour weights) and eating next to nothing. So it's not impossible. I'm going for 1 hour cardio today and all this week, then stepping it up the next week.   I'll swim a lot during my vacation and see whether I've still 'got it'. I don't even think I can do 1,000m .. much less 10,000+ that I used to do. But if I do, and since I will have swimsuits I'll go swim as much as I can after the trip. I loved it, and like travelling .. miss it horribly.  

						
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It's odd but my body .. composition, if you can call it that .. is changing. I feel better about myself even though the scale does not really reflect it. It's stagnant some days, dips below some days. But I feel better in my clothing, feel better overall and like how I look. I could be fooling myself, for all I know .. but there's nothing wrong with keeping to the light workout schedule I have (swim 3x a week, 1 hour program) and nothing else. I think I need to step it up eventually but it's only been a week or two.  The Xenical is working .. not in the weight loss manner but .. the 'side-effects'. They're not too bad since I don't eat that much fat - at least I know that I haven't been that bad, and the food I eat although in somewhat large quantities is not high in fat. So I know what I need to work on. It's a great panic button thingy .. exactly what I need when/if I gorge myself - instead of laxatives, which I admit I took when I ate a humongous meal like 2 - 3 slices of pizza.  I'm not sure if what I eat is a lot. If what I think of as a huge serving is actually a normal serving? And then I label the day as BAD and go off and make things worse by saying the day's spoilt so what the heck.  Not much junk food at all lately. Am happy about that.  

						
</post>


</Blog>