<Blog>

<date>26,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've set aside time to work on Chapter one of my Dr Who story later. It's mostly finished but still needs a little work. I still haven't come up with a title yet although I do have a few ideas. I also plan to do more work on my ST story with the Pegasus crew. I should be able to post chapter one on the FF site next week.  Haven't been able to work on photo chart as my mum has been home. Instead I have been working on the Mickey Mouse design for my sister. I should have that finished by the end of October. I've started the border but still have the shading and then the back stitch to do and there is quite a lot of that. I've decided to do Celtic Christmas as my Christmas design this year. I will start that as soon as Mickey is finished.     
      
</post>

<date>25,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Thought I would start this up in the hope that it would encourage me to do more writing. I have lots of ideas, it's just finding the time. I should really make the time so hopefully this will make me do that.  I'm also using this to keep myself inspired with my cross stitching. Working on a converted photo chart of my mum and dad on their wedding day. Have been put off it for a while. Started work on the skin parts and it made my mum look as though she had a bad skin condition. I picked it up for the first time in a while this week and have almost finished my mums face. Now that I have added most of the other colours it actually looks a lot better. Whether or not I will get it finished in time is another story.  Reading book two of Otherland by Tad Williams. I've almost finished it and so far really enjoying it.  Will do some writing tomorrow. Promise.
      
</post>

<date>02,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      The photo chart is coming along really well. I am almost a quarter of the way through it. Although I am regretting having the photo charted into a larger size. If I hadn't I probably would have been finished by now. Never mind! Mickey Mouse is also coming on well. I should have the silver part of the border finished by next wee. I want the black parts to be given two weeks. Another two weeks for the shading and another two for the back stitch. So I should have it finished in seven weeks. I am still waiting for Celtic Christmas to arrive. Once it does I will be starting it sooner than I thought. A crowd of us have decided to do a stitch along. It should be fun although my progress will be slow at first.  I have finished Otherland Vol2. It was just as good as the first one and would recommend these books to any sci fi/fantasy fan. There are still a lot of questions left unanswered but those will have to wait until I read the following two books. I am now reading The Ring of Five Dragons by Eric Van Lustbader which is the fantasy book discussion for this month. The start was a little confusing and it has a touch of sci fi in it but I am enjoying it. I have also started Naked God by Peter F. Hamilton. I have read this before and enjoyed it the first time so I don't mind reading it a second time for the sci fi book of the month. Besides there are a lot of things I have forgotten from it.  I might be getting a new full time job so my writing, reading and stitching may slow down a bit over the next few weeks.    
      
</post>

<date>29,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Sometimes the internet really tries my patience. I was on the book discussion site and someone had started a debate on hard sci fi. I had written out this long post on it. Basically this person believed that hard sci fi was to blame for the decline in the readership of the genre. Personally I don't think that this is the case although sometimes it can go over my head. I said that there are many brilliant sci fi books out there which get absolutely no attention simply because they are sci fi. Too many people now see it as trash and won't even open a book of that type. I think that is part of the reason. There are a lot of good books out there which aren't easier so I don't think the growth in hard sci fi has anything to do with it. I also said that there is a person I work with who is a prime example of this closed mindedness. He is well read in fiction, poetry and the classics and won't even consider opening a sci fi book because he sees it as pure trash. I then clicked on post and the page not found came up. There is nothing worse.   Here is the review of His Dark Materials trilogy I promised;    This book is about a little girl who lives in Jordan College in Oxford. Her parents are unknown to her and since several old professors and a housekeeper are responsible for her she runs wild around the streets with her friends. She lives in a different would from ours where part of the human spirit manifests itself in the form of a daemon. Lyra's daemon, pan, is still able to change form since she has not yet reached maturity. Lyra hears of children who are being captured and then separated from their daemons. At first the children and herself make a game of this until her friend is captured and Lyra sets out to rescue him. On the way she makes many friends and also hopes to find some answers to some questions that have been bothering her. What is dust? Why is her role so crucial? What is her mother and fathers part in this?   This eventually leads Lyra to other worlds and Will. Will is from our world who is trying to find his father and protect his mother. He soon discovers that he has a destiny too and becomes the bearer of the subtle knife. will and Lyra team up to search for his father and then to help with a war that is affecting all worlds.   I have to admit that when I heard people say that if you like Harry Potter you will like these that I thought they would be very similar. It has magic, strange creatures, witches and the central character is a child but this is where the similarity ends. These books were more complex and more suited to young adult than young children. I am a Harry Potter fan but I would say that I enjoyed these more and can't help but hoping that the autor will continue to write tales about Lyra.       I am about halfway through reading 1984. I haven't been able to read much because I was out on Thursday and then I was doing Christmas shopping today but I am enjoying it. I can't believe how good it is and I can't believe that non of the teachers at my school never thought of having us study this. This is definitely one of those timeless books and one that sticks in your mind. I actually find myself holding my breath thinking that this characters getting away with his rebellion can't last. I know it doesn't ;last which is the whole point of the book. However, I keep anticipating the moment when he is captured. If you haven't read this I strongly recommend that you do. I've since read that all of his books are warnings against totalitarianism. I think I will have to eventually work my way through them.  The play was hilarious. I have never laughed so hard. In the style of Morecombe and Wise (my spelling is terrible I know) there is supposed to a different famous person every night. The night we went it was Richard Wilson. He was brilliant. He did the whole, I'm a serious actor, routine.  Today as I said I did some Christmas shopping. I got everything I set out to get. On Monday it is staff discount day and I will be getting a few more things. Then I just need to get bits and pieces which I will do next pay day. Since I also did some wrapping I haven't done any stitching or writing today.  Tonight I plan to do a little stitching while watching the muppet Christmas Carol. 
      
</post>

<date>27,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Still enjoying 1984. It is very easy to tell the era this was written in. It has lots of references to communism and a few similarities to Hitlers time in power. I will try to go into detail when I do a review.   Mickey is going well. I have done the back stitching for most of the music notes and the frame. It's amazing the difference it makes. I might put off doing a Celtic Christmas update this week to try and get him finished. If I do I might finish it at the weekend.   Going to see The Play what I wrote tonight. Looking forward to that. Yesterday I bought the Muppet Christmas Movie on DVD. I didn't even know there was a new one out until I was browsing in the shop. It was very good. Lots of different Christmas movie references. I'm going to have to look out The Muppets Christmas Carol video and watch it at least half a dozen times before Christmas.     
      
</post>

<date>26,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay this is just a quick post.  Obviously the link in the last post did not appear. When I have more time I'll read through the instructions and see what I did wrong. My friend was very chuffed with the book mark. I have finished doing the main part of stitching on Mickey and I'm now doing the backstitch. I think that by the end of next week I will be finished.  I finished reading Get off the Unicorn by Anne McCaffrey. It's a book of short stories some of which are based on books she has already written. They were good and have bought another book of her short stories, The Girl Who Heard Dragons. I'm now going to start George Orwell's 1984. Since the Big Read on Saturday I couldn't put it off any longer. I also did my review on the book discussion site of His Dark Materials trilogy. When I have more time I will post it here too.  I did do some writing as promised. I'm working my way through chapter 2 of the Pegasus story. At the weekend I am going to type them both up and then make some changes to them. I want to give my characters more depth now that I have done an introductory story.    
      
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       I finished the bookmark for my friend. I'm actually proud of the way it turned out. I took part of the border from a blackwork book and stitched two rows of it. I then did a gold border and frayed the edges. I hope she likes it. I have also sent week 2s update of Celtic Christmas and have started a WIP album on my photo page so that I can post them there too.     Hopefully that link will work, not very good when it comes to things like this. With that done yesterday I can spend today concentrating on my writing. I'm going to look out chapter one of the new Pegasus story and do some work on it. I had already started chapter two but I think chapter one could use some improving. I will maybe look out the Dr Who story too and do some work on that.  Finished The Amber Spyglass yesterday. It was very good although the ending was a little sad. I have been left wanting more and can't help but hope that there will be more stories with Lyra. I know he has written Lyra's Oxford but it is a small book of short stories (although it does have a cool pull out map and lots of diagrams). I am planning to do a book review of that today and will post it on the book discussion group. I bought the fifth Stephen King book in the Dark Tower series yesterday. I plan to start that as Decembers horror discussion. I have forgotten most of the others because it has been so long since I read them I will have to read snippets on them from the site. Hopefully that will jog my memory. Still not sure what to read until then.   urlLink  
      
</post>

<date>20,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Did more of Celtic Christmas today as it is a SAL day. I love the colours. Still can't tell what it is but that will take time. I can see it but then I can't stop looking at the picture of the original design. Plan to put all of my stitching on hold over the weekend for a special project. Friend in the work uses a bus ticket as a book mark. She liked the one I was using (stitched by my mum) so I thought I would stitch one for her. I'm going to try one of the black work designs from the book I bought a while ago.  Still reading Amber Spyglass and still enjoying it. I'm going to do a book review of the trilogy for the book club. Still not sure what to read next. Tempted to buy the 13 1/2 lives of Captain Blue Bear. Quite a few people have been raving about it in work and I have to admit that it does look good.  Have a few ideas running through my head over what I will be writing over the weekend.    
      
</post>

<date>19,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        No, I didn't do any writing at the weekend. I'm actually a little disappointed with myself over this. I basically slept the whole weekend. I didn't have time to do half the things I planned. I guess that's what doing overtime on top of full time hours does for you. Thankfully I am back to normal hours this week. I plan to do a little Christmas shopping on Saturday, come home and then do some writing.  My stitching is going well. Hopefully this week I will have the border for Mickey finished and I can make a start on the backstitch. I also posted my first update for Celtic Christmas. You can't actually tell what it is unless you know the design. It will take a while to get there. Thinking of saving the weekly pictures to my album as well as the SAL page.   Reading Amber Spyglass which is the last book in His Dark Materials trilogy. It is very good. Definitely not just for kids. If you want to read something a little bit different to Harry Potter and a lot more complex then read this.   
      
</post>

<date>14,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Off at the weekend. I am very excited as I will get a chance to do some long awaited writing.  Went to see "Oh What a Night" at the Kings last night. If anyone wants some disco fun I recommend that they go. It was very good. Was even up dancing and singing and was sorry when it ended.    
      
</post>

<date>11,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Just wanted to rectify my mistake from last entry. I meant Wuthering Heights not Withering. My own fault for believing the spell checker completely. Also now reading Subtle Knife by Phillip Pullman. Very good and not just for kids.     
      
</post>

<date>09,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yes, I know it has been a while.  Actually I have a good reason for that. I now have a full time job. I'm working in a book store. I still can't believe that I'm working with books. It's sad I know but it is something I have always wanted to work with. It involves a lot of physical work since I spend most of the day shelving books which really tiered me out the first week or so. I'm now used to it and so I don't find myself falling asleep as soon as I get home. It has meant that I am very behind in a lot of things.  I have got back into my stitching again. I'm doing well with Mickey and should have him finished over the next few weeks. The photo chart I have put aside for now. I really can't face it and it is really beginning to annoy me. Hopefully I will go back to it in the new year. I did receive all the items I need to do Celtic Christmas. I made a start on it today and I'm restricting myself to just stitching it on Tuesdays and Thursdays as those are the two stitch along days. Once Mickey is finished I will lift the restriction. I know today is Sunday but I sorted out the threads for it yesterday and wanted to make a little start on it. It is my first time using linen and I have to say it is a lot easier than I thought it would be.  I haven't been able to take part in the book discussions at all over the last few weeks. My time spent on the net has been reduced drastically because of work. I can't get to use it as much after because those are the times my dad usually uses it. That doesn't mean I haven't been reading. I have read The Hollow Chocolate Bunnies of the Apocolypse by Robert Rankin which was extremely funny. I couldn't put it down. I also finished last week Bleak House by Charles Dickens which was amazing. I loved almost every minute of it. I was a little disappointed by the person who was supposed to explode. I had heard about it on the Big Read and I thought The reader would get to see it but in fact we just get to read a description of the remains. I am now reading City by Clifford D. Simak which is part of the sci fi discussion. It is a book of short stories which all follow on from each other. It is good if not a little strange. I like the idea of talking dogs though.   I did watch the Big Read although I haven't been able to watch each personality pushing for their book. Last night I caught the end of hitchhikers guide and Gone With the Wind. I was annoyed with myself that I missed the part on To Kill a Mocking Bird. Actually think I would like to read Gone With the Wind after listening to it being discussed yesterday. Next week one of the books discussed is withering Heights which I loved so hopefully I will remember to watch that. All in all though I am very disappointed with the top 21. Actually I don't really think much of the top 100. I can't believe what some people chose as their favourite books. Mind you everyone has different tastes.  I have 1984 there to read which I am looking foward to. I hope that does well. I don't think Harry Potter, Wind and the Willows, Winnie the Pooh or Lord of The Rings should win. Don't get me wrong I really enjoyed LOTR I just think that there are more deserving books out there. I've probably alienated thousands of people with that (including my boyfriend,LOL) but never mind.  Writing, I haven't had any time for at all. I may be restricted to just weekends for that. It is now the only time I get any peace.  
      
</post>

<date>29,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      It has been a while I know. I actually didn't realise how long until I looked at the date of the last blog.  I had a lovely Christmas but because of it I haven't been able to get much writing done. I get my new rota today (as an official permanent member of staff) so I will be able to organise myself and get some writing done on my day off. The annoying thing is that I have the whole thing sorted in my head I just need to find the time to get it down on paper. I will be getting back to it for definite this week.  I also ignored my cross stitch for a while and haven't been able to send updates of Celtic Christmas. That will also be starting up again. The only thing that hasn't really suffered has been my reading. I think that is only because I read during my breaks at work. I have finished the Stephen King book which was very good. Stephen King is definitely back on track with this one. A little strange in places and I will have to wait for the next two books to see where he is going with this. Now I am reading Renegades of Pern by Anne McCaffrey for in work and Gone With The Wind by Margaret Mitchell at home.     
      
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I finished stitching Mickey and have even posted a picture to my webshots album and the cross stitch group I belong to. I have received lots of nice compliments for him. I'm now finishing off a flower fairy that I started a while ago for my mums Christmas. It shouldn't take me too long to finish that. I also have a card that I want to do for my mum and dads Christmas. I was going to give them one that I had already stitched as I couldn't see a nice one. Today however, I saw the one that I have been wanting to get them and so I bought it. I think I will be able to do it in time.  Finished reading !984 which was amazing. I will do a review of it at the weekend. I have also since finished Skipping Christmas by John Grisham and have now started A Christmas Carol by Charles Dickens. I have read Christmas Carol before but since it is the season I thought I would read it again. I am only reading it at work. At home I am reading the fifth Stephen King book in the Dark Tower series (it's too heavy to take into work). It's part of this months book discussion and so far I am enjoying it. Still trying to remember what happened in the last four though.
      
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Over the weekend I made some revisions to chapter one of the Pegasus story. I have the whole story line in my head so hopefully I will plough through it. This is definitely going to be a story that develops some of my main characters. I have four in mind at the moment. I was originally just going to concentrate on two but I think there is opportunity in this story for another two of my characters. I twill then lead on to the next story where I will concentrate on some of my other characters who aren't getting as much time in this story. It means that most people will have to read my stories in order so that they can understand the characters. I might try to keep past  events of each story out of new stories as it isn't fair to first time readers but it will be difficult and I can see myself giving up on that idea.  
      
</post>

<date>27,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        I finished the Christmas card for my mum and dad. I have to admit that I am quite proud of the way it turned out. I also started a valentines card for the boyf. Normally we have a competition to see who can get each other the funniest card. My card at Christmas won so this time I thought I would let him win it and stitch him a nice card. I finished it this morning and posted it on my webshots page along with the Christmas card for my mum and dad.  I have sent everyone their instructions for the round robin and now they can get started. I was waiting for one person to get in touch with me but she is no longer able to take part due to family illness. It just means that the rest of us will stitch something in our last box. I thought that was better than giving up on it. I have chosen a theme. I decided on Christmas simply because I don't have enough charts of dragons. At least none small enough to fit in the boxes. I have since chosen which one I am going to stitch in the first box and I have written in the diary. Looks like I will be organised before I have to pass everything on in two months.  Still reading Michael Moore. Very funny but also scary. I will finish the book tonight.  
      
</post>

<date>24,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The Red Hot Chille Peppers are playing in Murryfield in June and I got tickets. So excited! I saw them last year when they played at Glasgow Green and they were so good. The whole time I watched them it felt so surreal. I just couldn't believe that I was there to see them playing live. My sister couldn't afford a ticket and I couldn't go knowing that I had left her behind. I would see her wee face in my head and would feel so guilty, so I got her a ticket too. She was overjoyed and has only now stopped jumping up and down. Nick is also going as is his brother and two of his friends. I think my sisters friend is also getting a ticket so she will be coming with us. The more the merrier.    
      
</post>

<date>20,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      oooh, it has been a while again.  I didn't do much writing because I have been obsessed with reading Gone With The Wind. However, I finished it on Saturday night and yesterday I finished chapter 2 of my Star Trek story. I know where I am going with the next few chapters so hopefully that is me back in the swing. I will have to do some research eventually though. I am going to have to do some research in mining. I know about some of the illnesses caused by it thanks to a course I did a few years ago. However, I couldn't tell you much about mining itself. I just need this research for the little details. I haven't touched my Pern story since I wrote down the bits and pieces a while ago. I don't think I will turn it into anything big especially since the author doesn't like fanfiction based on her work.  Gone With The Wind was amazing. I know that I found it a little dull at first but last week I couldn't even put it down. I did write a whole criticism of it in my diary. I couldn't help myself. The story was stuck in my head and it was the only way I could get it out. It was basically all on Scarlett and how she is seen as a heroine who highlights women's  rights. I didn't see that way. She wasn't fighting for women's rights. She was fighting for her own selfish needs and didn't care who got hurt in the process. She just wants pretty clothes and to be rich enough so that she doesn't have to bother with anyone she doesn't like. If she had a man who was rich she wouldn't have went out and did the things she did. I confess that I did cry when Melly died and that by the end of the book I thought Scarlett was a more likeable character and I hoped that everything would work out for her. It's frustrating that it ends the way it does. That was the whole point though. The reader was supposed to imagine what happened next. Still it would have been nice to know what the author thought.  I am now reading Stupid White Men by Michael Moore. I'm only a few pages into it and already I am extremely shocked. I must have had my head in the sand a few years ago during the elections. I mean I had heard a few rumours but because it was America I didn't pay that much attention.  Stitching is going well. I have sent updates of Celtic Christmas to the SAL page but so far none of them have been updated. I have saved them on my webshots page anyway so it doesn't really matter. I am doing really well with it. I am onto the difficult part of her dress and I seem to be making quick progress. She is just so easy to stitch. I have almost finished the Christmas card for my mum and dad. I just have the scarf of the little bear to finish and then the snow before I move onto the outline. It isn't much and I should have it finished by the end of the month. I also finished the second bookmark for the exchange group. I did an art deco rose design. My mum really liked it so I have promised to make one for her too but in red rather than purple. I sent out the first bookmark and it has been well received. There isn't going to be a charity stitch anymore. The person who runs it has been ill and she has decided to stop it so that it won't affect her illness. She has offered the site to anyone else who wishes to run it but so far no one seems interested.   I am organising a round robin which should start next month. I will tell you more about that then. 
      
</post>

<date>03,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I picked up me pen yesterday and did some writing. Not on the Star Trek story but just some ideas that were running around my head. I won't be able to get anything else done until I have got them all down on paper. Theses ideas won't be seen by others because the author of the original work doesn't want fanfiction based on her writing to be published in any form. I don't think there is any harm in doing this in a small notebook that no one is going to see. Basically I think this person has left huge gaps and I feel the need to put in a new story to fill in one of those gaps.   I'm still reading Gone With The Wind. I'm finding it a little dull but I have found myself itching to pick it up again so I will finish it. I am also reading All the Wyers of Pern by Anne McCaffrey. After that I only have four more books in the Pern series to read. Unfortunately I only have one of them so the others will have to wait until I work my way through that huge pile of books.  Stitching is going well. I have promised myself that I will stitch one Christmas card a month until July when I will stitch them more often. That way I will have enough for Nick's family too. My first one is the one I bought for my mum and dad. I am determined to stitch one that my mum won't have the chart of. Since I bought this one rather than got it from a magazine I shouldn't have any problems. Still waiting for the charity stitch to get in touch with details on which charity we are stitching for and who we are sending it too.  
      
</post>

<date>29,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The boyfriend and I have always said oh wouldn't it be great to try living in another country. Now we are seriously thinking about moving to Canada. He made it sound so easy that I am all for it. His kind of work means that it will be easy for him to find a job in almost every country. He is going to look into it as soon as he graduates although he might be required to have a few years experience first but that will just give us time to get ourselves organised. Sure we will miss our friends and families but that's what the internet is for. And we would still come home every now and then. Plus I would drag my sisters ass over there for holidays    I'm off for two weeks . I love my job but I need a rest. Today I am meeting a friend for coffee. I have said no shopping but what is the chances of that happening. I'll be able to give her the book too.  I'm also going to Edinburgh at some point with my sister. She wants to go and see a few exhibitions and then I'll take her out to lunch.
      
</post>

<date>28,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay so it has been just over a month. The reason is that I am fed up. I want to host my own blog. I want to be able to add my own pictures and links. I want to design what the layout will look like. And stupid me has been fretting about this and not doing anything about it. The reason is, I don't know how too. Compared to most people who use the internet I am far from computer literate. Again stupid me hasn't been doing anything about this. So I am going to have to learn. I love learning but computers have always been a little dull for me. I love the internet but learning how to use programmes bored me to tears. Now that I have something I want to achieve at the end of it then maybe it will be different this time. I have a goal. Also I am learning myself rather than having to listen to a teacher I don't particularly like (and who quite frankly scared the hell out of me). I have two weeks off work after today. This computer has a web design tutorial so I will look at that. I will also get a book to help (yes another excuse to by a book).  I went to see cats a few weeks ago. I've never seen this one before and I didn't even have any ideas what it was going to be like. It was amazing, I loved it. I am not a cat fan in general. In fact I think cats are just plain evil and out to take over the world (sorry to any cat lovers out there).  I love animals and I love big cats just not the domesticated kind. They look too much like they are planning something. Anyways as I said I loved it. I was doing a little search on Amazon to get prices on DVD's and discovered that it is actually based on a book of poems by TS Eliot. I found  a copy of the book and bought it for my friend who went with me to see the show. It's a lovely illustrated book so I am sure she will like it.  
      
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I was so bad, I have bought a total of seven books in since Thursday. On Friday I bought "Girlfriend in a Coma" by Douglas Coupland which I have now finished. I also bought two fantasy books by Eric Van Lustbader but those are for the discussion group I belong to. I then saw Douglas Coupland books on a 3 for 2 sale so I bought two more and another by Haruki Murakami. He is supposed to be very good and I have been wanting to give him a try for a while now. So I have broken my book ban in a huge way but hey, I've stuck to my new years resolution and I am trying out new authors.  Girlfriend in a Coma was very good. It really wasn't what I expected. Although the fact that I didn't read the back properly had more to do with that. I didn't realise it was about the end of the world. Actually, I think that it was trying to put the point across that most of us are no longer questioning the world around us. We are too preoccupied by work and getting more. We no longer open our eyes and look around us. I'm guilty of that in a big way. I am so preoccupied by my own thoughts or by my own life that I forget that there is world out there too.   Speaking of being too preoccupied with my own thoughts I am feeling a little guilty. A while ago I was reading the work of one of the most gifted people on fanfiction. I have probably mentioned her before. She emailed me letting me know that she has a new story up but I haven't even been able to finish the last one I was reading. I was just so busy with my reading, stitching, my own writing (which is sill going well) and my own life in general. I keep promising that I will get round to reading it but that has been about a month now. I will get round to it, I will.  I also have some news. I have finally decided on what course I want to do. I have decided to go into modern languages and I am applying to an open university course of French and Spanish next year. This could eventually lead to a Modern languages degree.  The boyfriend and I bought season 3 of West Wing on DVD and have began working our way through them. They had an episode at the start for 9/11. It wasn't shown in the UK but I did find it interesting. I will say that I didn't agree with all that was said but it was interesting.  
      
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Friends in work managed to get me out of that strange mood. Had my first ever complaint put in about me by a customer and my manager kicked them out the store, hee hee.     Going to the cinema tonight. Haven't been in ages so I'm looking forward to it.
      
</post>

<date>27,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just finished reading Hay Nostradamus by Douglas Coupland. I read it within two days and would have read it within one if I hadn't been working. It was just so good. It's based on the tragic events of columbine and its affect on four people. It has a religious theme. Although I am in no way religious I have to admit that I did find it interesting. It's a book that gets you thinking. Last night it got me thinking about how I have to plan everything I do out. I find that I won't do anything on my days off because I have planned out what I want to do in terms of my stitching or reading. Each week I plan how much of each I will get done and then write about it in my journal. It doesn't exactly make for interesting reading. Even then it just seems so trivial.    
      
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I HAVE INSPIRATION. Finally I feel the urge to write and not just the little spurts I've been having since Christmas. I mean full blown inspiration. Also it isn't fan fiction. This is my own original story. I spent all morning before work taking notes. I plan on taking notes for the next month or so until I know exactly what is going to happen and then I will start typing away. I seem to be getting more and more ideas when taking notes so it is better that I keep doing it that way and then I can organise all my ideas. I actually came up with it when going through my ideas book. I was writing some of my favourite passages into my paper journal when I had a vague idea. I immediately began writing some of them down and the ideas just began rolling.    
      
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have finished reading the Crystal Singer series by Anne McCaffrey. I plan to read all her books but I didn't think any of them would come close to her Pern series. While this series wasn't better it was certainly just as good. The first two books I loved. I again put off reading War and Peace to read them although I was planning to just read them in work. The third book I was at odds over. I thought that the main character, Killashandra, wasn't the same as she was in the others. Which I think was the whole point but at first I didn't like it. Also a lot of the characters in others were killed off or not mentioned again. I found this disappointing, especially since they were characters I really liked. Despite this I couldn't tear myself away from this book. When Killashandra's behaviour became really odd I actually found myself getting emotionally caught up in it. I couldn't wait to get home from work on Saturday so that I could get home and finish it. Then in the end I was disappointed that it didn't continue. I wish that she would write a follow up to this series. I can imagine what happened next and I imagine that a lot more characters would disappear but I still wanted to read more.  There are certain parts of it that I just can't get out of my head. It just keeps running over and over again. When this happens you know you have read a good book.  I have picked up War and Peace. I was a little worried about it as I thought I may have difficulty picking up the thread. It was as though it was only yesterday that I had last read from at. To me this is also another sign of a good book. I have been thinking about going back to uni to study English. Not sure this would get me a job any better than my last degree but it is something to consider.  
      
</post>

<date>19,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I don't know why but I have been over reacting to stupid things all week. Not getting upset but angry over things that really aren't that important.    
      
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's all sorted. She had PC trouble and now I feel bad for being angry. I didn't take it out on her so its not too bad. She is still taking part and we should all be back on track in a few weeks.    
      
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am so annoyed. This round robin thing was going well and three out of five of us had passed our pieces on and the first deadline isn't for another week. One person who received one of the pieces turns out wondered why. She hadn't gotten any of the emails. She knew one was being organised but hadn't heard anything. I double checked. I definitely sent her the email and I didn't get any notification to say that it had failed. I suppose these things happen but I also left massages on the group. Surely she read them? She would have wondered why she didn't get these emails and could have contacted me. I've sent her the email again. She now has just over a week to sort out her fabric, chose a theme, stitch in her first box, write in her journal, paste in some charts and then pass it on. I don't see her managing it and I have the awful feeling that she is going to turn round and say that she doesn't want to do it anymore. It will spoil it for everyone but I can't force her to do it. Why didn't she email me. I can only hope that the worst thing that will happen is that she will ask for a little extra time. That I could handle.  I'm back at work after two weeks off and it was surprising how much I missed it and how much I am glad to be back. My section is a mess but that was to be expected. I think I am at my best when I have a lot of organising to do.  I am now reading The Crystal Singer by Anne McCaffrey and it is very good. I thought maybe I would think that it just isn't the same as the Pern books. While it isn't it is still just as good. I wish I had that kind of talent (to write not crystal sing, lol)  Cross stitching is going very well. I don't have much left to stitch before I move onto the border. I imagine that will take a while since it involves a lot of bead work.  This actually seems all petty compared to the things that have been happening this past week. The bombings in Spain put everything in perspective. My thoughts go out to all the victims and their families. The scary thing is, this is what it is going to be like now. Terrorist bombings and scares. Sure they have happened in the past but the scale is growing and it seems to be more frequent. You can't help but have a pessimistic view of the world after things like this.    
      
</post>

<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have now finished the scissor keep that goes with the needle case. I am also getting on with Celtic Christmas. I can't believe I actually put it down. It's so nice to stitch. I love using linen. The stitches just seem to come out more smoothly. I am taking part in another charity stitch. A member of the msn cross stitch group is organising lots of charity events. Since the charity group I was a member of ended I thought I would take part in one of them. We are stitching little guardian angels for premature babies. I suggested to the manager that she sets up a charity board for people to organise these things and encourage more members to take part.  Finished reading another Star Trek book. Now onto Prey by Michael Chrichton. It is surprisingly good. It is so easy to read to. Last night I decided to read a few pages before I went to my bed and before I knew it I was 100 pages into the book.  I haven't been inspired with  my writing much lately. I thought during this two weeks off I would sit down and get back into it but I haven't. I read over some of the stuff I had wrote when I was still part of a sim group. I can see at the time why I was inspired to write it. Some of it actually wasn't that bad. I thought maybe going back to take part in a sim again may help me get back into the swing of it. I'm not going to do that though. I become all obsessive and get upset when others aren't very reliable in posting. I don't really have the time once I am back at work anyway.  I can't believe I left this until last but I now have my holiday booked. Going to San Fran and I can't wait.    
      
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I did it. Yes that is another post beginning with I did it. I finished the flower fairy I had promised my mum for Christmas. I knew I wouldn't get it finished in time so I had put off doing it. With two weeks off coming up I promised I would do it then and I have. Heliotrope fairy is now complete. I also finished stitching a needle case.  My book pile is going down at last. I finished reading all the books in the Earthsea series by Ursula Le Guin. They were good and I think anyone (adult or child) would get something out of them. True they are fantasy but there isn't a lot of action in them. In other words no sword fights. I also read a Star Trek/X-Men book which was awful. Really don't know what I was expecting but word to the wise. When cross over books are printed DON'T READ THEM. Or at least don't pay good money so that you can read them.    
      
</post>

<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I did it. I handed over my sci fi group to someone else. Thankfully it is someone on the group I know well. I am still an assistant manager but that will probably change over the next few weeks.  Went to the cross stitch craft fair and bought lost of goodies. I bought some nice sparkly fabric for Christmas cards. I also bought a book which teaches how to do hardanger. And I bought a tatty teddy kit to stitch for my best friend. She adores tatty teddies and I thought of her as soon as I saw it.  The manager of the msn cross stitch group is carrying out lots of these new ideas making the site more interesting.  She has started a member of the month page. Each month a different member is asked to fill out a questionnaire. I thought that one was a really good idea. Another one is a work in progress page. Each person has a thread of their own to write about how they are getting on with their larger projects. We can also paste pictures or put in links there. I'm impressed and I can see myself getting more involved with the group.  I haven't picked up my book much in the last few days. It does say that before you think of what you want your site to look like you should think of what you want in it. I've already got a rough idea of what I want. I should probably plan it out in a notebook. All I need to do is read on to find out how to do it and then how to make it look nice.    
      
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm going to have to give a few of my internet groups up. Mainly my own sci fi one as I mentioned before. So far no one has shown any interest in taking it over. I'll wait about a month and then give it up anyway. I would rather do that than delete it. I am also going to give up one of my cross stitch groups. Probably the yahoo one. I'll still stay a part of the thread swap group as I get a lot of fun out of that but the other one is starting to bore me to be honest. I also don't have the time to keep up with it. The msn cross stitch group I am going to stay with. I really like that one (plus that is where all the members of my round robin are). The manager has recently come up with a lot of good ideas to keep everyone interested. For example she is going to have a member of the month where one member is interviewed. Also she is going to have a freebies page where everyone can post their own designs. Things like that which make it more interesting. You can't do that with the yahoo group. The only thing that it is really missing is a stitch a long page.  I cleaned out my stash yesterday and I read more of my book.  I am definitely considering doing something like this in a night class.    
      
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Going into town today to buy thread for the floss swap. This months choice is favourite colours. Blue and yellow are my favourite colours but I think I will choose purple aswell. It is a close favourite plus it is my sisters favourite colour.  When I get home I am going to give my cross stitching stash a clean out and then I am going to look over my new book. Still very much excited about it.    
      
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I bought a book yesterday which teaches beginners how to design their own web site. I've had a flick through it and I am very excited about it. It looks not easy but at least comprehensible. If I get into it I think this maybe the kind of course I'll do at night classes after the summer.    Oh, I also meant to say that I have given up the sci fi group that I managed on msn. I can't keep it up with all these new projects. The truth is I kind of let it go when I started working full time. I wouldn't have let it happened properly if it hadn't been for the problems I had with some of the members. So in the end I just decided it wasn't worth it. I shouldn't have let those people get to me but it really did take all the fun out of it. I'm still a member of the book discussion group though and I don't intend to give that up. I like it too much.
      
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The links group really is gone. No more book discussions. The manager has now deleted it. It's so sad. It really does feel like there is something missing. I can no longer get a hold of anyone from the group (well I could contact the manager). I bought a book yesterday that we was up for discussion before Christmas. I couldn't get a hold of a copy at the time. I've decided to do my own review on it and hang on to it incase another group does start up. I really hope so.  On the bright side I did get an email from a friend who moved to Australia. She moved over there a wee while ago and it was a surprise to hear from her again. I'm going to wait until I can sit down and write a proper reply. I'll print out her message though and put it on the notice board so that others can read it.  Another good thing is that I am possibly moving departments in work. I took a fit over mine and asked. At first I was told no but I've since been told it is under consideration. Not because of me just because we are bringing in new staff too so they want to get that sorted before they move other staff.    
      
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I got an email from the manager later. Explaining that he was unable to keep up management of the group but that after the summer he may consider starting a new one. This one would be much smaller and would concern only books and authors although there would be a general page too. I've emailed him to keep me in mind if he does. He had only emailed a few of us who were regular on the group and I'm pretty chuffed that he thought to include me.  In saying that I now have this little void. I loved the book discussions. While I have been trying to look for a new one, non of them match up to that one. I may just hold off joining another one and hope that the manager starts up a new one later.  It keeps crossing my mind that I should start up my own but I really don't have the time. I wish I did.  Studied my French yesterday and did some more writing. I realised that there is something missing from my fantasy story. While it won't make any difference to the first book and possibly the second one. It will affect the third one. I don't want to start writing properly until I have that worked out.  I have also been considering doing drawings of my characters. My drawing skills are somewhat lacking. I haven't practiced since leaving school. While I was encouraged to continue with art and told I could be good at it I had concentrated on music instead at the time. I think I could pick up those skills again though. I have ordered a learn to draw fantasy book. And I hope to order a learn to draw people book. I know my sister would kill me if she knew (Very much the artist and very much against instructional books).  Anyway, there were a few other instructional books on different subjects that I have been thinking about getting but I had to remind myself that I can only concentrate on a few things at once.     
      
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My favourite groups board is closing down. The manager usually emails everyone to let us know what is going on but this time he only put the message up on the what's new page. Other than that there is no mention of it on any of the boards. I'm really disappointed. I loved that group and I enjoyed chatting with the people on it. Everyone joined in doing book reviews or joined in the book discussions. There was never any trouble and it encouraged everyone to try new books.  The manager hadn't been around lately and he had warned us about that. Whatever he was working on may mean he can't be around at all now. It just seems a little out of the blue because we had book discussions set up for next month and he was going to join in one or two of them. I was joining in the next fantasy one too because it was part two of the Eric Van Lustbader series (I was reading book one when I first started this blog). I really am going to miss it. I could start up one of my own. I did that in the past though and it didn't really work out. Plus I really don't have the time. I have also looked around to see if there were any others similar but there isn't.  My writing is going well. For my fanfic I am working on character profiles. I already know my characters in my head but I wanted to get them down on paper. One of them seems to have changed drastically since started the second story. She wasn't in the first one much so people reading it wouldn't notice but she has changed a lot from what I intended her to be. That may not necessarily be a bad thing as I think I like her better this way.  I have picked up my French again. I wasn't able to touch it when I was ill. I'm still having days where I think that I can do this and days when I don't but I'm determined to keep at it. I have a huge pile of French books to buy this week which will help me. I also keep looking at the Spanish books but that isn't really a priority at the moment.  
      
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My note taking is going well and I have decided to move it up a step. I am going to go into more detailed description of each book (I have now worked out three with a possible prelude). Next I am going to go onto a chapter by chapter description of the first one and then I can begin writing it properly. As for my fanfiction, it is going well enough but I want to concentrate on my original story.   Still catching up with everything that I fell behind while I was ill.    
      
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have been ill all week and haven't been able to do much. Even phoned in sick to work one day. The rest of the time I would come home from work and just sleep. It feels as if that is all I have done all week. On Friday night I fell asleep at 6.30 and slept right through to the next day. By the time I got to work I felt as though I could go back to sleep again no problem. I am feeling a lot better though and my appetite is slowly coming back. Still have a horrible cough thought.  Anyway, as I said I have done nothing all week except sleep and this includes my writing. Today though for the first time I have the urge to pick up my pen again. So I am going to go downstairs (I have the house to myself) and do some writing. The fact that I want to do this means that I am definitely on the mend. I have lots of ideas for my story and I have some ideas for my fanfiction. I have been writing some notes for that and I may actually get that story I started a while back finished.    
      
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I was writing in my paper journal about what a good mood I am in and I couldn't not write it here too. I just feel so energised this morning because I got so much done. That and I know what I am doing. This morning I studied some French. I then did some writing and I wrote out a couple of book reviews.  the French I'm a little rusty with to be honest but I am optimistic that if I keep up the studying I'll get there in time for my course starting in 9 months. I have something to aim for so I am not put off by it. I have my French CD's which I will tape onto mini disc and listen to on the bus into work. I bought a French teaching book which I have been studying from and I plan to get through a chapter a wee. I am going to spend most of my days off on it. I am eventually going to by an untranslated French book so that I can practice my reading. I am hoping to eventually get a French penpal so that I can practice my writing. This will be in the future though as I'm nowhere near good enough yet to do this. I have ordered the books recommended for the French course. The following month I am going to do the same for Spanish. I don't need to go as mad with the Spanish as it is for beginners. But still I would like to have some knowledge before I start.  As I said I did some writing this morning and I am pleased with the way my notes are going. I have moved notebooks so that this story has it's own one. Today I did some character backgrounds to my main characters. From this alone I have managed to come up with an idea for a possible prelude. I think that sticking with the note taking was one of the best ideas I've had. I can really see my characters. The more notes I write on them the clearer they become. I could actually have spent all day writing my notes. I really didn't want to stop. It really doesn't take much to get it flowing.  Only one thing has annoyed me today and that is something that is out of my control. The round robin is beginning to get on my nerves. One of the participants still hasn't sent hers on and has said it will take another few weeks. The person who is to receive it has been asking what is going on even though I have emailed her about it and it is obvious who was to send to her from the address list. Anyway, I think I'm just being easily irritated by this. These are nice people and postponing it for a month won't be any hassle.    
      
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm in reader mode just now. I finished Curious Incident of the Dog this morning after only starting it last night. It was just so easy to read. I didn't stay up all night to finish it either.  A friend in work didn't like it and I find it hard to see why she didn't. It was so moving and funny. It would have been hard not to like it and I can see why it is the Whitbread book of the year. I'm now reading Sabriel by Garth Nix. Another friend in work recommended it although I probably would have read it anyway. I love the cover, it's the kind that really catches my eye. Anyway, it is a children's fantasy novel so it is a little lighter than what I have been reading. I'm off now to do some book reviews.    
      
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I finished reading Microserfs by Douglas Coupland which was amazing. A little different from the other two I read. At first the characters seem a little dull but it is amazing how quickly they grow on you. You soon start to care for them. It's very funny but in a subtle way. I found myself laughing out loud a number of times. And in the end it was also very touching and it actually brought a tear to my eye. I would definitely recommend this. I am now going to start The Curious Incident of The Dog in The Night-Time by Mark Haddon. It came out on paperback yesterday and I have been looking forward to it. Actually quite a few of us in work have. It has been highly recommended by a number of people in work who read it while it was out in hardback.  I have been watching Blakes 7 on DVD which I bought last week. I've almost finished it and I am so annoyed. Not by the DVD's, those were just as good as I hoped but by the videos. My parents bought a few Blakes 7 videos when I was little. I used to watch them over and over again. However, since watching the DVD's I now know that those videos were actually just pieces of episodes mushed together to make it seem like extra long episodes. I honestly believed that those episodes on the video were actually the original. In a way its been good because I have been enjoying season 1 all the more but it is still frustrating. I'm going to have to look out the old videos to see if it mentions this on them.  My writing as I said last time is still going well. I am still continuing with the note taking. The more notes I take the more the ideas come. Eventually I hope I will have a sound structure to begin writing the book for real. 
      
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This morning I decided to practice some drawing. I've decided to concentrate on simple things. Just observing them and drawing them. I think my problem is I don't pay attention to what I am drawing. I read somewhere that most people have this problem, they don't really see what they are drawing. Despite the fact that I know this the outcome hasn't changed much.  I spent yesterday watching DVD's and stitching. I really should think of an activity that doesn't involve me staying in the house all the time. I am thinking of taking my drawing outside. After this week I won't get peace in the house with my sister off so I might find a park somewhere and just draw. Weather providing of course. Although I like rainy days I don't want to sit out in one.    
      
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Just a quick note before I go out. Yesterday I left to go to work in such a black mood and I have no real reason for it. PMS may have something to do with it but I usually don't duffer from it that bad. Anyway I got into work and quite a few others were feeling the same way. By lunch time we all managed to shake it off and were back to our usual joking around. It's amazing what working with such a great group of people can do for you. It's even more amazing what a great group of friends can do for you. They are such a varied group and each one of them is brilliant in their own way. I have never met a crowd like them and feel that each day I work with them is a privilege. I know that when I move on from there I am never going to have an experience like it again.    
      
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      On the 8th June we will see Venus cross the sun. Apparently this is something that rarely happens. How cool is that. It will take 6 hours to happen and it will look like a black spot is traveling across the surface of the sun. It's amazing the things you learn from a wildlife magazine. Just a pity I won't be able to see it (not unless I want to be blinded). Mind you it will probably be cloudy that day. The weather seems to have changed again. No more warm sunny days just rain, rain and more rain.  I tried out my pencils and sketch pad last night before going to bed and the result was disastrous. I could use the excuse that I was tired but I know that wouldn't be completely true. Hopefully I just need to keep practicing. I've decided to draw from the garden since I have become nature obsessed over the last few months.  Speaking of nature. Bill Oddie is back on TV next week so I will be watching that. There was a picture of him on the radio times with a robin flying onto his hand. It was amazing. I would never get over an experience like that. It looked almost as good as David Attenborough swimming with elephants.   I have updated my webshots with another picture of  urlLink Celtic christmas  . In the photo I have finished about a third of the border. I have since stitched a little bit more that that but not much. I haven't really had the time to do much more.  
      
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I admit it. I put my right hand up and admit that I cried over the last episode of friends. I did not cry over ER though which probably makes me cold hearted. But still, I am going to miss that show. It doesn't matter that they are on TV all the time and that I have most of them on video. I think it was around series six or seven that I began to get bored and thought they should end it soon but it started to pick up. I think they were right to end it on a high.  I went shopping as I said I would. I spent far too much. Season 1 of Dawsons creak on DVD was on sale. I couldn't help myself so I bought it. Yes, I'm never going to hear the end of this one but hey I like it. Bought some pencils and a sketch pad as I also said I would although I have still to try them out. Not sure when I am going to get that opportunity. I also got the threads I needed and some scissors.  Anyway, work was busy and very stressful as there was so much to do. By the time I got home my feet were so sore and so I had a long hot bath which has now woke me up. I might do some reading. I started that Penguin history of America which is quite good. Obviously it isn't going to get too descriptive but it makes for a good read and if there is anything that really catches interest I can always read in more detail from other books. Bill Bryson's "A Short History of Nearly Everything" came out on paperback today so I bought a copy. I've been looking forward to reading it but the hardback was just so huge I decided to wait.  
      
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Last night I managed to finish reading "Ombria In Shadow" by Patricia McKillip. At first I wasn't sure I would like it and at one point I thought it was going to be really boring but it did improve. It is about plalce conspiracies but there is more to it than that. It involves a shadow world which Ombria is in danger of turning into should the young prince be killed or the regent breaks his will. The illigitamate cousin does all that he can to protect him but even his life is in danger. I think I would like to try more of her work.  Not many people are pleased about Billie Piper being cast in Doctor Who. A few people I know have suggested that they should have stuck to chosing an unknown like they used to do.  I get paid tomorrow which means I get to buy more books. Also I'm going to buy the threads for The Castle. I plan to get some pencils and a good sketch book. I am determined to take up drawing again.   I actually sat the other day and organised how much time I should give to each of my projects every week (this was instead of working on one of them). By the end of it I had added something else onto the list. A few years ago I began reorganising my photo albums and never got round to finishing it. I have promised myself to pick up where I left off.
      
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Since moving to the kids department in work I am being given more and more to do. I am being asked to help promote titles and come up with some ideas. I'm chuffed to have been asked. I think if I was only to stick with my section I would be bored. Today I decided that I was going to sort the tables once and for all as they were badly needing it. It took me a while but I am really pleased with the results. Couldn't stop looking at them. Today was definitely a good day in work.  I'm growing to like "Ombria in Shadow." It's still very much palace intrigue and conspiracies but there is also some magic in it. I would definitely consider reading more of her work. I haven't really been able to get into "Tales of Earthsea" much. I just haven't had the chance to read it properly during breaks. It's usually been too busy.    
      
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Billie Piper to play the new Doctor Who assistant? That's just wrong. I was looking forward to it coming out but now I am not even sure I will watch it. If they were looking for someone even more annoying than Bonnie Langford then congratulations they've found her.    
      
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My boyfriend is thinking of buying a guitar. It would be something we could both learn together. I've always wanted to play the guitar and we really need something else we can do together. Just watching DVD's all the time can't be good for us. Mind you I am usually stitching at the same time (something that drives him up the wall).   I've decided to continue reading "Ombria In Shadow" by Patricia McKillip at home and take "Tales of the Earthsea" by Ursula LeGuin into work with me to read. This is just because I love the cover of the McKillip book and I don't want it to get damaged.  I bought the new wildlife magazine and so far it looks pretty good. There is a good article about sharks and another about aardvarks. The only problem is that it lists a lot of good books in the back. It is so tempting to want to buy them all. Mind you my collection of nature books is very small so maybe I should buil up on it (any excuse).    
      
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I did some updates to my blog. I actually filled out my personal profile. I turned my weblog pink and I actually managed to get the comments section working.  I went to see "Troy" which was amazing. A few people walked out because it wasn't true to the story but I don't think it ever pretended to be. Brad Pitt was actually good (not a huge fan) and Orlando Bloom was a bit of a wimp but he looked good doing it. Saw a preview for King Arthur and I'm looking forward to seeing that. Also lets not forget that Shrek2 is out soon.  What else have I been up to? Well I am now reading "Ombria in Shadow" by Patricia McKillip which is quite good. Very much a fantasy novel with the whole idea of evil ruling the city while the good try to think of a way to get rid of the evil. I think it is the first proper fantasy novel I have read in a long time.  I am getting on very well with Celtic Christmas and I did manage to get my updates downloaded into  urlLink my webshots site . I am now about halfway through the border. I think I will finish it in the next couple of weeks. I am evening planning my nest big project. I've decided to try my hand at a Teresa Wentzler design called "The Castle". Since I love dragons it is about time I stitched something with a dragon in it. 
      
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I managed to change my weblog to pink and the comments part is now working. Before you had to click on my name before it would appear.  I'm getting through Celtic Christmas very quickly and I'm already thinking ahead to my next large project. I've decided to do The Castle next. I love dragons so it is about time I worked on a dragon design.  Now reading "Ombria In Shadow" by Patricia McKillip. It's very strange, not at all what I expected. But I am enjoying it.  My French is going well and so is my work.    
      
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have more updates to post to my webshots site but I can't get on it. I'm not sure if the system is down or if it's just my settings that have disappeared. It's so frustrating because I really wanted to post them and then comment on how far I have gotten on the msn cross stitch group. I'm doing really well. I have finished the beadwork and have made a good start on the border. If I keep this up I will be finished in a few weeks.    
      
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Have picked up my stitching again. I have finished the celtic lady in celtic christmas and I am now working on the bead work before I make a start on the border. I have updated my webshots photo's of my progress. I am very proud of her and love working on it. It has been a while since I did any work on her but it feels as though I just left off from yesterday.  Reading is going well as is my French. I have inspiration on lots of different projects. Unfortunately I can't do them all. So I am going to have to sit down and try and put a structure to everything running through my head. I probably drank too much caffeine which is why I feel the need to do everything at once.    
      
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I finished reading Hard-boiled wonderland and the End of the World. It was very strange and not at all what I expected. Now that I have finished I am still not sure what to make of it. It was good though and I am going to do a book review before work. I am now reading Acorna by Anne McCaffrey and Margaret Bell. So far I don't think it is anywhere near as good as the Pern of Crystal Singer series. Hopefully the series will get better as I am now halfway through the first book.  Went to see Van Helsing. The boyfriend liked it but I wasn't impressed. For all the effects and action it was still really dull. I felt as though they were trying to hard by putting as many famous monsters as they could into one film. Plus Dracula's little servants sounded too much like Daleks.  Was becoming bored with the internet but have found a really cool craft site. I think I just need to expand on my favourite sites a little more. I'm going to make an authors folder and put (funnily enough) authors websites in there. I'm going to see if there is maybe a good website to help people learn languages.  Speaking of which I am loving my new French book. Because it follows the way we learned in school I'm remembering so much more.    
      
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I finished reading "Vernon God Little"  by DBC Pierre and it was actually better than I thought it would be. I wouldn't class it as one of my favourite books and I do think that one of the reasons I enjoyed it so much was that I had such low expectations of it. I found that it was a little difficult to get into. A friend who is also reading it felt the same. She said that it was difficult to get into his frame of mind which I agree with. Once you got used to it though it did start to pick up. Most people I know didn't like the ending but I did. I suppose it was a bit of a cop out but I wouldn't have been happy if it had ended the sad way although it may have had more of an impact. I have now just started "Hard-boiled Wonderland and the End of the World" by Haruki Murakami. I've heard good things about this author and I'm looking forward to getting past the first few pages. I decided to try this one first because the back of the book said that it had a science fiction theme.  I also have the "Wind Up Bird Chronicle" by the same author. I bought that one because it was recommended at the back of "Miss Wyoming"  I got my art book through, "Learn to Draw Fantasy Art". My sister would say 'I told you so' because so far I'm not impressed with it. I've only had a brief glimpse through it and it wasn't really what I was expecting. I will look through it properly later though. 
      
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just finished my fourth Douglas Coupland book and again I loved it. This one was "Miss Wyoming". I don't really know how to explain why I like them so much. I think maybe it is partly to do with the characters. The books aren't really that long and are very easy to read. Yet the characters always seem to have so much depth. I did enjoy "Miss Wyoming" but my favourite is still "Hey Nostradamus". I was tempted to buy more of his books but I put it off. I will put "Psychotic Family" aside to buy next month.  I am now going to start "Vernon God Little" by DBC Pierre which won the booker prize 2003. I've heard different things about this one but hopefully I'll enjoy it.  Was at a works night out last night. So many people are leaving just now. It isn't going to be the same. I still love my job though. I had a good time although I didn't stay long. I have been so tired recently that I haven't been able to do much but read. I think it is because I have stayed up late a few nights to finish a book and haven't allowed myself to catch up on my sleep.  
      
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Last night I stayed up to finish "The Song of The Lioness" quartet by Tamora Pierce. I loved it and hope to read more by this author. It was simply written and very entertaining. However the ending was just wrong. It just wasn't write and it screamed wrongness to me for the last 50 pages. If it wasn't such a good book I would have thrown it across the room (that and the fact that I don't believe in throwing books). Call me old fashioned by the shero (I don't think she can really be called a heroine) should have married the Prince. The fact that she didn't just seemed so out of place. I just felt that they were meant to be together although the author obviously didn't feel that way. I wonder if others felt the same.    
      
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I keep coming across references to Perdido St Station by china Mieville (sp?). It was a book I really didn't enjoy. It took me a while to finish it but I couldn't give up. I hate not finishing books and I wasn't going to allow this one to defeat me. The description were good with strong characters and the imagination behind the story was amazing.  Normally this would be an excellent combination and to be honest I really can't explain my dislike for the book. It was there almost from the start and it just grew. About month after I read it I saw his other book The Scar and almost bought it. I don't know why after the way I felt for the last one. I still would like to read it but it is set in the same universe as the last one and surely I am going to react in the same way. Maybe when my curiosity has gotten the better of me I will get it out the library.  
      
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I finished reading "A Prayer For Owen Meany" by John Irving and it was amazing. I came away feeling this is definitely a favourite (it is rare for me to feel that way). I would highly recommend this book to anyone. It is a little slow to start with because you aren't sure where the story is going to go. But if you ignore that and concentrate on the characters and the writing you will enjoy it from the start. There is a lot of religious content but you shouldn't let that put you off. It isn't preachy and there is also a lot of skepticism. I think if I had read this at school I would have did my RPR on it. It is definitely worth looking at further. I will be reading this again at some point.  I am now reading a series of four books called The Song of the Lioness Quartet by Tamora Pierce. This author was recommended to me a year or so ago and this is me just trying it. I have to say that I am glad that I finally did. This is a book I wish I had read when I was a kid. It is very easy to read but very entertaining. I'm finding it very hard to put down. I would say that it is a step between Harry Potter and David Eddings. I also like the idea of a female hero in fantasy.  I have been stitching away and have another photo update of  urlLink The Castle . I don't think it will be too much longer before I finish the Castle and move onto the dragon. I have also been trying my hand at paper crafts. I bought some care bear stamps on Saturday. A friend of mine is leaving work and she asked me to make a card using them. Yesterday I went out and bought some materials and thought I would give it a go. The result is a  urlLink good luck bear  card. I'm quite proud of it since it is my first attempt. I used little tabs to raise the bear and the care bears sign from the surface and used layers of different types of green paper as a background. I used glitter for the little bears symbol (it's supposed to be a four leaf clover). I had bought some lime green paper with flower petals in it. I was disappointed that I couldn't find a use for it until I decided to stick it inside the card so that the card had another layer inside. I now have my sister demanding that I make one for her. 
      
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am getting lots of crafting ideas from a message board. I have decided to wait until my week off before I try some of the more daring ones out.  I finally sent off letters to my penpals last week. I since received a letter from one of them and I posted her out a reply today. I've been bad at keeping in touch over the last few months.    
      
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have the house to myself this afternoon so I plan to get a lot done.  I am going to do some studying and some reading. I have slowed right down on my reading. Normally I would have finished "A Prayer For Owen Meany" long before now but I have been too busy concentrating on the romance novels. I think I am over that phase now and I can get back to my reading. I have also spent little time on the US history book but I will get back into that too. I have put aside a book for myself "The American West" by Dee Brown which I am looking forward to reading (same author as "Bury My Heart At Wounded Knee").  I have spent quite a lot of time on my stitching and am just about to start on the fourth shade in  urlLink The Castle  . I can really see the shape of the castle now. I will work on some more of it tonight. I have ordered another chart of a dragon design called Water Dragon by Janlyn. I am looking forward to having that one sent through.  I have my paper journal to catch up too. I have been as attentive to it as I usually am. Lets just hope that I get even some of this done.  Yesterday was a good day off. My sister and I went for a walk during the day which was lovely. Then at night the boyfriend and I watched Scary Movie 3 (wasn't really expecting it to be any good but it was one of those films that I had to see).  
      
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am not a romance novel fan although when I was about 14 I did try them. I have never been enticed to try them since. I have always wondered why people feel the need to read them or buy mills and boon. The other day I decided to try a mills and boon out of interest. Plus I can hardly turn my nose up at something I have never tried (it's an annoying habit and I try not to be one of those people who do it). I am ashamed to say that I am now addicted. I've been reading some of the medical ones when I have the house to myself and I have found myself deeply involved in the story line. I know they are not amazingly well written but they are so easy to read. Still, I hoping that this is just one of the things I become obsessed about and then forget all about it after a few weeks. Never again will I look down on those who buy them religiously and openly.    
      
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I hate diets with a passion. I enjoy my food far too much. More than that I hate all these books that are out on diets. I think most of them are pointless and some of them are just down right unhealthy. That doesn't mean I haven't been tempted to have a look to see what the fuss is about. Anyway, despite all this I am trying to lose some weight for my holiday. For me to stick to one I have to be in the right frame of mind. If I'm not then it never gets off the ground. Well I think I am now and as much as I hate them I think I am doing well.  Watched Britain Goes Wild last night and it almost broke my heart. Poor little Wagtail chicks had disappeared in the night. Obviously to the hands of a predator. No one is sure who got a hold of them but you saw the male wagtail looking around for his nest with some flies in his mouth ready to feed the chicks. It was such a shame.  Still reading "A Prayer For Owen Meany" and I am still enjoying it. I am finding it very funny and have laughed out loud quite a lot while reading it in work. So many people have approached me to tell me that this is their favourite book. I'm not sure if it would become my favourite since I find it so hard to chose one but I can see why others class it as a favourite.  Going to the cinema tonight with some friends from work (with any luck). No definite arrangements have been made but hopefully it is still on. Next week my cousin is coming home for a holiday. My cousin have made arrangements for a night out but I don't think I can afford to go. I will try and make it along for just one drink    
      
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I was invited to join another craft group on msn. I thought it was nice of the manager to invite me (she is also a member of the cross stitch one). I decided to have a look before I joined and noticed that one of the managers was one who had a fight with the cross stitch manager and left to start up her own. This is fair enough I suppose. I didn't take part in the fight although I think the one who left was a little petty over it. What really caught my attention was that some of the members are ones who used to be in the cross stitch group and some who still are. Also it's almost identical to the cross stitch one. It just seems so petty. I don't think I will join.
      
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I was just going through some of the craft sites I visit and I found a link to a paper craft site. The site itself isn't anything special but it did have one idea that I had to try out.  urlLink Memory envelopes .   So I decided to give it a try and make one for my friend and one for myself. I finished putting them both together but I am now in the process of decorating them. Each section is being given a theme. Unfortunately this means I have to collect things for it so it may take me a while. I am doing it in a collage stile. When I am finished, if I like the results, I may post some pictures of it on my webshots page.  Had a good time with my best friend. We meant to do some stitching but instead spent five hours gabbing.  
      
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I finished two cards and I'm sending them off to my friend for her charity sale. I know two isn't much but I kind of left it to the last minute. There is another sale in September for the same charity so I will send more then. I mad a start on  urlLink "The Castle"  by Teresa Wentzler. I've decided to do this one the same way as a friend of mine. I don't start another colour until I have completely finished the first one. My first progress photo is after the first colour. You can sort of see the outline of the castle.  Last night I watched "Big Fish" and very much enjoyed it. I would love to read the book as the film was very moving. Not at all what I expected. I might even buy the DVD eventually. I might be going to the cinema with some friends from work this week. I can't remember the name of the film but it is one I have been wanting to see.  Still reading "A Prayer For Owen Meany". I am enjoying it very much and was hooked form the start. A friend who has read it before said it was slow starting but well worth sticking with. I haven't found it difficult to get into at all. Despite this I haven't had much time for reading over the weekend so I have barely made a dent in it.  Having lunch with my best friend today. I haven't seen her in ages. Usually one of us has been working while the other has been off. I miss her and it will be good to catch up.  One more thing I almost forgot to say, I have inspiration for my fanfic and so may actually do some writing tonight.
      
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I saw my first deer yesterday. It was the most amazing sight I have ever seen. It ran out in front of the car. Luckily we had slowed down to s stop before it did. We had spotted it on the pavement trying to get into the park next to the Loch and we slowed down to look. The poor thing was terrified. I think it was lost as the normally stick to a little further along the road. I think it was quite young because it seemed so small.  I've had lots of nice comments about Celtic Christmas. A few people have even decided to stitch it too. I have stitched a couple of cards for the pink charity which I will send off on Monday. Over the weekend I have decided to make a start on "The Castle" by Teresa Wentzler. So watch this space for progress pictures.  I finished reading "Slaughterhouse 5" by Kurt Vonnegut. I very much enjoyed it. It was very strange with lots of time jumps. A friend has said that he uses this method in all his books but this one has more than the rest. She recommended that I try some of his other books as they are better. I probably would have given them a try anyway. Just now I am reading "A Prayer for Owen Meany" by John Irving. So far I like it. If I had more time I think it would be a book I would find difficult to put down.    
      
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have been practicing my drawing by drawing the birds in the garden. It's amazing how much you notice just by watching them. I was able to see that there was a family of House Sparrows. I was able to work out the sex by the markings and I saw the mother feed what I am guessing was her chick. Going to keep up my practicing this way.    
      
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ronald Reagan died on Saturday. I can't say I was a fan of his politics but I did feel a little sad. I think it was more to do with the fact that he was the first American President I could remember as I child. I remember being asked at school who the president of America was and being proud of myself for knowing who it was. It's like parts of my childhood are disappearing.  A while ago I discovered that Jonathan Brandis died. It was months after the fact that I found out. I felt so sad for his family and the fact that he wasn't there anymore. I always wondered why we didn't see more of him after Seaquest. I had a huge crush on him as most girls at my age did. Me and my best friend used to watch "It" over and over again because he was in it even though the film seemed so bad after reading the book. That was also like a part of my childhood disappearing. It seemed so important back then.  I'm only 24 but is this what it is going to be like as I grow older? Things disappearing? I think that is part of the reason why I keep a paper journal. To hold onto these things for as long as I can. 
      
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Last night I went to see the new Harry Potter movie. To be honest I found it very disappointing. This one was my favourite book in the series and I just don't think they did it justice. While I understand that not everything can go into a film I think they left out far too much. There were so many things that I thought was important that wasn't in it. Overall I still enjoyed the film but as I said I was a little disappointed. I also noticed some huge differences in some of the scenes compared to the first two movies. They also changed the music. One thing it has done though is tempt me to read the books all over again.  I finished  urlLink Celtic Christmas  . I spent all day on it after seeing how little I had left to do. That of course means I didn't work on anything else despite my good intentions. Now I am going to work on the cards I promised one of the msn members I would do. She has asked everyone to stitch cards for the pink campaign. They are due at the end of this month so I will do those and then begin work on my next large project.  I watched two films today that I had never seen before. "Casablanca" and "Rosemary's Baby." I thoroughly enjoyed Casablanca and think I will have to add it to my DVD collection. Not sure what to think of Rosemary's Baby though. It was a good film but a bit freaky. I can see why a friend of mine can't watch it. If it had been me I know I would have given Guy a square kicking and not just spit in his face. 
      
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today I am going to get back to reading fanfic. I was in the middle of reading some by an amazing author who I think could go out there and have some original work published. I took a break to try and get some of my own writing done. Since I have a complete block I am now going to take a break from that. Hopefully it will give me inspiration.    
      
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The new msn sci fi group is thinking about setting up book discussions like we used to do in the old group. Believe it or not this suggestion did not come from me but came from another old member. She and I used to take part in a lot of them and so I was pleased when I found out today that she had joined this one. I was hoping that we would do the new Stephen King book "Susanna's Song" but the group manager asked if we could stay clear of horror. I suppose these aren't really horror so he may be up for it. I won't suggest it just now as I want to wait until staff discount day before I buy it (on staff discount day we get and extra 10% off).  Tomorrow I'm going to see Harry Potter. I'm really looking forward to as this one was my favourite book. It's been selling out very quickly so I just hope that I manage to get tickets.  I finished read "All Families Are Psychotic" by Douglas Coupland. It was very good although I am starting to see a pattern in his books. Not a bad thing I guess it's just what comes from reading many of one persons work. The ending was pretty unbelievable but I don't think it was meant to be. 
      
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today has not been a good day. I was first given abuse from a customer because he didn't like notes in his change. He was nothing but aggressive. Said I had no right to give him it and that it was not legal tender. If he had stayed any longer I would have got a manager to remove him from the store. Then one kid was sick all over the floor I work on and another quite obviously needed a nappy change but his mother didn't seem to notice.  Anyway, the shift is over. I have finished reading "Chocky" which was amazing. I really shouldn't be surprised as I also loved "the Midwitch cuckoos" by John Wyndham. I'm surprised that the television series was true to the book. I was expecting huge differences but any difference was minor. Have moved onto another Douglas Coupland book, "All Families are Psychotic." This one came highly recommended from a friend.    
      
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yesterday I went to see "Day After Tomorrow". To be honest I wasn't really that bothered about going to see it. Despite the fact that some of the images looked amazing I didn't think much of the previews. However, the film was really good. I very much enjoyed it although in the end it did turn cheesy. I would recommend that people go and see this film.  Good news, some of the members from the old discussion group have started up their own group. They had the same problem as me that they couldn't find one to compete. They missed the old gang and so decided to invite everyone to a new one. While I am under no illusion that it will be in any way the same. I am very excited about this. I'll get to chat about the books and shows I like with people I have gotten to know over the last couple of years.  I finished reading "Tales From Earthsea" by Ursula Le Guin. It was a book of five stories that gave some background information to Earthsea. I probably should have read this before reading "The Other Wind" as one of the characters in the last story was linked to this. However, I don't think I lost anything by not reading it first. I am now reading "Chocky" by John Wyndham. I decided to read it after watching the children's show based on it. Actually there are quite a few of his books that I would love to read but haven't got round to it yet.    
      
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My sisters birthday is a good few months away. However, when she saw the care bear stamps she requested which one she wanted (it was really more of a demand, lol). Since she wasn't going to be in last night I decided to make a start on it. I had everything I needed there and I had a few ideas. I am really pleased with the urlLink  end result . I hope she likes it! I also made two Christmas cards but to be honest I really don't like the way they turned out. I'm not sure if maybe it is the stamp or if it is the shape of the cards but I really don't like them.  I am still reading "Great Expectations" and very much enjoying it (although I really didn't think that I wouldn't). I have saw both film adaptions and the original will always be my favourite. Maybe it is because of this that the book seems so familiar. Obviously I know what is going to happen but there were certain parts in the book that I was convinced I had read before. Whole passages which I remember seeing as text and not as part of the film. I know I haven't read this one though as I kept putting it off for others because I had seen the film.  I'm glad I picked it up now though. I think I am enjoying this one more than I enjoyed "Bleak House" (and I loved "Bleak House"). I find myself caught up in the story. My heart breaks for poor Joe and every time he enters the book I can't tear myself away from it. I think for anyone who wants to have a go at the classics they should read this one. Or for anyone who hasn't really enjoyed the classics they should also try this one. It is easier to read than some and such a brilliant story. Tempted to ignore the big pile of books I have sitting there and go out and get the other Dickens novels I haven't yet read. 
      
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Managed to get quite a bit done before work yesterday. I wrote quite a long letter to one of my penpal and posted it out. I also wrote chapter two of my fanfic story. I am quite excited about this one. I don't think it has been done before and I am curious to see what people will think of it. I think that next week I will do the drafts of those first two chapters and then post them on the fanfic sight. Hopefully I will get some reviews.   I also managed to get in a little stitching. Work was busy too. I had information sheets to make up on a new range we got in and then I had to organise the range. Hopefully it will make it easier when it comes to putting the stock out and talking to customers about it.    I have also finished another Acorna book. Still not impressed by this Anne McCaffrey series. It hasn't put me off though and I am looking forward to reading her Rowan series. I am now reading "Great Expectations" by Charles Dickens. Very much enjoying it but then it is Dickens and I didn't think that I wouldn't 
      
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I didn't really have that busy a day I just managed to get into a few things. First of all my fanfic writing is going well. I am hoping that in a few weeks I will actually be able to post something on the fanfiction website. I'm surprised by it because the character I am writing about was never a favourite of my mine. Yet I feel as though I have gotten into her head.   I didn't do much cross stitch because of the card making. I did manage to get a little more of the dragon done but not enough to make a photo update worthwhile. Hopefully I will get more of it done this week. I did make a start on another one. This time a little Christmas kit for myself. This one was bought at the first fair that I went to so thought that it was about time that I got started on it.   Yesterday I watched another Doctor Who DVD.&nbsp; "The Seeds of Death". I missed out "The Tomb of the Cybermen" because I had already watched that one the week before. Both of these are also favourites of mine. I love the second Doctor because of his humour. He is such a funny little character. The Tomb of the Cybermen is a good one because it is an early cyberman story. While the cybermen look funny compared to the later versions there is also something creepier about them. The Seed of Death is a favourite because it is an early Ice Warrior story. When I first saw it I like the futuristic feel of the Earth.   I also got quite a bit of "War and Peace" read. Very much getting into the story. I am enjoying it more now that it I am at a part during peace time. I think that the war scenes may have been one of the reasons I put it down for a while. I like the social parts of the story. The war sections were good. I think it was just that I didn't like the way the war changed a few of the character, I didn't like what they became.     
      
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      There is an article in my magazine debating whether or not we should worry about the changes Hollywood makes to its films concerning history. I thought it was quite interesting and I could see where both sides are coming from. I agree that it is irritating when films are made which are completely historically incorrect. However, surely if people believe that the movies are telling what really happen that really isn't Hollywoods fault. Hollywood are just making what they think will sell so of course they will change things. Surely if people are believing them isn't that the fault of a poor education system? If people don't know their history then of course they are going to believe what they see in the movies. I don't think history is well presented in the education system. I think that it is easier to change what is being taught in schools than it is to get Hollywood to portray an accurate account of the past in their movies.      
      
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I finally got to see Spiderman 2 last night and I loved it. I loved from the opening credits right to the end. This one is definitely better than the first. It had everything and I imagine was closer to the comics than the first (it was certainly closer the cartoons). The one thing I will say is that I don't think MJ ever found out who Spiderman was in the cartoons. Wasn't that the whole point like Lois Lane and Clark Kent? I loved Doc Oc. When I saw the interviews with the actor I wasn't sure about him but he was amazing, better than the Green Goblin. Anyway, the ending set up for a really good sequel with the return of the Green Goblin. I think it will be a while before that one comes out. A friend told me that it would roughly be about three years.   Yesterday I also made some more cards. These ones are for charity. As I mentioned before a friend from a group is setting up another stall in September for a pink campaign. I'm not sure if I will be back from my holiday in time and so made some just now. Not cross stitch this time since I am getting into the stamping. The woman organising it said it was okay so long as they had pink in them. I am pleased with the way the  urlLink cards &nbsp;turned out.     
      
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I made a start on my Doctor Who story about Susan. It seems to be flowing well enough but not sure yet if I will post it on the fanfic sight. It will be a while before I get to that stage anyway. I haven't completely stopped my original story. I am still doing my note taking. It may be a while yet before I begin the actual writing process. I want to get my characters just right before I start. I don't mind that not everything will go into the story. I just want to make sure I have a complete background for each of them. It just seems to be my start trek stuff I am stuck with. Or maybe not so much that. I have some ideas. I just haven't been in the right frame of mind.     
      
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I messed about with my new craft things last night as I said I would. I still had another leaving card to make so I was just messing about to get ideas for this one and I ended up finishing it. I actually added another layer to it. I had decided on yellow as I remember this person mentioning that she liked yellow. While I was picking out different types of yellow paper I saw this lovely transparent sheet of paper with sunflower prints on it (I also so another one with silver butterflies which I had to buy too). I use it almost like a cover round the outside of the card. I then did my usual layering technique after cutting out my decorated stamp and stuck this to the front of the card. The stamp is a flower with a stained glass background. I bought some coloured pencils the other day which had silver and gold amongst them and used these for the background. I then used silver and gold glitter pens for the frame. I am very pleased with the  urlLink end result  and I hope she liked it.   I also watched my second Doctor Who DVD. The next one was "The Dalek Invasion of Earth." Again this one is one of my favourites. When I was a kid I was convinced that it was in colour, turns out it was the film versions I remembered and when I first saw the original ones I was a little disappointed. That has since changed of course and I now prefer the original. I love the Dalek stories but this one is a favourite because it is one of the first ones with the Daleks on Earth. In this one the Daleks planet is dying and so they need the core of the Earth. They have enslaved humans to dig until they can find the right place to send down a bomb to get to it. The Doctor arrives with Susan, Barbara and Ian and they all help the resistance group to foil the Daleks plan. This is also the one where Susan leaves although she appears in another one, "The Five Doctors", years later. I think some good fanfic could be written about the time between then.      
      
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I had a bad day at work. Everything seemed to go wrong. The customers were strange and most of them seemed to be quite aggressive. I had an argument with one because he had to take the stairs (there was nothing physically wrong with him and seemed perfectly capable of walking down some stairs). Also mucked up someone's order although that wasn't my fault.   Never mind, it's over now and I treated myself to some craft items. So I am now going to try them out and make up a leaving card.     
      
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      One thing I forgot to mention about having my friend over is that we organised some more theatre trips. I am very excited because we are going to see Swan Lake and Sleeping beauty performed by the Russian Ballet. I haven't saw a ballet performance since I saw the Nutcracker when I was a kid. We are going to see a few other things too but those are the ones that I am very much excited about. Just a pity that it isn't until the new year.   I finished reading "If on a Winters Night a traveler" by Italio Calvino. It was an amazing read. If I was to even begin to describe it to you I think I would just confuse people. It was funny and had a great ending. I would highly recommend it.     
      
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      As I mentioned yesterday my friend was over for dinner. We always seem to have one of those good old natters when we get together. Usually about old movies (she is a fountain of knowledge when it comes to old movies) and books amongst other things. While we were also gabbing we were also reading from The Brewers book of Rogues, Villains and Eccentrics. Some of the stuff in it was interesting or hilarious. I have had the book for a while now but never looked through it. I think I will look at it more closely now. The weird thing is I was sent the book and I have no idea who sent it or why and I have never been charged for it. Anyway, it was a good night and she survived my cooking.   Before she came over I got my paper journal out. I haven't written in it in so long (15 days is a very large gap for me). It felt good to get back into it again. I could have written pages and pages but just didn't have the time.     
      
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Just a quick update on my stitching (yes, again). I have almost finished the second shade in the  urlLink dragon  and I'm quite pleased with the way it is turning out. I also stitched a bookmark for my mum with a  urlLink dolphin design .  &nbsp;  Nothing much else to tell, my friend is coming over for dinner so I am now going to get the place ready for that.     
      
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Discovered a King Arthur series by Stephen Lawhead which could be worthwhile looking into. I haven't seen the film yet and already I have this little obsession.  &nbsp;  Anyway,&nbsp;should anyone be&nbsp;reading&nbsp;and they have&nbsp;some King Arthur book recommendations I would love to hear them.  &nbsp;  First day back at work was good. Very tired though and I'm off to bed.     
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Last night I saw "Ladykillers" at the cinema. It was quite good, very funny. I have to admit that Tom Hanks character annoyed me. He was probably supposed to be annoying but it almost put me off the film. I don't think I would want to own it on DVD.  &nbsp;  Speaking of DVDs. I now own all released "Doctor Who" DVD's. I have decided to watch them all in order and yesterday I started by watching "The Aztecs". This one is one of my favourite ones and it was still early enough when the show was supposed to teach a little something of history. Next up is another favourite of mine "The Dalek Invasion of Earth".  &nbsp;  Still reading "If on a Winters Night a Traveler" by Italio Calvino. Very much enjoying it. I would have thought that reading all these brief stories that don't have an ending would be irritating but its not. The narration in between these is the actual story. It is very different which is one of the reasons why I am enjoying it so much. I am also still working my way through "War and Peace". Although it had been so long since I last picked it up I was able to get straight back into it. I am hooked to the storyline again.     
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just realised last night that I am reading quite a few books at once. Reading two at the same time is normal for me but this time I have went a little overboard. I am still reading the American history book (which I haven't picked up in a while). I am also still reading Tolstoys "War and Peace" and last night I started "On a Winters Night a Traveler" by Italio Calvino. That's not to mention the book I am also reading at the boyfriends. So my mission before I go on holiday is to finish these. The American history and War and Peace will take me longer because I don't take them into work. They are basically too large to fit in my bag.     
      
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just finished this and I was very much impressed by it. At first I wasn't too sure because of the child like narration but then it was being told by children. The storyline was complicated and there were lots of twists and turns with everything fitting together in the end. It took a lot of imagination involving magic and other worlds. I also recognised some things such as the way the little people are seen. Merlins world also was set during modern day times which was interesting but took a little getting used to. I highly recommend it but don't mistaken that it is a King Arthur story. While you may recognise some of the characters which are only briefly mentioned that is as far as it goes.     
      
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have finished another piece of stitching. This time it is for the round robin. The one that I was sent this time has a ballerina theme. I chose a little  urlLink girl ballerina  design because I thought it was very sweet. Actually the round robin only has to be passed on twice more before I get my own back. I must admit I am really curious to see the end result. I am also looking forward to seeing the others since we all contributed to them. When they are finished we are going to set up an album to put photo's of them in.     
      
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      While gutting out yesterday I found the chart to the tatty ted cross stitch design I had been working on a while ago. With only the back stitch to do I lost the chart and couldn't find it anywhere. So last night I finished it and he is now just  urlLink waiting to be framed . He's so cute I'm tempted to keep him. But no, I bought him for my best friend and she will get him for her birthday.     
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      One of the many things I am guilt of is that I am a hoarder. Today I ruthlessly attack my stuff and threw a lot of it out (Four bin bags to be precise including some stuff for charity). You have no idea how much it almost killed me. I also found a stash of books that I was trying to pretend wasn't there (I have to hide books when I buy them now). Everything looks so amazingly tidy. I feel as though I can get properly organised now. I even had room to keep a drawer for my new stamping craft. I have promised myself that I will never let things go into that state again (lets see how long it lasts). Anyway, I found loads of stuff I can decorate my paper journal with and so I am going to do that now so that I can get rid of it all.    
      
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Last night I stayed up to finish "Lost Boy Lost Girl" by Peter Straub. It is a fairly easy read so I felt that I had to finish it. It was a little creepy in parts and I haven't felt a book to be particularly creepy in a long time. However, I didn't like the ending. I didn't like what happened to the lost boy in the end. I felt the same way about the ending of "MR X" by the same author so maybe I just don't like the way he ends things in general. I guess I didn't think it truly explained everything. And there was certainly a lot of things which were left unexplained. Sure there are some things that should be left to the imagination of the reader. But sometimes it is important to know what the writer intended. Anyway, it hasn't put me off his books. They are a good quick read. And I loved the books he co-wrote with Stephen King.    
      
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've had a fairly constructive day.  I started "The Merlin Conspiracy" by Diana Wynne Jones. I've only read the first two chapters but it seems to be promising. I like the fact that it is magic mixed with the modern day. When you think of Merlin you think of medieval times and so it is refreshing that it is set during modern times. It is a little strange and unexpected when you read about cars and buses and media because you still don't expect it.  I also gave an update on "Lost Boy Lost Girl" . So far I am mainly guessing what I think will happen. It is a long shot since in part two it didn't reveal much more than it did in part one. There were a few supernatural encounters described but not much to give any clue as to what is going to happen next.  I then wrote a few more pages to go towards my story. Again mainly just adding to my character notes. I have more ideas for other characters but as yet no idea as to how they will fit in. If I do it may change the feel of the whole story. I don't think that will be a bad thing.  Lastly I did a lot of stitching. I've almost completed one shad of the dragon and despite the fact that it is only one it is showing up a good outline of it. Hopefully I will get onto the next one by the weekend and then I can do another photo update.  I watched "School of Rock" last night. It was good although predictable. I liked it for what it was - a feel good movie with lots of humour.
      
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I had the worst dream last night. I hate flying and every time the time to fly again comes closer I start to have dreams. Usually it involves me having to go in one of those very small planes. You know the kind that will only seat about six people and there is nothing much between you and the pilot. This time it was an extra long plane. It was like an extra section had been added onto it and the joint between the two could bend. I was in the second section and so could see the front of the plane turning before we did. It was horrible. I knew in my dream that there was no way this could work but the dream wouldn't stop.    
      
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Earlier today I finished reading "Artemis Fowl" by Eoin Colfer. A quick read but then it is a children's book. I think that I would recommend it to most kids. It really was a good book. It would be good for both boys and girls since it has strong characters of both genders. It was very funny and like the most popular children's books these days has a touch of magic. I won't go into too much detail explaining it since I have done so already. What I will say is that I encourage adults to read it too. Mainly because I think that it is important to keep up to date with what kids are reading today. But also because for a brief moment you will remember what it was like to be a child. Lets face it, most of us would love to be that age again.  Now going to go and read some more of "Lost Boy Lost Girl." by Peter Straub. A friend recommended another King Arthur story to me. This one is called "Arthur Rex" by Berger (can't remember his first name). It is out of print but I still might be able to get hold of a copy.    
      
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The Peter Straub book has been good so far. Just little things that have been annoying me about it. Like in what was supposed to be a journal entry the main character seemed to know too many details about his brother in one particular moment. Yes, his brother could have told him all these things but his brother is in no way being portrayed as that type of character. Other than that I am enjoying it.  I am also reading "Artemis Fowl" by Eoin Colfer. A children's book about a 12 year old criminal who tries to capture a fairie to get at the fairy gold. However, Artemis doesn't realise he has captured one of their police LEPrecon. It's very funny and I would recommend it to any kid or any adult who loves kids books. In a way it puts me in mind of Terry Pratchett. But only slightly as it definitely has its own style.  Did more stitching and I have another update for you of  urlLink The Castle . I am now moving on to stitching the dragon and have finished the actual castle. I hope to get more done this week as I have the week off.  I got out my writing again yesterday. I decided to expand my notes and go into more detail on my characters. I've also got more ideas for other characters which I am going to begin taking notes for. I'm not sure how they will fit in yet but I will take the notes anyway. They might come into another story.  Shrek 2 was very funny. I would love to go and see it again. I think the first one was better but not by much.  It was a very good sequel.
      
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I finally finished "The Mists of Avalon" by Marion Zimmer Bradley. If you want to read a good King Arthur book DON'T READ THIS!!!! It was well written but seemed so boring. Nothing much happened. It was the same thing over and over again. Then the bit that really bugged me was the threesome between Arthur, Lancelot and Guinevere. I will not be reading the other ones.  Now reading "lost boy, lost girl" by Peter Straub. I haven't read much of it so far but it has been quite good.  I have a week off work now and I plane to enjoy it. Starts today with going to see Shrek2.  
      
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      For the last hour I have been writing out my thoughts. Not sure if I am doing it the correct way but I think these things are very individual. I came away with pages of paper scrawled over. Most of them seem to be filled with questions. I probably could have sat all day writing. So I take back the belief that you can't spend three months just doing this. I would recommend it. It's a great way to express yourself more than anything else. And yes it is different from keeping a journal. I still intend to keep mine while I do this. I still intend to keep up my other interests too. I won't be stopping my life to write down my thoughts. I think some lines need to be drawn for this otherwise you could end up ignoring your friends and family and responsibilities. As much as it sounds good I don't think anyone should shut themselves away from the world for three months. Some of us can't afford to.  I did do some writing to and I do intend to begin the first draft of my story in the next week. I may write some notes on some of the new characters I have brought into it in between then.    
      
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have started writing again. Remember a while ago I was stuck with my original story? While I was stitching I was hit with inspiration. Last night I began the detailed notes for book one and it is going well. I think I mentioned before that I had ideas for a prelude story. Well I now have ideas for two more stories which will be set alongside the trilogy. Not sure if I am going to make them a book of short stories or if I can write them in novel length. I have written down some notes on my ideas but would really like to concentrate on book 1. I think it won't be long before I begin the actual writing.  Very much enjoying "The Mists Of Avalon" by Marion Zimmer Bradley. It is still a little slow at getting into the action but then it is a long book. The result is that I may come away with a King Arthur obsession and may go through a phase of reading all stories related to the legend. A friend recommended one but I can't remember the authors name. I may request some suggestions on the BBC big read board.  There was an  urlLink article on the BBC  about a guy who spent three months just writing every thought in his head. It's not like a journal because you don't date it. Instead you write all your thoughts out on single sheets of paper so that they can be sorted into subject. Apparently he teaches how to do this on his web page. I just don't see how it can be done. He says that you pretty much have to give up any normal daily life for three months. What about work? And surely after three months without any outside stimulus your thoughts would become dull or repetitive. Mind you maybe that's the point. Without outside stimulus your thought would maybe turn in the way and you would learn more about yourself. The idea does sound interesting and I may try it in a limited way. Just not sure how practical it is. Don't think my work would allow me to carry a ringbinder around all day so that I can record all my thoughts.  Another thing I read is that there is going to be a gallery of children's illustrated,  urlLink Quentin Blake's , work. I would love to see it. It is being held in Aberdeen which is really too far away. Particularly if I am going on my own. Maybe I can talk someone into going with me.    
      
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Another friend from work is leaving. Actually two are leaving but one isn't leaving until the end of the month. It's so sad and we are all on similar shifts. My shifts will be changing soon because I am going to be doing a different job. It's going to be strange. I made my friend a  urlLink leaving card  too. I decided to move away from the carebear theme although I was tempted. I will make one for my other friend nearer the time. I am thinking of a yellow card for her.  I have been working hard on  urlLink The Castle  and I am pleased with the way it is turning out. I can't wait to get onto the actual dragon.  Was supposed to be going out tonight to see Harry Potter again with my friend. We both had too much to do so have decided to leave it until next week.  
      
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      There is something wrong with blogspot. It won't let me update my profile. Annoying but not the end of the world. Just wanted to change what I was reading at the moment.  I think I mentioned that I finished "The Song of the Lioness" by Tamora Pierce. I am now reading "The Mists of Avalon" by Marion Zimmer Bradley. I had been wanting to try a King Arthur story and a friend recommended this one. Another friend warned me that it wasn't as good as it was made out to be but so far I am very much enjoying it. I hope to try some more King Arthur tales. It's weird because just now I am more inclined to read fantasy books and my boyfriend has changed from this to normal fiction. It's like we have traded places. Well almost, I still read other kinds of fiction as well as fantasy. I tend to mix what I read it's just that I am more in a fantasy frame of mind.  Anyway, I have a few suggestions for him but whether he will read them or not is another story. I will take over some tonight to see if any of them will catch his eye.  I am listening to the best of Bon Jovi. I haven't picked up this CD since I left school. Recently though I have had the urge to listen to some of my old favourites.  
      
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I finally have the link to  urlLink chapter 1  of my story. I even have my first review and it was a very nice one. The reviewer said that the first chapter was a promising start. Did point out a spelling mistake which I hope to change soon. I plan on working on the next chapter over the weekend and have it posted by Monday or Tuesday. I love getting reviews! I just like to know that people are actually reading it. I also like to know where I could make improvements for the following chapter.  I have been to the cinema a few time. I went to see Fahrenheit 9/11 which was interesting. A bit of an eye opener. A lot of what was said was in Moore's books but because there are images along with this it really brings it home. I also went to see 13 going on 30. Very much a teen chick flick but I enjoyed it. I went with my sister and we both found it very funny. Yes it is just a female version of Big but I don't see what is so wrong about taking a female spin on what was a great film.  Watched a few doctor Who DVD's too. I watched another third Doctor storyline called Carnival of Monsters. Not one of my favourites at all. Another one with Jo who was not a favourite companion of mine (as much as she has a huge fan base I just find her a little irritating). This one the Doctor and Jo get stuck inside a machine which holds creatures from lots of planets, used for entertainment purposes. I thought the storyline in this one was a little weak compared to others. The next Doctor Who is "The Green Death" as I watched it not that long ago I decided to skip it. So I next watched "The Ark in Space" which is another favourite. This one involves my favourite Doctor played by Tom Baker. His companions were Harry and Sara who end up on a space station which holds all that is left of the human race. They are all cryogenically frozen, to be awakened when the solar flares are over. Instead the oversleep and the Doctor has to save them from an alien invasion who are going to use their bodies to grow their young. This was also one of the scary ones when I was little. 
      
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I managed to get that first chapter uploaded which means it wasn't my fault. It must have been just the system that was down. Yeah! I will post a link to it when it appears under the listing (this can take a while).  I have been crabby all day. Just felt like everything was going wrong and everyone was annoying me. I think I just didn't get enough sleep. I don't think I took it out on anyone though.  I did a little stitching this morning. I don't have a picture update for you but I am now moving away from the green. I was getting very bored with those green colours so I am glad I am just about finished with them. The colours I am using now are blues.  I also did some reading. I am going a little more slowly with Absolution Gap but it is very good. It is a little like the others in the series in that there is a new character which obviously has an important part to play but you just don't know what it is yet. This particular character is in the future and she is in some way linked to another one from the past. I am trying to puzzle out what the link is going to be but I know that it will not be anything I imagine it to be. 
      
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I can now log in but it won't allow me to download my file. Every time I try it gives me an error message. I've checked the list of possible problems it gave me and none of them could be attributed to my file. Fanfic does say that they are having problems with it. They said it is unstable but should work. I'm going to give it to the end of the week. If it is still not working then it must be something I did wrong and I will email them.  I just feel so annoyed. I think I will go away and make something. It might make me feel better. 
      
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So I messed about with my first chapter again. Became pretty happy with the changes I made. It is a lot longer but I like the added detail. I am particularly pleased with the first chapter. I typed it all up and looked over it again. Still happy with the end result I went to fanfiction and its not working. It will let me view other peoples work but it won't let me log in so that I can download the first chapter. It is so frustrating when I am so excited about it.  I think I will just go to bed and read for a little while. Hopefully I will be able to download it tomorrow. 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I decided that I didn't like the redraft of the first chapter and have started to redraft it again. I'm glad I decided to because when I sat down to it last night I realised I had so much more to add. So I have deleted it from Fanfiction and I hope to have the new one posted for the weekend.  Other than that I have letters to catch up on and I'm away to do that just now. 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have changed the title of the Doctor Who story from Aftermath to Rebuilding. I was pretty tired last night when I posted the first chapter and now I wish I had left it a little longer. I think there are lot more changes I would have made had I not been so exhausted. I am going to look it over again tonight and I may repost it. In the meantime here is a link to my first chapter of  urlLink Rebuilding  (can't say I am all that chuffed with the title either).  I don't know where my head has been this last week. I have been able to do some writing just before work but when I get home I am so tired I just kind of zonk out in front of the TV or the computer. When I finally move myself to pick up my book I fall asleep. I then wake up again, have trouble sleeping and the same things happen again the next day. I'm off tomorrow and my sister is working during the day. So I am going to have a nice relaxing day sitting at the table catching up with all the things I had wanted to do during the week. Hopefully I am going to the cinema tomorrow night. That sounds like a good plan. 
      
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My Doctor Who story finally has a title and chapter one is now on fanfiction.net. I am currently working on chapter eight and I only have a few more chapters to go before I finish. The chapters are quite short but I don't really mind that for the moment.  Nothing much else to tell. I'm very tired as I haven't been sleeping. So I am going to go for a long hot bath, read some of my book and then go to my bed. 
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Not much to say on the cross stitch front. I have finished another shade of the  urlLink dragon  and it is starting to fill out. It won't be much longer before I finish the dragon and move onto the rocks at the base of the castle. Then it is onto the dreaded back stitch. I don't usually mind back stitch but there is a lot of it in this one.  I watched yet another Doctor Who yesterday, The Three Doctors. This one sees the debut of Omega, a celebrated timelord who gave the timelords the energy they needed to control timetravel. Believed to have been killed in the process he was left trapped in an anti-matter universe. He decides to capture the Doctor so that he can leave and have his revenge on the timelords for abandoning. The timelords unable to help the Doctor send him to of his previous selves to help (hence the Three Doctors). I like this one simply because of the reappearance of Patrick Troughton as the second Doctor. He plays the comedy role very well in this one.  And speaking of Doctor who, I wrote another chapter in my story. It is coming along quite well and I think, since I will get some peace this week with just my sister and I at home, I will get quite a bit done this week.  On the book side of things I am getting along very well with Absolution Gap. I am remembering more and more as I read along. I had to read my book reviews of the first two to remember some of the details. I can't believe my memory is so bad even though I loved those books. Anyway, I was bad and bought another one today. This one is a little different as it is a book of poems by Tim Burton called "The Melancholy Death of Oyster Boy." It's such a funny book with lots of lovely illustrations. A must have for anyone's library. 
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Went to the cinema to see the Thunderbirds last night. I should point out that the Thunderbirds was never a favourite of mine. Out of the puppetry that Gerry Anderson created Captain Scarlet and Stingray were my favourites. However, the movie was good. It was very much a kids adventure movie but still a lot in it for the adults to enjoy. There is also enough in it to keep the fans happy too. I don't think I would buy it on DVD or anything because it is too much of a kids movie but I would go back to see another one should they make it. I did find myself recognising characters I completely forgot all about (like Tin Tin). Well worth going to see. 
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yesterday I watched the next Doctor Who, "Spearhead from Space". Not a favourite this time but still one I enjoy. It is the first one with Jon Pertwee as the Doctor and the first one to be shown in colour. The Doctor ends up stranded on Earth as punishment from the timelords. He has no choice but to help Unit in exchange for a lab and facilities to help repair the TARDIS along with the help of his new companion Liz Shaw. Together they defeat an invasion of the Nestines who use plastic mannequins that they call autons to take over the world. This is also the first one with the Nestines who appeared in another Jon Pertwee story. I don't like the beginning of this one, too much running about to find out if the Doctor really is the Doctor. Once it gets past that it really is very good. The new Doctor Who is being filmed just now and funnily enough the bad guys in this one are again the Nestines. There is also a new Doctor Who book being released starring the Nestines. So they are very popular just now.  I was very bad last week and bought season one of UFO on DVD. It was on sale otherwise I wouldn't have bought it. My dad had said not to get season one as it isn't very good (I already have season 2). After the first episode I was about to agree with him. However, now that I have almost finished them I have very much enjoyed them. I love the whole 60's feel of the show and most of the storylines have been very good. Some have even surprised me. Only one thing though. I sometimes get the feeling that they aren't in the correct order. Just little things make me think that. It's hard to explain without explaining every detail but I really do hope I am just imagining it.  I have finished reading "Great Expectations" and as I said before it is now one of my favourite Dickens novels. Although it did seem as though I had read passages of it before after the halfway point it stopped feeling like that. I don't think that I started the book and then forgot all about it because I only bought my copy a few months ago and my parents don't have a copy of this one either. A friend mentioned that sometimes a lot of Dickens characters can be very similar across his books and I think that is probably what it is.  I am now reading "Absolution Gap" by Alastair Reynolds, the third book in the trilogy about the inhibitors. I bought this book before Christmas and it was months before that since I read the first two. I am ashamed to say that while I remember the main storyline I am going to have to go back and read my notes to try and remember most details. I am sure most will come back to me as I am reading but little things are niggling at me. So far I have only just finished the prologue so not much to tell. 
      
</post>


</Blog>