<Blog>



<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey. today i woke up got all dressed up and went to a ballet. it went from 2-5 and i wuz sooo hungry after that  ate like a feast at the chinese place, ollies, the have such good food it makes the food in darien suck. anywho so i ate alot there. i came home went intotown with kendall and had a big slice of pizza and a snapple. then we ate a whole box of scooby doo snacks and got a baskin robins shakes. and i ate all this in within like 3 hrs. hehe. in town all these people were like yellin at me and kendall which isn't really unusual but lke 3 or 4 people is. usually its just lie 1 or maybe 2. it wuz cuz there wuz all these people who got off from the hiway cuz there wuz lots o traffic on it. so all these people who usually arent drivin around were. one person wuz like "which one of u wants to sleep with me tonite", "abbbooottt! (i think that wuz colli)", and another one wuz like "heeeeeey ladies pussy come here why are you crossin the street hahaha" that dude wuz really creepy. so we walked around and then were waitin outside o dunkin donuts to be picked up and eddie and sum people were like heeyy. and it wuzn't that bad but kendall wuz like ehh i could tell she didn't like talkin to them. heh. well we got picked up and then came home. and when we pulled into the driveway there wuz sum racoon like in our garage and we were like ahh. and my mom wuz like ooh its just cookie and openly walks outside. haah me and kendall ran in cuz t wuzn't cookie it wuz definately sum rodent. oh well i think it left the garage if not oh well it will have fun in the trash. i'm stuffed so i get home andlay on the couch for a lil till i can't tolerate the shows my dad watches and i come upstairs to talk on da computer. well its later i'm gunna uh wander round the house. peace
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i'm in the weirdest fuckin mood right now.. its insane. i'm like extremely out of it. its almost like i feel drunk. and i wuz talkin weird to my mom. its just odd. its like my brain is rollin back into my head and i can't think. wow i get in such weird moods sumtimes.. i dont really even understand it. i have such highs and such lows. like durin the day im usually happy sumtimes just blah its summer and i can be a lazy ass.. but at nite i get all emotional and think about the past. the good times i miss sooo bad and all the stupid things i've done and really regret.  now i've done nothin really bad (sry nothin juicy to gossip about). and why i'm sad aint a big deal either. but to me it is and that's all that matters. now i dont need no help. i'm okay i tend to exagurate things a bit. but not that much.  i hold it together keep my kule round people cuz they dont wanna have to deal with it. but sumtimes (especially when i haven't chilled with sum1 in a while) and i'm alone at home.. i just break. as does anyone else. i've added more drawins to my ofoto thing.. its on my aim profile check it out. i'm goin to sleepy i'm zonked (is that a word i think my moms uses it.. haha.) peace!
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      last nite katelyn wuz over at my house from 7-10 p.m. we played ping-pong.. trampoline.. the normal stuff and den went swimmin. at first the water wuz just cold so we went in the jacuzzi and had to wait a lil cuz my sister wuz the only one who knew how to heat it up cuz the computer thingy is really confusin to me. so that works and we're talkin. and all these bugs are like eatin our faces.. not kule. and then a bat comes and swoops down. it got really close too. later we heard it when we were inside.  i remember once in our old house, like before we added onto the house. i walked into the sunroom and a few otha people like my mom were in there and the bat wuz just hangin from the ceiling! we left the door open and it just flew in.  and also another time octavia and katelyn were over and we heard this scream from the street. at the time we were just talkin about how my street is really dark at nite.. and how sum1 got raped near my house. and we were like ooomg wut is that? but now i realize it wuz just a bat probably cuz the bat scream does kinda sound liek that sound that nite. we thot it wuz a dog/girl screamiin.. i dunno we were just confused. yeah so that wuz my nite last nite. sry katelyn if i wuz kinda in a sad mood we both kind were. for sum reason the water makes us emotional. haha we both weirdos. but hey i had alot o good memories in my pool and house ... arg. well i'm out to watch more telayvision and eat food. peace.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i left the house today.. yeah. i went to go get my skateboard fixed. the wheel wuzn't turnin cuz it wuz all rusted out and stuffs but the guy fixed it which took like 2 seconds and that wuz that. but since we had already gone out me mom wuz like wanna go to utopia? and wuz like hells yeah. haha. i wanted to shop there for so long. the people in there were really nice. i got a tie die tanktop, pj bottoms that said sumthin silly on them, and a big tshirt that had the nite b4 xmas on it. i wanted to get a sublime shirt and a doors shirt and more.. but it would have been tooo expensive. i wish all the biiig tshirt were smaller and like fit. argg. then i would buy the whole store. ehhehe. and i saw the funky shirt there that katelyn has. yup its a kule store .. it smells good too. like sum incent thingy. i wanted to get incents too but my mom wuz like nooo too much stuff no more. burp* well lis is watchin silence of the lambs.. i'll brb
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey. i just got back from the movie white chicks. haha it's soo funny! their makeup wuz kinda creepy tho.. haha but their voices were so funny. u should see it. me and kendall watched it. there were sum people singing to the songs next to us... oh well.  and there were these two guys like our age maybe a lil younger behind us in the snack line and they were like steppin on eachother feet and actin like nerdy retards. and they were like  'dude where is my car is such an awsum movie man..  'hahha yeah'  'i think the new movie .. the white castle one is the new dude wheres my car'  'haha yeah mannn'  they reminded me of uhhh sum guys in our grade actually. anywho..  so randomly today rachel IMed me and she's like ur a whore and (i dont remember). but if she thinks i'm a whore... hahahah she's a crack whore.. oooh! GOD DAMMIT RACHEL SAY IT TO MY FACEE FOR CRYIN OUT LOUD! ARRG.  soooo other people readin this out there.. hows ur summer been? i want a tan so bad i'm goin insane. i cleaned my car like a crazy person waxed it, windexed it, even cleaned the plastic on the outside, the tires, vacummmmed EVERYTHING. i better get paid alot for that. me and kendall were talkin bout how people r always like ahhh i'm fat when they obviously aren't. i'm not liek one of those ballet freak stereotypes whoz liek omg OMG i look so fat in this mirror. there are so many of those at dance and i'm fuckin fed up with them. they'll be like (for the 20th time) I'MMMM  FATT WAHH WAHH AHHH. (and they look up and wait for sum1 to say nooo u rnt ur perfect). arg i just ignore them cuz they dont listen anyways. my goal this summer is to swim 10 laps a day. i liek swimmin and stuff so its not like not fun. i like to exercise. eh anyways. me and kendall got to chill alot today that wuz funnn =) luv ya. and katelyn cna't wait to chill with ya more.. i only go tlike 2 more weeks till balet boot camp.  Pigman239: haha i once drank several gallons in one night, it was awesome nutty dancer 4: oh at first i forgot we were talkin bout coke.. and i wuz like dude thats krazy matt i luv u ur awsum hahah PEACE.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hello thuurr. sup? burp* whatcha doin there? hmmm. today wuz a fabulous day *puts hand in air like gay guy* rite now its stormin. i like storms  "Hey hey hey! But I like it when that lightning comes Hey hey hey! Yes Ilike it a lot"     yay it's stormin fo shizzle. i wanted to tan today cuz i'm still uber pale er pail (however u spell it) but it wuz a bad tannin day. argg.  "you and i are the kule people in the skool" quote from katelyn hehe. she said that cuz she just read a note in my yearbook that said dont get too trashed. i dont get trashed.. psh! i hate how people think they r all kule when they smoke. most people learn pperrrty fast that people dont think its that kule and they're all alone and smokin is just dumb. unless its the ocassional pot smoking. earlier today i chilled with kendally and lis came over too. we went swimmin and had a war with my sister and the hose. hehe. i'm gunna start skateboardin lessons. when i get my skateboard fixed at axis. i got dirt in it so now it down even roll. but yeah i think lesson will work cuz i'm bad at teachin myself. i'm just afraid that i'll be the only girl er only person that i know. ehehhh. the pixies are kule yo. me like them. i mite go to saves the day concert in nyc with liz, lis, me, and maybe katelyn.. i think i can go who knows. it'll be funn =) i love katelyn hehe =)  0_0)   WOOOOW LITENIN. i gosta go yo! bybyieieiei adios!
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      that was a joke if u were wondering... JFIOEjkl;jkj sorry i have kendall over and she is   63uiowag   amazing. because she always brightens my day even tho she is a poo. i'm too bootylicious for ya babe........ move ya body up[ and down make ya booty touch the ground OOh Ooh, i don't think ya ready fo this jelly
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i made myself some split pea soup before i went to the mall today. then i drew some cooooOl drawings on the desk because i am cool like that. then i visited the museum of spiritual wonders in NYC. it was super spiritual man, dude. there were many sculptures of jesus that i could relate to because i am really in touch with god.   i'm lovin it. mcdonnnnalds. bah dah bah bah bah.... i'm lovin it.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey it's summer and why not start a new blog. All this weekend i've been a blob. the only thing i did wuz watch tv, eat sharkbites, and sleep.  on saturday i did go to one of my family's friend's son's graduation party. i had to hangout w lauren. she's okay i guess. a lil odd but hey that's okay. she thinks i'm really cool to chill w so the least i can do is be nice to her and all. one of eric's friends came over cuz he wuz bored to tears with all the old relatives who came to congradulate him. his friend wuz kinda cute =) hehe. while all the old people were talking about books and boring stuff me and lauren went to the beach. and i found this tag thing that belonged to a hotel in new york. it wuz kule to find so i kept it. we acted silly haha people probably thot we were drunk. so that wuz the excitement of my weekend. =p  now i gotta study for finals. yeah... i wuz sick on friday so i have to go on makeup day which sux. but if you think about it most people wont even wakeup till i'm done with my finals anyways. well atleast i wakeup at 12 usually. tuesday is the last day of skool. waahooo! i have about 2 or 3 weeks till i go away to ballet camp for 3 weeks. so i'm gunna enjoy as much as i can. i need a serious tan =) and it's gunna be fun chillin w all my friends. summer is always great. i'm out to go swimmin. adios!
     
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey dudes i'm back. fo sho! i'm chillin with my mom. yeah that's right. karlys at a concert er sumthin and mafreaka and me dad are at a cousin weddin. sucks for them. especially cuz mafreaka has to hear my dad snore. haha. much luv. but yeah wut wuz i talkin about oooh yeah.. so kendall is out workin at the restaurant. and katelyn is chilln with merri and supposidly has a new boyfrieeeend from new cannon. kuleness. i have to meet. i haven't talked to merri in like forever we didn't really get along but that wuzover stupid stuffs.. maybe she's kule cuz katelyn and liz both chill with her now.. *ponderous look*. but yeah i have so much camp stuff and just things to say but i'm in the middle of watchin a movie. so i'll get back to ya'll Lata.!. cyaz on the flip side .. hahah. byeeeeeeeeeieiei                   SHWANG -haha sarah         HUMP HUMP-margoTTT 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys. if you haven't noticed i've mainly been just talkin about things i've done this summer in this blog. i have another blog that is for personal stuff. if your a really really really close friend i'll tell ya the link. but so far i've only told one person. anywho... today liz came over for a lil from.. 2ish to almost 5ish. we played bad mitten.. (yes its set up in my yard), but it was sooo hot so we went swimming. s,m,l,jummbooo! hahaha. we made macoroni and cheese.. haha but we forgot to drain it. haha. us stupid heads. so it wuz all nasty. ooops. i wanna learn the dance to the music video 'dip it low'. hehe. its kinda hard though to learn dances to any music videos, because they cut the dance so that its almost to do with the music. like they edit out all the steps between the moves. anywho.. but me and katelyn r gunna work on that. another dance we know to our many. hehe. that'll be our 5th music video we know. hehe we so silly. um the last few days have been pretty boring. i haven't been able to chill with people much. either their mom's have been butty .. both liz's and kendall's mom were bein dat way. and also they have camp and jobs, unlike me cuz i'm a lazy butt. but hey i dont have time to get a job so dats a whole diff. story. today i was skateboarding down the rings end road again.. and i wuz goin sooo fast. like too fast and i thot that if i didn't stop i'd crash so i jumped off and almost triped. fewf* that was basically my day. for dinner i had chinese food. sumtimes chinese food makes me sick.. and guess what?this time it made me sick. =( well karly will be home at 12, the usual. out doin who knows what =) . and marika home lata maybe (shes out with her bf joooooooey). haha silly marika really likes this guy more than any of her other past bfs. i'm really thirst , off for a drink and TV. adios!
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      on the 4th of july i had katelyn come over to swim for a lil, but she had to leave at 6 =( liz came over and kendall too. we chilled lit sparklers. then my dad lit all these fireworks in the front yard. it was so kule. haha me, liz, and kendall *the wave. a few times the fireworks almost went into the trees. hehe. i got this annoying virus that appears on my away message. not kule. after i put up my away message, a lil later it'll be changed to this weird link. meh. currently my fav bands are no doubt, the cure, and bright eyes. today i had nothing to do, because people were busy, so all i did was just download music. if i have figured out just one thing in my life it is that music is awesome. i'm leaving this weekend for a 3 week camp in ny. it's gunna take forever to fuckin pack. eh not looking forward to dat. i watched jay and silent bob strike back. great movie great movie. it was weird tho to listen to, because all the swear were taken out. so it was really hard to understand jay. haha they are such stoners. silent bob is def. the coolest. well i'm out skateboarding. ttyl. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today i woke up at 12:15 because katelyn called. i probably would have slept till 1. hehe i stayed up real last nite readin through all the poems i've writtin this year. so i woke up and we talked about chilling tonite.  i went to tell my mom and she totally freaked cuz she told all the people at dance that i wuz absolutely going to this class when i told her maybe.. okay fineee. so the teacher is counted on me going and i beg her to let me go next week when i'm going to dance camp next weekend. i dont know why she wants me to go to all of these classes. as it is if i average it out.. everyother day of the summer i'm dancin. seriously why do i need to dance more. my mom is krazy. so i get out of going to the class and my mom says it's okay to chill with katelyn.  so i have 5 hrs to waste. i see the lawn mower in the lawn and i'm like 'yay the shed is empty so i can try out the mini ramp i set up. hehe it wuz fun. i went down it a few times and went around the pool. then i asked my dad if i could mow the lawn ($_$) moooonaaay! hehe* i did that and when i wuz done i put it on really fast mode and raced around the yard. that wuz fun. hehe. i went swimmin and finally the pool was warm enough to stay in. my dad wuz like 'ahh its disgusting!' haha silly dad.  i took a shower and katelyn came over. we swam for a lil and ate cheeseburgers (even tho we were goin to eat with her parents lata). her parents picked us up and i had only one contact in becuz i couldn't find the otha. oh well. we went to the pizza place ate pizza and got mozerella sticks. yum yum.  we came back to her house and danced to moozic for the first time in sooo long. it wuz fun. dancin to 'toxic' 'my luv is like wow' 'baby boy' 'crazy in luv'. then we were really tired so we sat down and watched dude where is my car which i never really watched. heh it wuz funny but wuz stupid at the end how the gf's boobs got bigger. stupid humor. her mom drove me home cuz katelyn wuz really tired and now i'm back home. ouchies* my knees, ankles, and wrist still hurt from falling down the stairs. it wuz really funny tho when i fell cuz my brain wuz like ..duh.. and i knew i wuz fallin but i didn't like do anything. i just fell on my knees and like tried to hold onto the rails with my arms. haha. it wuz very funny. but now i have rug burns. well i'm going to sleep and probably goin to have another ordinary day to tanning in the afternoon and then chillin with friends at nite.  holla back youngin .. haha wut a silly phrase. but my new fav phrase is still fo shizzle. i gotta say. anywho, i'm off like a prom dress.. haha i'll neva forget when steph said that. haha. bye dudes!
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      um i didn't go to the movies with katelyn, her boyfriend, and this other guy named donner. partly because of a family plans, and me bein in a weird position. and this donner guy was 19 =/ eh no thanx. so i just chilled with kendall instead. as we were leaving to walk to kendalls i told my mom i wuz goin over for dinner and stuff, but she didn't hear me. after i finished eatin dinner my mom calls sayin she wuz worried sick and didn't know where i wuz. i wuz like oh sry i told you.. and she like meh no you didn't tell me! so i asked when she wanted me home and she said after dinner which i had just finished, so i walked back home. i came back and she was really upset because she was plannin for the family to go out to eat and the to see 'the village'. but i didn't know she was planning all of this. she was all mad at me for thinkin  told her i was goin, and ruining her big plans.... which both weren't my fault. so i got mad and she said i had an attitude. eh it was annoying, i was really frustrated. i came back downstairs and we decided that since both karly and marika were out and i didn't really wanna go out that we'd just watch a movie at home. we watched a comedy and i wasn't so mad and neither was my mom and we enjoyed the rest of the night. i luv my mom, but she barely listens to me/hears me anymore. its like a one sided conversation half the time. and when i repeat my question er answer, she'll still ignore it. and when i raise my voice she'll say i have an attitude. or say i'm so cruel to her or something. its gotten worse this past year. i think that's what brings on all the arguments in my family most the time, or me and karly 'mis behavin'. i guess the reason i get caught for doin things is that i'm just not a good liar. then i got back online and talked to elliot for a lil while and he told me i had a nice smile which no one has ever told me so that made my day. =) then i went to bed. so all that wasn' really that bad, but the rest of my night i was really really depressed. probably the saddest i've been in and i can't remember. and my dream didn't help either. i still feel like shit and i'm not really in the mood to hangout with anyone, cuz they'll probably just tell me how to deal with the problem and i know i wont do it. they make it sound so easy... im done writin, bye. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      eh, i wuz feelin pretty shitty this mornin. waiting for kendall to call, and then once she did she said she couldn't chill. so that sucked. i went upstairs and my madre wuz like karly is gunna drive me to the car place to pick up the other car and we can pick up icecream on the way back so you can come if you want. so i wuz like yay gettin out of the house, which i hadn't been out for like 2 days. so i got all excited and got dressed up, cuz i had nothing better to do. on the way back we stopped at baskin robbins and i got a cookies n' cream reg. shake. those are yummy. =) as soon as karly and i got back we sat on the couch in front of the tv. i was gettin bored and sad again. so i called katelyn. she was just about to go and buy her mom a new fone. so she picked me up on the way out. while her mom and uncle were picking out a new cellphone, me and katelyn went to barns and noble. we were browsin thru. i dont really read books. haha. and we saw the hippie dictionary. PERFECT. hahaha. since we didn't have any money on us we just wrote down a few funny words from it. wacky t backy. her mom came and were got back in the car and back to her house. she talked to her boyfriend brian and we just hungout in the computer room. then katelyn's old neighbor danny, rusty's lil brother, called and was like come to get me i want to hangout. he's like 7. we were asking him what he wanted to do, cuz he was just wanderin around. i feel sorry for the little kid. he wanted to hangout with his brother so katelyn's mom drove us to the depot. danny walked up to rusty and was like hey, and rusty just said go away. poor kid, he doesn't like have anytime to hangout with his brother. we got back to katelyn's house and he really wanted to play air hockey, but we couldn't find the puck and stuff. katelyn's mom felt really bad, cuz danny was really loney and sad. so she kept searching and she finally found them. we played with him and he had so much fun. =) he's so cute. anyways, but it was time to go home and i got dropped off at home right on the minute. then i watched a show on vh1 about hollywood's smart blondes and on the top three was gweneth paltro, jessia simpson, and reese witherspoon. i can understand reese witherspoon. but jessica simpson.. come on that's a joke. now i'm on the computer just before i go to bed. tomorrow should be an interesting day at the movies.. goodnite.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>