<Blog>

<date>30,September,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Here is something to thing about:   A million roads, a million fears  A million suns, ten million years of uncertainty  I could speak a million lies, a million songs,  A million rights, a million wrongs in this balance of time  But if there was a single truth, a single light  A single thought, a singular touch of grace  Then following this single point , this single flame,  The single haunted memory of your face   ~STING~     

						
</post>

<date>29,September,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   W00t! Time to go home soon! Work is a B##tch but I tend to be able to go home on time and added to the fact that i live 15 minutes away from work is always a bonus =)  Wats my job you asked? well my official title is Quality Assurance Analyst (sounds cool eh =P) but I am just a lowly paid s/w and h/w tester.....Yep you got it right .. NERD ALERT!! (heh I wear glasses and everything)  Was this the job I studied for when I was in Uni ...God no! I had a dream to become the next Enistein ("Love brings much happiness, much more so than pining fore someone brings pain.") the next Sir Issac Newton, but when fate throws you a curve ball and all you can do is follow it through.  But I can't complaint too much, I have unlimited internet acess and test the latest internet technology. Currently I am playing with  urlLink WI-FI technology . It is pretty funky.... look mummy no wires =P  So if anyone is looking for some WI-FI hardware, word of advise, don't go for Dlink... it is total cr4p. 

						
</post>

<date>29,September,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   So here I thought to myself that my ramblings will be left untouched and unseen by anyone on the World Wide Wait and Lord and behold I get comments from the ever busy  urlLink minishorts  and the food connoisseur  urlLink wena . Well ladies, welcome to my humble abode,    urlLink Mi Casa Su Casa  .   Just a questions....how did you find me so quickly??... I am only a newborn =P     

						
</post>

<date>29,September,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Just finish my lunch and reading the latest posting of  urlLink mum-mum . Man am I jealous of all the delicious food that all this East Malaysian is eating!! As for me all I have is some last night dinner, rice and mince park with eggs. Simple and filling.  One thing which tweak my curiosity is the alcohol Chivas Regal. Why is there an attraction with this drink? Personally I would prefer a stronger drink. Scotch single Malt, preferably imported from the Highlands of Scotland... man that would put hair on your chest!! (even is you are a Asian =) )   But seriously I am not much of a drinker now. I am proud to say that I am a cadbury drunk, all I need is a glass and a half. In my Uni days, vodka was my friend! Happy hour on friday was always a constant blur. Damn those were the days.   

						
</post>

<date>29,September,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   So anyway I have been thinking last night about blogging. What should I write about? Do I really want strangers to read my thoughts and my ramblings? of course another question is would anyone even read this blog? Sometime it is hard enough admitting what your real thoughts are, let alone sharing it.  anyway got to do some work... to pay for this internet connection =P   

						
</post>

<date>29,September,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   oh yeah, why JonnJonzz??  I originally tried to register  picolo   but it was taken, so I choose the next alien on Earth. J'onn J'onzz - The Martian Man Hunter is a comic character. A character very close to my heart. A character alone in a world not of his own, trying to figure out what it is to become a human. Loliness is his constant companion and distrust is his mirror.  

						
</post>

<date>29,September,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   So anyway how do your start your journey into the blog world?  I have been checking out some blogs and I think a great ice breaker is a few short Q&A. So here goes:      How and why did you start blogging?   This is more of a why than a how. My inspiration for starting came from my first encounter of the blog kind.  urlLink Sixthseal  and  urlLink Minishorts  is the first 2 blogs I ever visited and they blew my mind away!! Sixthseal made me laugh and minishorts made me cry. I felt like I knew them and yet they were both strangers    Who is your biggest inspiration in life?   Beside my parents and my grandmother, is my Sifu, Timbo. He is my teacher of life and he teach only by examples.   When you look at yourself in the mirror, what do you see?   I see a shadow of the past haunting me. A person who live in the presents but dreams of the past. I know I have to let go, but it is easier said then done. I see myself going older. I see my future with trepidation (like everyone else).    If you weren't doing what you're doing now, what would you be doing?   I would still be studying and travelling the world   If you would star in your own TV show, what would it be about?   Hopefully it would be like  "It's a Wonderful life"     NB: I borrowed this Q&A from minishorts. I hope she don't mind. 

						
</post>

<date>29,September,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Hi There!   This is my first log on my blog...so be nice. 

						
</post>

<date>31,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Ran Last night. 10 rounds in 23 mins and 25 seconds Don't know why I am slowing down.. My shins and my calf muscles is really hurting... It feels like that I have injured my bones rather than pulling my muscles....  Maybe it will go aways with further training....we will see... 

						
</post>

<date>29,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   The wonders of Medical Research! What would find out next? urlLink CNN Health  

						
</post>

<date>29,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Since the start of the  urlLink Rugby World Cup , the beer sales has been amazing in Oz. Some bars has even reported that they nearly ran out of beer!! Currently the favourite beer is Heineken.     This is because Heineken is the offical sponsor of the World Cup. Imagine sports and beer together in their drunken embrace!! Lets get this straight, Alcohol company can sponsor sporting activities, but Tobacco company can't... Weird?  Oh also during my experience with my liquor, I also try to be artistic and take a pic of my reflection =P     Pretty lame eh? And yes that is my digi-camera. I know it is not much, but is was a pressie from my wife =) I have been thinking of getting a new one.... but which one? Any Digi expert ? Advise Please? 

						
</post>

<date>28,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink      urlLink      Blackadder: (to Baldrik) You wouldn't know a cunning plan if it painted itself purple and danced naked on the table in front of you singing "cunning plans are here again."   got this via  urlLink mum-mum  

						
</post>

<date>28,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Got to love Management!! Why do they love making us waste our time and ignore our advise. I spend 2 weeks to create a detail test case and test over a dozen wireless hardware. I emailed my results to my bosses last week, and one of them had the nerve to come to me yesterday to ask me resend it again, because he could not bother to check his inbox for the old email. And today to add to the insult, I have found out that they are planning to make a deal with the hw company which has the worst results in my test case.   SO WHY??  Why make me waste my time if they don't even read it?! 

						
</post>

<date>28,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						      I was too lazy to cook today, so after my usual run, I went to the local noodle shop "Noodle King" and tried their  "Lo Mein"  . As you can see it looks nothing like the Lo Mein you find in Malaysia and trust me it taste nothing like it. I think they were using some kind of Korean rice noodles. In any case I was famish after my run, so I ate it all =)  As for my run, it was nothing exciting. I only ran for 5 rounds in 11 minutes. I think my body is trying to tell me to slow down with the training, since it was very hard to do even 5 rounds. My calf muscles were really burning!! I think I might have to slow down before I burn myself out before the competition.    

						
</post>

<date>27,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						      There was a protest new my work today. The  urlLink protesters  were protesting that  urlLink SBS  (The Australian Multi-Cultural Channel) is allowing direct broadcasting of news programs from Vietnam TV. They believe that this news program only produces biased news from governing Communist Party.       I was told that there was approximately 3000 people involve in the protest, and since this was my first involvement in any kind of protest, I was eager to take some happy shots =P     As you can see although there were a large contigent of police, it was not necessary as this was a peaceful crowd. Unfortunately the speakers were all speaking in vietnamese so I had no idea what they were talking about.      I was only there for a few minutes during my lunch break, so I had to quickly take my shots and leave. Anyway atleast it was an interesting tuesday afternoon.     

						
</post>

<date>27,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   For those who are bored and can't get the motivation to work/study, here is a good place to waste your time on. The  REAL   urlLink White House  

						
</post>

<date>24,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Happy Deepavali  One of the many thing I miss about Malaysia is the celebration of the Multi-cultural festivity (of course the public holiday always helps). All Malaysian celebrates Chinese New Year, Hari Raya, Deepavali, Christmas, etc. All Malaysian recognise and understand the different believes and celebrate each others religious celebrations.   Whereas in Oz it is just another day for us. 22nd of January 2004 ( urlLink CNY ) is just another day for most Aussies. For a country which boast its tolerance and understanding (eg Different Colours, One People), aussies are just like every other Western country. The only religious celebration celebrated are Good Friday and Christmas.  Multi-Cultural Australia or just White-Australia?  

						
</post>

<date>23,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Since  urlLink Wena  is so stressful, I thought I would find something to help us all to combat stress. Lord and behold I got an email from  urlLink Heart 2000 Australia  telling me how to cope with Stress. So here there are:   # Don’t explode at every minor delay - have backup activity ready so that you can shift your attention when a delay arises   # Act immediately when something annoys you rather than keeping your feelings bottled up. If you do feel ready to explode, try a physical activity to offset your anger / emotions   # Plan your time ahead to try and get some order in your life. This will help re-establish control, and give a sense of achievement   # Arrange things so that you do them at your own pace without feeling rushed. Above all, don’t over-commit yourself as this will only exacerbate things   # If someone is doing something other than how you would do it, walk away from the situation rather than provoke a confrontation   # Set priorities for the tasks you have at hand. Decide which tasks are more important and address them first   #Life isn’t fair : you can’t right all the wrongs, and there are social injustices. Focus your attention on things you can solve, so you feel you are making a contribution   # Learn to enjoy the simple things in life - like sunshine on a sunny day   # Seek the opinions of others before you make a major decision. This may prevent impulsive actions which could lead to later stress. 

						
</post>

<date>23,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Tonights run! 10 rounds in 20 mins and 10 seconds!! Av 2 mins per 500m circuit.  So now my question is, for the last few runs did I just slow down or did I lose count on the number of circuit I ran??....emmmm  I think I am losing my memory in my old age =P  

						
</post>

<date>22,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   While I was running last night, I had this sound coming into my head  In My Life . I tried to sing it in my head, since it is pretty hard to sing it out loud when you are out of breath. I don't know why this sound came in my head, but I have always liked this song. I reminds me of the past and how each person you have met always touched and changed you.  It reminds me of my Uni friends, which I have haven't seen for months. The time we spend at the cafeteria just talking about life and what we are going to do... Oh what big dreams we have.  It reminds me of my High School, the bitter-sweet memory. The time when I felt like such an outcast.   How I am reminded that I am different and lower than all those big "Quai low". But in the end I survived, I rise above it and had some great friends.  It reminds me of my friends in Malaysia. The good old days, where we played with ice-pop sticks and bottle caps. When I met my ex. The great food, the awesome night life and the family.   In My life, tears and joy has come and gone, but memories will always remain.  Anyway here is the lyrics to the song, maybe it will help you remember something you have forgotten, as I have.   In My Life - John Lennon     There are places I'll remember All my life, though some have changed Some forever, not for better Some have gone and some remain All these places had their moments With lovers and friends, I still can recall Some are dead and some are living In my life, I've loved them all   But of all these friends and lovers There is no one compares with you And these memories lose their meaning When I think of love as something new Though I know I'll never lose affection For people and things that went before I know I'll often stop and think about them In my life, I'll love you more   Though I know I'll never lose affection For people and things that went before I know I'll often stop and think about them In my life, I'll love you more     

						
</post>

<date>22,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   President Bush landed on Australian Soil today. He is only here for less than 24 hours and he had already created  urlLink controversies . Of course in great aussie traditions, when President Bush addressed the Australian Parliament, he was heckle by our anti-war senators!  I am glad to see that our senators know how to behave when we have guess around =)  I wonder what would happen if Mr Bush addresses the Malaysian Parliament?? Would he even be invited. It seems there is no love lost between Mr Bush and Dr M. It is weird that in most western countries news, Dr M. is portrayed as a  urlLink  Tyrant  , whereas most Malaysian would believe he is one of the best Prime Minister that Malaysia ever had.  So which is true? Who do you trust?   

						
</post>

<date>22,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						     urlLink   free enneagram test    The Peacemaker  The easy-going, self-effacing type. Nines are accepting, trusting, and stable. They are usually creative, optimistic, and supportive, but can also be too willing to go along with others to keep the peace. They want everything to go smoothly and be without conflict, but they can also tend to be complacent, simplifying problems and minimizing anything upsetting. They typically have problems with inertia and stubbornness. At their Best: indomitable and all-embracing, they are able to bring people together and heal conflicts.   Got the link from stressful  urlLink Wena  

						
</post>

<date>22,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   I had my training today. 14 rounds in 34mins and 34 seconds! This is really bad!! Either I am losing my count when I am running or I have really slown down! If I assume that it takes me on average 4 mins to go 2 rounds, I should complete 14 circuits in 28 mins. Am I slowing down that much??!!  I 'll need to try again tomorrow to see what my time is.  What is happening??!!  

						
</post>

<date>21,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   All day in the office I would think about my training and my running. I am eager to run and try to push myself and improve my time, make myself stronger. I go home and change into my running cloths and run towards my local park.  I do some standard stretches and I can feel my tensions on my legs and my backs. I body feels ready for the run. My mind is eager to start. I am thinking I’ll be faster today, I will run further today.   Round 1  By now I am confident that I can do this with my eyes close. This is easy. My legs is still strong.   Round 3  Lactic acid is building up in my muscle systems. Pain. My mind is now creating doubts in my mind. My Mind is creating excuse for me to stop.   Round 5  I am close to halfway, I have not cross the pain barrier. I am sweating. I am breathing hard. I need a drink. I need a rest. Can I stop just for a minute for a drink… NO!   Round 7  I can feel my muscle on fire.  My throat is dry. My mind tells me that this is enough, I can stop now. My mind tells me that can I do better tomorrow. My mind tells me that You have to push yourself!! You have to prove to them all, that you are not a weakling Use your anger to feed your need   Round 10  I have lost count how many rounds I have run. The ground looks so inviting. I want to stop!  I want to rest! NO!! 2 more rounds!   Round 12  Yes! This is the final round! Do it. Push it!  Stop complaining and just do it! After this you can stop and rest, but not before. Arggghhhh!!! FINISH!!  YES!  Lets do it again......tomorrow  

						
</post>

<date>21,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   12 rounds in 26mins and 21 seconds  I think I am doing a good time, but the strain is getting to me. I may have to decrease the increments. I lost counts between the 9th or 10th rounds so the time could be for 12 rounds or 11 rounds, but either way it felt like my leg was made of lead....yikes!  I think my plans will be it improve my stamina this week by increasing my distance and then next week I'll try to strengthen my legs.  Anyone have any advise?  

						
</post>

<date>21,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Great little flash movie online. urlLink Super Hero , So if you are bored check it out =) 

						
</post>

<date>20,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   I can't believe some of the hw coming out in the market nowadays. I was given a box full of dsl/router modems today to test and it amazes me how bad it is. Don't this company have a QA to test this crap before they send it out to the public.  They want to bundle a DSL modem and a router together, cool that is great. Like most router and modem they all have a default IP address which you need to connect to the hw and configure it. So what does the manufacture do? They setup so that both the router and modem has the same IP! This means that if they are both connected together, you would not be able to talk to one of the hw!!  I would understand if the hw are from different manufacturer.....but they are not! Both the modem and the router are made by the same people!  So I spend most of my time today detailling what is the issue with the hw rather than testing it with our network. Bloody hell!! The manufacturer should pay me to troubleshoot their problems.  Thank you Net###m for wasting my time.    

						
</post>

<date>20,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   10 rounds in 22mins 27 seconds  I think that is an awesome time. Man it is amazing how 2 days of rest really help your body recupperate. So now I can approximately run 5 kM in 22 mins.  My Plan is to increase my distance to 10 kM (20 rounds) and once I reach the goal, I'll cut down on the distance and focus on the speed.  Fingers cross, I only have 3 weeks to increase my fitness to compete on the  urlLink run    

						
</post>

<date>20,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   YUMMY!!   Nothing beats a newly roasted pig!  I bet this pig would even impress  urlLink Mistress Wena    We got this little piggy for my Grandma's 80th birthday recently. Man I could not believe how quickly the pig disappear. I swear in less than 30 mins the whole pig was gone!  This is a Young suckling Pig, so the best bit is the crackling (or pig skin). Not the most healthy food in the world, but when who cares, you only live once.      

						
</post>

<date>17,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   This is my First ArtHouse Play "Departures and Arrivals".     We were invited by a friend who was in the play. The play was created by the Actors factory, where our friend was studying. I must confess that I had no real expectations of the play.     Atleast they have a booklet, so atleast now I know what the play was about. The plot sounded good.    The Warehouse This is the warehouse where the play will be staged. It was a bit freaky since the only noise I could here was the nearby dogs barking. It was dark and cold and the only light we had was the moonlight... (Slasher movie in the making...yikes!)    The Entrance.  What can I say, my expectation of the play was getting less and less. We had to climb up a flight of creaky old stairs and search of the stage. The place smells like a run down building too!    The Stage. Impressive isn't it?  What you see is basically all the props that was used in the play. Improvisation was the key I guess.    The Seatings. 7 seats per row and there was 3 rows on each side of the aisle. We were late so we were seated on the front row! Great seating eh?! All I have to say is that the seats were not made for big people, it reminded me of the tiny seat in primary school.   The Actors Pic of our Actor friend. I was was too close to the stage to take any more pics during the play. I thought the flash might be too distracting the the actors. Each actors played multiple roles, so you can really see the range of each actors talent.  All in all I must say that I was surprise that I actually enjoyed the play. It was funny and the characters were actually believable.    

						
</post>

<date>17,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						     You are Form 0,  Phoenix : The Eternal.   "And The Phoenix's cycle had reached zenith, so he consumed himself in fire.  He emerged from his own ashes, to be forever immortal."   Some examples of the Phoenix Form are Quetzalcoatl (Aztec), Shiva (Indian), and Ra-Atum (Egyptian). The Phoenix is associated with the concept of life, the number 0, and the element of fire. His sign is the eclipsed sun.  As a member of Form 0, you are a determined individual.  You tend to keep your sense of optomism, even through tough times and have a positive outlook on most situations.  You have a way of looking at going through life as a journey that you can constantly learn from. Phoenixes are the best friends to have because they cheer people up easily.    urlLink   Which Mythological Form Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    Got this site from  urlLink Wena  

						
</post>

<date>17,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   8 rounds in 19mins and 02 seconds.  I guess I am not surprise that this time I gain another minute for the extra 2 rounds.  I didn't train for the weekend. Yeah I know I am lazy but I really needed my body to rest after 4 days of pushing it.  I'll have to do 10 rounds today.    

						
</post>

<date>17,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   If you are geeking around and you want something to read, check this out " urlLink DOS " This is an awesome story about Denial of Service.    

						
</post>

<date>16,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   It is closing time for me. Everyone is already out for drinks so I can log out early and go for my job =)  Plans for the weekend?  Going to an amatuer play tonight Birthday party tomorrow night Probably dinner with the "inlaws" on sunday ...yikes!  Hopefully I will get some pics and do some show and tell on monday.  Have a nice weekends fellow bloggers!!   

						
</post>

<date>16,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Made good progress today. Ran 6 rounds around the field in 14mins and 07 sec  This means I did not slow down as much in the last 2 circuit! awesome...Hopefully I can keep this up.  It is strange but after the 3rd run I was in the running grove.... I could not remember what I was thinking or how many rounds I have done. I had to check my stopwatch to estimate how many rounds I had ran. This was a good feeling since I felt that if I wanted to I could run for another couple of rounds!  But I've got to remember to keep it an even pace and not to push myself too much. We shall see how my body copes with additional 2 circuits!  Till tomorrow.  

						
</post>

<date>15,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink I am William Wallace, and before me, I see a whole ARMY of my countrymen here to battle the English. Ay, fight and you may die, run and you'll live. At least a while. And dying in your beds many years from now, would you be willing to trade all the days from this day to that for one chance, just one chance to come back here and tell our enemies that they may take our lives.... but they'll never take our FREEDOM!!   I remembered when I was in Scotland, I was travelling with a bunch of kids from US and we had a chance to visit one of the battle site where William Wallace fought. We were divided into 2 groups, the English and the Scots, and we replayed the scenes from the movie urlLink BraveHeart . God it was amazing. In the midst of the Scottish Highlands, you can really feel the battle which have long pass.  Everytime I hear the speech from the movie, I still feel goose bumps on my arm and neck.  what a movie!  What a Man!! What a Country!!!  

						
</post>

<date>15,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   It's nearly time to knock off. My boss is already off to take his train off. I am pretty much by myself now.   Just like any other day at work... Work till lunch and we have a quick game of touch footy on the local field. I scored twice! yeah!!  I have a few scratches from the dive but it was well worth it. After running around for 40 mins, I had my sandwiches for lunch. Ham, lettuce, mushrooms and cheese sandwiches. Man I miss Malaysian food!! Even the worst food in Malaysia with be less bland than what I am having now..... But I guess it is healtier!  I think I have been sitting infront of the computer for too long... I am gradually getting a "gut" ...yikes!! The running will hopefully help me. I am thinking of a Gym again, but it is just bloody expensive and I can never invest a couple of hours everyday ....   what should I do ?  Just get off my arse and do something, as Bruce Lee said "Simplicity is the shortest distance between two points".     

						
</post>

<date>15,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   First night:  2 circuit: 4mins 33 seconds  Second Day:  4 circuit: 9mins 23 seconds  I am hoping to increase 2 circuit everyday, since 1 circuit is approximately 1 kM. I need to able to run 6kM in 20 mins and I only have 1 month to train.  wish me luck   

						
</post>

<date>15,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   It is strange but lately I have been feeling that I am lost in a maze and I don't really know where I am going. I have a good job with an ok pay, I have a lovely partner who loves me dearly and I have a good circle of friends who would do anything for me and vice verse.   Yet I feel incomplete.  Yet I feel like I have not achieve anything in my life.   I can't see myself doing the same thing I am doing now for the rest of my life. I know that a life span of a IT person is not that long anyway, so I know that one day my usefulness for this company will expired, or my company will disappear.  If I leave this sorry world now, what would I have contributed to this world. Who have I touched? I fear that one day people will realise my uselessness and I will be thrown away like used garbage.  This are the question which echo and resound in my head.   Sometimes I wish I am already an old man with his grandkids sitting next to him, to know that I do not need to prove anything anymore. All I do is relax and enjoy life.   Whereas sometimes I wish I was a teenager again so that I could choose the road less travel. To go back to Malaysia and see how my life would pan out.   Is this just crazy talk or just the greener pasture syndrome?  

						
</post>

<date>14,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Met this amazing man on Saturday in the city. He is an 83 year old Detroit born gentleman. John is still doing what he loves best, which is meeting new people and cutting silhouette of people. With just a pair of scissors, a sheet of black paper he can create a silhouette of you in 2 minutes.   On his display he has created silhouette of Bill Clinton, The late Princess Diana and the irreplacable  urlLink Picolo!  So here it is, my ugly mug... =P     What amazes me is not only is skills but his tenacity for life. He says that he still travels around the country and world. He has a shop in literraly every state, so his next stop is Tassie. He has been doing this for the last 64 years and he still loves it. His life story would be an amazing read!  I feel blessed to have met such a man. 

						
</post>

<date>14,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Disney is planing to make a move adaptation to the awesome HitchHikers Guide series. But it seems that they have a few hurdles to overcome. I am sure bloody Hollywood will try to change the story... urlLink BBC News    

						
</post>

<date>13,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   I hate my early morning start!  5 AM !! Just to test some web code on the net. Who cares about customer impact =P I am sure they won't mind if they can check their emails for a few hours ...heh heh ....  My biggest problem is that if I wake up early and check the code at home, I have to go to work the same time and work for 8 hours, whereas if I go to the office and check the code there...I can go home early. Logic?? And of course once I wake up, I can't go back to bed. Now it is the afternoon and I am cranky and tired and all I want to do is go home and sleep....  emmm....maybe chocolate will help....   

						
</post>

<date>13,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Just found a nifty site:  urlLink grouphug.us .  A site where you can anonymously confess till your hearts contend....   It is like an online confessions =P  I think this is perfect for the immaculate  urlLink minishorts.  

						
</post>

<date>13,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Here I am, lunch time and I am thinking this is a great day to start my Training for the  urlLink JPMorganChase Corporate Challenge  (yeah I know it is a bit late, but I think I still have time). It was slightly cloudy when I started my run. Then lord and behold the sky turned black and it poured! I managed to run 2 rounds on the football field before I had to call it quits...  Jeez it is cold! Thank god the A/C in the office is warm and I am cowering in my little cubicle and try to warm up. I think I'll get something warm to eat now....  So how was everyones weekend?   

						
</post>

<date>12,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						     urlLink      This is the most amazing and colourful musical I have ever seen! The singing was soul wrenching and the costume and the set was breathtaking! The theatre was pack with eager fans and I was lucky enough to get some tickets for the dress rehersals. It cost a bomb but I think it was well worth it.     We sat on the top left hand section.  It was not the best view in the world but it was close enough to the action. There were tribal dancing, singing, action, romance and comedy. I think that it might be a bit scary in some sections for the kiddies. The lady who played Rafiki was amazing. Her voice was haunting!   I tried to see it when I was in London a couple of years ago and it was sold out, so when it was out in Sydney, I had to check it out. I can't believe that it could beat the movie but after I saw the musical, I have to say that it rules. They did change some of the songs and scenes from the movie, but it generally follow the same story.   If you ever have an opportunity to check this musical out, do yourself a favour and go!           

						
</post>

<date>10,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Hey Does anyone know where I can get free hosting for images? You know what they say ... A picture paints a thousand words. 

						
</post>

<date>09,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   I just had a chance to finally played with one of this beauty! A  urlLink 12 inch Apple Power Book . If you have a chance to play with one, I dearly recommend it. I am PC user, but hell this baby rocks! Titanium casing, Small and Compact. I think it looks better and slimmer than the Sony Vaio. It has inbuilt WI-FI capability, USB, Firewire etc.... I think I am in love!  I know I sound like a sales-man, but I have to say that this baby rocks! Now all I need is get a pay rise, save up 4 grand and then I maybe able to afford it.  On second thought, I'll just stay with my desktop... and my pirated software =P   

						
</post>

<date>09,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   The rest of the world may think that the World Cup means soccer, but in Oz the World Cup is  urlLink The Rugby World Cup . In a few hours we will be celebrating the month long competition of the World Cup.   20 teams all around the World is here in Oz to compete for this coverted prize!  Giant men going head to head with each other!  ROCK ON!!  Tonight Oz is going against Argentina!  Aussie Aussie Aussie!! 

						
</post>

<date>09,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   I had one of the most diverse group of people together yesterday for dinner. We had the newly married couple.  The Single friend The Married couple with a young 1 year old daughter  and a recently divorce male friend.  It is amazing how we are see things and how we interact. All of the around the same age around the 20's  It was a great dinner, some home cook meal (from yours truly, which I think  urlLink wena  would be proud). Our conversations went from the dating scene now, family and of course Governor Arnie.  Metrosexual is the key word for guys. You have to be metrosexual to pick up now. You have to wear labels, shave (everywhere!!) and definitely workout and of course money. You go and have facials and used the solarium.  Clubbing and bars is the norm on the weekends and weekdays! It seems that we no longer look for the quite ones who work hard, but we look for those who can play hard and dress like Brad pitt.  But when you are married, that is when everything changed. You want someone who is hardworking and caring. You want to save up so that you can pay for your mortgage. Have you seen the cost of baby's clothings? Jeez!! louise!! it is atrocious! The baby may only wear it for 3 months for the clothings and it will cost you 60 to 100 bucks!  I can never understand how you can justify buying label cloths for your babies... it is just not logical.  Nothing is cheap now a days and if you are not a high paying executive... all you can do it work your butt off.  Welcome to the Rat Race.             

						
</post>

<date>07,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						    Generation Y tribes    Glitterazi: Largely conscience free and only interested in themselves.  Burbanites: Traditional values, with an emphasis on relationships, religion and family.  Drifters: Detached, introverted, and lacking drive.  Life junkies: Relationships and sex appeal are priorities as they pack as much into life as possible.  Walleteers: Focused on career and financial security.  Renegades: Live life on the edge, rejecting responsible behaviour in favour of adventure.    Stole this from  urlLink News  

						
</post>

<date>07,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   I find myself disturbed by the statement  urlLink she  said, "People are sadistic fools, hungry for sad stories".  I don't believe that, I can't believe that everyone is a bad as she thinks. I agree that we are all  kehpoh , it is in our nature to stop and look if there is an accident,  it is our nature to stop and listen when there is a loud argument occurring, but it is also our nature to celebrate when there is something to celebrate.   How many times have you been a restaurant where a birthday party is on and when they sing "Happy Birthday ..." and clap, you would clap too?  We are just a curious species of animal. Let’s say you walk pass your neighbour’s house everyday and you see their child playing on the driveway. You see her playing literally everyday. As time goes by you see her learn how to walk and learn how to cycle and you think wow she is pretty good. Then imagine if one day you saw her on the ground crying...what do you do?   I would stop and ask her if she was alright... I would stop and see if I could do anything to help her. I am not stopping because I was SADISTIC. I am not stopping because I am a FOOL I am not stopping because I am hungry for a sad story.  I stop because I care enough for this little girl to find out if I could help her in her hour of need. Nothing more, Nothing less.  And If she thinks that makes me a FOOL, then I am happy to be a FOOL.    

						
</post>

<date>07,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   First is was birthday, then it was graduations.... now it is engagement parties and Weddings!! Yikes!! Are we getting that old? In the last 12 months I have attended over half a dozens weddings and engagements!! Whats with the deal? Don't they have anything else they want to spend their money on?  Most of my friends is already married... so that meants the next gathering would probably be baby showers!!.... ;)  The only good thing about such gatherings are the food ... Lots of food and drinks... Yummy for the tummy!   

						
</post>

<date>03,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   I can see that most bloggers have been busy posting all weekend ;) and as for me I have been silent. Well that is because I only have a 56K connection at home and I can be bother to wait for the uploads and download ... very impatient lah !   After 4 years, where I spend 5 days a week,  9 to 10 hours a day infront of a computer and access the internet I made a rule not to spend my weekend on the internet. I try to interact with other people and try to enjoy the outdoors if I can and even get a tan if I can =P I think my monitor tan is getting a bit too much for me.  Also the Rugby League Grand Final was on sunday, Sydney Rosters vs Penrith Panthers! We can't miss that can we!  

						
</post>

<date>03,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink   A BLUE Dragon Lies Beneath!       My inner dragon is the Water Elemental dragon. If there ever was a draconic example of a supple attitude, my inner dragon is it. Just sit back and go with the flow. *contented sigh* Click the image to try the Inner Dragon Online Quiz for yourself.     

						
</post>

<date>03,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Wanted to go out after work, but my partner and I were too lazy and it was raining like cats and dogs...So we decided to rent a couple of videos and vege out. The first movie was   urlLink One HOur Photo . Robin Williams is trying to diversify again and I think he succeeded again. I think that the trailer for the movie was a red herring, which is a great idea. I love Robin williams movies so I can't really critique his movies =P But I must say that the bloody eyes were FREAKY!!!..... Yikes!  The second movie was  urlLink Cradle 2 the Grave . I know, the movie is old, but didn't have the time to check it out when it came out of the cinema. Jet Li, DMX and Mark Dacascos.. Wats up my brother ! I think that Mark a way better actor than most martial Artist / actor and it is sad to see him play some weak ass character.  Some nice action, but you can't really beat HK action movies!  The only upside to the movie is when  urlLink Gabrielle Union  started doing a strip tease ....Youch!! Hubba hubba.... Of course at the time I was not gawking... because if I was ... I would have been blinded by the boss lady sitting next to me.  Hey my question is, if they flaunt it ... why can't I see it =P  All in all a lazy night out, but quite enjoyable =P   

						
</post>

<date>02,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Its a long weekend for me... so I wish all my new found bloggers a beautiful weekend and I'll see you all in a few days.  May God Stand between you and harms way.   Picolo  

						
</post>

<date>02,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   With an eerie quietness, the men filed on to the field. The sun has left these fools, the cool and wet wind drives cool stakes into hearts of men. These men are no warriors, they have no skills on this field and yet they enter with heads held high and determinations with their eyes...."Strength and Honour me brothers..."  The battle began with no fanfare and soon bodies clashes like a slow beating drum. There were no weapons, just their legs and their arms and their BLOOD. Hagged breath soon filled the sky.   The battle soon became a massacre and before it began, it was over. The cries of victory could be heard from the heaven and the tears of weak seeps into the hollow earth.  We won 6 to 4. Oh how sweet is victory....     

						
</post>

<date>02,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   There is one thing I hate about Australia is the ridiculous time the retail shops are open. Most of the retail shops closes at 5.30 pm and the only time the it is extended is on Thursday (till 9.00pm - That is why we call Thursday Night shopping)  What this means is that every joe who is working on normal hours (9 to 5) has one day to shop. This means everything shopping centre is packed with people, the pay counter is 20 man deep and car parking is hell. It is time like this I wish I was back in malaysia where all the shops are open till late.. and normal people can shop after work.   I really don't know how retail shops here justify their opening times. They must see that most sales occurs after office hours, and yet they only open during office hours! Don't they want to make more money?? Where is the logic?  Thats my rant for the day... I am now off to play friday afternoon soccer =) I let you know how we go....      

						
</post>

<date>02,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Now I have seen it all.... There is a  urlLink World Championship for Rock Paper Scissors   in Toronto this month!  Does anyone know someone who live in Canada, who can confirm this phenomena??  I want to know how they survive high school when all their friends finds out that he/she was in the comp.   

						
</post>

<date>01,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Check this out!! Halle Berry is going to be Catwoman and LOTR: Return of the King preview is out!!  urlLink UGO.com   I can't wait for the finale. Finally Fantasy fans can enjoy an  A  grade film rather than suffer another crap like D&D, Willow and Beowulf. 

						
</post>

<date>01,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Well what can I say, I had a few comments on my Q&A yesterday, and I think I made someone *blush* too... I think that is a good thing. This must be my first time. I think this is also my first time I ever really thought about the questions before I answer. I try to answer it as truthfully as I can.   One can ask what is the truth, isn't it true that one mans truth is another man lies. We all wear emotional masks. Different facade for each occasion, one for work, one for family, one for friends and one on the web. We all uses half truth in our everyday life... we even have a word for it...White Lies.  From my very limited experience with blogging,I find that it is hard to share, it is hard to write down your feeling, your thoughts, your hope and your dreams. We hide behind our alias, so that we can find the courage to overcome our fears.  I think Mark Twain put it best:  "Courage is resistance to fear, mastery of fear, not absence of fear."     I think that is why I am intrigue by the ramblings of  urlLink minishorts , I think that there is some truth in all the false bravado.  I think I have ramble too long... so I going going back to work now =P    

						
</post>

<date>01,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Just read a hoax news which was bloody funny. The title of the news was also an eye catcher =P  urlLink "Kaneel Shatters Masturbation World Record!"   First I thought to myself that, jeez they will put anything on the news this days... then when I click on bottom link, I was taken to a site called   urlLink www.fakeawish.com  Man did I get my chain pulled!! But you must say that it is bloody funny. I must say that the creator has quite a limited imaginations in terms of fake news. 

						
</post>

<date>01,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Oh yeah, did I mention that I can bake too =) I made the most awesome banana cake last night. All from raw ingredients not those dodgy cake in a box. The secret ingredients are Sour Cream and Milo....yummy=)  Heh heh I am so happy with it that I am thinking of sending a sample to  urlLink wena  for her critique.    

						
</post>

<date>01,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Ahh finally I have answered all the questions, graciously provided by the immaculate  urlLink minishorts.  It took me half a day just to write down the answer. I know some of the answers is not complete, but I hope this is a start. So without futher ado, lets bring it on:      A bit about yourself please.     I am Chinese/Malaysian/Australian. Born in KL and lived in Taman Tun Dr Ismail for over 12 years. Family migrated to Sydney, Australia in ’88. Survived an all boys High School and Uni. I have been a pool boy, warehouse boy, chemist, and now a computer nerd and I just pass a quarter of a century. I have been to a few places in my life and I can say without a doubt Malaysian food is still the best! I miss the food, I miss the language and I miss the people. It is weird but only now was I able to appreciate the beauty that is Malaysia. Oh don’t get me wrong, I love Sydney too. It is my second home, but I guess some part of my heart is still bound with KL. I haven’t been to KL for a few years so I don’t know it I can survive the hustle and bustle anymore but I sure want to try it one day.  When I was young I was bullied for my Asian looks and my Malaysian slang. For years I had to learn to hide it, to assimilate. Now the tolerance is better and I find people are more open to changes and differences. After so many years of assimilating… it is hard to be an “Asian” again. To an Aussie, you are not an aussie, and to an Asian, you are not one either.  I still speaks Cantonese with my Grandma, but I can’t say I am fluent anymore =( My Bahasa Malaysia has been returned to my teachers, so I guess all I have is English.   So what else can I say about myself, currently my life consists of work and more work. I want to travel, I want to study again.      How did you first encounter the blog kind? (And btw, from a linguistics PoV, its very interesting that you labelled blogs as ' the blog-kind')    This is what happens when you have access to fast internet connection all day long. I normally download rip movies or s/w (of course piracy is wrong…not). But recently I felt a longing for Malaysia. The people, the food and my old home!  So I started googling. My first blog stop was SixthSeal. His blog what can I say, it was an eye opener, especially veritas’s log. His adventure returning home and going around KL made me really home sick. It was like being there myself, on a private tour of KL which I have not seen for a long long time.  The next I found the minishorts (I’ll talk about her in Q5) and then another favourite blog is from wena. Oh the food!! Man I salivate everytime I read her blog.      So what cyber-type plans do you have now that you've joined the big happy family of mad-cap bloggers?    I really have no plans in the near distant future, I feel like I am a newborn taking my first few steps. I am still  learning the etiquette of blogging(so be patient with me). Hopefully I will be welcomed into this family of bloggers and boldly go where no one has gone before… (Number One Engage!....) One thing I do know is, this new journey will definitely help me find who I am.       If minishorts were a fairy and could grant you three wishes, what would they be? (Don't go say things like 'I wish for another three wishes' and so on, ya?)        I wish I could have the knowledge and experience I have now and go back in time (10 years only) and relive my past. To mend my many mistakes and to take the  urlLink road less traveled . I know it is an impossible wish, but what a wish it would be if you could. As most people would attest we all have regrets and past we can’t let go, so I am sure you know what I mean.     I wish I have the strength and patience to overcome all obstacles I have and going to have in my life To live a life which may not be easy but atleast it is right by my own ideals.     To meet and study with Bruce Lee ( urlLink Truth has no path. Truth is living and, therefore, changing. )     of course if I can’t have any of that, then give me the wealth of Bill Gates, body of (younger) Jet Li and the amazing wit of Homer J Simpson =P        So what keeps you coming back to minishorts? (I'm intrigued mah, why he leaves that kind of funny messages on my blog.)    Ahh minishorts you are an interesting creature. I am intrigue with your blog. I am fascinated with your honesty. I am drawn by your sadness and your loneliness. Like a moth drawn to a candle of a flame, you are captivating. I haven’t yet unravel why I come back everyday to check out how you are, but yet I feel I have to.        Again I want to pass my thanks to minishorts for letting me be involve with her Q&A.  Oh and here are some of the rules for the Q&A: 1. If you want to participate, leave a comment saying "interview me."  2. I will respond by asking you five questions - each person's will be different.  3. You will update your journal with the answers to the questions.  4. You will include this explanation and an offer to interview others in the same post.   

						
</post>

<date>27,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   I woke up 5am today! Why? Well that is a life of a QA. We have to wake up early in the morning and test new production changes. Of course we can’t change any production system during normal working hours because that would impact our users, so here I am to test the new codes. The good thing about is, I am the only person in the building at the moment, no noisy workers and no one to bother you while you are blogging =P  I completed my work at 7 am, so I am now having my breakfast, milo cereal I brought yesterday. Actually the cereal is not bad, different from the usual all bran cereal I get, but heh I have to try something new… you only live once.   Guess what, it is my birthday this weekend ! Yikes! I am going to be 2& years old! Man am I old… I remember when I was 10, I would looked up to my older cousins in the 20s and stare at them in awe. Now that I am in the same age bracket, all I know is that I am still lost in this wide world and I still do not know what to do with my life.   Every year I go through this crisis where I try to justify to myself that I have achieve something in my life after another year has gone by. To tell myself that I have not squandered another year away on procrastinations and pure laziness.  What have I done this year?  I am still working in the same company (4 years now) I have moved out of home I did not further my studies I got married I am broke  I visited Thailand I work 6 days a week I own a car of my own (Toyota) I have no share portfolio or financial plan I am saving up to buy a place of my first home  So what now? Have I wasted my year or have I achieve something? How do I quantify my achievement and failures? If so why should I?  

						
</post>

<date>22,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						      Last night I went back home to have dinner with my parents. It was a cold and rainy night, so it was great to have a nice home cook meal. We had mee hoon in soup with meat balls and fish balls. It was a simple dish my grandma made but it tasted wonderful so I had 2 servings.   After the wonderful dinner, my mum had to wreck the evening by making me clean up old room and throw away all my stuff which I don’t need. This is want of the reason I rarely see my folks, because they always have something for me to do, when I am back home. I have left home for close to a year and everytime I go back home, I am asked to either fixed their computer for clean/fix something up. So I guess last night was no different. They had packed all my old things into a few boxes and my mum wants to minimize the number of boxes, so she asked me to check each boxes and throw away anything I did not want.  Thank god that she did not ask me to throw away my extensive collections of comics. Oh yeah why don’t I just take all my stuff back to my place, why I would love to, but the place I am renting at the moment can’t even fit a tenth of what I have. Anyway during my clean up I found a few interesting things.  I guess it wasn’t surprising that I still had all my notes from high school and my notes why I was in Uni, but the most amazing find was a letter from my old best friend from Malaysia Wong Li Soong. Man I have not seen or heard from him for over 10 years. In those times we used to write letter to each other every month (note 1988 before GUI emails clients). Man we were so young an innocent then, it was one of the saddest time in my life. I had to leave all my friends and not just move to another town but to another country. I remember the first few months after our migrations, I used to secretly cry in my bed, because I missed my old friends and also because Aussie kids were laughing and bullying me because I talked funny. I remember that I was the only Asian kid in the whole class.  But what am I to do? I was still in primary school; I can’t go back to Malaysian since my family is now in Australia, and so I was stuck here. It was hard, but I guess it is true in what they say, if it doesn’t kill you, it just makes you stronger. So I had to learn to speak Australian, try to lose my “Lah” and try to fit in.   In the course of trying to survive my new environment, I began to lose touch with my old friends from Malaysia. In the end I was only in contact with 3 friends Li Soong, Teo Eugene and JM (who eventually became my first love). I went back to Malaysia in 93/94 to visit them, man it was great. To talk about the old times in school and to see how much they have changed. Sadly after that get together we all started to begin to prepare for our tertiary education. The last I heard Li Soong went to Canada to study and Eugene, I had no idea where he is.   So anyway now here I am reminiscing of the good old days and trying to figure out what should I throw and what should I keep.   Should I keep the old letters I had from my old friends from Malaysia? If so why? Should I keep the old lecture notes? Or should I just trash everything and begin a new…?  

						
</post>

<date>20,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Finally the first  urlLink Australian Idol  series is finish, we now know who is the winner and we can finally go back to enjoying some good old American serials =P  For the last 6 months, my TV was commandeer by the "Boss", so that she could watch her Aussie Idol. After last night finale I thought I would find some respite from the constant karaoke singing, but I fear not, it has now been announced that there will a International Idol and another American Idol coming out soon!! (as early as next year)  What am I to do? How can I survive another barrage of losers singing old musics??..  

						
</post>

<date>18,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   To celebrate the wallabies trashing of New Zealand All blacks here are some jokes to poke fun on the all blacks:  Q. What do you do for a drowning New Zealand Rugby player? A. Nothing. You could drag him to the top, but he'll choke anyway.  ===========================  Q. What's the difference between the All blacks and an arsonist? A. An arsonist wouldn't waste 5 matches.  ============================  The All Blacks are bringing out a new bra! Plenty of support, soft and no CUP!!!  ============================  Did you hear that the NZ Post Office has had to recall their latest stamps? They had pictures of the All Blacks players on them. People couldn't figure out which side to spit on.  ============================  Did you hear about the Kiwi politician who was found dead in a All Black jersey?  The police had to dress him up in women's underwear in order to save his family from the embarrassment.  ============================  Four surgeons are taking a coffee break. The first one says, "Accountants are the best to operate on because when you open them up everything inside them is numbered."  The second surgeon says, "Nah, librarians are the best; everything inside them is in alphabetical order."  Third surgeon says, "Try electricians. Everything inside them is colour-coded."  The fourth one says, "I prefer New Zealand Rugby players. They're heartless, spineless, gutless and their heads and bums are interchangeable." 

						
</post>

<date>18,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Courtesy of  urlLink Joy tech.   urlLink     

						
</post>

<date>17,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   I finally saw matrix revolution on the weekend. I must say that I am disappointed with the lack of action and wire-fu in the Third instalment of the series, but overall it is still a great movie and a great series. Man is Persephone a hottie or what! It is such a waste that she doesn’t even have any significant camera time on the movie.   And what happen to the Morpheus, he looked like he has gain a few pounds and lost all his faith and strength? In the first 2 film he was portrayed as the indomitable character, but in the third film he looked like a scared little bystander, even the “kid” saw more action than him.   In the end, I am happy to say that I really enjoyed the film. It is definitely not a Hollywood ending which is always great to see. I know lots of people really like to dissect the movie and find the hidden  urlLink meaning , but who really cares. It is a movie, if you enjoy it then it is a good movie.  

						
</post>

<date>17,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Got the link from  urlLink wena , looked interesting =)                ISTJ  - "Trustee". Decisiveness in practical affairs. Guardian of time- honored institutions. Dependable. 11.6% of total population.  
</post>

<date>13,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   10. Being told to "think outside the box" when you're in a  freakin box all day long.  9. Not being able to check e-mail attachments without turning  around to see who's behind you.  8. Cubicle walls do not offer much protection  from any  kind of gun fire.  7. That nagging feeling that if you press the right button,  you'll get a piece of cheese.  6. Lack of roof rafters for the noose.  5. The walls are too close together for the hammock to work  right.  4. 23 power cords - 1 outlet.  3. Prison cells are not only bigger, they also have beds.  2. The carpet has been there since 1976 and shows more signs of  life than your coworkers.  And the number 1 drawback to working in a cubicle....  1. You can't walk out and slam the door when you quit. 

						
</post>

<date>11,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   My official time was 28 mins 17 seconds, but it took me about a minute before I cross over the starting line =) Not bad I guess, but I think I could have done better. Remember that I had been having issue with my foot, well it was inflame by the 4 kM mark... I think I have torn a ligament of something on my toe, I'll have to speak to a physio later today to check it out. I am still limping so I am guessing that it is pretty major.  In any case it was a good run, I had to walk for about 5 mins during the race to give my foot a rest, because the pain was excruatiating, but I still completed the run which I am quite happy of.  The fastest time was 16 mins I think and in my group/company I was the third fastest, so I am pretty proud of that =) Anyway you can checkout some pics of the event on the official  urlLink JPMorgan Site .  

						
</post>

<date>11,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   It is tommorow at 6.30 PM. So hopefully after my month of training, I 'll be able to finish this race on a good time =) wish me luck! =)  My time last night was  22 min and 29 seconds in 10 rounds.  So I am hoping for such time tomorrow.  I'll let you all know Thursday =)  Cheers   

						
</post>

<date>10,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   An online  urlLink diary of a London call girl   Of course it is still not as interesting as the adventure of  urlLink Sixth Seal  =) 

						
</post>

<date>10,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   This is baby Eion. Nothing really shows the beauty of the world like a new born baby. May God bless you and your family little Eion.     Hush child, Let your mommy sleep into the night until we rise Hush child, Let me soothe the shining tears that gather in your eyes  Hush child, I won't leave I'll stay with you to cross this Bridge of Sighs Hush child, I can help the look of accusation in your eyes In your eyes  The world is broken and now All in sorrow Wise men hang their heads  Hush child, Let your mommy sleep into the night until we rise Hush child, All the strength I'll need to find, I'll find inside your eyes In your eyes  ~Sting~ 

						
</post>

<date>10,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Got this from  urlLink Wena .      A kind soul!  urlLink Which Journal Site Are You?    

						
</post>

<date>10,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Friday   Man that was a bad day. Had a fight with the boss/wife in the morning. Heated words were exchange and angers flared. It was a silly argument, but I guess all arguments are silly. I was late to work, and I could not think or work the whole day. Thank god that we reconcile later in the evening when we both at home.   Man it was scary, cause I walked out of the argument and went to work... So I did not know what she did. I felt empty the whole day and I was scared that I might find all her things gone, but luckily it didn't.   We are not OK now, so it all ended well...Woo Hoo!!  Saturday  We woke up at 10am and had a quick breakfast and clean up out apartment. Man I hate vacuuming! The only good thing is that the apartment is really small, so the vacuuming is kept to a minimum.  Then we went to visit one of out friend who just gave birth to a baby boy. I got some pics, so when I have time at home, I'll upload pic of Little EION.  Then we went back to my old home and visit my Grandma and have some of Grandma's cooking !! Yummy! Man was I hungry =) Made sure grandma was ok and then went home.  Sunday  Worked at my dad's shop. It was bloody hot and busy! I do not like summer! Bloody flies! After work, we went to Church. I am now a choir boy for the local church... Woo pee =P Met some friend from SFC and we had dinner at my apartment. Cooked some yummy food but as always forgot to take the pics. 

						
</post>

<date>06,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Yes I have too much time on my hand. Yes I can't think of anything to write. Yes this may be the  urlLink Longest URL  And Care factor = ZERO! =)   

						
</post>

<date>06,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Courage is resistance to fear Mastery of fear Not absence of fear.  ~Mark Twain~   

						
</post>

<date>06,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink Minishorts  asked and so I comply. Enjoy      Regular underwear or G: Don't care unless I am allow to see it.    painted nails or not: not   Bra or sports bra: Is there a difference?   Cute n' mysterious or wild n' sexy: Cute and Sexy   Dressy or casual: Depends on the occasion. Dressy only applies for functions.   Dark or blonde hair: Dark hair. Blonde hair just looks too ditzy for me.   Long or short hair: Long hair definitely!   Dark or light eyes: Dark Eyes. Eyes you can get lost in   Long or short nails: Short nails. You know how painful it is when you get scratch with long nails! OUCH!   Hat or no hat: Why hide your beautiful hair under a hat?   Good or bad girl: normal?   Fat or thin: Neither. Someone who can be comfortable with their weight! You know how hard it is to handle a girl who have weight issues?!!   Hair up or down: Whatever she wants it to be. Your hair, your choice.   Jewellery on or none: If you have it, flaunt it.   Short or tall: I am 183, so you must be tall enough for me to kiss you without bending too much =P   Curly or straight hair: Again whatever takes your fancy.   Pants or dress: Practicality is the key. You are not going to wear a dress on a bush walk and you are not wearing a pants on a formal dinner.   Tan or fair: natural    Freckles or none: No preference   Indoor or outdoor: Both. Love the beach, bush and the bedroom.   Shy or outgoing: Outgoing. Carpe Diem!    

						
</post>

<date>06,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   One of our Portal developer is leaving tomorrow and we have to think of something to engrave on his cup... and here are a few suggestions: [only funny for geeks]  (1)	The Ron Jeremy of Infranet (2)	The Infranet Hedgehog (3)	This mug to be jammed up an Infranet poid (4)	Show me the flist (5)	Zzzzzz I was just having a test-nap (6)	Stand back! This mug may contain core dumps 

						
</post>

<date>05,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   It is out! Man I can't wait to see it, but I am guessing I won't have time till next week. I read on the of review " urlLink Matrix Revolution Review " and it sounds promising.  Trinity is going to kick butt!! YEAH!! 

						
</post>

<date>05,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   10 rounds in 23 mins and 37 seconds  NO improvement..yikes!  The race is on the next wednesday @1830 on Centennial Park. I am told that I am going to get a free company T-shirts... woo pee doo =P 

						
</post>

<date>05,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Recently my local Chinese video store has a sale on, so I brought 5 VCD for 38 aussie bucks, which is quite cheap. Bare in mind the only Hong Kong movies that I watch is Jet, Jackie and Stephen Chow movies, so my knowledge on HK movies are pretty limited to action movies. So this time to extend my repertoire I tried some drama/romantic comedy and/or comedy action movie.  Surprisingly I last night saw a very thought provoking movie which made me think about my life. The Movie was called " urlLink Tempting Heart ". It was made in 1999 and supposedly won some awards, but I had no idea when I saw the movie yesterday.  The Movie was basically about a Love Triangle, but not a typical love story.  There was a question which was pose in the beginning of the film, "If you believe that fate decide who you meet and love, does fate also decide when you break-up".  This question echo and resound in my head, it reminded me of the past, reminded me of my first. As they all say you could never forget your first and trust me I tried. Is it wrong to think about your past, about your first when you are with someone else.   I have known her for over 20 years, since primary schools in KL. When I left for Oz, we kept intouch and we finally got together when I came back to KL for my summer holidays. Man was it bliss...After so many years pining someone it was amazing to finally be together. The months we were together went by too quickly and in the end it was time for me to go back to Oz. The pain was excruciating. I could not do any work for months, we were talking on the phone every month and we were writing letters (note: pre-email era...yikes I am old!) to each other every day. I guess it was not surprising that in the end it was too much for her. The waiting, the loneliness, to have someone but yet you can't touch or talk to them when you want. Long Distance Relationship never works.  We promise to keep intouch, we were still good old friends. She even came to Oz to study, but since she was on the other side of the country, it was not easy to see her. We were both in Uni and that took most of out time.  At this stage I still had feeling for her. One time I even planned to go across the country to surprise her. I save up all my money and I check for accommodations and flight ticket, I even got a pressy for her birthday. But in the end, I chicken out... I don't know why but I didn’t do it. I guess I fear that if I go and see her and get rejected again, it would kill me. So I took the easier road.  Years later when we finally meet, it was when she came over to Syd for a holiday. She called me up and ask me if I wanted to meet. And I said, of course. I could remember how excited I was, how much I wanted to see her. When I met her at the lobby of the hotel... I also met Boyfriend.   

						
</post>

<date>04,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   I am finding that it is getting harder and harder to blog. Sometimes I can't find time to think let alone blog and sometimes when I have time, I have no idea what to say. It seems that all my time is spend working, run, watch TV and eat. My work is boring, the challenges of a new job looks more and more appealing everyday. This is why I admire my fellow bloggers  urlLink Sixseal  who seem to be always invited to parties and going to some place interesting,  urlLink minishorts , who always seem to have dilemma after dilemmas and  urlLink Wena , always eat the best food.  Me, I think I can show how quite life can be. Here is Oz, I have never found any great night life, except for pub crawling. It was fun when I was in Uni, but now just can't handle my hangovers anymore.  So what kind of fun do I get myself into?     Meet up with old friends I guess, but most of them are married and they all have their own life to live.    Watch a decent movie? yeah I am still waiting for the next Matrix  Read a good book. Any recommndations  I use to collect comics, but now the comics are too expensive. AU$5.00 per comic! Man it use to be AU$3.50  Spend time with my partner. Yeah I guess we do, but what do we do?    Boring eh.... Maybe I should take up a new hobby? or just go on a holiday ? Maybe if I get a decent pay I would...... 

						
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Monday 10 rounds in 22 mins and 15 seconds  Tuesday 7 rounds in 16 mins and 29 seconds  I guess it is an Ok time, hopefully I can improve my time before the run on next Wednesday. Fingers cross. 

						
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink Kill Bill vol 1  is the 4th film from the infamous director Quentin Tarantino. It was a much anticipated film by the fans of Tarantino, but personally for me, I didn't even know about this film until they were promoting the film on TV.  So what can I say about this film, well it has VIOLENCE!!, Pure unadulterated violence. I think you must be a fan of the old HK/Japanese Martial Arts movies to really appreciate the violence and the lack of story line. Even before the actual movie started Tarantino really tried to re-create the feel and flow of the old Martial Arts films, by using the old " urlLink Run Shaw Productions " film introduction.  The basis of the story is about an ex-assassin who survived a murder attempt on her life and now after 4 years, she is back for revenge. The "big bad dude" is Bill (David Carradine). We don't actually see him in the first volume, but I am sure everyone knows the famous  urlLink "Kung Fu"  actor.  Although the fight scenes was great(since the fight choreographer for the movie is Yuen Woo Ping, the same choreographer for the matrix series), it is never the same a watching a real martial artist fighting. No matter how much an "Actor" tries to fight, they are never as smooth as a real Martial Artist. Uma Thurman, Lucy liu and Vivica fox are no martial artist. Their moves are so "angular" and uncomfortable. In any case the fight scene is still kick arse compare to DareDevil.  ----- Oh just remember a side story, during the preview, Freddy Vs Jason was on and there was a bunch of young girls sitting behind us. They were all talking about the preview and this is how it went:  [Girl 1]: Oh..I wonder what this movie(Freedy vs Jason) is about.. [Girl 2]: It's a sequel from two other horror movies. [Girl 1]: Sequel to what movies?? Minute of silence.. [Girl 2]: emmm.. I think the movies are Freddy Krueger and Jason.  And I am thinking...YOU LOSERS!! You don't even know What movie it was !!  ------   Anyway back to the movie, if you are a Bruce Lee fan, you will be able to spot lots of scenes which are similar to the old Bruce Lee movies. So if you like the old 70s Martial arts film then you will love Kill Bill, where blood, gore and missing limbs are a norm. 

						
</post>

<date>30,December,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   So how is everyones Christmas?  Did you get your much deserved presents?  Here is what I got:  Bruce Lee T Shirt Box of Mrs Field Cookies A few christmas card, and A Fighting fish in nice fish bowl.  Nothing to write home/blog about but I guess it is better than nothing =) Man what I would not give to be a kid again in this era, everywhere I go, kids are given awesome hi-tech toys! No longer are they given legos and figurines, they are now given x-boxes and PS2 !!....  Anyway so what else did I do?  24th: Work, last minute shopping. Cook for the inlaws and then Midnight Mass. After the Mass they came back to our place and ate again... they did not leave till 3 am.... man I don't know about them but I was sure tired by then.   25th: Recuperate from Midnight Mass. Lunch at some friends place, watch Resident Evil (what a waste of time). Then Dinner some inlaws place. We had to celebrate the boss's Grandma birthday.  26th: Rest day. Stayed at home and ate leftovers =)  27th: Took some visitors from the south on a drive around Sydney. We went to Fox Studios and Paddys Market.   28th: Went to a Christening. The only good thing about the event was the food.    29th: I took some annual leave, so I had the good fortune to stay at home and do nothing but watch DVDs and read my book.  I saw the Classic movie, The Princess Bride and read "The Last Guardian" by David Gemmel.    30th : Watch LORT: Fellowship of the Ring and The Two Towers! In anticipation of watching the final installament. Had to clean up after the "Boss" Little Brother! He is close to eight years old, he knows how to read and write, but yet he spills everything he touches! The worst thing is that he laughs about it. He is not punish for him silliness, but he is coddled. I guess I can't blame it since he is the youngest and he is spoiled. But wht can't they discpline the damn kid!   Today: New Years Eve. I don't know what is plan yet, but I am sure I am going to see the inlaws again....Woo Pee Doo... =P  Anyway Wish you all enjoy a save New Year Eve party and an Awesome New Year.  Cheers   

						
</post>

<date>23,December,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Stumble on to this interesting site called  urlLink The Mayfly Project . The idea is to sum up your year in 20 words or less.  So since we are on the last legged of the year 2003, I think it would be great to sum up my life in 20 words.   My First try was this: Got married. Moved out of home. In debt. Getting Bored. Need New Challenge at work.   What is yours? 

						
</post>

<date>19,December,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Guess when I am going to be tonight... No Not at the Pub with the boys... Not doing the last minute christmas shopping  Not spending quality time with the Mrs...  But I am going to my inlaws... YEah!! =P Oh don't get me wrong I like my inlaws... but do I have to stay with them ??... Yep that is right.. the boss is missing her folks during the festive season and she wants to sleep over at her parents place...  So rather than finishing the week with a nice sleep at our comfortable bed.. we are going to sleep at her parents place and sleep on the floor, with no A/C and probably a dodgey little fan!  Jeez do you know how hot it is at the moment in Syd... the average temp is in the hight 30's ... yummy! So tonight I am going to roast and have a sore back... Great =)  Merry Christmas =)  

						
</post>

<date>17,December,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   The Trailer for Spidey 2 is out! urlLink SpiderMan 2 Trailer . Man it is awesome!! I think that Tobey is growing on me as Peter Parker and what can I say, Kristen is pretty hot as MJ.   I can't wait for it to come out on the screen. Doc Ock looks great and the CG claws looks mad.   

						
</post>

<date>17,December,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Read this funny article from UGO, titled  urlLink What Women Want: Comic Buying Guide  . This author fancy himself as a "PLAYA" and a Comic Connoisseur, but I think he is just a geek who likes comics and girls, but in anycase he is pretty funny.   But the most funny thing was the statement he wrote at the end..."In conclusion, women are strange and wondrous creatures. Without them life wouldn't be worth living, but with them it's an unendurable hell. That is until they become comic fans. Then it's more like purgatory. And purgatory isn't really that bad."   And gentleman.... that is So TRUE!! 

						
</post>

<date>16,December,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Why is that when I was single and working, I had tonnes of money.... I had no money worries, but now that we are together and both of us are working, we are both broke!!  Why is 1 + 1 = 0 rather than 1 + 1 = 2 ???   

						
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   So here I am, less than 10 days to christmas and I have yet to buy a present for "the boss", I am in trouble =P But what can I do, by the time I finish work, most of the shops are close!  Man do I hate Aussie shops!! Why do they closed so early! This is one thing I miss about KL, there are always good food available and great shops to buy stuff when ever you want =)  And I hate weekends, one because I have to work at my dads place on sunday and the amount of people out shoppin and is crazy. Since the weather is now hot and dry, most people will find their sanctuary in the shopping malls. Also with the school holidays it is just crazy.  So what am I to do ?  Should I secretly take a day off for pressies shopping or should I just try to fight the masses on the weekend and try to get something last minute.  any suggestions? 

						
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   For over twenty years, Kennedy has been acknowledged as one of the world’s leading violin virtuosos whose unique talent has brought fresh perspectives and a quantum energy to both the classical and contemporary repertoire.   I had the pleasure of listening him play 2 years ago, when he was in Sydney and now I am again given the gift of experiencing this amazing talent, playing his most famous music. And let me tell you it was amazing!!   Since there was no conductor, he was controlling the who  urlLink Sydney Symphony , which mean you can see and listen to his improvisations on all the concertos.  His dry Englsh wit is also a bonus, it is funny to see all the fuddy duddy at the concert cringe when he makes an inappropriate joke =) We even had audience participation in some of the music!! (in a classical concert! Yikes) During the Winter movement, the Audience had to shout "Oui"   To top this off, he final piece was  urlLink "Purple Haze"  by  urlLink Jimi Hendrix . That really rock the theatre! You should have been there ... You would have loved his music =) The concert was suppose to finish at 10pm but it went close to midnight!  Man am I tired now, but it was definitely a concert worth missing some sleep for. =)   

						
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>

						
						     urlLink      

						
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   I am going to watch  urlLink Nigel Kennedy  tonight at the Opera House!!  He is back in Oz to perform the piece which made him a household name in the 80's, Vivaldi’s The Four Seasons.  This is going to be Awesome!  I'll let you all know tomorrow, how awesome it was. 

						
</post>

<date>05,December,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Found this awesome site which translate all lingo and acronyms into real words urlLink www.lingo2word.com .  Here is an example:  D Lingo            D Definition   RTFM                Read the F**king manual  RTFM                Read the F**king message  RTFM                Read the fine manual   

						
</post>

<date>05,December,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   It is Friday, which means soccer day. Unfortunately due to the constant down pour, we were forced to delay the game. It was after 1 pm and it was still raining, so we decided that despite the fact, the show must go on. It is our last Friday in this old building and our old field!  So 9 brave soul ran out to the cold wet field and we played! And God did we play! Imagine 9 grown man playing soccer in a middle of a thunder storm.... We were all soaking wet!!  We were slipping and slidding all over the field or should I call it mud! We have mud on our face and determinations in our eyes! It was amazing. The harder the rain poured, the harder we played! And believe me, the sky was not happy that we were out having fun!!  Luckily for us the sky gave up before us =) The rain stopped but we continued! In the end our ageing body was the victor and we called it the end. We played for over an hour under the rain. It was amazing, it really reminded me of the time when I was young, under the malaysian sky doing the same thing. Sweet memory!  After the game, guess what happen... We went back to work HAHAHA! You may ask, did we shower??... HAHAAH NO!! We did not shower... The whole floor stink of man sweat!! Yeah baby... You should smell it now!!  HAHAHAHAH!!!... Enjoy you weekend! 

						
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   There are known knowns. These are things we know that we know.  There are known unkowns. That is to say, there are things we know we don't know.  But, there are also unknown unknowns. These are things we don't know we don't know.  --  urlLink (Rumsfield knows how to knowingly confuse his knowledgable Audience at a Pentagon briefing)   

						
</post>

<date>03,December,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Man today I am such  urlLink bludger . It is 14:00 and I have yet to do anything at all =P Since are all planning to move, the whole day has been throwing out all my old notes and document and packing up all the stuff I have collected during my stay on my old cubicle. It is amazing how much junk you collect in less than 2 years. I filled up 2 box full of notes to send to my spanking new cubicle. Did I tell you that I am going to have a Window seat...and it is currently summer time!! Yeah baby!!  So back to my relaxing day today. So I spend a few hours packing my desk then I had to help my boss to packup out cabinet where we stock out PS2s and Xboxes =) I suggested that rather than letting the movers to move the stuff to the new office, I should take the PS2 and xbox home for safe keeping ... Good idea right? Fortunately for my wife I am not going to do that, cause if I do, she would not see me for the whole weekend HAHAHAH!!.  So here I am now blogging, while I am trying to look busy. So what should I do next... I am bored. I tried browsing the net and read all my regular blogs eg,  urlLink Mum-Mum ,  urlLink minishorts , urlLink SixthSeal  and  urlLink CowBoy Caleb    Any suggestion to help me out of boredom??...    

						
</post>

<date>03,December,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   After over a year or rumours, we are finally leaving our dump of an office and moving into a new building! YEAH! Brand new building which is situated 5 mins away from where I am currently living! Double Yeah!  So before the end of the week, I'll have to clean my cubicle and throw away all the junk I have accumulated in over the years. This is going to be awesome. I check out the my new desk yesterday and it looks awesome. The new desk is double the one I am having now, so my 2 computers will have plenty of space. I have also a  urlLink high tech chair  which I am told cost a grand each. Let me tell you it is comfortable... But I am sure glad I don't have to pay for it.  I also have a window seat! Triple YEAH! I will have perfect view of the people coming out of the train station which is under us. And since there are plenty of café near the station.. I am finally able to buy some nice food near work, unlike now where I have to bring food from home or get some greasy and expensive food from the local cafeteria. Man what I would not give for a Wonton noodle soup right about now or a nice delicious  urlLink Konlon mee .  Man Talking about food is now making me hungry.. So I am going to go home now and eat some home cook meal.  Cheers.  

						
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Stole this from  urlLink Wena                                                                            YELLOW         You are very perceptive and smart. You are clear and to the point and have a great sense of humor. You are always learning and searching for understanding.           Find out your color at Quiz Me!              

						
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   So here I am, another year older and none the wiser.  I celebrated my birthday with a small group of friends on the weekend. I have known them since my Uni days. I would say they are my closest friends. We are all around the same age, each of us are now in the age range where we are getting married. In the group about half of us are married. It is strange really since the person who was most likely to be married first is still single, whereas like me I was loud and proud Bachelor enjoy home cook meal from my popo and working in IT. But I guess, fate had other plan for me.   So here I am in my late 20s and I am still undecided on what I want to do for the rest of my life. I don’t think I can work in my current position for too much longer. I need new challenges or I’ll just get to bored. I fear that if I am in my position for too long, I’ll be too comfortable in it and I’ll never have the courage to leave my comfort zone.   What is next in my journey? Should I stay in my comfort zone or should I leave? Should I do what is expected and become a dad?...yikes that is scary. Or should I climb up to the next mountain and see what the next valley have to offer me?  

						
</post>

<date>30,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Had a game of soccer again today.... man it is bloody hot out there on the field. I can literally feel my fat boiling off from the inside =P (which is a good thing..heh heh)  So here I am, my unco-ordinated self on the field, trying to be useful for the team. I am a mediocre defender, but I am total crap as a striker.... my only attempt to be a striker today, provided me with a sore hand, due to the fact that my hand was "lucky" enough to be inbetween the ground and someone stud shoes!! OUCH!!  To add to the injury, my right foot was also given the same treatment....  Fortunately for me, due to my mutant healing factor I survived the ordeal with only injured pride and a very stiff hand =P  Hope the weekend is better.... 

						
</post>

<date>29,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This is what happens when you move a dead whale ..... urlLink KABoom......  

						
</post>

<date>29,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I am sure, if you have been on the net for the last 6 months, you would have heard of the  urlLink Star War Kid . Well here is another spoof of another unlucky kid. Please welcome the  urlLink Movie Kid . It not as action packed as the previous, but no less imaginative.   

						
</post>

<date>29,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Don't know if I conside this a good week, but atleast is it going to be a short week. Oz celebrate it's Australia day on the 26th of Jan. This means that we had a nice long weekend. I don't think that most aussies would even know why we celebrate Aussie day, they are happy just because it is a public holiday.   Aussie day is the celebration of the landing of the first fleet. The day where the freedom of the aborigines were ignore and discarded like waste. A day when western disease was brought on to the untouched land.... What a great Australia day.  Anyway what else happen during the week?? Had dinner at my folks place on tuesday and met a high school friend for dinner yesterday. During the dinner I was reminded that I have been out of highschool for 10 years! Holey Cow! Man I feel so old. Years have flown by so quickly.   What can I say about my last 10 years?  Uni  Work  Wife And more work  What can I see in for my next 10 years?  Work  And more work =)  Woo Hoo..... 

						
</post>

<date>28,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Some of the countries I have visited.     urlLink create your own visited country map   or  urlLink write about it on the open travel guide   Got the link from  urlLink wena  

						
</post>

<date>27,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I know, I know, I rip this off from  urlLink Joy Of Tech  but I just wanted to let everyone enjoy this joke!   urlLink     The funniest thing is that the Macintosh that Bill is holding is called the MacintoshPlus, and I had the opportunity to play with it just last week. You don't know how far we have come, until you use a Macintosh in which all software is ran off a Floppy!!  

						
</post>

<date>23,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink The NeverLand Escape  

						
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     urlLink     

						
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The Year of the Monkey!  urlLink Those born in the Year of the Monkey are thought to be fun loving persons, always cheerful and energetic. Inquisitive, they constantly seek new opportunities and their intellect allows them to adapt to any situation. Their mischievous spirit is entertaining. 'Monkeys' tend to forgive but never forget. They will succeed in any profession; however, their innate desire to be noticed makes many “Monkeys” choose show business.   So Happy New Year, fellow blogger!  urlLink Minishorts  it is your year this year, so Shine Baby and makes us green with envy =)  urlLink Sixthseal  has a new job in "East Malaysia", so Good luck buddy and keep on giving us your awesome take on life  urlLink Wena  you have a new Kitchen Stove!! My mouth is already watering just imagining what your will entice us this new year!  urlLink Aunty Caleb , or should I call you KKK? So Aunty Caleb, I think one of the blogger is a psycho path, what should I do???..... =P  So what are my plans in the land down under? Nothing as exciting as shopping for red CNY underpants or go to a CNY banquet. I am meeting up with my folks tomorrow night (after work) for dinner at the local Malaysian Restaurant. I am told that if I "pour Tea" for my parents, I am likely to still get "Ang Pau" so guess what else am I doing tomorrow =)  Of course in Oz, the government do not recognise the CNY. So no long weekend for me =P  In actual fact, I'll have to be at work tomorrow by 6 am! AWESOME =P   So Anyway I hope everyone have a great New Year and May all your new year prosper and your life Joyous =)  Cheers PICOLO    

						
</post>

<date>19,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Just got a few emails today to inform me that one of my Uni friend has just gave birth!! They were married for over 4 years before they wanted a child and so now they are blessed with a baby girl =)  I know this is a joyous occasion, but all I can think is that I am getting old. My Uni friends are having babies! this means that soon I would be a dad too.  This means I will have to become a responsible man, like my dad.   Am I ready for this? Can you ever be ready for this?  daddy?....me??    

						
</post>

<date>16,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Read this question, come up with an answer, and then email your answer to me. This is not a trick question. It is as it reads.    A woman, while at the funeral of her own mother, met a man whom she did not know. She thought this man was amazing, the man of her dreams, so much so that she fell in love with him right there but never asked for his number and could not find him. A few days later she killed her sister.     Question: What is her motive in killing her sister?  FYI for those that haven't answered there is now right or wrong answer, atleast try and give an answer 

						
</post>

<date>15,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   	  Today the weather was trying to stop our weekly Friday Soccer, with her constant rain and grey sky. I am happy to say she failed =)  Even with her cold rain, we ran on to the field like fanatics and played some hard core soccer on this cold and wet day. We were slipping on the mud, we were blinded by the blinding rain, we were soaked to the bone with iced cold rain, but yet we played on.   Blood, sweat and mud mingle during this bout, we over came the cold and pain and we are sure we will overcome our opposition. They had the advantage, they had the extra man, they had the skills but they could not defeat our will. Our body maybe weak but our mind is strong!!  3 to 1 was our score!  3 to 1, We WON!  VICTORY!! 

						
</post>

<date>15,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Found this on an Email. So if you are bored or just looking for something funny, then continue reading =)    Japanese programmers have replaced the impersonal and unhelpful Microsoft error messages with Haiku poetry messages. As you probably know, Haiku poetry has strict construction rules - each poem has only 17 syllables; 5 syllables in the first line, 7 in the second, 5 in the third.  ++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++  The Web site you seek Cannot be located, but Countless more exist. --------------------------------------------  Chaos reigns within. Reflect, repent, and reboot. Order shall return. -----------------------------------------------  Program aborting: Close all that you have worked on. You ask far too much. ------------------------------------------------  Windows NT crashed. I am the Blue Screen of Death. No one hears your screams. --------------------------------------------------  Yesterday it worked. Today it is not working. Windows is like that. ---------------------------------------------------  Your file was so big. It might be very useful. But now it is gone. -------------------------------------------  Stay the patient course. Of little worth is your ire. The network is down. ---------------------------------------------------  A crash reduces Your expensive computer To a simple stone. --------------------------------------------------  Three things are certain: Death, taxes and lost data. Guess which has occurred. ---------------------------------------------------  You step in the stream, But the water has moved on. This page is not here. ---------------------------------------------------  Out of memory. We wish to hold the whole sky, But we never will. ------------------------------------------------  Having been erased, The document you're seeking Must now be retyped. ---------------------------------------------------  Serious error. All shortcuts have disappeared. Screen. Mind. Both are blank. 

						
</post>

<date>14,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink Aluminium Room =)  

						
</post>

<date>13,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Another day has gone by Work is now over for another day  Time to pack up Time to go home  Another day has pass by No more politics, just silence No more lies, just the truth No more stress, just rest  Another day.  

						
</post>

<date>13,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     You are  Spearmint . You are quick-witted and sharp.  You pay close attention to details and you can tell what your friends are feeling.  You are always the first to understand a joke and you are valued for your insight and advice.  However, you sometimes isolate yourself from other people, afraid to share your own feelings. Most Compatible With: Cinnamon    urlLink   Which Tic-Tac Flavor Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    

						
</post>

<date>13,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Mazda has finally made the ultimate car!! The  urlLink RX-8 Transformer . You have to check this out. Of course this car is an Autobots! AWESOME!!   urlLink Caleb  I think you should get this car!! 

						
</post>

<date>12,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   We had a couple of family friends from the states that came over during the week and since they were fans of RnB (or Hip-Hop), we decided to take them to one of the city new RnB nite club  urlLink Hunny . Man that was an eye opener. I have not been to a nightclub for over a year and man I felt so out of place.  I was never a fan of nite clubs and I am sure I am one of the world worst dancer, so it was a good idea that I did not visit such premises often. As always we had to wait in line for 20 mins to get into the club and be greeted by a couple of oversize gorillas. If you want to know what happens to people with steroid overdose, then do a speak to a couple of bouncers at a nite club. Anyway we climbed a couple flight of stairs and we are welcomed by a skimpy clothed girl which charged us 20 bucks per person to enter the club. Your senses is now pretty much overloaded by now. The music is so loud that you can't even hear if someone talks into your ear, the bass is so powerful that your whole body vibrates, your nose and lungs is filled with secondary smoke from all the chain smoker standing at the entrance to have a "fag" and you eyes are greeted with more gratuitous flesh than a butcher store. Welcome to hunny =)  So if you are looking for Sydney Nite meat market, you will know where to go. In the first 5 mins of entering the club, I know I don't belong here. Maybe I am too old, maybe I am just way too old... But I felt like so out of place. Don’t get me wrong, I enjoy watching skimpy clothed girls gyrating their arse, as the next warm blooded male, but I am not a fan of nite clubs.  Anyway we were there for over 3 hours, trying to dance (as much dancing as you can do when you are packed like a can of sardines). The friends were enjoying themselves since it was a feast for the eyes =P After the that we had some coffee at the local Gloria Jeans and then I drove them home. It was 5 am the next morning before my head hit my pillow.  Saturday was a daze. I slept in. Woke up and cooked some brunch and put on Bad Boys 2 (DVD-rip). The movie was not bad. Plenty of actions with no reason. Explosions galore and "Lethal weapons" plotlines. Clean up the apartment and just vegged out =)  Sunday was hot! I worked in an non a/c shop and I swear I lost a few pounds from the heat =P 

						
</post>

<date>09,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   If you are bored on the weekend, check this out.  urlLink  Trunk Monkey   

						
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   He who knows others is learned. He who knows himself is wise  --Lao-Tzu  

						
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Would you believe it, that people actually read this??!! And what are the chances that this person who read my blog actually knows me!!(I guess my anonymity may soon disappear.)  Yep that is right, I had a long lost friend emailing me after he read my blog and deduced who I am.. Wow that is amazing eh... The last I saw him was in KL, 10 years ago. He emailed me and ask me if I am XXXX XXX, and I say yep that’s me. Holy crap! What are the chances??!  Anyway I am waiting for his reply and find out where he has been for the last 10 years and hopefully we can catch up soon.   So who says that the NET is useless.... Thank you INTERNET... Thank you! 

						
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Sarah Mclachlan has finally release a new album  urlLink "AfterGlow" . The first single from this album is the hauntingly beautiful song Fallen. If you have a chance to get to listen to this single, please do. It is amazing. I got the movie clip for it on her site and I have been playing it all day at work. Unfortunately I have not been able to find the album in my local CD shop =( So I might have to get it online.   I was first introduced to Sarah's unique music on the Movie "City of Angels", when her single Angle was played during the movie. Immediately after I saw the movie, I went to the closest CD shop and brought her album. Since then I have not looked back. It is weird to say it, but she makes the best break-up songs. Songs which seems to know the pain you are feeling, during those cold lonely nights.   She is definitely in my Top 5 Favourite Music Artist!     ...We all begin out with good intent When love is raw and young We believe that we can change ourselves The past can be undone But we carry on our back the burdens time always reveals In the lonely light of morning In the wound that would not heal It's the bitter taste of losing everything I've held so dear  Though I've tried I've fallen I have sunk so low I messed up Better I should know So don't come round here and Tell me I told you so ... 

						
</post>

<date>06,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Saw  urlLink Cold Mountain  last night with some friends. Although it was a long movie, the time went by very quickly. Nicole Kidman, as always a beauty on screen...hubba hubba!! I must say though that she is getting thinner and thinner. If you have seen her in  urlLink Billy Bathgate  you will know what I mean.  Anyway the movie had another hottie in it... Natalie Portman!!  Yeah baby she had a small scene in the movie but she was amazing in it. Double Hubba Hubba.  This movie is definitely a date movie. There are some really sad scenes and there are some sexy scenes, so I am sure both sexes will appreciate it. Definitely not recommended for the lonely...cause you will feel more down when you come out of the cinema.  

						
</post>

<date>06,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Live in the past and you shall dwell in regrets. 

						
</post>

<date>05,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   By: Jewel   Just heard this song again, after a long silence...... man it makes me think of my past...     Inside my skin There is this space... It twists and turns It bleeds and aches  Inside my heart There's an empty room. It's waiting for lightning; It's waiting for you  I am wanting, and... I am needing you To be here Inside the absence of fear  Muscles and sinew Velvet and stone... This vessel is haunted It creaks and moans  My bones call to you In a separate skin. I make myself translucent To let you in, boy...  I am wanting, and... I am needing you To be here Inside the absence of fear  There is the splendor of this Secret inside of me And it knows that you're no stranger, You're my gravity  My hands will adore you Through all darkness, and they will Lay you out in moonlight And vent(?) your name  For I am wanting, and... I am needing you To be here... I need you near... Inside the absence of fear.   

						
</post>

<date>05,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I finally found my dream present! If you can get me this, I'll be your best friend forever!!   urlLink Star Wars AT-ST walker 1:2 size replica.  This model was built in 12 months by a master model. This bad boy is 4 meters in size and it is built out of a steel skeleton....  The starting bid is US$19000.00 and you have less than 3 days to bid for this dream toy!  

						
</post>

<date>05,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Question: What do you think about talking in the bathroom? Case in point, you walk into the bathroom and you met one of your colleague and he starts talking to you, what do you do? Do you stimulate the conversation or just say hi and minimise eye contact?  For me, I don't like to talk in the bathroom, especially when I am at the urinal... Man when I am with my boys, I don't need you to interrupt us !! =P  Comments? 

						
</post>

<date>02,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Today I experienced the worst Monday-itis in my short working life. Only after a week off work, my care factor for work was less than zero. Thank god most people were experiencing the same problem as I. Most of us, spend most of our time reading the accumulated emails in our inbox and catching up with colleague and gossips.  We all had sun burnt marks on our faces and gain a few pounds from the junk food we ate during Chrissy and New Year. Hmmmm..... Chocolate!!  As for me I spend most of my time catching up on my regular blog readings =)  Welcome back  urlLink Wena . I hope you had a great time in the states. My mouth was watering when I saw the fried Turkey =)...Yummy!  And the black dress, you wore on the wedding, makes you look stunning =)  The ever changing  urlLink Minishorts . Love the new layout, can you make a new layout for me?    urlLink Sixthseal , The Melbourne Scene looks great, I can't wait to visit it myself. Hope you feel better soon buddy.   urlLink Caleb , man I wish I had your smarts to invest at a younger age =)  And many more blogs. More and more blogs are getting included into my regular reading and it is really slowing down my productivity =P ...Who cares =P  Happy New Year digital friends !! And hope to see you all in the coming year in the same blog channel and same blog time! 

						
</post>

<date>02,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Finally the year is over and new one has just begun. So what did I do to celebrate the coming of the New Year?   Well nothing much really. As always Sydney will go out gun blazing and have a huge fireworks at the Harbour =) It was not bad, I saw the fireworks at a friends place which was near the harbour. The fireworks were not bad, but nothing could beat the fireworks at the year 2000. We also had some light shows on the surrounding building in the city.  We had a nice little feast with some close family friends, had some champagne jelly and celebrate the night away.   So now here I am in a New Year, part of me is excited to begin this brand New Year and part of me is frightened of the all the obstacles before me. I am sure I am going to fall at some point and I am sure I am going to lose faith in the darkness, but what experience has shown me is that my friends and family will always be there to help me, and for that I thank God for it.  So what is ahead of me in the near future?    Get a New Job with better pay (but then who isn’t)  Look into getting the finance to buy a place of our own. (Sydney Real Estate Market is crazy)  Further studies. (May be a certificate of some kind)  Go on an oversea Holiday (Show my wife, my Homeland, Malaysia)  And most important of all, be content with all the gift I have.   

						
</post>

<date>27,February,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Man I hate it when I am sick. I hate it even more when I am not sick enough to justify staying at home, so I have to go to work and feel like crap. The bloody sudden change in weather is also really pissing me off. One day I am wearing shorts and T-shirts and the next jumpers and beanie!!    So here I am counting the minutes to 5 pm, so I can log off and go home... YEAH!! No more boring meetings and writing reports which no one reads anyway.   So whats my plan for the weekend? Tonight we are staying at the inlaws. why? cause mum and dad is going somewhere, and they need us to babysit their 7 year old son... yep yep you heard it right.. I have a brother inlaw and he is only SEVEN!!....   so since I am not feeling 100%, I am sure tonight I am going have a shit sleep and I am going to be really sick the next day ... Woo hOOO!!  Saturday, We are going to have Yum Cha with some of my close friends, which is the going to be awesome. Haven' seend them for ages, so it will be great to touch base.  Isn't it sad that once you are in a relationship, you tend to lose touch with your friends....  Then saturday night, we are going to watch urlLink The Passion of Christ!  I can't wait to see it, I know it is controversial, but it is an amazing story. My wife is a catholic, so I don't know how she is going to be feeling during the crucifixtion... but I am sure she is going to cry....  In anycase, I'll give my 2 cents worth on monday ....  Have a nice weekend.  

						
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Some say , a change is like a holiday...so here I am.  What do YOU think about it ?  It is simple, not as bright at  urlLink minishorts , but I guess it is home.    

						
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   yep yep.. the sudden change in weather have played havok to my immune systems. I have a slight headache and a slight sinus problem.. but yet I soldier on at work .... aren't I,  a hard worker.  So how was the long weekend, you asked?  Well it was great, better that I have hoped. She was surprise and she like all the stuff I got her =) The place was very nice and relaxing. The mountain air is clean and it feels so peaceful. We were there for only 2 nights but it was great.  The first day, we had a late lunch at quite little chinese restaurant in Katoomba. It was called the Youngs Chinese Restaurant. Of course the food was nothing compare to KL dishes, but we were hungry, so everything tasted nice =)  After the quick lunch, we checked into the hotel. Upon entering the room, she was presented with 2 dozen red roses on the bed =) she was happily surprised!!  This followed with a nice relaxing dip on the spa (with jets!!) and then Champagne and Chocolate dip Strawberries were delivered to our door =)  Niiiiicccceeeeeeee..... =)    

						
</post>

<date>20,February,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Guess what, this week will be my first Anniversary with my wife!!  Man time really flies.  In a blink of an eye, we have been married for a year.  And lucky for me, she still have not left me =P  To celebrate this joyous occasion, I have organise a nice romantic weekend on the mountains, Blue Mountains that is.  If all works according to plan, when she enters the hotel room, she is going to be presented with beautiful roses, champagne and Chocolate dip Strawberries =)  Hopefully the weather is not too hot at the mountains, so that we can do some bush walks... =)  Awesome!!   Can't wait for it... =)  Hope everyone have a nice weekend.... I know I will =P  

						
</post>

<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Have you ever met someone you have an immediate dislike? I always think that I can get along with most people I meet. I might not be their friends, but at least we respect each other and there is no ill feelings.  Well it seems that I have met this guy at work which in the beginning I dislike, but now I am feeling hate for this annoying little 5h1t!! Unfortunately for me he is a superior and he is atleast 10 years older than me. The good thing is that I don't have to report to him directly, but I do have to work with him occasionally.  Why do I dislike him ? Well in the beginning was his attitude towards me. He is a man who thinks he is smart and who acts like he knows everything. Yes you could say he is a smart arse. Whenever I ask him a question, he would always give me a smart arse comment before helping me. Another thing he likes to do is to *sigh* when I ask him an easy question. His attitude is that I should know that, and I should not be asking such "stupid" question.   Sometimes I think his antagonistic ways is only towards me. My other colleague has no issues with him, but I guess it is because they are at the same age level and they have work together longer than me. And of course I am the only Asian in the department. Most of the time I am OK with his behaviour. I try not to ask for his help.  Now my dislike for him is even greater and this is because of his constant insults on the playing field. We normally have a game of soccer during our lunch time. Most of the time we would have around 8 people on the field playing soccer. There are no competition, it is just a game so that we all have some exercise.   Truth to say I have no Hand-Eye co-ordinations skills. I never played soccer competitively when I was young. I am more of a long distant runner and swimmer. So you can imagine my utter lack of skills when I play soccer. So when I make a mistake, which is quite often, I get utterly ridicule by this a55hol3.   What really piss me off is that he is worst than me! He cant kick, he cant run, but he has a huge mouth! Most times I ignore his taunt, but I fear than one day he is going to push me too far and I am going to give him a knuckle sandwich!!  What should I do...  

						
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I am going to be first Basketball Game at the Entertainment Centre... Truth to say that I am not a big fan of the game, but I am interested to experience the game live! So I am going to pack up now, and take the train to the city.  So see you all tomorrow.   

						
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Worked had been hell... I had an installation which started at 2 am in the morning...imagine sleeping less than 4 hours and go back to work and work for 8 hours =P  Man my body is still trying to get back to normal....  And public transport in Sydney has gone haywire... Which is fine with me, since I work next to home, but "the boss" works in the Sydney... So this means that after work I have to drive throught the city traffic and pickup the with.... Woopee doo... Am I am a caring hubby or what =)   Just got my car service and it cost me 300 bucks!! Ouch!!  They had to clean my fuel injections??.... Man I should have been a mechanic!! I just got paid and I know I am already broke =P  Also of course on Saturday was Valentines day .. I had to find the time away from the wife to look for a pressy for her =P So what did you get for your honey ???.. 

						
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Let me watch by the fire and remember my days And it may be a trick of the firelight  But the flickering pages that trouble my sight Is a book I'm afraid to write  It's the book of my days, it's the book of my life And it's cut like a fruit on the blade of a knife And it's all there to see as the section reveals There's some sorrow in every life  If it reads like a puzzle, a wandering maze Then I won't understand 'til the end of my days I'm still forced to remember,  Remember the words of my life  There are promises broken and promises kept Angry words that were spoken, when I should have wept There's a chapter of secrets, and words to confess If I lose everything that I possess There's a chapter on loss and a ghost who won't die There's a chapter on love where the ink's never dry There are sentences served in a prison I built out of lies.  Though the pages are numbered  I can't see where they lead For the end is a mystery no-one can read In the book of my life  There's a chapter on fathers a chapter on sons There are pages of conflicts that nobody won And the battles you lost and your bitter defeat, There's a page where we fail to meet  There are tales of good fortune that couldn't be planned There's a chapter on god that I don't understand There's a promise of Heaven and Hell but I'm damned if I see  Though the pages are numbered  I can't see where they lead For the end is a mystery no-one can read In the book of my life  Now the daylight's returning And if one sentence is true All these pages are burning  And all that's left is you  Though the pages are numbered  I can't see where they lead For the end is a mystery no-one can read In the book of my life   

						
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   What is the etiquette of talking/meeting the opposite sex, when you are in a relationship?  Should your dynamics with your male/female friends change once you are in a relationship? If you are a guy, your gf is normally patience when you say that you have to hangout with your guy friends, but what is your have more female friends? Should you hang out with them? And if so does your partner have to be there, the whole time?  Also how about talking on the phone or emails etc...  How mutually exclusive is the relationship?  Do you have to amalgamate all your circle of friends with your partner? Does the world really collides when your persona with your partner meets your persona with your friends??   

						
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Had an interesting weekend.   We were invited to a baby welcoming party (Welcoming the new born baby home from the Hospotal) and we were invited to a 21st Party at the local pub.  On the first party, I met up with friends of my own age, most of them settling down, some newly married and some just had their first baby!! We were all at the parents place, enjoying some home cook meal and talk about who is next to have a baby or who is next to get married. We joke about baby's poo or getting into trouble with the better half.   On the Second party, We were at a pub with Live music and lots of drunk.... we dance and we cut the birthday cake... we try to talk, but who can hear under those loud speakers. And at the end of the day I smelt like smoke.  So on the same day I participate both end of the spectrum of my life. The life of the matured married person and the life of the young party goer.  So which one do I like?    

						
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I saw this and I thought that this gift would be perfect for all the ladies blogger out there =P Enjoy.  urlLink Geek Girls   

						
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Got this from a friend of my, via email. I thought it would be good to share this to the world. So here it is.   Welcome to the next edition of getting to know your friends. Okay, here's what you're supposed to do..... and try not to be LAME and spoil the fun!  Just give in.Change all of the answers so that they apply to you. Then, send this to a whole bunch of people you know *INCLUDING* the person who sent it to you. The theory is that you will learn a lot of little known facts about your friends. It is fun and easy. ***Remember to send it back to the person who sent it to you***  1. WHAT IS YOUR FULL NAME?  Well you should know, if you don't then, there is no point continuing   2. STAR SIGN  Sagittarius   3.WHAT COLOUR PANTS ARE YOU WEARING?  Faded Blue Jeans   4. WHAT ARE YOU LISTENING TO RIGHT NOW? the constant humming/buzzing from the computer tower...  5. WHAT ARE THE LAST 4 DIGITS OF YOUR PHONE NUMBER?  1787   6. WHAT WAS THE LAST THING YOU ATE?  and still eating, special K with strawberry   7. IF YOU WERE A CRAYON, WHAT COLOUR WOULD YOU BE?  black   8. HOW IS THE WEATHER RIGHT NOW?  Dark and cold   9. LAST PERSON YOU TALKED TO ON THE PHONE?  My Wife   10. WHAT DO YOU NOTICE ABOUT THE OPPOSITE SEX?  The size of their package =P   11. DO YOU LIKE THE PERSON WHO SENT YOU THIS?  She is like a brother to me =P   12. HOW ARE YOU TODAY?  Bloody sleepy!! it is 6 am in the morning!!   13. FAVOURITE DRINK?  Currently Coconut Juice   14. FAVOURITE ALCOHOLIC DRINK?  A new sweet Riesling    15. FAVOURITE SPORTS?  Swimming and Cross Country running   16. HAIR COLOUR?  Black, peppered with grey =P   17. EYE COLOUR?  brown   18. DO YOU WEAR CONTACTS?  Nope. Glasses, cos it makes me look more geeky =P   19. SIBLINGS AND THEIR AGES?  2 sis, 29, 20   20. FAV Month?  The month when I have my Annual Leave   21. FAVOURITE FOOD?  Currently Pineapple tarts!! Bloody Awesome!   22. LAST MOVIE YOU WATCHED?  The Debut   23. FAVOURITE DAY OF THE YEAR?  Holiday of course...duh   24. WORST DAY OF THE YEAR?  Sunday... I have to work    25. ARE YOU TOO SHY TO ASK SOMEONE OUT?  Don't need to anymore... I am married =)   26. HUGS OR KISSES?  Both, you can't have one without the other =)   27 RELATIONSHIPS OR ONE NIGHT STANDS?  I am MARRIED... duh...   28. CHOCOLATE OR VANILLA?  Chocolate   29. DO YOU WANT YOUR FRIENDS TO WRITE BACK?  eh...   30. WHO IS MOST LIKELY TO RESPOND?  ??   31. WHO IS LEAST LIKELY TO RESPOND?  Everyone..   32. LIVING ARRANGEMENTS?  At an 11th floor Shoe box =)   33. WHAT BOOK ARE YOU READING?  The Sword in the Storm, by David Gemmel (second time)   34. WHAT'S ON YOUR MOUSE PAD?  Canberra Raiders (Rugby League Team)   36. WHAT DID YOU DO LAST NIGHT  Watch movie and sleep late =P   37. FAVOURITE SMELLS?  Freshly baked bread   38. CAN YOU TOUCH YOUR NOSE WITH YOUR TONGUE?  Tried...but failed   39. WHAT INSPIRES YOU? The Strength of the human spirit....and the Incredible stupidity of humanity!    40. BUTTERED, PLAIN, OR SALTED POPCORN?  caramel?   41. FAVOURITE CAR?  N/A.... maybe BMW Z3   42. FAVOURITE FLOWER?  Roses   43. HOW MANY KEYS ON YOUR KEY RING? I have 2 key rings, 2 and 3    44. CAN YOU JUGGLE?  my responsibility?/.. yeah ..balls... nope   COME ON YOUR TURN  ! IT WONT TAKE YOU LONG.   

						
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Finally the day is at an end and I can go home and pack for my 3 day trip !!  We will be sailing in a 24 foot yacht !! We are going to sail the seven seas in 3 days and We are going to catch some sexy mermaid!!   Lets Rock and ROLL!!!  Anyway, see you all soon.  Enjoy the rest of your working week .... =P 

						
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   One more day and I am going off to sail the Seven Seas!! wOO Hoo!!  Well ok, not the seven seas, but I am going to be in a sail boat, and I am going to learn what is the starboard and port, how to trim the sails and the best of all, I'll be able to say... "Number 1 engage....."  3 of us are going to hire a boat and sail the local habour and learn a few tricks. Hopefully no one will drown =P  Can't wait!! 

						
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Another Farewell dinner for work. I think IT has the biggest churn stats in all the professionals. People come and go like a conveyer belt. And the funny thing is that if you stay in a company long enough, you will probably see them again in the same company.     So, here I am thinking, maybe it is also time for me to go too. My absolute fear is to be stagnant. To be stuck on in an dead end job for the next 20 years. I have a work mate sitting behind me, who is starting a family and he is over 30 , been in the company for 8 years and he is stuck here. He doesnt want to change, he is comfortable. Everyday I come to work and I see this fat dude, complaining that he is not getting paid enough, playing with his web site and just doing the same thing. I fear in 5 years time I would be him.    I  have been in this position for over a year, and my  average life span  in  a position in the company  is 1.5 years. So I guess it is time to leave. There is not future prospect here . I can't go anywhere...well actually I don't want to go anywhere in this company. I think a new company and new people will be great. I have met some great people here but I cant stay here forever.   Now I have to decide which path I should go. Somewhere similar to what I am doing, or something all together different. 

						
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   What is it about Anniversary and girls.....  Yesterday the "boss" reminded me that is was our 13th month anniversary!!... yep you heard it right... ??  Comeon, I can understand the celebration of the first 3 months, 6 months, the first year!!... but why 13th months. And if I do remember, what do we do to celebrate this occasion?   Does Hallmark have a card for such a celebration?  Does it say "Happy (Insert month) Anniversary"??  Thank god it was late and she did not make a big fuss about it... but does this mean that I should do something for the 14th  month ? or 15th or 16th ??...yikes!!  I am already broke from the 1st year anniv.... and it was only a month ago...  Is so, maybe I should start thinking of getting another job =P   

						
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Due to my curiosity, I finally borrowed the infamous movie  urlLink Gigli . This was the movie which features Ben Affleck and J-Lo, and it was a major flop in the box office.  Ok, here is a summary of the movie. BA and Jlo are both "bullies" for hire. They were both hired to kidnap a kid who is mentally challenged. J-Lo was a lesbian, but decided to change team after she saw BA topless. Then they decide to saw the kid and run aways together....The End.  Yes that is right, it is a shit story!! I think they wanted to make something like  urlLink Rain Man  meets  urlLink Out of Sight , but all we see is a pile of steaming doo doo.  For the fans, they is no sex scenes, there is no nudity and they sure hell did not have any chemistry at all!!!  So for god sake, dont' waste your time and watch this.   

						
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It is amazing how much hype this nerdy guy is getting. From what I have read, this dude is going to get man an ALBUM!! that's right, he is going to produce a "music" Album. God Help us all.  Anyway, if you enjoy is "style" of singing, then you will enjoy this site.  urlLink William The Dancing Man  

						
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Another work mate is going to be a dad!! And I wonder when will it be my time!! Sometimes I think I am ready to help bring a new life into this crazy world and sometimes I fear that this world is just too crazy and I am not strong enough to care for this new life.  I guess we are biologically ready, well actually biologically we should have had one before we were 20, but now a days, who are in a commited relationship at that age.  But am I mentally ready? I guess no one can be totally ready until they are in the situations, so I guess I am not ready. I think of myself still as a child learning the hard life in this harsh world.  Are we Financially ready? Definately not. But again can we be ever ready. The cost of living is not going down and the pay is never enough.  So how do people do it ? How do you decide when you are ready ? Do you just have a leap of faith ? Do you just do what you always do in a life situation? Just take your chances and role the dice?   

						
</post>

<date>19,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Survived another week!  Man do I need this weekend !!  This week is worst than most is because my boss was not here today, so my lazy arse work mate would not do any work. I had to do everything. He would not talk to Ops eventhough he was the one who was more experienced with the plugins.  Damn Lazy arse bastard.  All he does at work is download torrents on his laptop and go onto forums...  Anyway it is time to go home, so I am going to leave this place once again....  I think I really need a new job. Something which of course would pay me more, but atleast appreciate my hardwork....pah...if pig might fly....   

						
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It seems that the infamous  urlLink CowBoy Caleb  have moved and made himself a new home. His tribe has decided to expand their empire and start conquering the Net as well.   I have to say that the site is Wang-a-li-sious. And if I ever get more pay than a local McDs boy, I might move into a real site, rather than leaching of a freeby =) Not than there is anything wrong with leaching of a freeby =)   

						
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It is funny because it is so true =P     1. You accidentally enter your password on the microwave.  2. You haven't played solitaire with real cards in years.  3. You have a list of 10 phone numbers to reach your family of 3.  4. You e-mail your mate who works at the desk next to you.  5. Your reason for not staying in touch with friends is that they do not have e-mail addresses.  6. When you go home after a long day at work you still answer the phone in a business manner.  7. When you make phone calls from home, you accidentally dial "0" or "9" to get an outside line.  8. You've sat at the same desk for four years and worked for three different companies.  10. You learn about your redundancy on the 11 o'clock news.  11. Your boss doesn't have the ability to do your job.  12. Contractors out number permanent staff and are more likely to get long-service awards.  AND THE REAL CLINCHERS ARE  13. You read this entire list, and kept nodding and smiling.  14. As you read this list, you think about forwarding it to your "friends".  15. You got this email from a friend that hardly talks to you anymore, except to send you jokes from the net.  16. You are too busy to notice there was no No. 9.  17. You contemplate scrolling back up to check that there wasn't a No.9.  18. And now you are laughing at yourself !  Finally, you forward this to your friends ..   

						
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   lunch time soccer is getting more and more aggressive. It seems most people are bring out the read hardware, soccer boots, shin pads etc.  I think it is time for me to get some shin pads too. Currently my shins feels like a big bruise. It seems that every game we play, I get my shins kick in. The "boss" is definately not happy about my bruises, but she doesn't understand that it is like a badge of honour. It is like saying that you put your body on the line for the game. But I have to agree with her that the injuries is taking a told on me. I fear on day I might get a broken bone or something... fingers cross I dont.  A new game may be an alternative. I think touch footy or ultimate frisby will be my next suggestions for game. Hopefully I will not experience as much injury.     

						
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Monday: Work, then drove to the city to pick up the "boss". She Was not feeling too well. She had double bad news. The office was broken into on the weekend and one of her workmates mum past away on Friday night. She works a very close knit environment, so it was quite depressing for her.   We met the deceased just last month for her daughters 21st birthday. She went into hospital last week for some minor surgery for her stomach. Her daughter told us that she was find on monday morning and she was just starting to eat solid food... but later that evening..she past away. It was a shock to everyone.  No one was prepared.  It is something so sad and so shocking, which reminds us, how fragile life is and how life of one of our love ones can disappear so very very quickly. Sometimes such sadness really highlights the futility of life. How can we move on from such sudden lost. How can we ever be the same again, when part of your life just disapper.   Is life is part of GODs cruel joke ? Or there is a meaning to this? A meaning to a human life?   Sunday: Work work work... Then Church and Sleep.  Saturday: went to a Mega Centre in Liverpool (1.5 hrs from home) and brought lots of  urlLink Krispy Kreme  donuts. If you have not heard of it or eat it, then I trully recommend it. It kicks all the other donut makers ass!! The donuts is soft, sweet and very very fluffy =)   

						
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Somethin’ in your eyes, makes me wanna lose myself Makes me wanna lose myself, in your arms There’s somethin’ in your voice, makes my heart beat fast Hope this feeling lasts, the rest of my life  If you knew how lonely my life has been And how long I’ve been so alone And if you knew how I wanted someone to come along And change my life the way you’ve done  It feels like home to me, it feels like home to me It feels like I’m all the way back where I come from It feels like home to me, it feels like home to me It feels like I’m all the way back where I belong  

						
</post>

<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The weather is really killing me, after an early start on Tuesday morning, I was looking forward to a nice rest last night, but due to the incredible heat in the apartment, I was sweating like a pig in bed and so I had a horrible night. I was twisting and turning all night long.   I do have A/C in the apartment, but it is only in the living room, so it takes forever to cool down the whole apartment... Man I swear if I ever have enough money to get my own place I am going to put an A/C right next to be in bed.  Anyway today was looking promising, since it looks like it is going to rain and the weather is really cool, so I was thinking this morning that I am going have myself a nice relaxing sleep tonight ...but guess what.. I have another early start for work again !!!  Yep, just got told about it!! we have an emergency release and I have to be there to ensure that is it fine! Bah!! I swear it is one problem why you should never live too close to work ... everyone wants you to be here at work early in the morning!!  My only bright side is that I get to go home early tomorrow....woo pee dii do!  I think I need a new job 

						
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It was a balmy 32 degrees celsius today. Thank god for A/C!! As always I had trouble waking this morning... I don't what it is, but once your body have tasted sleeping in on the weekend, it just wants more... no matter how much you sleep, you can always sleep more, especially when it is time to work.  Anyway work today was ok... learning a things about Perl. Man I can't believe we still use Perl, this is so old school... I guess that is why most of the developer here don't want to leave... or can't leave.  Played Ultimate frisbee today... it is an awesome game. Lots of running and lots and lots of sweating!!... especially under such heat!! Man I think I nearly suffered a heat stroke under the sun. Now I have a great tan line on my face, tracing my sun glasses... =P  After the game, I had a nice rest and a shower at home and went back to work... then comes the bad news... I have to start at 6 am tomorrow morning!! Fark!!  I hate morning release!!  I need my beauty sleep!!!  

						
</post>

<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Saw the movie,  urlLink A Man Apart  last night. This is definitely a guy flick. Starring the stiff face  urlLink Vin Diesel , this movie moves like an old mule with 3 legs. I truly believe that vin diesel could take the crown from  urlLink Steven Seagal  for the least changing facial feature in a movie. This man can't act and worst of all he can't fight.   It is just painful watching him "try to" cry... A dead cat has move emotive behaviour than him. I am guessing he gets his acting skills at the same school as Arnie.  Anyway the basis of the story is that his wife was murdered by the Mexican drug cartel and he wants revenge. The action is few and far between and the ending is a disappointment.   And if you think that there are girls to perv on...you are sorely mistaken, the movie don't even have any nice female to entertain us between the mediocre action.   Why did I even bother watching this movie?  Cause I thought Vin actually had some potential in XXX, but I guess it was just the bright lights in the movie. 

						
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Why should I be jealous of other people achievement? Why should I be jealous of other people joy? Why should I be jealous of other people Good Luck?  Why am I never contended with what I have, and why am I always blame someone else for my failures rather than owning it.  Does it matter that they are smarter or richer than you? Does it matter that they have a better car or a bigger house?  Why be envious of material things?  Am I not in a supporting family? an adoring wife? an easy job and close friends? What esle do I need? What else do I want?   

						
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Network Marketing! Why is everyone going into Network Marketing? Does it really work ? How do I say no to my friends who are inviting to one of this seminar? Why can't they leave me alone ??!!  Which one have I been to ?  urlLink Emma Page   urlLink Usana   urlLink Amway  And the latest  urlLink Gold Quest !!  So what do they sell? Nothing!! That is the whole point, what you buy is the business!  From my experience, in each seminar they would only spend 20% of the time telling you about the product they have, but what they sell is not the product (eg gold coins, vitamins, etc), but the business.  What they want us to do, is to be their walking, talking shop. We buy the business to make money and the product is like a benefit for getting the business  They spill out names like  urlLink Robert Kiyosaki  and  urlLink Denis Waitley . Saying that they approve of this product and if they approve of it, this means it will work for us!  They say that we can be free from the shackles of work, by selling the business. They say that if you believe it, you will be rich.  What do I say ?  F**K OFF!! Leave me alone! I don't want your business and I don't want your "Financial Advise" 

						
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   When I saw  urlLink The Passion of the Christ  last Saturday, along with a predominantly Catholic audience, there were an audible sadness and praise for this powerful movie. Even coming from a Buddhist background, I confess that the suffering that Jesus of Nazareth could even be felt in the pit of my stomach. I have read numbers of article on the film, critics calling the movie Anti-Semitic, the movie is too violent, etc..  But unless you have read the Christian scriptures and seen the movie, you can’t really judge the movie. Yes, the movie is violent. As a avid fan of bloody action, I can say I no problem with violent on screen, but the violences shown on the film, is not only about physical violence this character is subjected to, but it is the pain and suffering experienced by other characters. The emotional battle of Pontius Pilate (the Roman Overseer whom sentenced Jesus), the look of betrayal on Peter (the disciple whom denounced Jesus 3 times) and most of all the anguish felt by Mary (Mother of Jesus). I think the actress who portrayed Mary, is just amazing, she really showed the pain a mother would experienced.  Is the movie Anti-Semitic? Personally, I don't think so. The story comes straight out of the Bible. The Passion (ie 12 hours before Jesus's Death) has been played by every Church and every year on Easter! Nobody is claiming that the Bible is Anti-Semitic. Nobody is claiming that Jesus did not get prosecuted by the Jewish people. Nobody is claiming that Jesus did not get punish viciously by the roman. Nobody is claiming that Jesus did not get crucify by the roman.  People forgets that Jesus himself was a Jew, he was actually considered a Rabbi! So therefore the Passion is about a Jew getting prosecuted by his Jewish peers and some people think that it is Anti-Semitic?... I just don't get it.  Anyway that’s enough of my 2 cents worth. So as for the general  urlLink Agnostic  movie goer, word of warning, if you have never read the book called "Bible" then be prepared to be lost in the movie sequence. The movie is slow and it assumes that you are a faithful christian and you know your gospel. If you are a sadistic bastard, than you would love the blood and gore, if you like a period piece or you just enjoy to tell people that you have ignore the words of critics and judge the film by yourself, than you might appreciate the film.    It is a movie, which will make you contemplate about your faith if you are a believer and if you are not a believer you may get a little more understanding on the Christian faith. So my suggestion is go out a see it, and make your own mind up.  

						
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Had a nice short day today. Another guy is leaving today!! Which meant 3 hour farewell lunch, 1 hour farewell speech and pressies. 1 hour deciding on where to eat and 4 hours of real work =P  EXCELLENT!! Got to love Friday farewell.  The only bad thing... Which is not really a bad thing is the big lunch. Too much food!! Gluttony!! It has been 2 hours since lunch and I can still feel the pressure of the food in my gut!!. Pasta, pizza and gelato Do NOT mix!! Yikes!  I am now trying to drink some green tea to calm my tummy....I am just glad it was not curry for lunch... If it was I would not be at work =P heh heh ...HIROSHIMA BOMBING!! =P   

						
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Thank god for a loving wife =) I might complaint about her nagging, or her parents, but it is great to have her, especially when she comes home, just to give me the house key =) Unfortunately for her she had to work late, so she had to take the taxi back.   Anyway for anyone who cares, I got home safely with what little self esteem I had left after all the jokes from work-"mates". Man I got to create a systems so that I wont forget next time. I was thinking getting an extra key made, but that means I have to get the owners permission to create a copy, and that is just too much of a hassle... Since we are planing to leave soon.  Any ideas? 

						
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Today started so well, until I lock myself out of my apartment!!  As usual, during the lunch hours I went home to change into my sports cloths to have a game of soccer. Of course in my rush to paly, I left my freaking keys, wallet, every-farking-thing in my apartment!! What am I suppose to do. I don't even have a mobile to call anyone !! I am Farking stuck!!  So rather than freaking out, I decide to release my frustration on the field. And what do you know, it was one of my best game on the field today. I scored once and assisted a couple of times! Shit man I was hot, I was assisting in defence and offence. Our team won, 5 to 1 (I think)  So what to do next. I have to go back to work in my sport cloths and my stud shoes and ask someone to buzz me into the building. Called the wife and advised her of my foolishness. She laughed. I laughed. She told me that she have to work overtime, but she will try to drop the key at 5 pm. This means I had to walk around for the last 3 hours in my shorts and t shirt. Thank god that my company is pretty liberal about clothings. Added to the insult I am freezing my butt off under the A/C and I have no money to even buy my lunch.  So how was your day ....  

						
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Have anyone tried this...  While sitting at your desk, lift your right foot off the floor and make clockwise circles.        Now, while doing this, draw the number "6" in the air with your right hand.        Your foot will change direction and there's nothing you can do about it!   

						
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This is one thing that movies don't talk about ...  inlaws, and the simple like Mother' day.   My inlaws are planning to have a get togther with grandparents and have a big feast on one side of the city and My parents want to have a family feast too, on the other side of the city.  So what do I do? Who takes the priority ?  And such problem happens with Christmas, fathers day ..etc.  Thank god my parents are not christians, so they are not too pissed off if I don't visit them on Christmas day itself. Whereas the inlaws, wants their whole family together every year...  Image the havok if we have conflicting birthday parties....yikes!!  What do you do ? Who decides whose family is more important?  where is the simple life!!   

						
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I have finally join the ebay revolution =) I am finally a member of the ebay community and added to the fact I won my first bit =()  Damn it is kind of addictive too. The point of looking for bargain and seeing if you win your bid.   I tried to bid for 700 comics, which started at 1.00 and it is now 100!! .. I am guessing I am not going to win that =P  In any case I'll wait for my first product and see how the service is before I jump into the fray of buying or selling any stuff.   

						
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   back to work after enjoying the long weekend.  Saturday morning, we were invited to a Birthday Party, a 1st birthday party, which included a white bunny and a jumping castle...  My question is why are we invited ? we don't have kids and we are sure hell not going to play at with the bunny or the castle, so my conclusion is the presents. The parents wants lots of pressie for their little baby, so we are invited. I am sure the baby have not accumulated enough friends yet to qualify a party... Anyway, atleast there were some nice food.  Later in the evening we went a saw an amatuer play of "Much Ado about nothing", the great Shakespearian comedy. One of the wife's ex work mate was playing the character Hero.  The play was awesome. some of the actors were amazing, in the second part of the play they even move us into a real Church to play out the wedding scene.  It was pretty funky, it reminded me of the time when I was watching King Lear at the Globe Theatre in London. Awesome time.  Sunday, went to a picnic with the inlaws. Had to drive for over 2 hours to this place. It was one of the minor Dam for the Sydney catchment area. Had a nice time checking out the Dam and played some frisbee and cards.  Later, we went back to the inlaws place a palyed some Karaoke. My wife is an awesome singer, wereas for me, I am only a great singer in the shower....  =) It was my first time ever tried to sing and I was horrible. so I am thinking I should retire young, and look for a new profession =)  Monday, rest time for for both of us. We vege out on the tv and ate the whole day =) then in the evening I played Ultimate frisbee!  Damn the team is going good. We have played 8 games and we lost only 2 (in the first week), so now we have a chance to come second in the comp!! YEAH !!  And added bonus and I am getting better....   Tuesday, back at work...damn! Another developer just resign double damn! He is going to our major competitor... Triple damn!!!  I have yet to receive a reply from the position I applied for last friday... Bugger me!!   

						
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   What I love about Australia is the the long weekend =) This long weekend is to celebrate or commemorate the Australian and New Zealands soldiers who have lost their life in war. The special day is called ANZAC Day.  So this means that we have Monday off !!  YEAH!!  So what is my plans for the long weekend.    Have a good night sleep. which mean not to be woken up by the damn alarm clock! Do some house work maybe.  Read my new books which I brought recently... the latest book from David Gemmel. Watch a nice movie. See my parents. (and maybe get some home cooked meal)  And maybe I'll find some time to update my resume and start looking for a new job, cause work polictics is really starting to piss me off!  As they say a new job is like a holiday =)  So does anyone have a good site to go to for creating a good resume?       

						
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   it is always good to tell the truth ?  If the truth will hurt the recipient, should your still say it.   Like your partner asking you, if her butts looks big, or is she getting fatter. Should you tell the truth?  If yes, why? She doesnt really need to know the truth from you, you answer will only hurt her.  If No, Why? Can this "white lie" become more, where do you draw the line? Who decides when to tell the truth and when not to ?   

						
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   "Only two things are infinite, the universe and human stupidity, and I'm not sure about the former" -- Albert Einstein  "If practise makes perfect, and nobodys perfect then why practise?" -- Unknown   "A man can build a million bridges and suck one cock, at the end of the day he is a cocksucker." -- Unknown   "When you sit with a nice girl for two hours, it seems like two minutes. When you sit on a hot stove for two minutes, it seems like two hours. That's relativity." --Albert Einstein  "Ever notice that 'what the hell' is always the right decision?" -- Marilyn Monroe   "Today's youth are unbelievably horrible. They disrespect their parents. They are rude to their teachers. They use disgusting language and crave easy sex. They have no respect for even the basic forms of authority. They are lazy and avoid hard work. The world really is at risk from their bad attitudes. I truly pity the future of the planet..." - Socrates -- 235 B.C.   "Sometimes I think the surest sign that intelligent life exists elsewhere in the universe is that none of it has tried to contact us..." -- Unknown   

						
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Another day at the salt mine.  I finally found out that I am 10 K underpaid compared to my colleague. And what is my manager doing about it.. well I am told that they are fighthing for me to get a pay rise... for the last year and a half... Woo hoo! and what have I got ? nothing .. peanuts...   and they wonder why people have no loyalty to the company. Man do I need a new job.   

						
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   To the tune of "hey there, Georgie girl"…  Hey there, nancy boys When you gonna put down your nerdy toys Can't you see you're lacking vit-a-min Deeee Cos you don't get enough sun you look way pastyyyyyyyyy  Hey there nancy boys Improve on those air swings don't be coy By watching masters at work such as meeeeee Scoring goal after goal while huggin' a treeeeeeeeee  Cha cha cha  

						
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So how is everyones Easter holiday? Lots of chocies??  As for me, Easter could not come any sooner =) I finally had some chocolate, about 40 days of chocolate fasting. I know I am now catholic, but my wife is, and since she is giving up dairy for lent, I thought I would join her too. Man was that a big mistake. It is amazing how hard it is to stop something as Chocolate. And where do you draw the line? Can you Oreos cookies? Dring Milo? Chocolate milk etc...   Something I have to argue with my conscience, Milo is not chocolate !!... =P I love my Milo. I have been drinking Milo every morning since as along as I can remember. It is my daily source of energy =P  Anyway I am glad the fasting is over. I can finally taste the beautiful food of the gods.   So why the silence? Well I have been away. Not away away, I just took a week off during the easter holiday to help my dad in his shop. My parents decided to go on a holiday during Easter, so they needed someone to look after the shop. So guess who had to take Annual leave, to work at the shop.   Added to the insult, the whole week, the shop was quite, everyone was on holiday. I am stuck there with the only entertainment is reading my novel. Well atleast I finally finish my book. Anyway if you want to read a freaky book, with a whole lots of twist, then I trully recommend Invisible Monsters by Chuck Palahniuk (He is the author of Fight Club). If you have seen or read Fight Club, you would know what kind of genre the book is. Let me tell you, after reading this book, I would never look at a female stranger the same way again.      

						
</post>

<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Good thing about Easter in Oz..... We have a Long weekend break! Good Friday, the weekends and Easter Monday .... SWEEEETTTTT.... =)  So Happy Easter everyone ... Hope you all have a save on.  I have not eaten chocolate for 40 days and man am I ready for some .... soon my precious.....soonn.... 

						
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Got this QA from a "Mini" friend, so I thought I should post it here too.   1. NAME: Picolo 'The Merciless' 2. DO YOU THINK YOU'RE NORMAL: Absolutely, and I have a certificate to prove it!!  3. DO PEOPLE FIND YOU STRANGE: Of course... Everyone from work =P  4. DO YOU BELIEVE IN GOD: Yes  5. DO YOU SING A LOT: always, especially when I am driving alone  6. DO YOU BACKSTAB: sometimes  7. ARE YOU A GOOD FRIEND: I think so 8. ARE YOU IN LOVE: Of course, I am married 9. ARE YOU YOUNG: Young at heart  10.EVER BEEN A LEADER OF SOMETHING: yes  11.HAVE YOU EVER KILLED A LIVING CREATURE: Insects, Rats, etc...   12.LAST ODD THING DONE: what do you consider odd? 13.DO YOU WEAR MAKE-UP: once....don't ask =P 14.DO YOU REBEL: of course and without a cause 15.EVER STARTED A FIRE: absolutely!! Love to recycle candle wax....emm that is pretty odd eh? 16.DO YOU THINK YOU'RE EVIL: heh heh ... Without good, there is no evil. 17.DO YOU LIKE LYING: Only to customers 18.DO YOU REGRET: Always 19.DO YOU HAVE A BESTFRIEND: Of course 20.DO PEOPLE HATE YOU: sometimes 21.DO YOU HATE PEOPLE: Some people.  22.CAN YOU KILL SOMEBODY: depends on the motivations  23.DO YOU CUT YOURSELF?: Paper cuts, cooking, broken glass.... OUCH!!  24.EVER TASTED BLOOD: Yes, too much iron... 25.DO YOU CARE WHAT OTHERS MAY THINK OF YOU? Not always, and only from close friends  26.EVER DONE ANYTHING OCCULT: I drew a pentagon once 27.ARE YOU GOTHIC: no way!! I shower twice a day!  28.DO YOU SMOKE: Never. Anti-cigarettes/cigars  29.CONSUME DRUGS: Nope.  30.WHAT DO YOU WEAR: T-shirts and jeans  31.YOUR SKIN COLOR: slightly tanned 32.DO YOU LIKE THE SUN: only went it is rising and setting  33.HAVE YOU LOST SOMEONE YOU LOVE: Yes  34.HOW DOES GRIEF FEEL: and empty heart and soul 35.YOUR ROLE MODEL: My parents 36.YOUR HEART DESIRES TO BE WITH WHO: Only my heart knows... 37.YOUR LISTENING TO: Sarah Mclachlan - Fallen 38.DO HATE YOURSELF: only when I make a really silly mistake 39.DID THIS QUIZ MAKE SENSE: nope 40.PARTING WORDS: It is better to burn out than to fade away. 

						
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						      Jerry Seinfeld has teamed up with film-maker Barry Levinson to make a series of short online episodes that feature Jerry and Superman hanging out. The first episode, " urlLink The Uniform " features Superman going to help Jerry install a new DVD player.  Some Loser, who like to eat/drink. And his new taste is breast milk ...yummy urlLink Loser   Friends of urlLink Akira  would love this site. They have finally created a real replica of Kanedas bike!! and it runs!!  Man Do I ever want one!!   

						
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I am Back and I am now a trained SEa-MeN!! All girls BEWARE!! HAHAHA!!  The trip was awesome!  I saw dolphins swimming on our starboard bow and I swam in the clear blue sea. I learned that reading the wind is an art, and sailing boat, takes more patience than skills. We  urlLink tack  and we  urlLink jibe , we learned how to turn the boat went it capsize and make all kind of knots =)  The drive to the bay was a long 3 hours drive. Since we were using my car, I was the designator driver for the 3 day road trip. We went pass vineyards, farms, and refineries. We met some funny locals and nearly got lost, because my navigator only had an A4 piece of paper as the map!!  Of course like the typical road trip, we stopped at the local McDs for their breakfast deal on our first day. The pit stop was a heaven send, since we started the trip on the wee hour of the morning.   The boat was only a 20 footer, so it was nice and cosy for the 4 of us, which included our instructor. The conditions were great, 10 to 15 knots, perfect for the amatuers. We learned about the set up the main sail and the jib and of course we learned the sailors lingo. Navigating around a small ship takes some times to get use to, especially when the swells is not kind to us.   The only thing I regret about the trip were that I did not bring my hat and I did not use enough sunscreen, cause now I am nursing some serious sun burn on my legs, arms and lip!! My lip is cracked and so, when I eat, drink or try to kiss my wife, extreme pain course through my lip.  OUCH! 

						
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Got this from  urlLink Caleb       Exhibitionist movie! You'd get off on letting ANYONE and EVERYONE watch you have sex...even small children, you sick sonofabitch! Kinky is your middle name.    urlLink   What kind of porno would you star in?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    

						
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink Pentecost , a feast of the universal Church which commemorates the Descent of the Holy Ghost upon the Apostles, fifty days after the Resurrection of Christ, on the ancient Jewish festival called the "feast of weeks" or Pentecost (Exodus 34:22; Deuteronomy 16:10).   It is amazing what you find interesting when you are new into a religion. I am not a catholic, but my wife is. So I am gradually learning all the nuances of a whole new side of the catholic faith.   Before meeting my wife, all I knew about christianity is that the holy book is called the bible and their messiah is Jesus Christ. I always thought that the religion was very similar to the Islamic doctrine (althougth I confess I am not a follower of either). Following the Islamic believe, their holy book is the Quran and their messiah is Muhammad (peace be on him).  Anyway I find myself thinking about my own religious believe more now than ever before. I think that one must really live and experience life, before one can really appreaciate the power of religion.  I remember when I was young, I regularly follow my parent to the buddhist temple to pray. I don't know the doctrine nor do I understand what I was doing, but all I knew was I needed to pray cause my parents told me to. But now I know why. Now I feel the need to know the religion I was brought up as.   Is this what Buddha means by enlightenment ?   

						
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Another friday is upon us WOO HOOO!! I can finally sleep in and not worry about due dates and work politics. I can finally convert all my avi into VCD. I can finally finish my book Survivor. I can vacuum, and clean the apartment. I can do I laundry, I can cook food for the rest of the week.....  Damn... on second thought I think I'll stay at work and do some overtime =P   Have a nice weekend guys and gals...  

						
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						      There was a certain Professor of Religion named Dr. Christianson, a    studious man who taught at a small college in the Western United    States. Dr. Christianson taught the required survey course in    Christianity at this particular institution. Every student was    required to take this course his or her freshman year regardless of    his or her major. Although Dr. Christianson tried hard to communicate    the essence of the gospel in his class, he found that most of his    students looked upon the course as nothing but required drudgery.    Despite his best efforts, most students refused to take Christianity    seriously.  This year, Dr. Christianson had a special student named Steve. Steve was only a freshman, but was studying with the intent of going onto seminary for the ministry. Steve was popular, he was well liked, and he was an imposing physical specimen. He was now the starting center on the school football team, and was the best student in the professor's class.  One day, Dr. Christianson asked Steve to stay after class so he could talk with him. "How many push-ups can you do?" Steve said, "I do about 200 every night." "200? That's pretty good, Steve," Dr. Christianson said. "Do you   think you could do 300?"  Steve replied, "I don't know... I've never done 300 at a time." "Do you think you could?" again asked Dr. Christianson. "Well, I can try," said Steve. "Can you do 300 in sets of 10? I have a class project in mind and I need you to do about 300 push-ups in sets of ten for this to work.  Can you do it? I need you to tell me you can do it," said the professor. Steve said, "Well... I think I can...yeah, I can do it." Dr. Christianson said, "Good! I need you to do this on Friday. Let me explain what I have in mind."  Friday came and Steve got to class early and sat in the front of the room. When class started, the professor pulled out a big box of donuts. No these weren't the normal kinds of donuts, they were the extra fancy BIG kind, with cream centers and frosting swirls.  Everyone was pretty excited it was Friday, the last class of the day, and they were going to get an early start on the weekend with a party in Dr. Christianson's class.  Dr. Christianson went to the first girl in the first row and asked, "Cynthia, do you want to have one of these donuts?"  Cynthia said, "Yes."  Dr. Christianson then turned to Steve and asked, "Steve, would you do ten push-ups so that Cynthia can have a donut?" "Sure." Steve jumped down from his desk to do a quick ten. Then Steve again sat in his desk. Dr. Christianson put a donut on Cynthia's desk. Dr. Christianson then went to Joe, the next person, and asked, "Joe, do you want a donut?" Joe said, "Yes." Dr. Christianson asked, "Steve would you do ten push-ups so Joe can have a donut?" Steve did ten push-ups, Joe got a donut. And so it went, down the first aisle, Steve did ten pushups for every person before they got their donut. And down the second aisle, till Dr. Christianson came to Scott.  Scott was on the basketball team, and in as good condition as Steve. He was very popular and never lacking for female companionship. When the professor asked, "Scott do you want a donut?" Scott's reply was, "Well, can I do my own pushups?" Dr. Christianson said, "No, Steve has to do them."  Then Scott said, "Well, I don't want one then." Dr. Christianson shrugged and then turned to Steve and asked, "Steve, would you do ten pushups so Scott can have a donut he doesn't want?" With perfect obedience Steve started to do ten pushups. Scott said, "HEY! I said I didn't want one!" Dr. Christianson said, "Look, this is my classroom, my class, my desks, and these are my donuts. Just leave it on the desk if you don't want it." And he put a donut on Scott's desk.  Now by this time, Steve had begun to slow down a little. He just stayed on the floor between sets because it took too much effort to be getting up and down. You could start to see a little perspiration coming out around his brow. Dr. Christianson started down the third row. Now the students were beginning to get a little angry.  Dr. Christianson asked Jenny, "Jenny, do you want a donut?" Sternly, Jenny said, "No." Then Dr. Christianson asked Steve, "Steve, would you do ten more Push-ups so Jenny can have a donut that she doesn't want?" Steve did ten....Jenny got a donut.  By now, a growing sense of uneasiness filled the room. The students were beginning to say "No" and there were all these uneaten donuts on the desks.  Steve also had to really put forth a lot of extra effort to get these pushups done for each donut. There began to be a small pool of sweat on the floor beneath his face, his arms and brow were beginning to get red because of the physical effort involved.  Dr. Christianson asked Robert, who was the most vocal unbeliever in the class, to watch Steve do each push up to make sure he did the full ten pushups in a set because he couldn't bear to watch all of Steve's work for all of those uneaten donuts. He sent Robert over to where Steve was so Robert could count the set and watch Steve closely. Dr. Christianson started down the fourth row.  During his class, however, some students from other classes had wandered in and sat down on the steps along the radiators that ran down the sides of the room. When the professor realized this, he did a quick count and saw that now there were 34 students in the room. He started to worry if Steve would be able to make it. Dr. Christianson went on to the next person and the next and the next. Near the end of that row, Steve was really having a rough time. He was taking a lot more time to complete each set.  Steve asked Dr. Christianson, "Do I have to make my nose touch on each one?" Dr. Christianson thought for a moment, "Well, they're your pushups. You are in charge now. You can do them any way that you want." And Dr. Christianson went on.  A few moments later, Jason, a recent transfer student, came to the room and was about to come in when all the students yelled in one voice, "NO! Don't come in! Stay out!" Jason didn't know what was going on.  Steve picked up his head and said, "No, let him come." Professor Christianson said, "You realize that if Jason comes in you will have to do ten pushups for him?" Steve said, "Yes, let him come in. Give him a donut" Dr. Christianson said, "Okay, Steve, I'll let you get Jason's out of the way right now. Jason, do you want a donut?" Jason, new to the room hardly knew what was going on. "Yes," he said, "give me a donut." "Steve, will you do ten push-ups so that Jason can have a donut?" Steve did ten pushups very slowly and with great effort. Jason, bewildered, was handed a donut and sat down. Dr. Christianson finished the fourth row, then started on those visitors seated by the heaters. Steve's arms were now shaking with each push-up in a struggle to lift himself against the force of gravity. Sweat was profusely dropping off of his face and, by this time, there was no sound except his heavy breathing, there was not a dry eye in the room.  The very last two students in the room were two young women, both cheerleaders, and very popular. Dr. Christianson went to Linda, the second to last, and asked, "Linda, do you want a doughnut?" Linda said, very sadly, "No, thank you." Professor Christianson quietly asked, "Steve, would you do ten push-ups so that Linda can have a donut she doesn't want?" Grunting from the effort, Steve did ten very slow pushups for Linda. Then Dr. Christianson turned to the last girl, Susan. "Susan, do you want a donut?" Susan, with tears flowing down her face, began to cry. "Dr. Christianson, why can't I help him?" Dr. Christianson, with tears of his own, said, "No, Steve has to do it alone, I have given him this task and he is in charge of seeing that everyone has an opportunity for a donut whether they want it or not. When I decided to have a party this last day of class, I looked  at my grade book. Steve, here is the only student with a perfect grade. Everyone else has failed a test, skipped class, or offered me  Inferior work. Steve told me that in football practice, when a player messes up he must do push-ups. I told Steve that none of you could come to my party unless he paid the price by doing your push ups. He and I made a deal for your sakes. Steve, would you do ten push-ups so Susan can have a donut?" As Steve very slowly finished his last pushup, with the understanding that he had accomplished all that was required of him, having done 350 pushups, his arms buckled beneath him and he fell to the floor.  Dr. Christianson turned to the room and said. "And so it was, that our Savior, Jesus Christ, on the cross, plead to the Father, 'into thy hands I commend my spirit.' With the understanding that He had done everything that was required of Him, he yielded up His life. And like some of those in this room, many of us leave the gift on the desk, uneaten." Two students helped Steve up off the floor and to a seat, physically exhausted, but wearing a thin smile. "Well done, good and faithful servant," said the professor, adding "Not all sermons are preached in words." Turning to his class the professor said, "My wish is that you might understand and fully comprehend all the riches of grace and mercy that have been given to you through the sacrifice of our Lord and Savior Jesus Christ. He spared not only His Begotten Son, but gave Him up for us all for the whole Church, now and forever. Whether or not we choose to accept His gift to us, the price has been paid. Wouldn't you be foolish and ungrateful to leave it laying on the  desk?"  Share this with someone. It's bound to touch their heart and demonstrate Salvation in a very special way.    

						
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Got this from  urlLink Cowboy Caleb        THIS WAY UP   á      picolo has fragile contents which may break!      Username:     From  urlLink Go-Quiz.com   

						
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Can anyone be ever content with their own life?  Work, family, life, friends, money, love...etc   Work, I am sure I want to rise above the daily drudge of an IT personel. I have good work mates, but the company is shiting me after 5 years of boold and sweat...  Family, they are your past and your future. No matter what you do or say, they will always be by your side (I hope). Can it be better ? I always wish I could be related to Bill gates, so that I won't have to work .. =P  Life, all I need is more time and then I will have my life...  Friends, too many, too little... too far, too busy.... My friends are my family.  Money, ahhh the all encompassing evil. You can't get enough of it and you can live without it. Would I be happy if I have a million... or would be thinking if I can get one million, why can't I have 2 million...etc..  Love, What is love? Which love? The love from the heart, the mind or the groin?  Can I ever be content...... 

						
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Women are like hurricanes. When they come, they're wet and wild, but when they go, they take your house and car 

						
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I hate bloody managers!!! Why do I always feel like I am anally f**ked everytime I have a project meetings?  Why is developers always get the shit thrown at, when business owners change their mind or promise a release date which is impossible to uphold!!  And if it all works, the business get the bonus at the end of the year, whereas we who worked overtime will get our little pay-check and a pat on the back for all the hard work!!    

						
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Here is another spam I got from my friend....    * What time do you get up? 7.45 am =)  * If you could eat lunch with one person, who would it be? What?   Sarach Mclachlan!!... She is a hottie  * Gold or silver? Gold  * What was the last film you saw at the cinema? Troy.... Good but cheesy  * Favorite Actor? Sean Connery  * Favorite Actress? Jennifer Love Hewitt (She got Great sets of Personality!!)  * What is your favorite TV show? At the moment Las Vegas  * What do you have for breakfast? Special K with Apricots and peach  * Who would you hate to be stuck in a room with? Mark M ...he smells =P  * What/who inspires you? My family  * What is your middle name? Merciless  * Beach, City or Country? Beach  * Favorite ice cream? Cookies and cream  * Butter, plain or salted popcorn? Caramel  * Favorite color? Black  * What kind of car do you drive? Toyota  * Favorite sandwich? Club  * What characteristic do you despise? snobbish  * Favorite flower? Titan Arum  * If you could go anywhere in the world on vacation, where would you go?  The scottish Highlands!!  * What color is your bathroom? White with silver lining  * Favorite brand of clothing? Best and Less  * Where would you retire to? In a Home.  * Favorite day of the week? Friday  * Favorite time of the year? Vacation time  * What did you do on your Birthday? Dinner Party   * Where were you born? In a hospital.  * Favorite sport to watch? Is Swimsuit modelling a sport?  * Who do you least expect to send this back to you? Someone with plenty of spare time  * Person you expect to send it back first? Someone with lots and lots of spare time  * What fabric detergent do you use? I don't =P  * Coke or Pepsi? Water  * Are you a morning person or a night owl? Neither... I like my sleep  * What is your shoe size? Between 9-10 depending on the make.  * Do you have any pets? Mara, the Lady of Acoma. She is the fighting fish which guard the house!    

						
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Dedicated to all the Lost Love....  Love is finding that the things you like best about yourself are not in you at all, but in the person who completes you. - Orson Scott Card     

						
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I saw  urlLink Sarah Mclachlan  in concert last night and it was amazing. Her voice is amazing live and her live music is awesome!!   It was her first concert in Oz and you can tell that she is really enjoying it. 3 nights in Sydney and it was fully booked!  This is definately a must for all the fans!! If you have the opportunity to see her live..then do!!  She is so sweet and beautiful!!  Sarah Mclachlan ROCKS!! 

						
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So beside the low blood count =P I had to enjoy my day at work without mail!! Yep yep .. our mail server took a dump and we had no mail for the whole freaking day!!  Imagine what happens if you don't get email for a whole day ?  People actually have to get off from their chairs and talk to other people face to face!!! (scary!!) No email trail!!.. damn how am I going to cover my butt!! Do you mean I have to write it down on a piece of paper!!...  Where is my pen and paper.... can I still read my own hand writing ?   

						
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Performed my regular good deed today... I gave blood to the Red Cross.  You can only give blood, every 3 months, so this is my second time. It is pretty cool, especially you get out of work for 2 hours!!  The bus comes and pick you up from work, you get all the free juice and water you want. I had to drink atleast 6 to 8 cups of liquid before donating blood. Then you spend about 30 mins giving blood and at the end you get free meal too.  We go to the Head Blood bank, so we get free food, if you go to the mobile blood bank you will only get some cookies and water =P  Anyway it is the giving which is important. Trust me it is not even painful. You get a finger prick to test your hemaegoblin count and the second jab is from the needle to get the blood.    So go out now and save some lifes and become a blood donor!! 

						
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Another bloody long day today ...  Spend the whole day troubleshooting one of our test mail server and it is giving me the shit. Bloody logs don't tell me anything and all our developers are gone!  The only thing which lifted up my day was, I had an hour lunch and watch my latest Enterprise episode which I just got from torrent... Thank you Torrent =0 Hoshi and T'pol are both hotties!! =)  oh guess what, I was invited to go to another network marketing last night... inlaw friend, which I could not say no. OmegaTrend was the business name. Another replication of Amway. Another bunch of sales guys/gals telling me that in 4 years I can get 1/4 mil per month!!   Damn!!! if that were true, why were we sitting in a lousy meeting room and the sales man wore only a 100 suit??....    

						
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    "Keep chasing the DBA till you stop getting this error despite dba suggesting all the other things. You get this message only when there is something wrong with the listener and only DBA can fix it."  

						
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It is amazing what you can get now on the internet!!! Check out the  urlLink Very Big Knife  

						
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   You know the deal....     1. WHAT COLOUR PANTS ARE YOU WEARING?  GREEN   2. WHAT ARE YOU LISTENING TO RIGHT NOW?  tapping of keyboard   3. WHAT ARE THE LAST 4 DIGITS OF YOUR PHONE NUMBER?  5299   4. WHAT DID YOU LAST HAVE TO EAT?  Chinese dumpling...very nice =)   5. IF YOU WERE A CRAYON, WHAT COLOUR WOULD YOU BE?  black   6. WEATHER RIGHT NOW?  freezing, blue sky   7. LAST PERSON YOU TALKED TO ON THE PHONE?  wife, asking here where she was    8. DO YOU LIKE THE PERSON WHO SENT YOU THIS?  Absolutely not. She is a pain in the butt =P   9. HOW ARE YOU TODAY?  recovering from a cold   10. FAVOURITE DRINK?  water   11. FAVOURITE ALCOHOLIC DRINK?  a nice resiling   12. FAVOURITE SPORT? ??  ultimate Frisbee   14. EYE COLOUR?  black   15. DO YOU WEAR CONTACTS?  no glasses   16. SIBLINGS AND THEIR AGES?  2 sister   17. FAVOURITE FOOD?  Malaysian Chinese   18. LAST MOVIE YOU WATCHED?  Van Helsing (very crappy)   19. FAVOURITE DAY OF THE YEAR?  30th of November...my birthday !! woo hoo another older.....yikes!   20. ARE YOU TOO SHY TO ASK SOMEONE OUT?  absolutely!!   21. SUMMER OR WINTER?  Winter   22. RELATIONSHIPS OR ONE NIGHT STANDS?  I AM MARRIED....what do you think?   23. CHOCOLATE OR VANILLA?  chocolate   24. DO YOU WANT YOUR FRIENDS TO WRITE BACK?  Absolutely .  25. WHO IS MOST LIKELY TO RESPOND?   everyone....no one   26. LEAST LIKELY?  ??   27. LIVING ARRANGEMENTS?  Living in a shoe box apartment, with the wife and paying a bomb for it.   28. WHAT BOOK ARE YOU READING AT THE MOMENT?  Sarah By Orson Scott Card   29. WHAT'S ON YOUR MOUSE MAT?  Canberra Raiders 2000 mouse pad   30. FAVOURITE BOARD GAME?  Rat Race   31. WHAT DID YOU DO LAST NIGHT?  shopping    32. FAVOURITE SMELLS?  fresh bread   33. CAN YOU TOUCH YOUR NOSE WITH YOUR TONGUE?  nope   34. WHAT/WHO INSPIRES YOU?  Human stupidity   35. BUTTERED, PLAIN, OR SALTED POPCORN?  buttered, but caramel is better   36. FAVOURITE CAR?  BMW Z 3   37. FAVOURITE FLOWER?  Lily        

						
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   On Friday night, I had dinner with my folks. A family get together once a week is always so much more pleasant than seeing them everyday =P Saturday morning was a 1st birthday party. I was his best man for his wedding 3 years ago and now we are celebrating his sons first birthday !! Damn time fly by very quickly!!... The one thing I hate about this kind party is that we are inundated with the annoying question of "when are your going to have a baby?" Damn I hate that question... I would like to tell them, when I bloody feel like it !! Why is there a need to have kids so quickly after you are married anyway??.. Can we just enjoy the freedom first before we are stuck as parents... Or am I just selfish?  Then Saturday night was a big birthday party for a Uni friend at a Indian restaurant Called Planet Bollywood. Good company, alright food but horrible service. The place was over crowsed, since the small restaurant was hosting 2 birthday party, one engagement party and one big 20th wedding Anniversary party. You can just imagine how loud the place would be =P  Then Sunday I worked at my dads shop and went to Sunday mass.  

						
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   As always we had the weekly farewell friday to one our own. This was a big one!! This dude has been with us for over 8 years!! so there was plenty of speeches and bitches =P  Anyway went to the local bar for the usual beers and food.   But the most interesting thing that happen was, I met my old high school friend!!  We have not seen each other for close to 10 years and suddenly we bum into each other at my local pub!!! What is the chance of that ....on second thought I think I'll buy myslef a lottery ticket tonight =)  So we chatted and I found out that he just moved to my area and he is working down the road from me. So I am sure we will meet up for lunch soon !!  Damn!! it has been 10 years since I left High school!!! SHIT I AM OLD!! I wonder what the hell is everyone doing now.  Man I hated my first half of my high school life. I was small and the old asian in my year. I was bullied and pick on till I grew some balls to fight back.  Well they do bred you tough in my neighbourhood... all boys school and no asian.... I learned quick on how to assimilated to the brave new world.  10 years!!!  Where am I going to be in my next decade??....  

						
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Had the weirdest dream this morning. Normally I never remember my dreams, but today it was so vivid, that I still remember it.   The dream starts of with a group of us on a excursion to somewhere. While we are travelling on this dirt road, we saw an "Alien" (from the aliens movie) on the road. I shouted Accelerate !!! and the driver speed up. But the alien anticipated the action and jump ontop of the bus!!  Everyone was freaking out... I was freaking out....   I would see a small hole opening from the aliens acidic saliva... and I quickly grap a pistol from one of the passengers and try to pull the trigger.  The last thing I remember is the Alien jumping throught the openning towards me and I am trying to squeeze the trigger...then the alarm woke me up.  Strange eh..... any dream readers out there ?? 

						
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Unfortunately I have been under the weather for the last few days. It started on last Friday and I didn't work on Sunday and Monday... but I am back to work now...WooPeeDee doo.   I think it is just the sudden change in weather. I am not coughing. but sometimes I get a mild temperature and I feel really lethargic. Hopefully I feel better soon, cause I already missed my first day on my ultimate frisbee winter season.  Also I am going to the blood bank next friday.   Anyway today we had another farewell speech from one of our tech. To celebrate his departure, we had an extra long soccer game. I was still feeling unwell, but I had to play cause we needed the number. It was a good game. We were tied till the last minute of the game.   

						
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It's my ex birthday today. It has been years since I have seen her, but I'll always remember her birthday. I remember when I was in Oz and she was in KL, I would call her and send her a pressy every year. A tradition which continue even after we broke up, but I guess as time goes by, we tend to lose touch.   Eventhough sometimes I might not acknowledge her special day, I'll always remember her special day.  Happy Birthday JM.   Hope you are having a wonderful day. 

						
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Man I didn't log in for a few days and blogger.com has completely change the whole admin page... Not bad.  As they say, a change is like a holiday =) 

						
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Can one still wish their ex's a happy birthday?    

						
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Damn damn damn!!  what do you know, I am Sick!!! Yep, even with vitamins C I am SICK! and on the bloody weekend too!!   On the 2 days I can enjoy my self and relax... I have to be sick!! and add to the bloody insult... I cant sleep. It is 1 am in the morning and I am bright eye and bushy tail... what am I to do. Should I take some night tablets or should I blog.... guess what I chose? =P  Anyway today is Mothers day... so remember to wish your mother a Happy Mothers day....  As a good boy, I brought my mum a frame with a buddhist mantra. Pretty cool I think.... and I took them out for dinner on saturday night.... so what did you all do??...  Damn... where did I put my sleep.... 

						
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Man don't you hate when you know that you are not feeling 100%, but yet you are not sick enough to justify taking a day off, so you go to work anyway. Well today is my 95% day. A day where I don't really want to work because it feels like I am getting a headache.. but not yet. I feel like coughing... but no cough is coming out. My head feels like it is drunk, but I have not taken any alcohol for a long long time.... DAMN!!  I hate it!!!  I had to cancel sport because I don't want to exert myself. I don;t want to get sick for the weekend. I have things to do!!  Mother's day dinner on saturday, work at my dad's shop on sunday and I have to clean the flat.  oh finally solve the problem about mothers day ... We are inviting both side of the family to dinner to celebrate the day! Kills 2 bird with 1 stone! ... YEAH!  

						
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It seems that everyone is on one diet or another, even the famous online food Connoisseur urlLink wena is on a diet. What is the world going to?  Why are everyone on a diet? Are we eating so much more than yester-year ? that we have to change our eating habit.  Are you such a sloth that we are not burning the fat away?  I have never thought myself as fat, sure I have a slight gut like every other "normal" guy. I eat what I want and I sometimes play sport. I confess I want to be a "beef cake" when I was in high school, just because all the bullies in the school was picking on me. But now I don't see the need. I am happy as I am.   Of course like any guy, I would like a "6 pack" too, but do you personally know actually have a "6 pack".  Personally I just want to be healthy. But I guess the big question is, what is healthy? Is it being happy with who you are and what you are? or Someone who have to control everything they eat and do ..?   

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Are you allowed to Think/Talk/See your ex after you are married ?  Is that bad? 

						
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Had an big soccer game today, with another company for lunch. Damn my shin hurts like hell...!!! Shins clashes is the worst!!  The opposition plays rough ... and they are much bigger than us too.  It was dissapointing that they beat us, but it was still a good game. I broke their attacks a couple of time and I have the bruises to show it... OUCH. My shins feels like speed humps... =P  I think it is time for me to get some shin pads. 

						
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Have anyone seen   urlLink Newlyweds: Nick & Jessica .  I swear that is one of the most funny reality series out there!. It is like the osbournes with more peroxide!! Jessica simpson the blonde bimbo with nice tits and arse, must be one of the most ignorant girl on TV. And it is amazing how funny it is seeing live her life with her new husband, Nick Lachey.  One of my favourite quote from the series :   Jessica: Is this chicken or is this fish? I know it's tuna. But it says chicken. By the sea.    Can you get anymore blonde ??  

						
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    I once thought of inserting my ex's name in the song and sang it to her, but I didn't have the guts to do it. Maybe I should have eh?....    Oh, Donna, Oh, Donna Oh, Donna, Oh, Donna  I had a girl Donna was her name Since she left me I've never been the same 'cause I love my girl Donna, where can you be? Where can you be?  Now that you're gone I'm left all alone All by myself To wander and roam 'cause I love my girl Donna, where can you be? Where can you be?  Well, darlin', now that you're gone I don't know what I'll do All the time and all my love for yo-ou-ou  I had a girl Donna was her name Since she left me I've never been the same 'cause I love my girl Donna, where can you be? Where can you be?  Oh, Donna, Oh, Donna Oh, Donna, Oh, Donna   

						
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Guess what, another work mate resign today... which takes up to approx a dozen people in 6 months!! yeah baby... I think the ship is sinking and people are not waiting for the siren...  The funny think is that this person only started less than 6 months ago...yikes... and I am been here longer than i want.  But there is a some good news. I had an interview with a agency and they are organising some prospect employer in the next 2 weeks. So wish me luck ok....  On another news, we had our frisbee final yesterday and we came second!! Damn straight, it was my first comp I ever played and our team came second.. so that was pretty awesome.  Also brought 2 new dvds, dirt cheap.  1.  urlLink La Bamba . The rise and death of Richie Valens.... Awesome music. Los Lobos kicks arse!!  2.  urlLink Last of the Mohicans . Another one of my favourite. This movie is much better than The Patriot and Daniel Day Lewis kicks Mel Gibsons butt anytime!  If you have not seen any of these movies, then I highly recommend it.   

						
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I think I am going to be a Born-Again fan for Woman Tennis!! Why you asked? 3 words buddy....microscopic hipster shorts Check out the babe below and you will be a new convert too =)    urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						       I don't know why, but she grows on you after a while. She is a crappy actor and I hate her nasal whinny voice and I don't think that she has an awesome body, but she is sexy!  There are currently  160,000 sites about her on google. So what is the attractions?      

						
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   T-minus 3 days  I think I am beginning to enjoy my last week of work. It is like the last week of school, where your care-factor is going to zero and you do what ever you want.  My day consisted of coming in late, going home to try to burn some DVD, go to the post office to get some stuff, have a 2 hour lunch with a colleague, drink a couple of nice cold beer, check out some websites and read some news.  Damn life is great !! I can't wait for tomorrow. I think I'll set up an FTP server on one of my Test PC and move all my stuff there, so I can burn it off.   Also I think thursday will be Spiderman 2 day, since it is coming out on thursday and I can't be bother going to work =P heh heh ....  Hopefully my work ethic/conscience will not destroy my evil self =P  

						
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						       Would you believe that a Champion Ice skater would become an amatuer boxer? Well   urlLink Tonya Harding  has made that switch and man I think she is regretting it.  Tonya Harding's new career as a boxer took a severe beating Friday, along with her face, as she was knocked out by Amy Johnson.  The fight was stopped at 1:04 of the round. 

						
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Read an interesting article about blogging on the local online news  urlLink SMH . It gives a nice overview on what software you can use to blog.  

						
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Remember her?  urlLink Erika  was the hottie in Baywatch when it first came out. I am sure all the guys in the 80s had the hots for her. She was like the wet dream of all teenage kids... I know I dream of her a couple of times =P To make even sexier was that she was a playmate !! Which mean if you have the guts you can always try to get the mags!! Man those were the days when you sneak out late at night and go to the local petrol stations and get those Adult magazines =) Those guys who worked the grave yard shift were the best, they didn't care if you were underage, they just let you buy what ever you want!! Of course most of the time we had to draw lots to see who would go and buy the first one and see if you do get caught. Luckily for me I never was the first =)  Anyway now adays you don't even need to do that anymore. If you want a pic of a celebrity you like, just type their name on google and bobs your uncle..       And the funniest thing is that most of pics of her is nude =P  

						
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Yep that is right... I am an Uncle again! My sister in-law has just pop up another child. Supposedly a healthy daughter.  This means I will have to travel for an hour to check out how they are and spend the rest of the month getting a earful from the wife, about how she is getting old and she wants a child. How that all her friends are having a child and she wants one too!  Can she not realise that we just got married. And we should have some time enjoying the freedom and getting our self settle in. Get a place of our own and get some capital before we launch ourself into making an baby. Heh I am happy to practice all she like, but comeon lets be practical, a child is the single most expensive thing in the world, do we really want to jump straight on to it.   I love our freedom at the moment, we can travel when we want and we can do anything on a drop of a hat, what is going to happen with a baby......  

						
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Here is an update on the new Curry in a Hurry  urlLink Spiderman . Check him out!! Don't you think that his shoes is sexy!!       Definitely he is Bollywood material 

						
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink Are you 3ll3?  Can you h4x0r codes like trinity ? OR are you just a "script kiddy" ....  In any case you can speak like them, the this cool little  urlLink 3ll3 Translator   

						
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   According to the news  urlLink Colin Farrell's manhood  is reportedly so big it was considered too shocking for moviegoers.....  I guess that might be true, but that is only because they have not film my Stainless Steel WANG on film yet!!  

						
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						       She is a great beauty in real life, and not bad as a digital one....       Now you can enjoy her weekly on ER.  

						
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   When you were young, all you need to do was to get good grades. To study hard and get good grades, so that you can go to a good High School.   Then you have to study even harder to get into a Good University.   Then you have to study even even harder to get a Good Job.  Once you get a good job, what do you do ? What does your family expect you to achieve next ?  MARRIAGE of course!!  After the marriage what is next??......  Do you get a place of you own or do you have a baby first ? I have been told that by the wife that she wants a baby!!  But I want to get a place of our own first....  So what is next ?   

						
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Ayn Rand named her philosophy “ urlLink Objectivism ” and described it as a philosophy for living on earth. Objectivism is an integrated system of thought that defines the abstract principles by which a man must think and act if he is to live the life proper to man. Ayn Rand first portrayed her philosophy in the form of the heroes of her best-selling novels, The Fountainhead (1943) and Atlas Shrugged (1957). She later expressed her philosophy in nonfiction form.    Can she be the next  urlLink L. Ron Hubbard ?       Scientology Aims: A civilization without insanity, without criminals and without war, where the able can prosper and honest beings can have rights, and where man is free to rise to greater heights, are the aims of Scientology. — L. Ron Hubbard    

						
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Can computer really be faster than we ever dream of??.....   urlLink Computers in 2034  

						
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						       Would you believe she is  urlLink Chiaki Kuriyama , the actress who played the Psycho Killer Go Go in  urlLink Kill Bill vol 1 . She looks pretty harmless from where I am sitting, but damn was she scary in the movie ....   

						
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I have finally got my whole collection of Batman Animated series, Superman Animated and Justice League Series 1 and 2!!  It is great to have unlimited bandwidth at work and a overused CD burner =)  Now I am trying to convert all my AVI collections into MPEG so I can burn into DVDs with funky menus. I am currently using TMPEG DVD Author... Does anyone have other software suggestions? 

						
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   She is the new Guinevere.     Now I understand why Lancelot would betrayed Arthur..... 

						
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Had a great weekend.  Went and saw Shrek 2 on friday and it was awesome!       They have some great movie spoof. LOTR, Zorro and of course mission impossible!! I love puss n' boots, he was great. All the girls cried out when they puss showed his "cute" face.   If you have not seen it, I absolutely recommend it.  On saturday we had a get together with a bunch of my Uni friends. We basically started yacking from 2 pm to 2 am !! and the best thing was that there was no alcohol. Just pure good natured get together.  We talk about life, old uni life, gossip about old friends. We had pizza and pasta for dinner and played  urlLink Taboo . Awesome game!! It was the battle of the sexes and I am proud to say that the guys won!! and we were handicapped. 5 against 3!!  It was the most enjoyable time. It has been 6 years since uni, and it is amazing that we are still together. To be invited to weddings and to talk about the good old days. It sometimes makes me feel very old...in a good sort of way.  

						
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   SPIDERMAN will put on a sarong and fight the bad guys through the rickshaw-clogged streets of Bombay in an Indian version of the US comic classic, according to reports.    urlLink Bollywood spiderman!!   I wonder if they have the typical bollywood singing half in the story .... 

						
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I officially handed in my resignation today .... man I was a little bit nervous about that.  I could not sleep the night before thinking about it ... but now I am glad it is over!  I have 2 weeks and I will be out of here and into my new role at a software company... +0  Wish my luck in my new job!!!  

						
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						       I can't believe that  urlLink The SUN  can have a full page article about how Kate Moss have a wedgie!!?  Who cares?!   In anycase I think Kate is a little bit cold... so I think I might drop by NY and warm her up =) 

						
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   You've got to see this.  It's incredible !! 1st look and see the shark under the water. Keep your cursor out of the picture until you see the shark.  Then move your mouse cursor onto the picture, but stand back, you might get wet (it's like it's 3D).    urlLink Click Here  

						
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The  urlLink Art of war , is governed by five constant factors, to be taken into account in one's deliberations, when seeking to determine the conditions obtaining in the field.  These are:  (1) The Moral Law: The Moral Law causes the people to be in complete accord with their ruler, so that they will follow him regardless of their lives, undismayed by any danger.  (2) Heaven: Heaven signifies night and day, cold and heat, times and seasons.  (3) Earth: Earth comprises distances, great and small; danger and security; open ground and narrow passes; the chances of life and death.  (4) The Commander: The Commander stands for the virtues of wisdom, sincerely, benevolence, courage and strictness.  (5) Method and discipline: By method and discipline are to be understood the marshaling of the army in its proper subdivisions, the graduations of rank among the officers, the maintenance of roads by which supplies may reach the army, and the    control of military expenditure.   This is a 2400 years old work! And it is still as important now. Doesn't it makes you proud to be a chinese =)  

						
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Is she a hottie or what. I haven't seen her in a lot of movies, but she is damn good.       She is close to 40 years old and she is still gorgeous! What is she taking or doing??!! 

						
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Bad news first, we have just been told that our company is up for sale!! We don't if we have buyers, but all we know is that our mother company wants to sell us.... BITCH!!  We don't know much details, but as you may guess the morale here is crap. In any case nothing will change till there is an offer and even that will take 3 to 6 months.   Good News, I have been offered a new job!! Pays 10K more and it is close to home! It is a small software company but I think it will be good for a change.  Man, someone upstairs is really smilling upon me =) 

						
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   NO FREAKING WAY!!  urlLink Malaysian Idol  is coming to TOWN!!  So is anyone on the blogsphere going to sing their little hearts out??.... 

						
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I just found out that Elisha Cuthbert was born on the same day as me.... Hot Dang!!    Is she a hottie or what =P Can't wait to see her in  urlLink The Girl Next Door  

						
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   There is a  urlLink Pastor  in Denmark which has been quoted as saying that he did not believe in God, resurrection or eternal life. Additional to this, he was asked to resigned by the church and he refuse!!  And people from him Church actually wants him to stay!!  What the Hell For!??! He is a Pastor, he is suppose to preach the word of God, so logically if he doesn't believe in what he is teaching should he not just leave?  The people from the parish is "arguing that the church must tolerate differences of opinion."   WHAT THE F**K!!   HE DOES NOT BELIEVE IN GOD!!  That is the whole point of religion! That is the whole basis of the Church. The pastor is not just disagreeing about what colour shorts he should wear on the weekend... he has lost the faith and he is preaching it!  DAMN!! The is political correctness gone wrong!    

						
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   What else can I say, check it out... it is pretty funny =P  urlLink Keep Your Jesus off My Penis  

						
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   "Artificial beauties" from around the world will gather "soon" to show off the skills of their plastic surgeons, the Xinhua news agency reported, citing the head of the organizing committee, surnamed Lu.    urlLink news.com.au  

						
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Just got a call..... I have a second interview next week with the MD!!!  HOT DANG!!  Wish me luck boys and girls.....  

						
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   A boy was walking down the road when a car pulled over.  "If you get in," the driver said, "I'll give you $10."  The boy refused and kept on walking. A bit further along, the man pulled  over again.  "Ok, how about $20 and a bag of lollies?" the driver asks. The boy told the  man to piss off, and kept on walking. Further up the road, the driver tried  once more.  "Right this is my final offer , I'll give you $50 and all the lollies you  can eat".  The little boy stopped walking, went towards the car, leaned in and said,  "You bought the f *&king  Volvo, DAD...... live with it." 

						
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink Dancing Hippo  

						
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Anyway the upside to waking early is that you can go home early. Left work at 3 ish and went straight to the local RTA (Road Traffic Authority) to renew my drivers license. Of course the place was packed with house wifes and the retired!! I think government office has the worst customer service skills in the all professions! And you know why, cause no matter what they do to you (customer), you have to come back they do not have any competitor!  The average wait time is 1.5 hours!! It doesn’t matter if you want to renew a license or pay a bill, you have to wait 1.5 freaking hours just to see someone!! There are atleast 30 people waiting just to pay their bills (which you can't pay online). If you are running your own private business, would you let your customer wait so long just to pay you? If you are a customer to any other commercial company, would just leave and never come back?   Then Why are there so many frustrated people hanging around? Because we have to! There are no other way!!  As for me, I went in and took a ticket, check what was the next number to be called and went out for lunch. Had myself a nice Portuguese Chicken burger and lipton ice tea, walk around the nearby shops before I went back to the RTA. 

						
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Had to be at work early yesterday. 6 am start!! We had a few release in the morning and lucky me I was the one to test that it works in production. 4 hour sleep and cold morning shower is always great for the body =P  Had no breakfast, just a banana and a cup of tea. Of course the installation was did not go in smoothly. I had to fix a couple of bugs on the way. Man it is so hard to troubleshoot when you are running low on sleep and food in your stomach. In any case it all worked well in the end. And what did I get for all my hard work? Nothing ZIP!! Just more work.  

						
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Q.) What doesn't belong in this list: Meat, Eggs, Wife, Blowjob?  A.) Blowjob: You can beat your meat, eggs or wife,but you can't beat a blowjob.   Q.) Why does a penis have a hole in the end?  A.) So men can be open minded.   Q.) What's the speed limit of sex?  A.) 68 because at 69 you have to turn around.   Q.) What do a Rubix cube and a penis have in common?  A.) The longer you play with them, the harder they get.   Q.) What's the difference between your paycheck and your dick?  A.) You don't have to beg your wife to blow your paycheck!   Q.) Three words to ruin a man's ego...  A.) "Is it in?"   Q.) What do you get when you cross Raggedy Ann and the Pillsbury Dough Boy?  A.) A red headed bitch with a yeast infection.   Q.) How can you tell when an auto mechanic just  had sex?  A.) One of his fingers is clean.   Q.) What do you do with 365 used rubbers?  A.) Melt them down make a tire, and call it a Goodyear.   Q.) What does bungee jumping and hookers have in common?  A.) They both cost a hundred bucks and if the rubber breaks, you're screwed.   

						
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Had a job interview on last friday...damn it was nerve racking. I have not been in an interview for 5 years and I was a wee bit rusty.  My palm was actually wet and my throat was dry...  But as time went by, I was more relaxed and got into the groove. I guess interviews is like riding a bicycle... you never forget how to do it... but sometimes you do get a bit rusty... =P  Good thing that the interviewer was also rusty and non technical =P I think I impressed her, cause she asked for my reference and she is organising a second interview with me and the MD.   So finger cross and I'll be in a new job and much much better pay!!!  

						
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Also I think  urlLink Emmy Rossum  is such a hottie!!  Can't wait to see her in her future screen hits =)  Yummy Yummy!! 

						
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   went and saw  urlLink Day After Tomorrow  last night with the wife. Had KFC for dinner and gelato for dessert and for entertainment we saw the movie.   I must say it was not bad. The first 40 mins of the movie was awesome, the CGI was great and no cheesy acting.. but after all the money was spend on the CGI I guess you can't blame them for the bad acting and cheesy lines.   Overall I don't mind the movie at all. It has all the key entertainment value:   1. Action 2. Special Effects   What else do you need??...  Also I had the most awesome chocolate fudge gelato !! It was a great dessert after a greasy 3 piece meal =)     

						
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Thank god that my boss is back tomorrow... for the last week and a half I have been the unofficial boss in my little department.  I hate just taking over..cause I don't want my other work mates thinking that I am power monger. But the problem is that my other co-workers are lazy arse and never wants to take over the resposibility, so it just gets default on to me.   All I do is go into management meetings and bitch about how marketing ask for ridiculous time for deployment!   Of course the best is, when you speak to Ops and try to convince them that we need to install the release on a specific date.  I swear today, I have to argue with this ops rep that we need to release a code before 6.00AM.... So she replied "Ok make it 6:30" ???!!??  BEFORE 6.00AM YOU DUMB ARSE BITCH!! NOT AFTER!!!  Man at that moment.... if I had a gun... I would have gone postal on her =P 

						
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   If it is good enough to clean your toilets, it is good enough to drink =)    urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Damn!! I have an invitation and no girls are climbing on me!!    

						
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The good thing about working here is that the boss is really friendly and nice. Today was one of the techie Birthday, so the Boss decided to shout everyone Lunch to celebrate the occasion. It was a spur of the moment thing, everyone just rock up to the local bar & grill and had a nice get together.  He even brought us a round of drinks (alcoholic too)!!  I must say I can envisage my ex-manager buying us lunch or even a drink after work. In such a small and fairly new company, they have an open door policy and pretty laid back. I guess that is one of the good thing in working for a nice small company. Also I find out today that some of the guys can even work at home. They just rock up once a week for meetings and the rest of the time they just provide support via the net at the comfort of their own home... wouldn't that be cool =)  

						
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Its a bug, Its a wacky toy, NO its "Monsieur II"    urlLink      These little guys are said to be the world's smallest and thinnest micro-actuator- and Bluetooth-equipped robot prototypes.  Attached a camera and a Hearing device, and this will be sold out like hot cakes, on the next Voyeur Convention  

						
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Corporate Lesson 1   A man is getting into the shower just as his wife is finishing up her  shower when the doorbell rings. The wife quickly wraps herself in a towel and runs downstairs.   When she opens the door, there stands Bob, the next door neighbour. Before  she says a word, Bob says, "I'll give you $800 to drop that towel,"  After thinking for a moment, the woman drops her towel and stands naked  in front of Bob. After a few seconds, Bob hands her $800 dollars and  leaves.   The woman wraps back up in the towel and goes back upstairs.  When she gets to the bathroom, her husband asks, "Who was that?" "It was  Bob the next door neighbour," she replies.  "Great!" the husband says, "did he say anything about the $800 He owes me?"  Moral of the story: If you share critical information pertaining to credit  and risk with your shareholders in time, you may be in a position to  prevent avoidable exposure.   Corporate Lesson 2   A priest offered a lift to a Nun. She got in and crossed her legs, forcing  her gown to reveal a leg. The priest nearly had an accident.   After controlling the car, he stealthily slid his hand up her leg. The  nunsaid, "Father, remember Psalm 129?"  The priest removed his hand. But, changing gears, he let his hand slide up  her leg again.  The nun once again said, "Father, remember Psalm 129?" The priest  apologized  "Sorry sister but the flesh is weak."  Arriving at the convent, the nun went on her way.  On his arrival at the church, the priest rushed to look up Psalm 129.  It said, "Go forth and seek, further up, you will find glory."  Moral of the story: If you are not well informed in your job, you might  miss  a great opportunity.   Corporate Lesson 3   A sales rep, an administration clerk, and the manager are walking to lunch  when they find an antique oil lamp. They rub it and a Genie comes out.   The Genie says, "I'll give each of you just one wish."  "Me first! Me first!" says the admin. clerk. "I want to be in the Bahamas,  driving a speedboat, without a care in the world." Poof! She's gone.   "Me next! Me next!" says the sales rep. "I want to be in Hawaii, relaxing  on  the beach with my personal masseuse, an endless supply of Pina Coladas and  the love of my life." Poof! He's gone..   "OK, you're up," the Genie says to the manager.  The manager says, "I want those two back in the office after lunch."  Moral of the story: Always let your boss have the first say.   Corporate Lesson 4   A crow was sitting on a tree, doing nothing all day. A rabbit asked him,  "Can I also sit like you and do nothing all day long?"   The crow answered: "Sure, why not." So, the rabbit sat on the ground below  the crow, and rested. A fox jumped on the rabbit and ate it.  Moral of the story: To be sitting and doing nothing, you must be sitting  very high up.   Corporate Lesson 5   A turkey was chatting with a bull. "I would love to be able to get to the  top of that tree," sighed the turkey, but I haven't got the energy."   "Well, why don't you nibble on my droppings?" replied the bull. "They're  packed with nutrients."  The turkey pecked at a lump of dung and found that it gave him enough  strength to reach the lowest branch of the tree. The next day, after eating some more dung, he reached the second branch. Finally after a fourth  night, there he was proudly perched at the top of the tree.   Soon he was spotted by a farmer, who shot the turkey out of the tree.  Moral of the story: Bulls**t might get you to the top, but it won't keep  you there.  

						
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Just had an interesting phone call today. One of my ex manager found my mobile and gave me call. She is asking if I would like to join her company. She is in need of my "talent" =P  She asked me about how I am going with my new job, if I am happy with the position. She wonders if I would be interested in changing again.  What can I say ? She is not a person you can say no to.  She wants me to go for this position   Pros  The company she works for is one of the biggest IT company in Oz.  Big Money   Cons  Contract work I just started a new job  What should I do ? 

						
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Both Sides Now Lyrics by Joni Mitchell      Bows and flows of angel hair and ice cream castles in the air   And feather canyons everywhere, i've looked at cloud that way.   But now they only block the sun, they rain and snow on everyone.   So many things i would have done but clouds got in my way.      I've looked at clouds from both sides now,   From up and down, and still somehow   It's cloud illusions i recall.   I really don't know clouds at all.      Moons and junes and ferris wheels, the dizzy dancing way you feel   As every fairy tale comes real; i've looked at love that way.   But now it's just another show. you leave 'em laughing when you go   And if you care, don't let them know, don't give yourself away.      I've looked at love from both sides now,   From give and take, and still somehow   It's love's illusions i recall.   I really don't know love at all.      Tears and fears and feeling proud to say "i love you" right out loud,   Dreams and schemes and circus crowds, i've looked at life that way.   But now old friends are acting strange, they shake their heads, they say   I've changed.   Something's lost but something's gained in living every day.      I've looked at life from both sides now,   From win and lose, and still somehow   It's life's illusions i recall.   I really don't know life at all.  

						
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Top 5 on what not to do when your wife ask you "Honey when should we have a baby"  1) Don't ignore her and continue watching CSI on TV 2) Don't say  "I don't Know"  3) Don't say  "Maybe Next Year"  4) Don't say  "when we have out own place"  5) Don't say  "Do you really want a baby now??...."    Of course unless you want the silent treatment...go ahead an use those lines.   

						
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink Why should I cry for you  Sometimes I see your face, The stars seem to lose their place Why must I think of you? Why must I? Why should I? Why should I cry for you? Why would you want me to? And what would it mean to say, That, "I loved you in my fashion"?  What would be true? Why should I? Why should I cry for you? 

						
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Damn Bill is an awesome orator!  I guess he has to be, to become a President. Man I wish he was still in office, maybe then we will not be in this kind of mess.  Anyway you got to read  urlLink bill Clinton Speech  at the Democratic Rally in Boston. Adter hearing his speech I am sure everyone would want to vote for John Kerry.  

						
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This is an Awesome movie !! Check it out ...  urlLink This Land   You're a liberal pussie!...You're a right-wing nut job! 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   A boat docked in a tiny Mexican village.  An American tourist complimented the Mexican fisherman on the quality of his fish and asked how long it  took him to catch them.  "Not very long,"  answered the Mexican.  "But then, why didn't you stay out longer and catch more?" asked the American.  The Mexican explained that his small catch was sufficient to meet his needs  and those of his family.  The American asked,"But what do you do with the rest of your time?"  "I sleep late, fish a little, play with my children, and take a siesta with  my wife.  In the evenings, I go into the village to see my friends, have a  few drinks, play the guitar, and sing a few songs...I have a full life."  The American interrupted,"I have an MBA from Harvard and I can help you!  You should start by fishing longer every day.  You can then sell the extra  fish you catch. With the extra revenue, you can buy a bigger boat. With the  extra money the larger boat will bring, you can buy a second one and a third  one and so on until you have an entire fleet of trawlers. Instead of selling  your fish to a middle man, you can negotiate directly with the processing  plants and maybe even open your own plant. You can then leave this little  village and move to Mexico City, Los Angeles, or even New York City!  From there you can direct your huge enterprise."  "How long would that take?" asked the Mexican.  "Twenty, perhaps twenty-five years," replied the American.  "And after that?"  "Afterwards? That's when it gets really interesting," answered the American,laughing.  "When your business gets really big, you can start selling stocks and make millions!"  "Millions? Really? And after that?"  "After that you'll be able to live in a tiny village near the coast,sleep late, play with your grandchildren, catch a few fish, take a siesta,and spend your evenings playing the guitar, singing a few songs drinking with your friends!"  If you are already happy, why change ? 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   New T610 mobile  $0 up-front 24 months contract $38 monthly call Fees   Join Now and you get a free PS2  What do you think ?  Should I get it ?  

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So Mr Cowboy did you ride the horsey?? =)     

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I saw the funniest thing today.  Here I was, in the morning rush to work and we are all waiting to go through the ticket machines on the train station. (I hate the peak hours!! We are packed as sardines in the trains and when we come out, it feels like you are a sheep lining up to be culled). So here we are waiting in line to put out ticket in, so that we can leave this hell hole. As I was moving into position to put in my ticket, I saw this "punk" secondary student abusing the ticket machine next to me.   He was yelling "Take the #### ticket" and kicking the machine...  The funny thing is that everyone could see that the machine is closed and there is a BIG red cross on the machine, right under the ticket slot. So my question is, is he just stubborn or just plain Stupid? 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I have to say that I am happy in the new job. Why ?  No more old company politics New stuff to learn  Brand new computer Admin access to my computer!! And I have just been told that since I miss the last monthly pay, they have prorata the pay and bank in some today!! Which means I have EXTRA money till my next real pay!!  YEAH!!  whay I miss? I miss old friends I miss my old chair...the 1000 dollar chair the company wasted on =P  It is great to be in a new job!! it is just like a holiday =) 

						
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Had some time to kill between projects today and so I did, what I normally do waste my time browsing or googling... One of the weird things I do is search for sites with names of people I know..and of course I entered my ex's names. Could not find my first ex, since her name sounds like months of the year. What was surprising was I found my other ex, who lives in sydney on the net!! She is a member of a club for Malaysian and Singaporean who lives in Sydney. Her name was publicised on one of their online newsletter!!   Damn Google is good! It is funny since, when I first met her, it was in one of those asian in Oz party. Anyway I was reading the newsletter and she is going to be at a Chinese Restaurant in September for a dinner pary of some sort for the club. And for a split second I was thinking of checking it out. I guess I am just curious about how she is going. We didn't really part ways in a good way. (Basically she keeps calling me and I keep ignoring her) Yeah what can I say, I was young then and I was a heartless bastard. In hindsight I know I was a bastard and I should really apologise, but would that benefit her or just me?  She was a really nice person, just way too needy, when we went out. I just could not handle it then. And worst is she reminded me too much of my first ex, so at the time I feared that I was just going out with her because I was still hanged up about the first one.  Crazy times!  In over a quater of a century I've had only kissed 3 girls. And since I am married, I don't think I will kiss any more new girls... so I guess I will always remember all 3 different kiss.  How many have you kissed?  

						
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						       I am think to get this...what do you think ? The Sony Ericsson z6000 flip phone. If I get it, it will be the first flip phone I ever got... I am told flip phone are more fragile but it looks so cool.  Functionality or looks....which is more important??!! 

						
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Life is starting to get into a routine.   Waking a little bit early to take the train to work... ( man I hate the trains!!) have a quick breakfast and then have a quick shower.  Work is good. I have my first project to do. People are friendly and nice. My boss is pretty alright...  Love the desktop... man I wish I can take it home. I am told that I might get a laptop in the near future ... AWESOME!!  Life is different .. but now I am out of the comfort zone....it is going to be an adventure =) 

						
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   For the last 2 days i have been getting delay mail from gmail.  I have a slight delays in sending emails via gmail, 2 to 5 mins delay, but it is taking 22 hours to receive any replies!!  I tried sending emails to my work account via gmail and I receive it with no drama, but when I tried to reply to gmail, I did not get my response until the next day!! 22 hours delay!  I tried various server and I get the same issue. No incoming mail is going into my gmail account.   Is anyone getting the same issue? 

						
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						       Caleb is that you, dress in blue ? 

						
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Don't know if this is Kosher, but I am blogging from my new job. Nope no spyware is logging my sites =P Currently I am just trying to get use to a new environment. This place is smaller than the one I left but the much better desktop! &nbsp; Atleast now I have a p4 2.8 512 Mb Dell computer with a burner!! &nbsp; Atleast now I can actually do my work in peace =) &nbsp; It is strange to be in&nbsp;a new environment after so many years in my old job...  but the people here is nice and some are even friendly... &nbsp; So hopefully all will be well =) &nbsp; &nbsp;  

						
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Ladies and germs, may I present to you the imfamous  urlLink Cowboy Caleb!!          &nbsp;  Is this man Sexy of what!! This pic was on the front cover of the Pedophile 'R Us Magazine =P  

						
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This is the only time when I hate Firdays!!! Cause I got to go back to work on Monday. After 2 weeks of holiday in the sun and watching lots of Anime, I have to go back to work. &nbsp; Of course there is an upside to anything.  &nbsp; 1. I don't have to go back to the hole I have been working for the last 5 years!! 2. I am going to be paid lots more =) 3. New Job, New people ... and hopefully lots EYE candy!! 4. Did I mention I&nbsp;am going to get more money? =) &nbsp; Anyway I have yet to see Spiderman&nbsp;2... which I am not happy about .. hopefully&nbsp;I can convince the "boss" to go this weekend. &nbsp;   

						
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It seems that  urlLink Caleb  has been posting lies about me on his blog!!   I just want to say that I do not look like that picture of the monkey at all!! To disproof him, below is a picture of me, when I was training at home.       And a word of warning to  urlLink Caleb , if he ever tell lies about me.again.. I am going to kick his arse like I kick this white dude.    

						
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   What I hate about blogging from home is that I have to rely on my "super Fast" 56K connection!  Man After years for using a T1 line at work, 56K connection really test your patience. So why am I at home blogging ? Cause I have a week off, before I start my new job. This means the only connection I have is a dodgey NARROWband connection =P   So why don't I have DSL or cable at home... Good questions.  The main reason is really because I am still renting the apartment and I don't want to pay a 100 bucks for line activation and then I have to move it later, which will cost me another 50 bucks or so.   The telco here is a rip-off. In anycase I am hoping that my new job have Broadband and I will get my own place soon so I can get a DSL provision!!   I really miss my broadband speed...... 

						
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   After a week of hiatus, I am back to the real world. The opportunity for the trip came up so quickly that I didn't have time to mention on the blog. So if anyone cared, nothing big happen, I just went on a holiday and forgot to post a vacation notice on the site =P  Anyway I was given a surprise gift by my folks. They needed someone to go to a conference in Queensland for a few days and wondered if I wanted to go. The conference was only for 3 days, in a holiday resort with white sandy beaches and clear blue sky!!  And guess what... I said YES!! And Since I will be flying there for the 3 days conference, I might aswell stay the rest of the week ...right?  So there I was in this awesome resort in QLD, enjoying the sun and to top it off, I DON't have to pay a cent!! Thank you mummy and daddy =)  Man I have to say that my luck is working bloody overtime... New job and a free holiday =)  

						
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This is going to be my last post .....at my old trusty work-station!! Damn it feels great to leave a company after 5 years!!...especially when you have had a couple of beers during lunch =)   

						
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   A father entered his daughter's bedroom and saw a letter on the bed.  With the worst premonition, he read it with trembling hands.   Dear Mum and Dad,   It is with great regret and sorrow that I'm telling you that I've eloped with my new boyfriend. I've found real love and he is so nice.  Especially with all his piercings, scars, tattoos, and his big motorcycle. But it's not only that, I'm pregnant, and Ahmed said that we will be very happy in his trailer in the woods. He wants to have many more children with me and that's one of my dreams.   I've learned that marijuana doesn't hurt anyone and we'll be growing it for us and his friends. They're the one's providing us with all the cocaine and ecstasy we could ever want. In the meantime, we'll pray for science to find the AIDS cure, so Ahmed gets better. He deserves it.   Don't worry about money. Ahmed has arranged for me to be in films that his friends Leroy and Jamal make in their basement. Apparently I can earn £50 a scene. I get a £50 bonus if there are more than three men in the scene, and an extra £100 if they use the horse.   Don't worry Mum. Now I'm 15 years old, I know how to take care of myself. Someday I'll visit you and Dad so that you can meet your grandchildren.   Your loving daughter, Aimee   p.s: Dad, it's not true. I'm watching TV at a neighbour's house. I  Just wanted to show you that there are worse things in life than  ENGLAND GETTING BEATEN ON ***** PENALTIES AGAIN,.   I love you. Aimee 

						
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   My boss, just resigned today ....is this the sign of a ship sinking.... Thank god I have my life boat ...how about you ? 

						
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Like any red-blooded, masculine man, I love PVC weaponry. You should too. If the concept of heading on down to the local Hardware Store and transforming $100 worth of random bits into a killing machine doesn’t appeal to you, you’re a goddamn pansy.   urlLink     Man I am going to make this for my Birthday!!  My very own Flame Thrower!! All Evil-Doers BEWARE!! HAHAHAAHAH  

						
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   You see last night I went back to my folks place to get some nice home cook meal. My grandma cook me some very yummy Prawns sambal, vegies and some mince pork, peas and potatos. Very yummy.   Anyway after the dinner I had some time to kill, so I went to the computer room to surf the net (yeah yeah ... I know, I am a nerd). I log on to blogger and check out the new templates. So here I was thinking, this might be a good time for me to update the site. I have 30 mins, I thought no worries ?  So off I went, switch the template and start editting the page. Adding Halo scan, link, etc... and then I realise that time flew and I had to leave asap, to pick up my wife from her night school. So as a "silly" user, I thought I could just log out without saving and the template would revert back to the original.....  But I WAS WRONG! This afternoon when I log in, the new template was up! My link was gone!! My Comment page was gone!!!  So inbetween writing an urgent report and rebuilding a new computer, I Hax0r the template and entered some essentials back into the site. It is still not complete, but atleast it is presentable.....right?   

						
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     Excerpt from  urlLink News.com.au "AUSTRALIA could be on the brink of a startling underwear revolution, thanks to Gold Coast couple Jan and Chuck Digney ("just your average mum and dad") and their invention: the backless brief."    My Question would be, if it is such a problem why you would bother wearing it? Who wants to have wear a wedgie all day long anyway, and if you ARE wearing it for fashion or to look sexy, don't you want people to know, ie showing your G-String Strap?      

						
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     Can the World be any crazier? The World class loser, William Hung from the American Idol famed, will be featured is his own Hong Kong film co-starring Nancy Sit and Belinda Hamnett.  Don't believe me check it out  urlLink here  The big guy upstairs must be laughing his head off =P   

						
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink Romanian police  is going to ban ladies over 60 years old to sunbathe at beaches topless. The police states that this "ugly show" distracts tourists.  "It is always pleasant to see young women sunbathing topless, provided that the women are attractive. But ironically, mainly elderly ladies sunbathe topless. This looks disgusting", says officer Ionut Polesku patrolling the beach in Constanta.   Cheers to the Romanian Police!! I think, they should also ban:    Policeman who eats too many donuts and carries a beer gut.  Workmen's crack  Big arse ladies who wears spandex for the gym  and Hairy Chest!!        

						
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   If you are a fan of  urlLink Batman - Dead End , then you will interested in new Fan film  urlLink Grayson . This is another Kick Arse Fan Film, which should be in the big screen. I know the special effects and costumes are a little lame, but imagine what the film will look like if WB invest a couple of Million into the production!!  One day the Fan boys will demand the studios to take us seriously and make a movie which do the comic/book character justice.  

						
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink http://www.cameltoe.org/  It is amazing what you can find on the net =)    urlLink Download your latest Trailers Here  Batman Begins looks cool =)    urlLink Wedding Roasting    FOUR members of a family have been arrested and charged with murder for allegedly killing and eating a relative during a wedding reception - and serving his flesh to unwitting party guests, police in the Philippines said today.     

						
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     From  urlLink SMH    " YOUTH radio network Triple J has outraged the families of Australians killed in the September 11 terror attacks by using mocked up images of the World Trade Centre to promote the station.     Why is everyone so sensitive nowadays? It is a freaking joke! Why can't we remember the WTC as it was? They remove it from Spiderman and now they complaint about a Photoshop picture. What is next?  Are they going to remove it from all the other movie which showed WTC in its former glory, like Deep Impact and Armageddon ?  I know 9/11 was a horrible and scary act of terror, but it doesn't mean that we have to forget the beauty of WTC. It was an awesome piece of architect and it should be remembered as such. It feels like if WTC is shown now, it is sacrilege to all the poor souls lost, but I think it is sadder if we forget what WTC really meant, a Kick Arse big Building.   

						
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink IceRocket  is just another "next Google". The upside for this Meta-search engine is that it shows a thumbnail of the each site on your search results. IceRocket also displays the ranking each listing had in each of the search engines used. Other features include a news search, image search.    Anyway it is another source of entertainment for me, when I am procratinating =)   

						
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   "Peace begins with a smile." - Mother Teresa of Calcutta     My wife and I had the most wonderful thought provoking time on the weekend. We Went to a Couples retreat called  urlLink Celebrate Love . It is was advertised by the local parish and my wife suggested that it was a good idea to check it out, so we went.   I must confess that initially I was skeptical of such retreat. Heh I am a guy and like most guys we don't really want to express our inner most feelings, let alone spending the whole weekend expressing our feelings about love and relationship and family. I guess fortunately for me, my wife convinced me that if was a good idea and so we went.   The 2 days went by very quickly, the format of the retreat consist of, 2 couples who are the presenters for the weekend. The couples would present to us various topics on Marriage and relationship, they will share with us about their experience and then each of us will be ask to answer some questions relating to the topic. Once that is done, we (as a couple) are asked to find a quite place away from everyone and discuss the answers we wrote.  We talked about:  Our Family and how they still control our behaviour with each other What faults do we think we have and how do we react to that Sexuality as Husband and Wife Sexuality as define by the Church and Bible and much much more.  Although the topic is very interesting, it is nothing new. It is the fact that we as a couple decided to set aside 2 full days to investigate and help grow our relationship, which was important. Think about it, when was your last time you and your love one went away and just talk about your relationship and how you both think about your relationship. I know we go for holidays and enjoy the occasional small talk, but we would never intentionally sit down and write down out ups and downs and discuss about it. Where we can't hide behind work or TV, we can't hide behind anything, where we have to sit down and really talk.   How many times have we tell ourselves that all the problem we have only happen to us?  Well I don't know about you, but we are not unique! As we listen to the talks and sharing, we realise that we are experiencing the same thing, we are not alone. We realise that if they are standing talking about it, there is hope for us. We are OK.  So next time you want to buy something for your partner, think of this retreat. It will be the greatest gift for you and your partner.   

						
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     LOVING ONE. You need  safety in your relationship. You want to  be sure in his/her arms, knowing that he will protect you and you can be totally devoted to your other. At this point you are very vulnerable. You open yourself and dont even think that he/she could cheat you. You totally trust your partner in every single way. SO if you find out that she/he lied to you or played a game this trust is broken. You may try to forgive your other but this will be very difficult.He/She has to be friendly and trustworthy. PLEASE VOTE, I want to know what you think about my quiz, I worked hard on it. You can always message me or tell me how I can improve that quiz. Ill sure write back.    urlLink   	~THE big LOVE TEST!! What do you need? With PICS! For girls and boys!~     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      

						
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						        Category X - The Changeling     Witty, amusing and a bit weird, you're welcomed into most social groups, even though you don't 'fit in' perfectly .    urlLink   What Type of Social Entity are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						      Hi Viv, it is a bit cold right now, would you like to join me for a nice "hot" shower?    You know youÂre a cute little heartbreaker Foxy You know youÂre a sweet little lovemaker Foxy  I wanna take you home I wonÂt do you no harm, no YouÂve got to be all mine, all mine Ooh, foxy lady     

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     urlLink       This is one of the best "Fan" film I have ever seen! Sadly it is only a "preview" movie, so for now there is no plans to create a full feature. But isn't it ironic that a "Fan" movie is better than most of the "real" movies that the studios produce. Maybe it is time the studios let one of the "Fan boys" create the movie and never ever let out another piece of crap like Batman 3 & 4.  Here is the link for the clip:  urlLink http://www.capedwonder.com/Worlds_finest_Hi.mov   Sandy Collora, you kick arse and I hope one day  urlLink Warner Bros  will let you produce this film for real.      

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I am so glad that it is Friday! in Approximately 8 hours I'll be going home and eat, rest and play!  I won't have to worry about work and I won't have to wake up early the next day. I am going to sleep in.  I am going to convince my "boss" to let me watch my Japanese Anime...(which I am sure I'll fail =P)      

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   "A part of me is excited to begin this brand new life and a part of me is crying for the past I left behind but I embrace the brave new future let all my bridges burn with vacuous eyes we watch life's bridges turn you and I have so much to learn"  

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Just found out that one of our friend just got married! The got married 2 weeks ago, without the parents knowing.. ... why you asked, cause they also annouced that they are going to be parents!!  Surprise Surprise!!  Don't they know that if it is not on, it is not on??!! Comeon people, this is not the 18th century, we have contraceptives!!! Jeez I know everyone experiments and in the heat of the moment you tend to lose your head (literally), but comeon for a minute of pleasure, you are both going to grow up real quick and become parents...    

						
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I got the contract!! Minimum 6 month contract, with a very lucrative pay packet!! I have been advised that I might even get a permanent position once the contract finish.  I finally get paid for my Overtime!! yeah!!  I have never been a contractor, so I am not too sure what the difference is, but if the money is any show of it... then I am happy to do it!!  So now I am waiting for the contract to be drafted and signed =) In the meantime I have to think of a nice was to leave my 2 week old job =P 

						
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Part of me is Excited for the new opportunity  and Part of me is guilty for my current boss, especially when she walked up to me and told me that she was glad that I am here to help her with the work load.   Whereas in the back of my mind I am thinking, not much longer. I feel like telling her that I might soon leave, so you better prepare for the workload again, but of course that would be a way way silly move.  I can't lie and I hate keeping secrets.. 

						
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The meeting went well today. I have to meet with 3 executive, which was quite unnerving. But atleast they were not hard core. I have pretty much been told in the meeting that I have the position, if I want it, but I should get the documentation by the end of the week.  The projects I'll be invloved will be similar to what I had done, but in a much larger scale!!  In my old and current company, our team was less than 5 people, they have over 100, in 3 different states!! Damn the potential is limitless...  The funniest thing about the meeting was that after we completed the meeting, one of the exes asked me, so what are you going to do now? Are you going to "Sneak" back to work now?  I couldn't help but laugh =) 

						
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Hot DANG!! The car looks more like a tank!!  I can't wait to watch the movie!!  It is coming out in 2005.    urlLink http://www.silentcorner.com/video/batman.mov  

						
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   1. "Hello. My name is Inigo Montoya. You killed my father. Prepare to die." --Inigo Montoya (Mandy Patinkin) in "The Princess Bride"  2. "Inconceivable!" "You keep using that word. I do not think it means what you think it means." --Inigo Montoya (Mandy Patinkin) in "The Princess Bride"  3. "Have fun storming the castle." --Miracle Max (Bill Crystal) in "The Princess Bride"  4. "As you wish." --Westley (Cary Elwes) in "The Princess Bride"   For more click on  urlLink Netscape News  

						
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   What is the deal with people with Body Odour??!!  Don't they realise that they smell like soiled gym socks? How hard is it to get to Anti-perspirant or Deodorant and put it on everyday. It is like brushing your teeth or washing your hands after using the toilet. I know it is winter and you think that you don't sweat, but YOU DO!! Especially when you wear a couple of layer of clothings and you have been walking around. YOU will SWEAT!! Comeon just a little bit of common courtesy please. It is not hard. If you want I get your some deodorant, just please use it.   And you know what is worst than standard BO? Standard BO with Smoke and alcohol mixed with it !! Definately a potential chemical weapon!!   So now my question is, how do you tell your work mate that they smell.... 

						
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Meeting with new potential employer on Wednesday. May possibly change job again in a few weeks time. Will decide after the offer is made.  Fingers cross. 

						
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   11.	Show Amidala being artificially inseminated by C3P0.	 10.	Have Greedo's father shoot Han's father.	 9.	Have the Empire invade the planet of Erak on the pretext that they have weapons of mass destruction.	 8.	Anakin shouting at the end, "I'll get you, Obi Wan, if it's the last thing I do!"	 7.	Forgetting the whole plot and killing Anakin and Yoda.	 6.	Tell the actors and actresses that they were over-emoting during the last two movies, and they should act with less excitement.	 5.	End the movie with the Sith holding a large celebratory barbecue in the woods, with fireworks bursting overhead.	 4.	Cast John Stamos and Dave Coulier as Luke and Leia's Uncle Jesse and Uncle Joey	 3.	Have the actors make light sabre and blaster sound effects themselves	 2.	Have the incident that finally pushes Anakin over to the dark side, be the Jedi Council making fun of his new haircut	 1.	Entitle it Revenge of the Sith, and continue to write and direct it on his own.    urlLink Ripped from bbspot.com  

						
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Oh how time has pass, in a few weeks you will turn 80. Wow that is an amazing age! I am so glad that you are still here with us, strong and healthy.  I know I have not been seeing you as much as I have, since I left home and got married, but please know that you are always on my mind.  You have taken care of me from the day I was born. You are my second mum.  You are the one who always took care of me when I was scared. You are the one who always took care of me when I was sick. You are the one who rub Vicks on my chest and back when I have a cold. You are the one who made me ginseng tea when I was studying late You are the one who cook, clean and care for me.  I know I have not always been a good grandson.  Sometimes I ignore you (when you nag me to clean up my room) Sometimes I forget to call you and see how you are.  I know I have no excuse for my laziness, but trying to adjust to a new life as a husband and living away from you is a very hard thing. I miss your delicious cooking, I miss your stories and jokes,  I even miss your nagging.  I know you will never read this (since you can't read English) and I'll be too embarrass to tell you face to face.  But please know you will be always be close to my heart.  You have taken care of me for close to 30 years, and I hope you will let me and my family take care of you for another 30 years.  Love,  Your Grandson.  

						
</post>


</Blog>