<Blog>

<date>20,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      We drove orcs from the great gate and guard room we slew many with arrow.  He slew the great one.  We've taken the twentyfirst hall of North end to dwell in.  Balin has set up his seat in the chamber of Mazarbul.  Balin is now Lord of Moria.    Yesterday being the tenth of november Balin lord of Moria fell in Dimrill Dale.  He went alone to look in mirror mere. an orc shot him from behind a stone.  We slew the orc , but many more came up from east up the Silverode.  We have barred the gates, they can't hold them long.  We cannot get out.  We cannot get out.  They have taken the bridge and the second hall.  Frar and Loin and Nali fell there.  The pool is up to the wall at Westgate.  The watcher in the water took Oin.  We cannot get out.  The end comes, drums, drums in the deep.  They are coming.  I'm just kididng I didn't write that, J.R.R. Tolkein actually wrote it in The fellowship of the Ring.  I just thought it would make a cool blog entry.  Good day to you all. (excitement level obviously down a few points, irritation level up a whole heap however.) 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
         It's monday, Lunes es Monday,  Martes es Teusday, Meircoles Wednessday, Queves thursday, Viernes Friday, Sabado es Saturday, Domingo es Sunday, Lunes Martes Miercoles Queves viernes Sabado Domingo!  Sorry spanish attack.  Today was a rough monday.  It started off with me going in 45 mins early to school, because somehow last night I figured out that my go cart was going over 5000 kmph.  I was thinking the problem wasn't reffering to a bullet go cart, so I needed help.  I found out that I had just made a stupid mistake, and was done in all of 2 mins, and as I walked out guess what pretty much my entire calss needed help too, so I became designated as their personal tutor.  Oh Joy!    I was doing better, unitl after school, when I went in to start editing the tennis movie, It usually takes a long time to do so, so my teacher has gotten in the habbit of jsut locking whoever is working on it into the room, since she trust us.  So about 10 mins after she left, my computer crashed, which is ok, because I can get it back to the place i need it to be, and the program I was in automatically saves.  So I tried to get back in, and the computer started loading, kept loading for about 10 mins, so I started another computer, to start on my other movie project while the original computer loaded,  the second one loaded for about 10 mins, and I got sick of it, so I left my teacher a note saying help, I don't know what to do.      Then I was on my way home.  And I realized that my dad had given me a free carwash this morning, so I turned around and headed back into town to get my car wash, and when I go there there were two cars in front of me, so it took a while to get in, and I finally got up to the deal to punch in my code, and it had alot more buttons than I had anticipated, so I pushed one, and it was obviously not right, so I finally figured out what to do, and I got my number punched in, and I had my windows rolled up an was ready to go.  I was about ot start driving in, and the thing started talking to me.  So I rolled down my window to see what it was telling me, and I negelected to roll it back up befoer I drove in.  I got just drenched.  Not the brightest move on my part.      It was just one of those days were you have to disbelieve survival of the fittest, because if it were true, I'd be long dead.  Alhtough I did come up with a teen page topic, do teens get enough sleep?  Obviously I don't. (excitment level stable)
     
    
</post>

<date>04,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      It is now Saturday.  Yey Saturday!  Last night I went to the football game, and we lost, really quite sad, because we were doing so well.  Oh well, we'll get them next time.  At the game, my friends and I we wondering if we would be allowed to oob, because it's the opposite of boo, so it has to be something positive right?  It didn't really seem to catch on however.  Yesterday my teachers kindly game me lots of homework for the weekend, I was pumped.  I only have about three hours of math, and 2 of chemistry which I totally have time for.  Although I did get to go shopping for a little while yesterday, I went to Target, and I got a new purse, quite exciting, it has venice on it!  I also found sweettarts lip gloss, that was exciting.  I think I may go  make myself some lunch though, I haven't really eaten yet today.  (The excitement level rose 3 points)
     
    
</post>

<date>02,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I just made my first blog today.  It was quite exciting.  My friend told me about blogs, and I thought it sounded kind of neat, so I decided to try it out.  So far, I'd say mine is pretty boring.  Yeah, that's about it for now, I'll update you on the excitment level of my blog sometime soon.  Oh by the way, I get to be Samwise Gamgee for Halloween!  (excitement level rose 2 points)
     
    
</post>

<date>20,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well it's been a long time since I wrote in my blog.  My bad.  Apparently Mahinda has read the same thing at least 6 times out of here, so I thought it was time for an update.  Let's see what has happened.  Well we started the new semester today.  that's always  exciting.  I like my classes.  They're just as good as last semester if not better.  And I don't have a complete stoner math group.  One guy actually knows what he is doing!  It's awesome!   I just got off the phone with one of my camp "friends".  I really need to start being meaner, then these people wouldn't latch on to me.  Every year this happens.  Maybe they have meanness classes at the U of M, they do teach everything else.  Well, I ran out of steam.  That's all for now.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So it's a Monday, Monday's suck big time.  Pretty sure we have four big tests this week.  I'm scared.  But I can handle those. Currently I would like to give a big standing Boo to Paco.  I am incredibly angered with him.  Pretty sure I asked him to prom last week, and he said he would think about it.  That's all well and good, but then today I saw him asking Kristi.  That little poop didn't even have the balls to tell me that he didn't want to go with me before he asked her.  Damn him! So now I'm pretty sure I'm not going to prom this year, and that sucks, because I bought a dress.  Damn him.  And damn prom.  Prom makes me swear.  It wouldn't be so bad, but I have spent a whole lot of time getting this prom ready, because no one else is, and now I don't even get to enjoy it.   Although Mahinda said I could reserve a seat for Grand March, and take pictures.  Still Boo all of Prom. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Happy Monday to you all.  today went really really fast.  I can't believe I'm already home.  I got to see the episode of HOSD where they interviewed Abner's girlfriend.  It was great.  She looked pretty nervous though, and a little confused.  I also worked on editing our next episode, and we're doing a segment on how everyone complains about our episodes, but they never have any suggestions for us.  I would have to say Lola is a very talented actress, she plays a very good valley girl.  Props to you Lola.  Well I'm off, I have Envirothon.  We're preparing our skit.  It's going to be good.  *And Scene!*
     
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Prom is over, and it was so much fun.  I don't think I've had that much fun at a dance since probably 7th grade.  Maybe even never.  Paco was awesome, he talked to me, and danced with me, and didn't even complain about the millions of pcitures he had to take.  I was proud.  I felt bad for Agammemnon though, his date ditched him at the after party, and she wouldn't dance with him much at the dance.  The best part was when Aden showed up for pictures only wearing his shoes, pants and shirt.  He couldn't figure out the rest of his tux.  It was so cute, so Paco had to help dress him.  Although Wonder Woman was telling me this morning how her date kept breaking a button on his tux, and sewed it himself.  It didnt' go as well as they had hoped.  Her date also ate some of the crystal ice that decorated the tables.  Pretty sure that that is not edible.  Although he has eaten an entire pizza box before.  Good fiber.  But I'm off to work on my monton de tareja.  
     
    
</post>

<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Waiting, Waiting, in my really comfortable prom dress.  I hate waiting.  Paco is due in 4 mins.  I got ready two hours early, so I worked on my math, I got half of it done too.  My Math teacher is a slave driver, and kindly gave us a huge assignment when he knows it's prom weekend.  I can't believe he expects it to get done.  What a loon.  I want them to play Rent music at Prom.  But I know it will be rap and country.  boo that. Oh well, not much I can do about it.    *Sits bored in prom dress*
     
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      One week later.... Today is prom.  AAh run for the hills. I'm done with all my decorating and prom committee responsiblilities.  Wonder Woman is going to do my hair in about an hour.  Then I have to do my makeup which may take up to five minutes today!  Then I grab my chemistry an head to Grand March.  I'm going to recite the elements and their atomic numbers as I walk down the stage.  Then I'm writing my english paper during the banquet, and my student council paper during the dance, and then I'll start getting my social presentation ready during the after party.  But I'm off.  *Dissapears in a whirlwind of flowers, hair spray, film, and shredded mylar.*
     
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        So today Lola, Wren and I went to Great Spoons to check out the Thrift Stores.  It went pretty well. I found a cool little boys Gator BasketBall shirt, with a number, and name on the back and everything.  Lola found one too, so we're going to wear them to the after prom party.  Exciting stuff!  Wren even made me a duct tape coin purse on the way home, because I don't have a wallet, and am using a plastic bag.  She's too cute.  We got some good interviews, and we got Wren trying on a wedding dress with Dorthy esque ruby slippers.  It was awesome.   I also watched Requiem for a Dream tonight.  I'm officially never taking drugs.  (Since we all know I was going to before I saw it.)  But oh man,  that's a really depressing movie.  It scared the poo out of me.  I can't decide if I'd remcommend it or not.  Definitly not if you're faint of heart, but it was really well done.   
     
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'd like to give a big congratulations to Uma for winning State Speech two years in a row!  Way to go!
     
    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        It's just another frenzied friday.  I wish it were summer, cause I won't be here.  It's just another frenzied friday.  Or was that Manic Monday? Oh well too late now.  With assignments due, and Yearbook deadlines fast approaching I hardly saw today go by. I had a quick recap figuring out what homework I needed to bring home though.  It didn't fit in my back pack.  I love it when I have that much homework.  Score all weekend to research and solve, and figure.  I love these kind of weekends.  Oh wait my sacrcasm switched on again, I really need to get that fixed.     In other news I went to the soft ball game, and had fun playing with my telephoto.  I hope I got some good ones of Lola and Xola.  They also so celebrated their first season victory.  Go softball! Lola, Wren and I are going over to Great Spoons tomorrow to film a segment on thrifting for HOSD (our school news program).  It should be fun, and hopefully informative.  See you all later. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello my faithful blog viewer, I am living life on the edge tonight, I lit a candle and left it unattended.  *Sees a vision of house burning down.*  In other news, I have little to no time to finish by books for both English, and Social.  Score, reading for days straight!  Today in Spanish Aden confirmed for me that my english book is incredibly boring, and he read the ineresting part.  Go great American literature?  My book on Marylin Monroe is much more intersting, but it is much longer.  Sigh.       I was actually semi-productive tonight, and I'm scared.  I finished my math, spanish, and found a part of a movie I need for my presentation.  Now all I have left is Chemistry, finish my books, and one more movie.        Oh the frustration, the two people I need to talk to aren't on, but I don't need to talk to them so desperately that I should call them.  What I really should do is get off here, and do some more productive things. So I'll write later. Oh shoot my candle!
     
    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well hello to both of my blog viewers.  How's the weather?  Most likely a bit chilly, but it's warming up.  Speeking of chilly, i went to Lola's softball game today, and it was cooold!  I'm still not quite warmed up.   But I decided that I don't really feel like writing because I have lots to do tonight, but I'll update tomorrow.  audios, y arivederci. 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just read my last post, and I sounded kind of depressed.  I'm feeling better today though, last night Wonder Woman and I watched Notting Hill, and who wouldn't be in a good mood after that?  That's such a good movie, I love British humor.  Oopsy daisy!     It was so  cute I got to church today, and the Easter bunny had visited the Tech room.  There were york pepermint patties all over.  It's been so long since the easter bunny visited it was awesome.  The service struggled though.  I think it was two years ago that we decided that since we get so many people coming on Easter that never come other wise, we should minister to them, and do sort of a seeker service on Easter.  But this year we did traditional hymns, and we didn't even have any power point.  And of course we said the Lords prayer and the apostles creed without putting them on the screen.  I have no problem with saying them, it's just that the new people aren't going to feel very welcomed when they don't know the words, and have to fake it.     We did that at our really contemporary service (designed specifically for people who are maybe not quite christian yet) too.  We had two baptisms, but we said the apostels creed during them, and we didn't put it on the screen, so even the family who was up for the baptism didn't know the words.  It was aweful.  We definitly need to work on that hospitality thing.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Today has not been a good day.  Last night I had a dream, that I went to the National Honors Society induction ceremony, and I sat in my seat, while everyone else was called up to be inducted, and they never called me up.  Obviously I have esp, because after I woke up this morning, my mom told me that I didn't make it.  I probably would have, except I have no musical talent whatsoever, and so I missed out on half of the points alloted to the people who are musically talented.  The get an entire point for each ensemble thing they do, and I go three points for everything I'm in.  Unfair? I think so.     I'm just so sick of being seen as untalented in this stupid town.  The only things that matter in their eyes are music and sports.  Sighting my lack of talent in either area, I'm painfully average.   I really need to get out of this town, it's not good for me.  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        So, I have noticed that I like to start my blog with so.  Hmm I think I tend to start my sentences with so alot too, you should try it sometime, it's much fun.  Today Mahinda taught me how to make my blog actually fun to look at, with links and pictures and such, so it may get a big exciting for a while, since I don't know precisely what I'm doing.  We already put a quite large pciture in, and it looked rather silly, so we made it into a link instead.  Yey for technology.     As far as prom goes, I think Paco and I are pretty much ready, wich is amazing considering neither of us knew if we were going last week.  All we have left is to decide on pictures.  Two weeks to spare!  He even signed us both up without me even saying anything, I was very impressed.     Today was way fun, Mahinda, Wonder Woman, and I went out into my woods, and found some really neat stuff to takes pictures of.  Mahinda got to use her new camera, and Wonder Woman finshed her film from Hawaii.  I think it would be really fun to be a photographer, but I want to have a nice house, and a little family, you know, the American dream.  To live like that you would probably have to be near as good as Ansle Adams though, and I'm not.  So I was planning on becoming some sort of doctor, because science really interests me too.  But I can up with a new plan.  I'm going to marry the maker of Apple computers, and then I can photograph stuff all I want, my children will be geniouses, and I get all the free software I want.  How awesome would that be?  Pretty awesome I think.   I was also inducted into the Mermaids club today, I watched the movie, and it was so cute.  I ran out of stuff to say however, and it's getting about time for bed.  So ttfn.  I'll see you on the flip side.  (I just now understood the origins of that saying.)
     
    
</post>

<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        So it's now approximately one week later, and Everything but pictures and a garter are in place for prom (as far as I know).  I went to Great Spoons today and bought the rest of my prom jewelry.  I'm going for simple, and cheap this year.  Next year I will be going for cheap.  I found a really BIG ring.  It's awesome, so I definitly don't need a bracelet.     I also bought a villa in tuscany this week.  it's really pretty. And it has a gigantic garden, witha wall!! Abner said he's moving in with me, if he can bring Xiang, and Lila and Mahinda claimed rooms too.  It's exciting.  The boat leaves tomorrow.  See you all there. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Update on the prom situation.  Paco didn't realize he was being incredbily stupid, because he'sa boy, and now he feels really bad, and so two days ago he asked me to go to prom with him, and I am.  Time for rapid prom preperation.  About three weeks to get everything done.  
     
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Dudes!  You gotta check out the party at Manda's house.  Just kidding, it's over now.  With a whoping total of three guests we decided the fate of the "mystery couple" from the graduating class.  We decided it was going to be Giles and *sex voice* Ashely.  We also watched the senior video, although we skipped "The Dream Season."  Sadly enough.  It was a good time though, and we did get rid of some more reception food.  Strange I seemed to get enough of football during football season.  Oh wait let's bring it back one more time.  Oh Oh and once again.  And for old time's sake, one more time.  Sorry, I'm just so sick of football.     Today I went ot Great Spoons, a picked out alot of stuff to bring to the Ukraine, and found some clothes for when I'm job shadowing my aunt, and I'm feeling a little better about the trip, now that I'm that much closer to being ready.  But I'm still rather nervous.  I don't speak the language, because they speak Russian, now if it was Spanish I could communicate a little bit, at least enought to survive, but Russian, I'm screwed.  And right now I have a social life, and friends, and I like it alot.  I want to leave next september, when almost all my friends leave, that would be ideal.  Next september, I will have a whopping total of 3 friends.  And they're busy people, and I'll hardly see them.  Although if I can make the cut for Drama which is probably not very realistic, I'll spend alot more time with them in the spring.  But I want t spend time with my friends now.  But I know it will be a good experience, and I really do want to go to Europe, and I really should get out of this stupid town, aside from yearbook camp this summer, maybe.  And I do want to go, I'm just torn.    I am now debating whether I really want to be in tennis next year.  I mean I hate tennis, and I hate doing Geff's poop work.  (pardon my french) But I like being on the team with Leila, but then I suck, and Leila is good, and I won't ever see her next year.  I didn't even get to sit by her at Paradiso teusday this year.  I sat at the freshman table.  And I hate tennis, and I hated last year, but I want to be in the pepfest, and I know I'll be so jealous whenever anything tennis related is happening, even though if I was going I'd give anything to stay.  So how conflicted am I?  Very very very conlficted, so I'm not going to think about it right now, because I have to go in for yearbook tomorrow, and I need to get to bed.  Sorry this was a rant entry.  I hate when I complain like that.  
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I think after today I'm done with all the graduation receptions I have to go to.  I do have one going away "reception" for one of the foreign exchange students on Teusday, but other than that I think I'm done.  What a relief, and now I know how to do it for next year.  I wonder if I'll have as many next year.  Sadly probably not, even though I will be a senior.  Lol, how ironic.  Oh well, they don't like me, and I don't like them.  It all works out.     Tomorrow I have to go to Great Spoons, and find dressy clothes for my trip to Pittsburg.  I am job shadowing my aunt, and I have to be dressy while I'm at her office.  that's 10 days, and I certainly don't have 10 days worth of dressy clothes.  I have maybe 4.  So Wonder Woman helped me put some stuff together tonight.  So far we have 6 outfits, but that's four short.  Hopefully my mom is understanding with her checkbooks tomorrow, or I'm going to struggle.     Tomorrow should be a good day though, I don't have to go in to yearbook since it's a holiday, so I have time to go to GS, and then relax later.  That's all for now.     I'm sorry this post is written so poorly, but I'm really spacy today.  I too two really hard naps.  It was tough to wake up.   
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        And altogether now, collective sigh *Whoosh*.  And the depression sets in.  I got through the bulk of my receptions today.  Wonder Woman had hers, so we can live in the house once again.  Lola also had hers, and Uma, and Lana.  Sad times at Ridegmont high.  Oh wait, that's not my school, oh the delirium.  "What does that mean?"  And that is a quote from a graduating senior on a word during Giles' speech.  Quite amusing.  So I was the designated photographer at graduation, and I failed miserably, I loaded the camera wrong on my second role of film, so I missed alot of pictures of the ceremony, and we had to re-do many afterwards.  But it all worked out eventually.     I just got back from Lana's house, we met the EGSers (East Great Spoons people)there, and played mafia, and I never (with fingers, not alcoholic beverages).  I had names down by the end of the night, but sadly I still refer to them by their character names from my first and only EGS play.    I'm really going to miss all my seniors when they leave.  They are so much more fun than juniors (except for a select few, and you know who you are.)    I really need to get to bed though, because it's about 2 am, and I need to work at church tomorrow.  So have a wonder full whatever you are doing.  This is Amanda of I Dream of Genie signing off.  *boing*
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Wonder Woman and I are currently preparing puppy chow for her reception on sat.  I was singing Rent to her, and she burst out laughing.  Apparently normally when I sing I'm only like a step to a half step off but this time I was a whole staricase off.  But really, it's like laughing and throwing things at the stupid kid.  It's not funny, It's not fair.  How can I atone?  Are you okay? (sorry Rent tangent).  Oh and I finished my Hawaii movie today, and I got Abner's LOTR spoof on tape, so all I have left school wise is the Yearbook, but they always work into the summer, so it's not surprising.   I would like to give a big thanks to Mahinda for helping me to resurect my links, and chatter box.  We are enterally grateful.  And as far as I know my quiz is now functional.     I have decided that it's time to bring back the 50's era high pony tail.  It's similar to sparkly things in that it makes me very happy.   Much like sparkly things.  Which as you already know are the key to happiness.  Next year for prom (if I go) I want to go with a 50's inspired dress.  Ivory satin with a greenstripe acrossed my ribs.  I'm so excited.  Even if I don't go to prom I still want to make it a wear it everyday.  With my high ponytail, and little ivory heels.   And of course sparkly jewelry.   Well I lost my train of thought.  I'll reboard when I find my ticket.  Until later. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I am currently eating some Berry Burst Cheerios, they are good I might add, and I have  had a realization.  I can't eat with certain spoons.  I dug through the silverware for almost a minute trying to find a spoon i could eat cereal will.  I found that to be really wierd.  Although not quite as wierd as having an unexplainable twitch.  Right Mahinda? You know, I don't think it's totally unreasonable to say that you can't go to school because it makes you twitch.  I would use that excuse if I was you next year hun.     I also just realized, even though my quiz is working, my links are not, because I don't know how to do them, so you'll all have ot hold in the anticipation until tomorrow.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        As you may see, I picked a new template today.  But I don't really understand how to update the sidebar, so I'm sorry to my chatterbox visitors, but Mahinda is going to help me fix it tomorrow so never fear.  On a good note I had my last day of Spanish EVER today!! *Hallelujah Hallelujah.  Heavenly light streams down*  And my quiz is now functional, but most every one has taken it already so what can you do.  But I have finals to prepare for.  Have a wonderful evening. 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        So my post from yesterday is currently missing.  intriguing.  Well have no fear, you didn't miss much.  I just rabbled on and on and on and on.  I also informed people that I created a quiz, and there is a link to it under my links if you feel so compelled to take it, be my guest.     In extemely happy news.  I got a B on my last Chemistry test.  *and the peasants rejoice*  I think I did alright on my Chemistry final day 1 of 3 as well.  It was all stuff I remembered how to do.  Joyous.  Mahinda came over tonight, and we "studied" for day 2 of 3 of the chemistry final.  It went well she was here for approximatley 4 hours and we studied for about 20 mins.  We also narrowed Mahinda's hair style choices down to three, and viewed Lola's lastest videographic masterpiece.  It's very very very very very good.     Well since my last post is MIA I should probably update you on the results of this weekends poker tournament.  I took 3rd (out of 5) but I ended up only loosing one dollar. Not to bad I don't think.  Agemmemnon practially played the beginning for me.  But I needed the help.     We had our first student council meeting today, and I'm worried for next year, because I've signed myself up for alot of stuff.  Which wasn't in my plans, and I also signed myself up for alot of classes, hard classes.  bad plan Manda.  But it's too late to change now.     I was also published in the Great Spoons Periodical.  I did a student profile on Giles, and it was actually published!  The only thing I technically wrote for it were the interview questions, and the title.  Hooray for getting to keep my title.  And thanks to Giles for providing me with the interest factor my other stories were lacking.   That's all for now.  By the way, if you haven't tried Diet Coke with Lime yet, you should be throw in jail and never released.  It's rocks.  Have a wonderful [insert time of day here].
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Well it's another day of reception preparation.  And my family is being so kind.  my mom told me that if my room isn't clean by tomorrow I'm not allowed to go to any receptions.  So I feel like hitting her.  And you know it's not like I have finals I should study for next week, or other homework, or my own life.  For the next two weeks the world revolves around Wonder Woman.  And she's being a little whiny brat lately.  We went to Great Spoons yesterday, and we were supposed to return some napkins my mom didn't want at target, and get some digital pictures ordered.  Well Wonder Woman didn't feel like doing it, and so I have to do that today in my two hours I have to get a bajillion things done.  Then she asks me to pick up a guest book for her too.  I figured since I was doing so much for her, it wouldn't be unreasonable to ask her to get me some gas right?  (she doesn't even have to pay for it, my parents pay for it ) Apparently I was wrong, she's too self ritous to do something for the lowley stressed out juniors of the house.  Then she tells me how I wouldn't be so stressed out if I didn't talk to my friends on MSN all the time, and it's somewhat true, but you know they're al moving away in about three months, so I think I have the right to talk to them now.  And for the past month probably while I've been on MSN I've been working on essays and other homework as well.  You'd think she would understand, seeing as the same thing happened to her last year.  Apparently empathy has no longer term memory.  Well I'm off to get gas.  wish me luck.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        This is probably a record, three posts in one day.  Well technically it's now tomorrow, but I'm going to count it as yesterday to set the record.  It's currently pretty late, but I can't go to bed for about another hour.  I'm being an ebay shark, and I love it.  I got sharked out of my first Erik Satie cd, and it's not happening again.  There are only so many to be had you know?  I'm also bidding on Broadway playbills which excites me.  So far I'm winning with $3.  But there's two days left on that one.     I'm currently cleaning for Wonder Woman's graduation reception.  And someone (who shall remain nameless) dumped her shoe basket on my bed, so I could sort them and the bed is currently covered in leaves and dirt etc.  Seeing as it's too late to vaccumm it looks like a night on the couch for Manda.  Oh well, you really can't overcome your own stupidity sometimes.  Common sense along with spelling is hard for some people.     Tomorrow Abner has his reception, and I'm excited for the present I got for him.  I can't reveal what it is yet, but tomorrow post reception I will.  I wish I could be there when he opens it though.  Oh well, can't win them all.  Sadly Abner's girlfriend couldn't make it up for the reception.  Poor guy.  That also frightens me for after the reception, I was invited to learn to play poker with "the boys", and I am afraid they're going to take all my money.  (Abner's girlfriend was thinking about coming to that too.) Which they probably will.  We're each only contributing $5 but that's alot of money if you think about it.  That's two rolls of film, two white chocolate mochas, a cheap shirt, thrift store shoes.  So many things.  Wish me luck, and pray for my financial situation.  I really don't like to gamble, so I don't know if I'm going to have fun.  I'll let you know though.   This sunday is the last day of Sunday School.  Leila and I are going over to Great Spoons tomorrow to get little presents for the kids, and about a bazillion other things I need to do within two hours time.  I know they were difficult at times, but  I'm sad to see my little 3 yr olds go.  They're incredibly adorable.  I signed Leila and I up for 3rd graders next year.  I should really let her know that.  We have stuff planned already.  I'm really excited.  But it's going to be very different from this year. I'm looking foreward to it though, I love teaching kids.     And on a completely different subject, Wonder Woman and I took a trip over to Great Spoons today, and we went to the college there, and found a cool fountain in the park that I definitly want a senior picture by.  I'm excited for my senior pictures now.  I'm going to go to the place that Giles' parents run, and they have a tuscany scene set up in their basement, so I'm going to tuscany, and I'm going to take a picture with my books and Wonder Woman's glasses, and I'm going to take one with me taking a picture with my camera, and one stupid formal picutre for my mom.  Boo formal pictures.  I think I want to wear my Rent t-shirt in my books picutre.  Wow, that was a good tangent.  So anyway we went over looking for a guest book for Wonder Woman's reception, and we met Lola and Mahinda at the Urb, and had an awesome photo shoot outside afterwards.  It was so much fun.  I want to do it again.  Then on the way home, Wonder Woman and I sang duets from Rent, and even acted them out once we got home.  It was a good day.  A sad, but good day.  I am writing Abner's graduation card right now, and I think it may be a bit sappy, and I feel bad.  But I am a little emotional right now, which is strange for someone who has been dubbed cold and souless, and given rocklike attributes.  I hope he doens't mind.   Well I am rambling now, and I need to keep sharking.  Good night/morning/afternoon/eveing to you all.  Keep you children out of the water.  bum bum, bum bum, bumbumbumbumbumbumbumbumbum, BUM BUM!  Cue the red food coloring!
     
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Twenty minutes later, I'm back.  Still in Newsbroadcasting, and one of the long lost juniors has returned.  there's the bell.  And off to Social.  Joy!
     
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello Everyone.  So I'm sitting here in my news broadcasting class, and since the seniors are gone, and the juniors don't come, it's just Mrs. K and I.  Right now I am capturing some footage I took of the tunderstorm on wednesday I want to say.  I think I'm going to take it and combine it with some music and make myself cd.  I have one Evanescence song with a thunderstorm on it, and I absolutely love it.     So i went into the commons today to see if Lola had left anything for me in the office.  I was assigned the task of handing out a few undelivered graduation announcements, and I was giong to make a copy of her self in technicolor tape.  But all the seniors were sitting in the commons waiting to get on the buses to go to oak lake for their senior skip day.  I went and talked to Lola, and it was very sad.  If I had a soul I would have cried.  I decided that I hate graduations.  It was kinda of exciting last year, but I now know how Wonder Woman felt lasr year when all her friends graduated.  But enough for now, I'm going to work on my personal video.  On the bright side I get to use final cut pro for another year.  Weee.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Hello my faithful blog viewers.  How was your day?  Mine was pretty good.  I got to sleep in *baloons and confetti fly*  ow, my eye.  Then I worked on my english paper, yuck, but it really needs to be done.  And my pastor called to let me know that I am speaking tomorrow about my trip to the Ukriane, to ask for donations.  Which is pretty cool, but I hate speaking in public.  I also went with Wonder Woman to Great Spoons to shop for jewlery.  Now just so you all know, never specifically go shopping for jewelry.  It's a bad idea.  I found two pairs of chandeliers earings and a  braclet to match each.  I love them but I really shouldn't buy so much jewelry.  I did however find a shirt to wear to Wonder Woman's graduation, and to her reception, and tomorrow!  New clothes are fun.  Tomorrow I am also taking Wonder Woman's sunday school class, because it's bacheloriat (pretty sure that is spelled wrong, but I'm too lazy to look it up) sunday, and she has to be at a breakfast for the seniors during sunday school.   Her class is notorious for their "energy".  I am going to attempt to read them a story, and offer gummy bears as a reward if they can answer questions afterwards. We'll see how it goes.  I really should be getting to bed though.  I have to look presentable tomorrow.  Happy May to you all.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I have returned from the Great Spoons outing.  It was an experience.  I'd never been on a boys night out before, and I have some to the conclusion that boys are wierd.  We left right after school for the 8:15 movie.  Don't ask, I didn't get it either.  We then went to the mall, and looked around for less than an hour, and promptly headed to the Mexican Restaurant.  It was spicy, and people were smoking.  Bleck.  But don't tell  Abner, he's already threatened to break up with his girlfriend (jokingly of course) because she said that it was over rated.  I was impressed with how much those boys can eat.  They each spent $5-10 on food and they ate it all.  I spend a total of $1.23 and was fine.  Agamemnon told us a really  funny story about one of the people he works with who is apparently not the brightest fellow.  They told him that there were no left-handed straws left, and he needed to go put some more out.  They told him to look right next to the right handed coffee cups, and he should be able to fisn them.  So he goes back, and looks for about 10 mins, and returns to report that he couldn't find them.  Acting frusterated, they tell him that it's really not that  hard, they're right next to the right-handed coffee cups, he can't miss them.  Then they go so far as to tell him that if he can't find them, he's moping when they close.  With a downcast face he heads back, and searches for another few minutes.  He returns once again, to tell that he still couldn't find them.  So they send him back to someone else to ask where they might be.  He informs this poor guy that they are in the sky hook.  (there is no sky hook)  So he's wandering around looking for the non-existent sky hook, and the left-handed straws.  They did let him konw eventually that there were no left handed straws.   After this we went to the park which was rather fun, and then we arrived at the movie 45 mins early, to get good seats apparently.  So since we were sitting there for so long, the movie theater people came in, and one of them told us that his friend Andrea was going to come in, and that we should make fun of her.  So as she walks in, Agamemnon yells, Hey Andrea.  And she looks at him, and looks again, and then goes "Oh, Hi!"  and continues to her seat.  Her theater friend approved.  I would be wiling to bet she tried to figure out who he was for a long time.     Sadly I missed Giles' reception tonight.  I really wish I could have gone.  Wonder Woman got to go, and she got to be an ion.  I mean I've been an electron, but never an ion.  It sounded like a lot of fun.  So I'm sorry Giles, and I'm even more sorry about the not I wrote and had Wonder Woman put in your card.  I suck at writing stuff like that.  But that one was praticullarily bad.    I realy should get some sleep tonight though, so it's off to bed for me.  Goodnight stars, good night sheep, goodnight chair, goodnight moon.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Another day, another dollar.  Oh that's right, I always work for free.  I forgot.  So it was another day of panic editing HSOD today, and as always we got it done.  It struggles, there is not obvious order to follow, but it's done nonetheless.     So I was "watching" the Two Towers (with the cast commentary, which is quite funny) through a tower of graduation decorations, I began to realize that this is the last spring Wonder Woman and I will be here for, and after this summer we're really not going to see each other much.  It makes me sad.  But then I am going out to visit her in California next spring, when all the music students go on a trip to Florida.     I shoudl really be going though, I have a chemistry test tomorrow, and no idea what I'm doing.  Have a wonderful evening
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I appologize for the anger in my last post, but this one might not be terribly "love and peace" either.  So last night we had an awesome thunderstorm.  It rocked my socks.  I was sitting at my window, watching the lightening, which by the way I took pictures of, which I hope turn out.  As I was watching the lightning I see part of our tree, that broke during a previous storm, come tumbling off.  Right on to my car!  I watched it and thought, "well that's not cool."  so this morning we assesed the damage, and I have three dents, a broken back window wiper, and a hole in my bumper.  But it could have been worse, Wonder Woman already scratched the front left side, with a trailer, so we're just going to get it all fixed at once.  And the best part is they're doing it while I'm gone this summer, so I don't have to be carless.      In other news HOSD has to be on tape tomorrow, and you know what?  We were still taping today.  Aaah!  I was at school until almost 5 editing today, and I have a feeling I may be tomorrow too.  The blood drive was today as well.  I, being a youth, was not able to donate, but I have a feeling even if I was old enough, my iron would have been too low to donate anyway.  Judging by my complexion though, you'd never know it.  *wink wink*  Paco, Mahinda, and Agemmemnon, all donated.  I was jealous.     So on friday, I'm going with Abner, Paco, and Agememnon to Great Spoons to see Troy, and we're going to their favorite mexican restaurant, and I'm scared, because I don't go well with spicy food.  Especialling since I've had indigestion for like a month porbably due to stress, because it started about when my hair started falling out.  Going off on a tangent, I read and article on MSN a few days ago, that said extended periods of high stress can take 10-15 years off of your life.  I found that quite frightening.  Back to the topic at hand, Wonder Woman said she went to the Mexican restaurant and ordered a quesadilla with just cheese, and they put so much chili powder on it she couldn't eat it.  Oh well, I'll get by.  But i'm heading away.  Probably not to bed.  Have a wonderful evening.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Damn School!! Damn it all to the fiery chasm form whence it came!!  I have too much crap to do and no time to do it.  So why am I writing this instead of working on my homework you might ask?  Well I'll tell you.  I've become quite a fan of procrastinating.  I hate school the stupid "nerd banquet" as Lola so appropriatly put it took four hours out of my night.  And for what? For me to go up on stage for three seconds and have the announcer say Amanda participates in crap, now get off the stage!  I'm sorry, I really shouldn't be communicating with people right now.  I'm going to stop writing and try again when I can be less of a cry baby.  oh that's right I can't cry.  How about just a baby.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        So I made a sad discovery today.  I tried to see my villa in Tuscany, and the links don't work.  I was saddened.  Then I came on to write this, and blogger has made major changes.  I was really confused at first.  I think I have a handle on it for now.  Today was so fun, in Sunday School we took the kids out and we blew bubbles.  A little messy with three year olds, but that's what paper towels are for right?  I also got to take a summer nap.  That's where you sleep with the windows open, and it had just rained, and smelled soooo good. So I started my paper on my book for college in the high school for english, and it's already about six hundred words long, and I have discussed three of the ten things I was planning on discussing.  I hope Mr. B. doesn't have a limit for these papers.  It's too bad I can't make conversation like I can write essays.  I'm awesome at ackward silences.  But what can you do?   so for HSOD we are doing a salute to seniors episode, and I was looking through tapes of old tv shows last night, it was fun, I was looking through the Winne-The-Pooh for old comercials, and I found episodes of Alf, and I have come to the conclusion that I was the only child in this county who watched Cheers and Mash on a regular basis, but wasn't allowed to watch The Little Mermaid.  I also found a kindergarten program of the seniors it's so funny.  I remember singing the did you feed my cow? song, and at the end the cow dies and gets eaten by buzzards.  And to show you what a warped child I was that was one of my favorite songs to sing in msuic class.     Tomorrow is our last day of titration.  *tear*  We're hoping for a sucessful titration from Mahinda.  She's been a bit titrationally challeneged as of late.  But it's rather comical to me. She's some what frusterated.     I had best be going though.  I have to finish my Espanol and practice my social report.  Mine is on Marilyn Monroe, the sex goddess of the 1950's, and so much more.  I'm getting nervous though, my class showed their consideration during Leila's presentation.  Wish me luck.  
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        So today went by really quickly.  I'm pretty sure I was in a daze all day.  I hardly remember anything between lunch and when I took my nap.  I wonder if my body didn't just go into an automatic sleep mode after being awake for too long.  I do however remember counting how many times Abner changed positions, and dropped his pencil during Spanish class.  The final count was changing positions 35, and dropping pencil 15.  He is a hyperactive child.  I almost feel like I was drugged this afternoon.  It took Wonder Woman about 20 mins to wake me up to go to Great Spoons.  We had a good time.  I got new shoes!  They're so pretty. They're black and strappy and sparkly, and little bit expensive, but they're comfortable, and will last a long time.  Abner and Paco actually called me to go to Great Spoons tonight too, but I was already gone.  I was really surprised that they called though.  Next weekend I'm going with them to the opening of Troy though, so that should be interesting.  But how can a movie that has both Orlando Bloom and Brad Pitt in it be bad?   So on the way home tonight I was thinking, and next year is really going to suck.  Wonder Woman, Lola, Abner,Uma, and alot of other school time friends are going to be gone.  It's going to be a really hard year too.  I'm taking first semester: English, Social, Advanced Bio, Pre-calc, Web Page, possibly Discrete and Finite if I can do it as an independent study class, and Journalism.  Second semester I'm taking all but discrete and Web Page, those will change to science seminar, and a technology aid, or technology independent study, whatever they want to call it.  I'm going to be very stressed next year.  I'll have even less hair.  score!     In other news the results of the student council elections were in today, I was beaten by my one competitior.  I can't understand.  both of my friends said they voted for me.  I obviously didn't do much to appease the masses.  Oh well they'll be fine without my leader ship.  I'm a born follower.     I think today was a be mean to people I like day.  In english this morning one who will remain nameless was reading the article Lola and I had published in the great Spoons paper which was against tanning.  He is an avid tanner, and he was making fun of us when I was right there in the class.  I'm not deaf, and it's not like he was discrete about it either.  Then in social another one who shall remain nameless counted the um's in Leila's presentation about the Beatles.  I wanted to hit him, it's hard enough to give a presentation without someone pointing out what you did wrong after you were done, to the whole class.  Kids these days have no respect.  But I'm exhausted.  I'm heading to bed.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Mondays suck.  But it's almost over.  I felt really awful, because yesterday I was helping Aden and Abner with their videos for Spanish, and Aden's went well to start with, and then Abner came out, and found my house on the second try, after returning to retrive his map.  And his was going well, until the tape ended, and the battery died twice.  Well the problem solver that I am, I'm thinking.  No problem, we'll just tape before Aden's video, and it'll be no problem.  Bad idea.  I taped over and small scene of his, although he still got his video in on time.  Abner however had more difficulties, and in the process of transfering his, the machine ate the tape, and it was unusable.   So he had to reshoot his whole movie today, and he was editing it, as I left school.  Poor guy.  it's rough.  Mrs. Evil Spanish Lady better not dock him points, but she would be in character if she did.   In other news, I found a Marilyn Monroe time line, which makes my social presetation preparation much easier. So much for today.  Back to my homework.   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's Saturday, and it's also Mahinda's Birthday!  Happy Birthday!  I went to Great Spoons with her today, and found some good clothes for summer, and my trip to the Ukraine this summer.  I'm excited.  I'm not really in a writing mood though.  I'm crazy tired.  I need to work on my homework.  Check you later.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Another difference between Europe and the US.  In Europe they actually give you portions that are the size for a normal human being. You can physically finish something you order in a restaurant.  You can even order more than one course.  It's so strange.  For example.  We went to a McDonalds in Budapest.  My aunt and I both got a McFlurry, and they were quite a bit smaller than they are in the US.  They probaby had one cup of ice cream, and candy.  And that's reasonabe.  Whereas in the US, you get probably 2 cups or more.  Last night we went to a place called Brewsters for desert.  It's alot like the Pittsburgh equivalent of a Dairy Queen.  I got what was called a blast(blizzard).  I got the smallest size you could, and got probably three cups worth of ice cream and candy.  I couldn't believe it.  I could hardly finish it, by putting half in the freezer and eating it tonight as well.  It's crazy.  I now understand why American has the weight problem it does.  And I'm out.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have to say, I am rather jealous of your poker night last night.  I really wanted to go.  And I didn't have the bright idea to call Abner's house after I talked to Lola on her cell phone, until this morning.  So...I missed it.  We're having one when i get back.  I've missed far to many.  I think I'm starting to get a bit homesick.  I miss all you guys.  The feeling is not completely mutual though.  I talked to my brother on the phone yesterday, and I asked him if he realized he hadn't talked to me in close to a month.  He went Whoa, when did you leave?  Glad at least my family loves me.  But he is only 13.  I suppose he can be excused. So wild day in the medical world today.  We saw patients all morning, and I got the stack of charts I've been sorting since I got here done today.  Woohoo!  Then we went in at about 3pm for the emergency surgery, and they weren't ready, so we didn't get sarted until almost 3:45.  I was about to sit down to observe, when my aunt says, "Patty (her nurse practitioner) why don't you take Amanda, and show her how to scrub up."  Pretty sure my mouth dropped open.  So I went out, and I was really confused for a while, because I don't quite understand all the sterility rules.  So two gowns, and a pair of too small gloves later, I was scrubbed in.  At first I was just observing, and I could actualy get close enough to see things.  Then the ovarian cyst we were trying to remove exploded all over.  This poor lady had a cyst the size of a grape fruit in her stomache. She thought she had been gaining weight, but it was all fluid.  I ended up having to hold retractors, and clamps, and even helped to close the patient.  Not many other high school students will do this.  I'm still in awe that she let me help.  If I was her, I wouldn't have let me help. But that is my story of the day, I'm going to go have my supper, and then see if I can't actually talk to someone tonight.  See you all in 3 days.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Woah, I skipped a day blogging, without realizing it, and while internet access was avaiable.  Wierd.  This is a new experience for me.     Today was a busy, but productive day.  Yesterday I watched one surgery, and then did office work the rest of the day.  Today I observed seeing patients for half the day, and did office work for the other half, with the occasional urine analysis thrown in.  I think lab technician could be a cool job.  I did always like labs in Cheistry.  And I thing the urine analysis thing is pretty darn cool.  And it would also give me more time with my prospective family.   Today one of my aunts patients was admitted to the hospital with abdominal pain, and it turns out she has a mass in her abdomen about the size of an orange.  So tomorrow they scheduled an emergency surgery, that one I think I'll observe.  It could be quite interesting.     So get this, I've sarted diagnosing people with what I think they're sick with.  How wierd am I.  I diagnosed a guy at the airport with Parkinsens(I dont know how to spell it.) and one of the drug reps with an eating disorer. (you could see her muscle fibres through her skin.  It was sick.)     But I have to get going, we're going on an evening outing, to get our drycleaning, ice cream, and to drop one of Dan's friends at home. Talk to you all later.   Sorry I missed the "scholarship pageant" meeting last night.  Oh wait I have no talent!  Never mind.  Love/Miss you all.  See you in four days. 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alright, I should really be napping, but I can't sleep since I'm cafinated.  So I'm going to finish the telling of my Ukrainian adventure.    On our last day of mission work, we had a picnic for lunch with the Pastors from both Methodist churches, and their families.  It was really nice, and we had really good food.  We got salad, vegetables, some kind of ethnic food, I don't remember the name, but they were seasoned rice rolled in cabbage leaves, and cooked in something.  They were really good.  And to finish, they made traditional Ukrainian barbeque.  It was all really good.  And we had a beautiful spot, right next to the river (well it was a stream).  At this spot, we were less than a mile from the Slovakian border, so I could have visited another country, except for the armed gaurds.  During the picnic I taught Ira how to use my camera, and she had alot of fun with it.  I got my pictures back today, and she did a really good job.  I think she could have potential as a photographer.     So one thing in the Ukraine that really bothered me was that I was dehydrated the whole time I was there.  You can't drink the tap water, because it has bacteria in it that Ukrainians are immune to, but we feble Americans get very sick from.  To solve this dilema you buy bottled water right?  The only problem with this is that a lot of bottled water in Europe is carbonated, and alot like seltzer.  So in otherwords, undrinkable.  It's so disgusting.  No matter how hard you try, since you can't read the bottles, you inevitably pick one out that has been carbonated.   On the flip side, their chocolate is amazing. We learned that when they are shipping the cocoa beans from South America, they send the highest quality ones to Europe, and send the next best to America.  And you really don't realize how good thier chocolate is until you have ours again.  I ate a kit kat bar on the plane on the way home and I couldn't belive how bad our chocolate is.     And for my last story from the Ukraine.  On the way to Budapest our van driver Ivan decided to take us to a winery for lunch.  I was a little wary of the idea, seeing as I'm not of age to drink, and I don't like wine.  But I thought it would be fun to see nonetheless.  So we get there, and the outside looks quiant enough.  It's a little cottage, we walk in, and they hand us each a glass, and then take us down into the wine cellars.  I don't know what wineries are like in the US, but this one was way cool.  If you've ever read the story A Cask of Amontillado by E.A.Poe you will kind of understand how the cellars looked.  If you haven't they we remeniscent of a medival dungeon.  Way cool. The walls were covered in about 2 inches of mold, which was a little frightening with my mold allergy, but I did take my zyrtec that morning, so I didn't come out too badly.  While we were there, they brought us tons of different kinds of wines to try.  Overall I think I have less than half a glass.  I couldn't drink it.  I really don't like wine.  It think my aunt had about four glasses, and Christine had possibly seven.  Those two were pretty darn funny as we were leaving.  My aunt was having trouble walking straight, and as she was having a conversation with Ivan her hand gestures were pretty wild.  Christine on the other hand was pretty far gone, and she was walking funny, speaking really slowly (FYI when speech slows, volume increases), and developed a definite slur.  She was explaining Mormanism to me in the car and I had such a hard time not laughing at her as she slurred the explanation.  Well this is really long.  so I'm out for now.  I'll talk more later.  Miss you all.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So back to the European escapade.  The next morning I had nothing to do, so one of our translators Ira (pronouced eara) took me shopping.  It went pretty well.  I found a few souveniers.  The thing I was the most impressed with, was their jewelry.  In thier version of a department store, they had a stand with tons of sparkly jewelry.  It was so pretty, and almost everything was under $10.  I didn't buy much the first day, but I wish I had, because I never got back.  That night, we headed over to the same methodist church, and my aunt taught the second half of the Esther bible study.  That night I watched the pastors two children, and one of the children from Comanitza(another methodist church is here, we visited it later.)  They were adorable.  Little Abigail was not quite 1, Martin was about 3, and Rubin was maybe 5-6.  They played really well together, and really liked the toys I brought.  (Martin loves hotwheels cars.  He called them Malenchy Machencas which is spelled all wrong but means small car in Russian)  When we were going home that night, we saw a motorcycle accident, and it was obviously recent, because there was a guy laying dead on the road, they hadn't even covered him yet.  It was pretty disturbing.     In Ukraine the roads are aweful.  The government doesn't have the money to fix them, so they don't.  The cars are bad too, because no-one can afford nice ones, so they all have that horrible old car gas fume, and none of them have seat belts.  To top it all off, Ukrainians are crazy drivers.  Their highways are two lane, and they will pass cars even where there are cars coming the other way.  It's pretty scary.  I was very glad to get back to the US where I had my seatbelt.     Most of our days went like this, one day we visited Gypsy villages all day.  The first one was crazy.  As soon as we got there, we attracted a following, and my aunt gave me her camera to take some picutres while we were there.  So I started doing that.  Now in gypsy villages everyone is very poor, and none of them can afford cameras, so they ask anyone with a camera to take their picture.  So after the adults went into their church, (which had a dirt floor, and a set on roof) I was mobbed by the younger people, and took more pictures than you would believe.  Then we tried to get the children to play with us, and Christine was upset because at the beginning some of the toys dissapeared, which was to be expected, because in thier culture stealing is ok as long as you don't get caught.  We had plannd for this, and only brought some of the toys we had to this village so we would have more for the next one.  After our attempts at games failed they began pulling the grapes off of trees and throwing them at each other. We finally (with big help from Ira) got them to sit down, and sing.  They really enjoyed this.  I was surprised.  It was really nice.      The second village was much more calm, it was a more suburban village, and we didn't have any children to take care of.     Another day we visited The boys and girls orphanages.  These aren't technically orphanages, they are for children who were in orphanages, and were too old to stay, but not ready to be on thier own.  So they set up these sort of transition homes, so that they don't end up begging, or in prostitution.  The boys home as a little bit overwhelming.  There were probably amlmost ten boys, and they were wild.  But apparently they had settled down quite a bit from before.  The girls house was really nice.  They had a  big house for them to live in, and then a gigantic yard, with farm animals, fileds, huge gardens, and a bunch or cherry trees, with some realy good cherries on them.  We were there when they were ripe.  Those were some of the best cherries I've ever had.   One of the girls at the girls house befriended me, and before we left she gave me her teddy bear.  I couldn't belive it.  That was probably one of the only things she had, and she gave it to me.  I had a really hard time accepting it, but she would have been really insulted if I hadn't.     This is getting really long, and I'm tired of typing, so I'm going to wrap it up for now.  I'll wirte more later.  Miss you all.    
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        And I'm back.  It's currently very late, or very early.  However you want to look at it.  I had an aweful dream, and now I can't fall back asleep.  So I thought I would confide in my blog and see if that calms me down.     We begin, it was the last day of school (11th grade again).  But it was more like a last day of school in grade school, because we were all there, and we were all cleaning out our lockers. As I was cleaning out my locker, Leila came up, and we started talking.  I'm not quite sure what all was said, but then I suddenly realized where the conversation was heading, and asked her, Did you move to Bismarck?  She had.  I couldn't believe it.  I was super mad at her parents, and just didn't know what to do with myself.  I mean it was bad enough that all the seniors were leaving at the end of the summer, but now she was gone already.  So that put me down to a minute amount of friends for my senior year.     Then Leila had to leave to go somewhere else, before she headed back to Bismarck, and Mahinda (who was also in the conversation by the way) and I started to head to the parking lot to go home.  As we were leaving we passed by Mrs. Soliegaard, and she asked us what was wrong, but neither of us answered, and we just kept walking in a daze.     Then I was suddenly home, and I was talking to Wonder Woman, I told her that Leila moved, and then I started bawling. And I cried for a long time.  Then I woke up.    So first I have a query, if I can bawl in my dreams because of something that should make me bawl, does that remove some of the cold and soulless tendancies, or is it void because it was a dream?    Now a theory.  I think this dream is because most of my friends are leaving end of the summer, and I'm really afraid the other ones will leave me too, and then I'll have no friends again.  Because that has happened before.  In grade school I had two years, where I had about 13 friends move.  It was aweful.   I had dreams like this when Marika moved as well.  A few nights before she left, I dreamed that Leila was moving as well.  Here ends the musing of Amanda.  tune in next time for, why do the lids on pringles can pop up in the mountains? (this is especially for Mr. Chemistry man)   Ok, This is really long, and I'm running out of typing steam, so I'm going to try to go back to bed.  So goodnight to all, and none of you are allowed to leave, unless you have completed your senior year of high school.  Night Night. 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Heelllloooo My friendly blog mates.  I have returned from the great beyond, also known as the Ukraine.  It's currently 8pm, I had 13 hours of sleep last night, woke up at 1pm this afternoon, and I'm exhausted.  Time travel does a number on you.  Although coming this way is much easier than going the other way.  At least when you get here it's night time, and they don't expect you to start another day after 24 hours of traveling.     So when we first arrived, we actually flew into Budapest which is the only town I can spell that we visited.  We had our van driver Ivan (when pronounced it ryhmes with Lavonne) pick us up, and he took us on the 6-9 hr drive to Mykatchevo(pretty sure that's spelled wrong, but this is the town we stayed in).  On the way he took us out to supper, and ordered for us because we don't speak Hungarian, and couldn't read the menu.  Ivan only spoke a little english, so we learned a little about the country, and the landscape looked just like home.  Flat with alot of vegetation.  So for supper we had what they called Ham, and then they told us it was from a cow.  We're like okay whatever, we're just hungry, so they brought us out beef.  We arrived in Mykatchevo at about midnight, and it was two days after had left I think.  I still haven't figured out the time change thing.  I never knew what day it was.  Our hotel was awesome, we had three rooms in our room.  We had a bedroom, with two beds, and a couch, then a bathroom, and a hallway, with a big closet.  The only bad things was that in Ukraine, the sewer system is so poor that if you flush your toilet paper it would get really messed up, so you have to throw it in a garbage can, which is rather gross.  And probably unsanitary.    The next day we woke up, and headed over to Dale and Janis's apartment for breakfast.  We met everyone, and after breakfast we headed over to the Children's hospital for a meeting, because my church sent a donation.  When we got there, they were very appreciative, and are using it towards their physical therapy room, which consits of a broken swimming pool, with dirt and rocks in it.  And then they gave Christine who we traveled with (she was pretty much nuts) a really neat book about the hospital, in Russian of course.  Then htey talked about different needs of the hospital etc. for probal 20-40 mins, and then the head man in the meeting asked me if I was American, and i responded yes, and he goes OH!, I'm sorry, I thought you were Ukrainian and gives me a book and his card and everything, which really didn't help me, because I can't read either of them lol.  They then offered to fidn me a nice Ukrainian husband if I would like.  That night we went to a Methodist church in Ooshgarad (don't know how to spell that one either but's that's how we're going to spell is from now on, it's phonetic) That night, my aunt taught a bible study about the book of Esther.  It think that's all I'm going to write for tonight, but I have two more lay low days to fill you in.  And one of the days my aunt said she might take me to the Museum.  How cool is that!  And I have to say I've really enjoyed having comments and the chatter box while I"ve been gone.  Keep it coming.  Love you all.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello my friends, how are you all today?  I'm alirght.  I'm still here in the Ukraine, we have three days left.  I'm getting United States sick.  I miss being able to communicate with people, other than thank you, yes, and hand gestures.  It is nice over here though, and I know I'm not going to want to go home when it comes time, because I've made good friends in the week I've been here.     What has been happening in our little hometown? Same as always? Not too much?  I should really get going, we have to leave for Ooshgarad(I haven't learned how to spell in Ukrainian yet either, they have a different alphabet than us.)  We're going for church, and my aunt is teaching.  Love and miss you all.  Talk to you soon. ~Amanda
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Amanda here, coming to you live from the Ukraine.  I'm just writing a quick post to say I got here safe, and we're having alot of fun.  I can't talk long, because other people need the computer.  I love oyu all, and I'll talk to you all later. Mwah!
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      And the last post before I leave for the Ukraine.  It appears everyone is leaving for somewhere tomorrow.  Mahinda, and Aden head of to Boys/Girls state, we're off to the Ukraine, my grandma and aunt from ND are heading home.  Crazyness.  And Mahinda I feel your pain about the duffle bag, I'm leaving a bunch of my stuff here, because people over there really only have three pairs of clothes, so you won't fit in well if you wear too many clothes.  But all the supplies we have to bring over there.  Wow!  We have four big suitcase full, and then there's some stuff in my suitcase with my clothes, because I had extra room, and stuff we really can't afford to loose is going in carry on bags. Tonight we had a really fancy dinner with my aunts ex-husband, his parents, and his sister's family, for Lenni's graduation.  I got to wear my homecoming dress again, and that was exciting, because I love that drss.  And I got to wear my new pair of "expensive" shoes.  Holy cow was that a pricy reastaurant.  My meal was $30 with out a tip.  My aunt and her ex-husband split it, but I feel really bad, and I really want to pay them back for it, because both my aunt and my grandma have been buying me alot of stuff while I've been here, and I have money specifically for these things, but they won't let me use it.  The dinner was nice though, and wasn't as tense as I thought it would be.  Everyone was civil at least.  It looked like it was really hard on my aunt though.  We got in the car afterwards, and she started crying.  I still don't quite understand why.   Oh man, it's getting late, and I need to get some sleep.  If I can't blog again until I get back, I'll be keeping a journal, and I'll have a gigantic post then.  I'll miss you all.  I love you.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello Everyone (to borrow a line from Mahinda). Yesterday was anoher eventful day in the humid ciy of Pittsburgh.  It was my cousins graduation.  We went to the ceremony, but they hold their's in an autitorium, and it can't hold all the people for the ceremony, so each child gets four tickets for people to invite in the audiorium, and the rest of the people sit in the cafeteria, where they wire in audio, and video for us.  My aunt from ND, my grandma and I sat out there.  That as one of the longest graduations ever, it lasted 2 1/2 hours.  The diploma presentation took 1hr and 15mins alone.  I liked it though.  I realy wish I went to their school.  People are allowed to go beyond what the entire rest of the class wants to do. (which in our case is absolutely nothing, well except drugs and each other.) Last night I had this crazy dream.  I drempt that my cousin Xenith was taking me to my dad's seed plant, and for some reason he knew the way better than me.  As we were entering the forest we had to go through, he changed into some sort of mouse (of rat size) and ran off into the forest.  The kanagaroo I was riding couldn't keep up, and had a lot of trouble with the steep hills, so we lost him, and he ran off into a nearby field.  When I looked to the side I had arrived at my dad's seed plant.  Now if I couldn't figure out what the dream meant that I had two days ago. There is no possible way I'm going to figure this one out.     Today is the final of packing for the Ukraine, we leave tomorrow morning after church.  I'm really looking foreward to it too.  It takes 24 straight hours of traveling to get to the town we're staying in.  After all the flights we had a 6 hour van ride from Budapest, and when crossing the border into Ukraine it's possible they'll try to take our stuff from us.  They didn't get anything taken last time, but sometimes the guards have to be bribed to let us through with all our stuff.  It's a little diferent than inter United States travel.  I had best get going, we still have a lot of packing to do, but I will talk more later.  I'm pretty sure at least.  I don't know if I'll be able to blog over there, we'll see.  Miss and Love you all. 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today, I got back some pictures with the worst developing I've ever seen.  I'm exteremely underimpressed.  Granted they were developd at Walmart's one hour photo, but still even they should be able to do better than this.  It looked like they printed them off, and the printer was running out of ink.  The color saturation was nowhere near what it should have been.  They all have these lines running through them, and there is one line on each picture that is the saturation it should have been.  So from now on, Walmart will take no part in developing my pictures.  I got back some of the ones from when the EGS'ers were at Laura's house.  I had two of those that looked decent.  One of Uma, and one of Giles.  But the rest are crap.  My aunt from ND was trying to tell me that the focus was off, but it wasn't, you just couldn't see anthing because of the lack of color.  I seem to be really upset about this.  You wouldn't think it should matter so much.  It's strange. Well anyway.  I met the other lady that is going with my aunt and I to the Ukraine.  She's seems a little scatter brained.  Although she did manage to find us almost 20 bibles in Ukrainian.  We're going to be giving those to some of the orphans. Right now I'm reading Main Street, and I'm so frightened by it.  One of the farmers even has the same last name as one of my dad's emloyee's does.  I really wish I had my own copy so I could hilight the parts that sound like home.  Oh, i wish I had a hilighter too.  This entry really isn't going anywhere, so I think I will.  I'll talk to you all later.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Aloha all.  Another eventful day in the life of a Pittsburgher.  They should make that at a Fast food resaurant.  Aden, Abner, and Paco one of you bring that up to your boss.  But I better not see a sign reading... "Introcuing, The New Pittsburger" until I get my royalty money.   Today was a busy day at the ofice, we had even less patients than yesterday, but they all had many things wrong, either physicaly, or emotionally.  One little old lady came in today, and she has a bit of dimensia.  The staff had been encouraging her for years to get a mammogram, and she never would.  So today they found a lump in her breast, and they tried to get an appointment set up with the oncology doctors, she looked so scared. I felt awful for her.  That will be one of the hardest parts of being a doctor.  I think I'm realy going to have trouble not telling people about my cases too.  I find this stuff really interesting, so I'm going to have to marry some one with a strong stomache.  We also discovered a drug addiction in one of the post op patients.  She was trying to get herself more pain pills than she should have had, and so the pharmacy did a background check on her, and it turns out she's had enough pain pills in the past few months to sedate a horse.  Frightening isn't it?  But on the brighter side of things, I learned how to do a urine test today.  So I can help out with those in the Ukraine if needed.  That's good. I had the craziest dream last night.  I drempt that Leila had become really good friends with one of the horniest guys at our highschool.  If you knew me in Junior high, it's my seventh grade crush. And I was pretty uneasy about that, but I was like whatever, as long as nothing bad happens.  But then they started tormenting me, and I ended up leaving them, and I found Wonder Woman and some of her friends and my ninth grade crush, hung out with them for a while, until they began to shun me as well.  Then I headed into the gym, and  found Mahinda, Abner, Aden, and Paco.  They didn't shun me.  And I really don't know what this dream means, because Leila and Wonder Woman wouldn't do that, unless they had some sort of conspiracy to gain my trust.  They're probably just trying to get close enough to find out the secrects of the Universe!  Well, here's their warning.  I'l never tell!   So going to the office is done for this week.  Now begins the manic packing so we're not staying up until 5 am Saturday, and skipping church to pack.  Tomorrow we had a 6 am prayer meeting to get prayed over before we leave, and then we're sleeping and packing.  Lenni's graduation is tomorrow as well.  We're alo going out to dinner on Saturday to celebrate.  And more good news, Xander got his drivers liscense today.  He passed his test.  So your's truly doesn't have to do any drving in the frightening city.  Joy! Oh man, this is getting long.  Sorry about that.  Talk to you all later.  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello Everyone.  It's now storming here! Rejioce!  Today was an easier day of work, there were less paients, and we had to leave early anyway to pick up my aunt, from ND, from the airport.  My grandma came in for lunch today, and stayed the afternoon repacking sample pills to take to the Ukraine.  It's so awesome, we bring diffle bags of pills, an medical supplies over.  We also got a bunch of donations in the mail today.  It's shaping up, no all we need to do is pack.  It's really too bad that the girl my age can't go though.  I'm rather sad. Big news today, Wed. is the day all the sales reps come into my aunts office, and today they brought pens!  I have two new ortho-trycyclene pens!  And then they had this bucket full of old pens, and I got to take as many as I wanted of those too.  I love the medical pens  they're so mch fun.  I'll have to show them to you when I get back.  I love them.  That was definitly the highlight of my day.   After the airport we went for a walk again.  My aunt is trying to get us in shape for the Ukraine, because the cars are so bad over there, everone walks if the destination is within a few miles.  So I need to bring comfy shoes.  But walking is better on your feet than just standing there in my opinion, so I don't think it should be a problem.   I think my grandma is getting somewhat senile.  She's really confused a lot.  She's getting lost in my aunts house, and we have to watch her to make sure she comes back from the bathroom when we eat out.  It's really sad.  She can't move around very well either, she has to take a cane everywhere she goes now.  And she looked exhausted as we left the airport, and I bet she didn't even walk a block while we were in there.  So I decided I could definitly never go into geriatrics.  It would make me so sad.   Well that's all for now.  Oooh that was a good thunder!  It's bedtime for this girl. Miss and Love you all.  Mwah
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Good Evening.  How are you all?  I'm mucho tired.  I did a full day of surgery today with my aunt.  I saw three historectomies, and one D&C which I didn't completely understand what is was either, and i figure you gusy don't want me to recount in detail.  We had to get up early today, the first surgery started at 7:30 this morning.  So we had to leave the house by 6:45.  Craziness.   After supper we decided to go to the mall for some last mintue shopping, and I found a cute yellow skirt.  I like it.  But it was really hard to shop with my grandma and Aunt who shop in the old ladies section.  They pick out the big flower prints with matching pants and shirt, and it hurt even me.  Man, if Wonder Woman had been there, her head probably would have exploded.  I've never seen so many fashion violations.  Sadly being as we were in a nice department store, Macy's style I found a ton of cute things, all out of my price range.  Oh well, you can't win them all.   Leila, I don't know if you read this, but I started Main Street today, so far they are still in the cities so it doesn't remind me of our hometown yet, but I'm only in chapter two.   I need you guys to pray for our trip, my aunt's Nurse practitioner was sick today, and if she's sick tomorrow we won't be able to get everyone done very quickly, and the girl my age going has a knee injury and is on crutches right now, but we have alot of stuff we need.  We jus need our health more, I'm not feeling to hot tonight either, granted I'm exahusted, but I think I have hives, either that or lots of bug bites.  But hives are very possible, seeing as I forgot to take my Zyrtec this morning.   Otherwise things are going well.  We leave Sunday,  I'm getting really excited.  But i have to get to bed.  Love you all.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Hello my blog viewers.  How is everything at home?  everythig is pretty good here.  I actually had a really good conversation with my Aunt today on the way to check on some of her patients about having medical anointing.  (That's where when you pray for people you can actually feel the hol spirit going into that patient.)  She's had this laot apparently, it's pretty cool.  She also told me some interesting stories about my mom.  There's alot of stuff she never told us.      The house has settled down now.  Htis moning we went to my Aunt's church, which was really fun, it reminded me alot of  Willow Creek, and it cracked me up, because they were projecting their powerpoint sutff on trampolines.  It was neat.  hen we came home and took a nap after I followed her on rounds.  Naps rock.  Then we took her dogs for a walk on a trail she has three houses down from her. That is the prettiest trail I have ever seen.  I'm definitly getting ym camera down there asap.     I should get going though, we have to be at the ofice ealy tomorrow as my aunt's first surgery is at 7:30.  I'll talk to you all later.  Mwah!
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just kidding Mahinda, the chatterbox and everything else came back.  My Bad.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Ahhh! What's happened to my chatter box and quote of the day?!   I can't find them.  Mahinda, help me!  Sorry, I just had to have a minor freak out.  I'm done now.     So Right now, I'm at my cousin, Lenni's, graduation reception.  It's not exactly my kind of party.  It's either all people over 40, or boys my age, who only know how communicte in video game language.  I sat for a while watching them play thier X-box games, and I was thinking that had I put some bars around them, and gotten some peanuts, I could as well have been at the zoo.  They even have thier own system of communication like animals.  Oh well, I got my fair share of friends time before I left.  I don't think I've ever been as social as I was at the end of June.  I don't think I have much else to say.  I think I might go read my book.  Living the wild life now!  Miss/Love you all.  Talk more later. 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        What a busy day.  I went to a nursing home consult, which as really sad.  Ruled out Geriatrics.  Then we figured out how to use a new machine in my aunt's office, and I followed the physician's assistant around for two patients after that, and learned more things about the female anatomy than I thought possible in two hours.  I even got to use a microscope.  Cool huh?  Then we went to surgery, and I had to wear the whole sexy surgery ensemble with the hair cover and even shoe covers.  Surgery actually went well,I couldn't see all that much, because I wasn't fully scrubed up, and couldn't touch anything that had been sterilized. But my aunt said I did really well, I didn't get dizzy or faint.  Apparently I'm the first girl she's brought in that didn't get sick.  So that just enforces the cold and soulless theory.  Too bad.  Well, we have to run to the grocery store to pick up supplies for my cousins graduation reception.  Miss you all.  talk later.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I have arrived.  I don't believe my aunt has messenger though,so I am confined to blogging for a month.  I wonder if I'll go through withdrawl?  That could be interesting.  So the flights over were pretty boring, no good turbulance even.  Oh well, myrandma and I arrived safe and sounds here in Pittsurg.  We got to see the Heinz fatory were al teh ketchup is made.  Pretty col huh?  Ad I saw mre sky scarapers today than i have seen in years.  I saw them flying into Minneapolis, and we drove through downtown Pittsburg.  eciting stuff.  I was thinking on teh way over how wierd of a feeling it is to see the stuff come up and get closer and closer to you.  They all look like toys until you touch down. Its pretty cool.     Mahinda I decided you would make a realy fun flight attendant.  Now I'm not saying that's what you should go into or anything,I would just like to be on your flight.  I can jsut see you starting off with "Well helo everyone.  Welcome to flight [insert numer here] with non-stop serice to [insert city here]." and she would continue, and this sounded better in my head. but I still think you would be a good flight attendant.  But I have to be getting to bed.  I have to get up early tomorrow, I get to observe ovarian surgery.  Exciting and frightening at the same time.  Pry for me, and wish me luck. Mwah.  Goodnight.  Oh and ps. Mainda I finished Go ask Alice today.  good book. Ill bring it back wel, in a month.   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Ok I'm back again.  I'd like to say Manda you're not a horrilbe person for missing stuff, you're just a busy person.  and That's totally excusable.  I wanted to say on behalf of my blog that it's feeling the lack of commments.  Let's remedy that shall we?  *phsycicly seeks non-commentors, and extract mace*  jk.     So nervous/stressed symptoms in full swing?  sure thing.  can't sleep, got a tummy ache, and commence biting thumbs.  (My nails dissapeared around finals time)  T-H-U-M-B spells relief.  but I really do have to get to bed now, I have to leave the house by 10 tomorrow.  Have a Merry and a Braaaaaaaaa. Sorry Rent again.  I really am going to be the wierd kid.  Oh well, I"m used to it.  Have a wonderful day.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Oh boy, frenzied packing ahoy.  I am almost packed.  But it's really nerve wracking.  I'm so scared I'm going to forget something.  And then people have entrusted me with well over $1000 for the orphanages and childrens hospital, and I so very frightnened that I will be lose it.  And I'm gettgin nervous, because my stuff is already over the weight limit, and I'm not even done packing.  I still have some shower stuff to pack.  Augh!  I even have to use hal of one of my grandma's suitacases, because the stuff for the Ukrainian people fills more than a suitcase.  And it's heavy.  Sorry I'm stressing all over my blog.  *pets blog* That's not what blogs are for.     So Wonder Woman and I decided that I'm going to be the wierd girl in Pittsburg, because I'm going to sporatically burst into Rent songs.  I really hope the girl my age who's going to the Ukraine has seen Rent.  but that's unlikely.     So I was walking out of my last day of yearbook today, and I found a note on my car.  It was very cute.  Thank's Uma, from Wonder Woman as well.     So Wonder Woman and I were discussing today, as I was picking pictures out of my photo album to take with me, that I have a strange mental depletion.  (I couldn't think of a better word than depletion) I have this problem that after a few weeks I can't recal faces of people. even people I know realy well.  So that's why I bring pictures with me places.  She just couldn't believe that.  But that's how I am. But not to worry, i made sure I have pictures of all my blog readers, I'll never forget you.  Lol I have to keep reminding myself that I'm only leaving for a month.  Oh I'm getting emotional (well as emotional as a cold a soulless person can).  Oh I'm done.  and look at me babble.    Well I'm going to get going.  Wish me luck with the packing dilemas.  Mmmmwah!  A big kiss to all my readers.  Love you all.  Have a wonderufl June even though I'll probably post again soon.  Apparently I'll be in Pittsburg for 10 days befoer we leave, we leave for the Ukraine on the 13.  Good thing some one told me.  See you.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Another day another hemmorage.  At least it's Mr. F's nad not mine.  We have to have the yearbook done by tomorrow.  Unlikely.  I'm so glad I'm leaving, and don't have to deal with the completion.  Yey!  Next year however I will.     So 20 hours and counting until I leave for a month.  Augh! there's so much to do, and so little time.  And one more time. Augh!  okay, I feel better. Oh wait, I"m still on the computer and haven't accomplished anything.     I have so much to do though, I'll try to write later, but I have to go to a reception now for a friend who's going back to Germany ( she was an exchange student) see you all later.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Hello everyone, I have just returned (well about an hour ago) from a church service and Nerraw, with Abner and Mahinda.  I liked it, although the speakers really didn't have that much effect on me, because they talked about their drug addictions and drinking problems, and gang problems.  But they did pray for my trip to the Ukraine, and Abner found out I was going to the Ukraine.  I'm starting to get more nervous, I leave tomorrow, well since it's very early wed morning right now.  But I leave for a month tomorrow!  Frightening!  I don't feel like I'm ready, I'm definitly going to need you guys to pray for me, pray that I don't forget anyhting.  And that the flights go well, and that we stay safe.  You guys rock.     Besides my freaking out, Abner succumbed to the world of blogging, and started his own.  It is proudly displayed in my links.  (we've trapped another one.  only a few more and we will begin to dominate the world.)  I would like to inform my readers that I think instead of e-mailing everyone while I'm gone, I'll just update my blog, because that is a heck of a lot easier than sending an e-mail to tons of people.  And in conclusion, I have noticed a strange urge of mine lately, when I go to write if,  I end up typing iff.  Unless I think about it.  As in shorthand notation for if an only if.  There, I had to suppress it twice.  I don't know if that goes along with the lack of spelling, or if (there it is again) I am just wierd.  For the time being I would say the latter.  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Well hello my blog viewers.  Today was a landmark yearbook day.  I spent 3 and 1/2 hours in yearbook today.  I finished my pages for the most part, and parts of other peoples pages as well.  I got a Rent quote in the yearbook!  hooray!  And I found out that I'm an editor next year, and my co-editor is Valencia.  Which is who I was hoping for.  A good day definitly.  Oh, and I found the best picture of Mahinda for the Knowledge Bowl page.  You'll all just have to wait to get your yearbooks to see what it is though.  (hidden selling technique.  Brilliant)   Exciting, I jsut ordered a spelling Bee trophy for my "brag table" at my gradutation reception next year.  I'm so excited to make up my own awards.  Yey!  Someone gave me the idea to get awards with someone else's names on the m too, in something that isn't even offered here.  And I'm going to make a macaroni medal.  That's all for now.  See-ya.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I have reached a conclusion on tennis, after a lot of babbling.  I decided that I'm going to be indecisive about it anyway,  but I'll end up signing up, because it's my senior year of tennis, and I don't want to miss that.  So I'll hate it, but I might hate it more if I'm not in it.     I had something else to say last night, and I found it fascinating, i think it had something to do with Lola and Wonder Woman, but I can't remember now.  So I'm off to work on the yearbook.  Joyous.  I'll be back. 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      And we're back from the land of Yearbook camp.  No more Picas, no more layouts, no more pagemaker until Septemeber!!  Though Mr. F did send a camera with me to take pictures of communtiy events throughout the summer.  But I can handle that.  Camera's make me happy.  I also re-met an old Knowledge Bowl acquaintence, who is quite fun to talk to, except I negelcted to gleen his e-mail address from him, and with the help of google and hotmail, have located his profile, but alas no e-mail address to accompany.  Not really sure what to do next, so if anyone has an ideas let me know.  This is frusterating, I'm off to the Cities ina few days, and I don't believe I'll get ot see Abner before he heads off to college.  I'm kinda bummed, it's the beginning of the great friend decline.  Whoo hoo.  But life goes on. I"m now contemplating my senior pictures clothes, and hair styles.  I don't know what to do.  My mom wants one in my prom dress *sigh*.  I wanted one in my new green dress by the fountain in UND.  I don't know how that's going to go over with my mother.  I have a hunch this is going to cause the first big fight between my mom and I since maybe 9th grade.    Oh well, we've done so well for so long, it's about time. 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey blog viewers, I'm here at yearbook camp, apparently you can get outside contact.&nbsp; It's pretty boring, today we learned about picas in one session.&nbsp; We learned about picas the first day of yearbook last fall.&nbsp; But some stuff has been really interesting, we learned how to take better sports photos, I learned a bunch of cool stuff on photoshop even though I don't have access to it out of school.&nbsp; But still.&nbsp; Yeah, not too much to talk aobut.&nbsp; We got here, and there was no alarm clock, let alone a regular clock in our room, so we had to take an emergency run to Pamida to buy a clock.&nbsp; We found a lovely&nbsp;timex number for approximatly $5, don't know who to set the alarm obviously, because it has yet to go off at the right time, but it does have a nice little nightlight that lasts for apporimately three seconds.&nbsp; Yes life at yearbook camp is grand.&nbsp; But we have team time now.&nbsp; Time to make up a sports page layout, and many other fun things.&nbsp; Have a lovely rest of the week. 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello blogger community.&nbsp; This is my first transmission from the world ofyearbook camp.&nbsp; I can't talk. Have a happyday.&nbsp; Session is starting. *mwah!* 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello Hello everyone.&nbsp; So last night I had my first school dream of the summer.&nbsp; I do admit I am starting a tad early this year.&nbsp; It may have something to do with Yearbook camp, but I'm really not sure.&nbsp; But as usual.&nbsp; I was up until 3am, hadn't finished my homework, got to school, couldn't find my homework.&nbsp; And of course I didn't even know my schedule.&nbsp; And to make things worse, the class was overfull, and I didn't get a desk, because I was late, because I didn't know my schedule.&nbsp;  I had an interesting dream during my nap too.&nbsp; I drempt that I was going as Elphaba (the wisked witch of the west) for Halloween, except i couldn't find the green face paint, and everyone left without me.&nbsp; We were trick or treating in this huge city too, as we stepped outside, there was this giant capitol building.&nbsp; That was really cool by the way.&nbsp; But I never got to go, because I didn't have a costume, I didn't have a hat or broom or anything.&nbsp; The green face paint was my costume.&nbsp;  I'm kind of jumping all over the place tonight, but I thought it was really interesting what Aden said about his friend turning into a druggie though.&nbsp; I really don't know about some of my friends, I've had alot move away, but Leila is my only childhood friend that I stil talk to.&nbsp; I've noticed that my friends change alot from year to year.&nbsp; Is that a bad thing?&nbsp; You know, if I do the same thing with guys, that could cause quite a problem with the whole manogomy thing.&nbsp; None of the people that were my friends in Kindergarten are my friends now.&nbsp; Granted I never had many friends through middle school up to well last year, but still I've only held on to a couple.&nbsp; It kind of worries me.&nbsp; Of course if I move to a city I might find a whole life's supply of friends, because here there's really not much to work with.&nbsp; But still, I hope the pattern stops.&nbsp; I don't think it's a healthy way to do relationships.&nbsp;  But anyway.&nbsp; I'm going to go finish my laundry and let my brother have the computer, he's been buggin me for a while.&nbsp; Have a happy day. 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello blog viewers.&nbsp; Today is a thursday.&nbsp; And tomorrow I get to ....&nbsp;Go Shopping!&nbsp; My mother is freaking out a littel bit since Wonder Woman is leaving in about a month, so she has been super nice to both of us lately.&nbsp; And she decided to take us school shopping tomorrow.&nbsp; And we get to school shop in the cities too.&nbsp;  So&nbsp;I went to grocery store this morning.&nbsp; My mom needed bleach so she sent me off.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I was going to buy some frozen meals, but I was like well, I have one at home that I got last time.&nbsp; So I get home, and Wonder woman had eaten both my dry pasta bowl and my frozen meal!&nbsp; She always eats my food.&nbsp; But if you drink one of her Frappacinos it's death to you.&nbsp;  I've noticed that my blog has been losing it's ability to communicate lately.&nbsp; When I came home from Pittsburgh the chatterbox started to flounder, now recently my comments have been struggling.&nbsp; Next thing you know my quote of the day will lose the will to quote.&nbsp; I just don't know what to do.&nbsp; my poor blog. So&nbsp;in conclusion&nbsp;Con: Wonder Woman is leaving Pro: I may end up with a nice wardrobe, food, and closet space.&nbsp;  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It all started before a basketball game.&nbsp; Wonder Woman and I were late for the game.&nbsp;&nbsp; Wonder Woman was driving my car, The Vibe.&nbsp; She sped around, forgetting about the trailer behind us that was being used by the men re-siding our garage.&nbsp; We almost cleared, but she smacked the right front corner into the trailer.&nbsp; Strike number one. A few&nbsp;weeks later, there was a big thunderstorm.&nbsp; Now there is an evergreen tree right next to my parking spot in the driveway.&nbsp; This tree is three to four stories tall, and last year a quite sizable branch at the top broke, but didn't break enough to fall off the tree.&nbsp; So towards the end of school we had a huge thunderstorm.&nbsp; (I loved it I was watching out my window of&nbsp;course)&nbsp; As I was watching&nbsp;I looked over, and saw the&nbsp;lose branch of the tree plumet from the top and&nbsp;bounce right off the top of my Vibe.&nbsp; And I thought, well that probably wasn't very good for my car.&nbsp; The next day I went out on my way to school, and it turned out that I had a couple dents in the roof, my back windshield wiper broke off, and there&nbsp;was a hole in my bumper.&nbsp; I was not please.&nbsp;  Now while I was in Pittsburgh my dad got all this fixed, and I was so happy, when I came home I had a car that worked exactly how it was supposed to.&nbsp; Two days ago I told my&nbsp;dad I was really bored, so he suggested I clean out the inside of my car.&nbsp; I said okay,(that's how bored I was) and when I was done cleaning I though i saw soemthing on the outside.&nbsp; It was a scratch.&nbsp; And it's not the only one.&nbsp; Apparently there's a dent too.&nbsp; I'm convinced my car was a horrible person in a past life.&nbsp; My car has horrible karma. 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello My blog viewers.&nbsp; Today is a very slow day.&nbsp; I was supposed to work at my part time job today, and was very excited.&nbsp; As you have probably picked on,I've been slightly bored lately.&nbsp; Now my part time job is fairly part time.&nbsp; I work one nigth a year.&nbsp; Oh and it's a fun job.&nbsp; Every year my dad holds what's called a plot tour, where he invites his customers to come and see new kinds of grain and other crops available, and after they do that they get a free meal.&nbsp; So my sister and I have been serving rootbeer floats at this for probably 6 or 7 years.&nbsp; Last year my brother joined the team.&nbsp; And more than serving floats our job is to laugh at the farmers aweful jokes.&nbsp; My little brother on the other hand rolled his eyes at all the farmers, and gave them funny looks.&nbsp; I hope he did better this year.&nbsp; But I wasn't allowed to work this year, because I'm sick and for some reason my paretns don't want to contaminate all my dad's customers.&nbsp; What is that?&nbsp;  Oh well.&nbsp; I got to spend some quality time with my wardrobe, sorting out my clothes.&nbsp; I haven't done that in a while.&nbsp; I was amzed at some of the stuff I found.&nbsp; I haven't found my Korczack shirt yet though, so I should really get back to it.&nbsp; Have a wonderful evening. 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bored Bored Bored Bored.&nbsp; Really Really Bored.&nbsp; You konw what?&nbsp; I'm bored.&nbsp; There's nothing to do here.&nbsp; I really need a job.&nbsp; We had church this morning, but that hardly lasts and hour in the summer.&nbsp; I wish I could get a job, but who's going to hire me for two weeks?&nbsp; No one, that's who.&nbsp; Do you know how bored I was today?&nbsp; I bought a college agebra book in Pittsburg, and I got it open, and almost started learning.&nbsp; (I just couldn't do it, too many painful math memories)&nbsp; Then I thought, well I liked spanish alot better than Math, and I bought a second year spanish text book at the library, and I pulled that out, and started to read, except I had no idea what they were saying.&nbsp; So then I went out and tried golfing into a net with my brother.&nbsp;&nbsp; That didn't go well.&nbsp; It only takes me like 5 mins to hit the balls now though.&nbsp; I'm improving.&nbsp; Oh, I coudl never be a housewife.&nbsp; Well I"m off to try to find something midly entertaining.&nbsp; Tata! 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Woah! look at all the buttons.&nbsp; Someone changed blogger again.&nbsp; Lets play with it shall we?&nbsp;  New font.&nbsp; Ooooh Aaaaah&nbsp;&nbsp;  New color.&nbsp;   Woah, that is pretty neat.    &nbsp; But back to the task at hand.&nbsp; You know, I've noticed I get distracted easily lately.&nbsp; I wonder why that is.&nbsp; Oh look a butterfly!&nbsp;   &nbsp; So after my minor freak out due to lack of human contact, I got relief. Giles invited me to go with him the next morning (thursday hey that was yesterday morning) to an auction being held on acount of Crazy Dayz.&nbsp; Now I had never been to an auction, so I'm like ok, if it gets me out of the house.&nbsp; We met at the used book store, very fun place.&nbsp; Then headed down to the auction.&nbsp; it was pretty interesting.&nbsp; Giles and I joked about the merchandise and the purchasers.&nbsp; I saw about $20 worth of cigarettes smoked.&nbsp; Don't you love the smell of lung cancer in the morning?&nbsp; I know I do.&nbsp; And I really like it when I see the EMT's chain smoke.&nbsp; It makes me feel real safe.&nbsp; I mean what do you do when your EMT has a heart attack while trying to save your life?&nbsp; I didn't bid on anything.&nbsp; Ooh speaking of bidding I need to check my ebay stuff.&nbsp; Ok I checked it.&nbsp; But there was this lady sitting in front of me, who kept bidding, and the auctioneer would look at her, but very much in my direction and say amounts of money, and I'm like no no I don't have any money.&nbsp; Giles bid a couple of times though.&nbsp; Oh you better believe it was intense.&nbsp; And he won a tool box.&nbsp; Wee.&nbsp; I was then happy, because I had had my human contact, and could face the rest of the day until Wonder Woman returned.&nbsp;  &nbsp; When she got home she decided since she didn't have to work friday (that's today) we should do something fun.&nbsp; So we went to Great Spoons and shopped at target for a while after going to the Urb, and then we went to see King Arthur.&nbsp; Now some one (that may have been me) forgot that even though it's hot outside it's not necesarrily hot in the movie theatre.&nbsp; So even leaving Target I was really cold, and I sat throught the whole movie (2hours and 10mins)&nbsp; curled in a ball in my chair shivering.&nbsp; A t-shirt and shorts are not adequate for a movie theatre.&nbsp;&nbsp; This wouldn't have been so bad, except tat the movie got the story all wrong! (We went to King Arthur by the way)&nbsp; The only similarities I saw between the story I know and the movie were that Arthur and Guienevier fall in love, and it was set in Britain.&nbsp; In my opinion, don't waste your money, and read the once and future King instead. &nbsp; 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I woke up, and no-one was home. So I did absolutely nothing, until I finally decided I needed to wash my clothes because I didn't have any to wear. And about 20 mins before Womder Woman returned home from work I actually took my shower. This very boring day made me come to the conclusion that living in the country Sucks. I have had no contact with any one other than Wonder Woman, and I'm going crazy. And this is only the first day. Augh! I did however get an interesting phone call this afternoon.  So I was on the internet craving human companionship, and the phone rings. I look on the caller Id and it says Camp Emaus. Now my little brother Max is at a canoe camp there. So the first though that enters my mind. What bone did he break this time? So I pick up the phone, and one of the counselors asks for my mom, and I informed her that both our parents left for vacation for a few days, but that I'm his sister, and maybe I can help. And she informs me that Max is getting homesick and wants to come home. Well he only has a day and a half of camp left, and he is 14. And I know that generally they try to get the kids to stick it out for the whole week. Now last year he had a really bad experience with camp. He was put in a really bad cabin, and ended up comng home early. So that probably had something to do with it, because he's never had a problem with homesickness before. So (now you may find this cauloused but remember I'm cold and soulless) I told her to have him stay, because we really didn't want to come pick him up.  That's all that happened today! How boring! I have to move somewhere where there are people. In a city even if you live alone there are tons of places you can go, just to have some human contact. You can run to the grocery store, rent a movie, browse the nearest target. Augh! But I'm stuck here for another year. We do get to go on a trip to the cities this summer though. And we are going to the museum!! I'll stop boring you for now. But have a wonderful day.  
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I just got done watching Moulin Rouge, and I've determined that I've experienced too many tragic love stories lately.  It seems strange for a love story not to end in a death.  Rent, death, and many looming deaths.  Romeo and Juliet two deaths.  Moulin Rouge, a death.  Wicked, much turmoil, a death.     Wicked is this really cool musical I just discovered, it's the story of the wicked witch of the west and how she became wicked.  It's really neat, and I feel really back for the wicked witch.  Her name is Alphaba in the musical.  And she's an outcast, and decides she doesn't want to be held in by all the rules of society, and wants to do good on her own.  Then she is declared wicked and hunted down, until the inevitable end.  My theory is that the writer wrote Wicked just to screw people up when they watch the Wizard of Oz.  I now feel incredibly sorry for Alphaba and rather despise Gelinda(the good witch).  Most artists are a little warped though, they probably figured well, if we're warped they might as well be too.  Well I had best be getting to bed.  Have a wonderful whatever time you read this.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello my faithfull blog viewers.  Today is a Monday.  Yesterday was a rather eventful Sunday.  We had church in the morning as always, but it was kinda fun to be back after my five week absence.  Then we went home and slept for a really long time.  Sleep is mucho good.  And this was a Breathe week, so practice was at 6:30, and we had a new member of the tech team.  A male version of Leila.  We're going to call him Leeland.  He actually knows alot more about computers than me which was very good when I couldn't get the computer monitor on unless I pushed the button and held it in.  So he stuck a paperclip in it and now it works fine.  And so go the normal fixes in the tech room.  I think he could be a valuable asset to the team.   So today is the last day of Pennsylvania cousins, they are leaving on a jet plane in a couple of hours.  Sadly I actually got to know all of them pretty well this summer, but I won't see them again for proably a year or more.  Oh well that's how relatives are.     Oh and get this, one of the ladies in our church came up to me and asked me "Amanda, how was your trip."  and I was like, you know my name?  Are you feeling alright?  You see at my church all the senile people have a very hard time keeping Wonder Woman and I seperate.  Wonder Woman sings on the worship team, so they see her every sunday.  I however am in the back in the Tech room, so they don't see me.  We've become known as the Callihan girl.  People come up to me after church, and say you did such a nice job singing today.  Now originally I would correct people, but it took so long to explain that now I just say thanks.  And before I left people would come up to Wonder woman and say I have things for you, but I forgot them at home.  And she'd look at them and say things?  You know, for your trip.  And she'd said oh, great. So now we answer for each other, it's just too complicated the other way.  Although they are going to be very surprised when Wonder Woman sundenly stops singing on the worship team, and flys back from California every weekend.  Oh well.   I have to run though.  I have an orthodontist appointment in Great Spoons in a little bit, Oh joy.  I'll talk more later.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello my blog viewers.  How is everyone today?  I'm excellent.  I just got back from playing in the rain.  I don't know how long it's been since I played in the rain.  I love it.  I found a really deep puddle, and I jumped in it for a few minutes, and Wonder Woman even came out to join me.  It was so much fun.  I'm definitly going to have to do it more often.  I'm pretty sure tha last time I played in the rain I had a little pink polka dotted umbrella.  I miss those days.  I think I need a new umbrella.  I'm going to have to buy one some day.  I don't think I have one.   A while ago, I was in Marshall Fields with Wonder Woman, and we were looking at rain boots.  I kinda wish I would ahve gotten a pair, but I wish more that I had gotten on of the cool umbrellas with a frog or a duck on it.  Fun rain gear is esential for sanity. But enough about that.  I just looked at our calendar, and apparently, we're supposed to go to my grandma's lake cabin tomorrow.  I think it would have been nice to be informed of that.  But whatever.  I'll have to pack a bad.   I can't think of anything else worthy of blogging, so I'll blog later.  Oh and Abner, I showed my cousins your LotR spoof tonight, and they loved it.  I'll see you/type to/talk to you all later.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm back form my few day break from blogging.  It decided my blog need a vacation.  It worked hard while I was gone.   Yesterday I went on a delightful trip to Great Spoons with Mahinda, Lola, Leila, and Wonder Woman.  We went to the mall and I found a homecoming dress for $18.  Then we went to target and got some lunch tot ake to the urb,then we went to the thrift store.  That was fun.  I found books, and really cheap dishes.  I got salt and pepper shakers, and cups for under a dollar.  Lola found a rockin' alarm clock/cd player too.  It has gems for buttons, and it's pink.  And the clock face changes colors!  She named it Bitchin'.  That's one of the best thrift store purchases I've seen so far.   Tomorrow we have relatives descending upon our house.  I really hope it stops raining so we can kick some of them outside.  Our house is rather small for that many people.  We'll have seventeen people here.  That's too many.  Wish me luck, I have to get back to cleaning or my mom is going to suck me up in the vaccuum.  Have a delightful day.  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ahh Air conditioning.   This morning I decided to bake cookies.  This was a bigger task than I though.  I searched through the cupboards for 1/2 hour trying to find all the ingredients.  Finaly I had located everything except vanilla, and a mixer.  And I'm like whatever this is close enough to make cookies.  So I starte handmixing the dough, and was ready to put them on the pan, and I tasted the dough. It was pretty wierd, so I'm thinking, maybe the vanilla is a key ingredient in cookies.  So I searched for 15 more mins, and finaly found it, right under my nose.  I put them in the oven, and let them cook.  I came back to check them maybe 10 mins later, and they're still pretty runny.  I came back 5 mins later.  They have spread across the entire pan, and doubled in height.  I finally take the out, and they're kind of spongy.  Oh well, I put in the remaining dough, and promptly forget about them.  Twenty minutes later, I smell something, and remember that I was baking. I had to hrow those away.  They hurt my teeth.  Then I was washing the pan, and was using the sprayer.  Their sprayer has a bad temper.  I thought I had it under control, until I set the sprayer back in it's holder, and turned on the water.  Vengance usually isn't a common thing for apliances, but needless to say, I am now in different clothes.  Later on this morning, I had to go with my cousin to my aunt's ofice,(he didn't know where it was) to get his menegitis shot for college.  When we got to the hospital, we tried to take the elevator up to the fourth floor, we get in and push he 4.  The crazy elevator goes all the way down to the ground floor. We're like ok, push the 4 again, and it goes up one floor, and then back down again.  Finally it goes up to the 4th floor again.  Apparently this happens alot. Well this was a pretty long entry about nothing.  So I'm going to go.  See you all Tomorrow! 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Can some one please tell me when it was that Abner changed his name to Karl?  I did however figure out Paco's transformation into Steve.  I'l see you all in less than two days.  A Saturday poker night sounds really good to me.  I'll be home!  as long as I make my plane.  Miss and Love you all.  See you soon.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, there is excitement here in Crappsville,  I just had quite the encounter.  I added a guy to my msn that I had talked to at knowledge bowl a few years ago, and saw again at yearbook camp.  When I talked to him he seemed like a perfectly nice guy, even funny.  Well, I started talking to him on msn tonight, and we talked about yearbook, knowledge Bowl, and then got on the topic of Musicals.  He told me that he thought Rent sucked, so I asked him what he though a good musical was.  I though I was only being fair, considering I loved Rent, and didn't yell.  Well then he goes on to tell me about a composer/writer he really liked.  I asked him what musicals he had written, and this guy responds with, and I quote "Wow, you really don't know much about musicals do you?"  Now I was wondering whether I should take offense to some of the things he said earlier, but decided not to.  After this though, I was shocked, and informed him that it wasn't nice to make fun of people who don't know as much as you.  Then we got in a big fight,  he didn't play fair, called me a bitch, stubborn, pretentious, and judgemental.  I was impressed, I've never been called stubborn before.  You know I think we could really turn out to be best friends.  Oh wait....  I don't know why I blogged about this except I need somewhere to relieve my shock.  Well, no he has blocked me, so I gues I don't have to worry about it anymore huh?  It's just so wierd, he seemed so nice.  I don't think I'm a good judge of people. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>