<Blog>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Spike is a sociopath. Spike has fun hurting people. Spike is a man without guilt. Spike is a man for whom the world has been opened, and he can get what he wants when he wants it. Spike  does not carry a wallet ."  -- James Marsters
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    *chomp*&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I also want Willow. Wo ai ta! Dai suki da yo! Ani ohevet ota!  Wirro ga ii desu kedo, desain ga chotto ne...  Uhhh... You're a nerdnerdnerd... I want to watch season four! Give me tonight?  WO XIANG QU NI! WO XIANG CHI NI!
     
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I will fight you for her, MacKenzie.  Choose your weapon and time of battle.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Fred's DEAD? But she's still on the show, and Wesley still pines for her and not me? And Spike hasn't been dusted yet?
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Come. Informal. Blah.  Info  urlLink here .
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey suckas, it's me.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      but Giles and all his British, fuddly-duddly sex appeal is  mine. 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Who will fight me for her?
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      at least it's better than season 4... that was boring... and bun-bun, i STILL don't hate riley. i can't.
     
    
</post>


<date>29,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Today is my favorite day of Spirit Week. For the uninitiated (I know there are a few of you out there), Wednesday is the day when each class wears their class color. Freshman are orange, Sophomores are red, Juniors are yellow, and Seniors are green. Not only is it not too difficult to dress appropriately, but it is also fascinating to see the patterns of students by grade. Since it's so easy to dress up, maybe 95% or so of everyone is school wears the appropriate colors, so it becomes clear what grade everyone is in.  Some observations I made today: • At brunch, the crowd of people who hang out under the trees in the corner of the Quad by the English department is  entirely  made of Freshman. It was like this big orange blob today. Kinda freaky. • The majority of people who go across the street to Town and Country during the extended brunch on Wednesdays are underclassmen. This is especially odd if you consider the fact that Freshman were supposed to be at advisory at that time. • Most of the people in the MRC at lunch are juniors. Add that to the fact that most of them are also asian, and you being to wonder just how many asian junior (mainly boys) there are at my school. I mean, that place was crowded when I got there and the passing period had already started, so one can assume that a few of them had already left. It's kind of mind bloggling. • There are more juniors in my chem class than I thought there was. That is always another interesting part of color day. You have clear evidence of what grade specific people are in, and sometimes this can be very surprising. I think Gabrielle said that every year since she was a Freshman people are always surprised to see that she's not a Senior. • The "decky" half of the deck was the most colorful part on the quad... that I noticed. I wasn't looking too closely, but that's how it seemed to me. Of course, some of that was because there were some people who weren't wearing the appropriate colors. • My CS class is full of unspirited, slightly prickish nerds. Some of them are nice most of the time, but they're still prickish when it comes to Spirit Week. I could go into a rant, but suffice to say that I'm annoyed at many of them.  On a side note, I'm inordinately pleased with myself because I got a lot of work done today. In CS I got all of our ("us" being Gabe and myself) helper classes for our semester project encoded, commented, and debugged (or at least, the syntax is right). Now all we need to do is write the driver class, which we have the pseudo for, and get all of the kinks out. Considering we have a good couple of months to do this, I think we're in good shape. Also, during 5th when I was TAing, I actually finished dealing with  all  of the relevant papers in 3 of the 4 math classes that I handle. Considering I have  never  caught up in any of them, I was terribly pleased with myself. Also, the 4th class shouldn't take too long to finish up either, and then I'll be entirely caught up! Maybe then I can finish my TA work during ther period I'm actually a TA and spend my prep doing thing other than grading papers (except once a week when I grade the Java programs, but that's a separate matter). What a refreshing thought... 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I suppose I should comment on the fact that it's spirit week this week. Most of you know that, but I'm gonna jabber on about it anyway since there's nothing else to talk about. Today was definitely fun. Who doesn't love the idea of wearing a toga to school? Of course, the idea of wearing a toga is much better than the actual wearing of it. I definitely had to wrestle with it a number of times before someone finally helped me figure out a way to wear it that stayed in place sufficiently to get me to the end of the day, although it was definitely starting to slip a little at the end.  Of course, the minor annoying details fade into the background in general. Sprit Week is fun, and that's all that matters, right? And hopefully our class won't emarrass ourselves horribly again this year by losing to the  Freshman , never mind any of the other classes. I think last year we were just having an off year or something. Of course, I firmly uphold that we were punished unfairly for our dance. It kicked ass.  Oh, and am I a big loser if I'm amused by our class shirt? "We don't take no croc!" hehe. It's funny cuz we're Crocodile Hunter. Or Dundee. I always get those two mixed up. Does it really make a difference? I think not. 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Ugh. I've definitely lost the concentration to do all of my homework. Especially my sociology homework. I mean, it's an interesting class, and we have lots of cool discussions, but it's  a lot  of work. I mean, it's more than some of my AP classes, and it isn't even laned! It's kind of ridiculous. Doing the reading is a pain in the ass, and we have these big projects that we have to do that are annoying too.  *sigh* Is it June yet? Am I in college yet? God, I haven't even finished my application yet... *groans* 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       My nephew is cute.   urlLink http://reid.org/victoria/photos/fall03/  
    
    
</post>

<date>24,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Tonight I watched my nephew Dwayne for a couple of hours so everyone else could go out and have a relaxing dinner, and he was a tired puppy. I'm just glad that he was the kind of tired that let me put  Blue's Clues  on an endless loop for about 4 hours and he would stay pretty satisfied, with only the occasional wandering off. Of course, that meant that  I  had to sit through Blues Clues for that long as well. God, I hate Blue's Clues... *grimace* If it weren't for the fact that I could use headphones to listen to music on my computer while I sat with him, I think I would have gone mad. I mean, not only are the episodes amazingly boring, repetative, and do-gooder (which isn't surprising because the show is aimed at toddlers), but the damn songs are horribly catchy! I mean, I was in the room while he watched an episode of it a couple of weeks ago, and the next day I had the "circle time" song stuck in my head for a while, and it wouldn't go away unless I drowned it out with other music.   Anyway... yeah. That was my evening. *shrug* I have no life. Anyone want to do anything this weekend? Or actually, maybe not this weekend. I'm gonna need to buckle down and finish my application since it's due next Saturday. *wince* Also, there's Spirit Week. How the hell am I going to dress up for 80s day? Or Senior Citizen day? And I need to go find a toga and...  God, I can't wait until this quarter is over and all of this is  behind me . 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I did 8 hours of homework tonight. That is all I have to say. Thank you, and  goodnight . 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       It's funny, you know how people often have smells associated with people that they know well? You know, like the aftershave your father has always worn, or the fact that your grandparents' house always smells like grandma's cooking? I had never really noticed anything like that before with any of my relatives, but tonight as I was walking through the kitchen to put away my 2-in-the-morning-dinner remnants, I caught a whiff of something, and immediately knew that it was my mother's coffee, or coffee-like thing. I've never had any, but I know that she drinks it. I used to wake up in the mornings and see her drinking it as she read the newspaper, and I would sit on the couch and pick up the comics and I could smell this drink - whatever it was. I mean, it doesn't  smell  like coffee; it has this almost sickly sweet aroma to it, that I can't identify. I'm not sure if this is just how it smells, or if it tastes as sweet too.  Anyway, it's kind of neat to think that I have a smell associated with a parent. Of course, I'm sure I have more, but this was the first one that I consciously realized. Maybe I'll pick up on others now that I'm more aware of their existence. 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I must say that I actually had a lot of fun today, despite a misadventure or two.  My day basically began with Jonathan calling me about hanging out, as we had arranged the night before. After a few rounds of telephone tag, because of silly parents (mine) and weird telephones (his), we made contact, and I went and got dressed and headed over to his house. We headed downtown, and wandered around being bored for a while, got some ice cream, and talked to some random Casti friend of his who I didn't know in Borders for a while. Oh, and I bought some new headphones, too. That was cool.   After that we went over to Bun-Bun's to get him and go see  The Laramie Project . However, we decided to take Jonathan's car, since the two of them were going to see the midnight movie afterwards, and I was not (stupid midnight curfew. Can I just say that I can't wait for my birthday? I hate the Cinderella clause) so we went over to Jonathan's house and traded my car for his, and headed over to Sacred Heart.  The production was good, and we ran into lots of other cool people (Gabe, Kendal, etc.), since this was supposed to be a GSA trip. Also, Jonathan's friend  urlLink Ingrid  was there, who I hadn't really been introduced to, but had heard a bit about. Oh, and her friend Shane (sp?) was there too, and she was nice.  The show was over around 10, and since that was 2 hours before midnight, which was everyone's next deadline, we decided to go hang out together elsewhere, and went to our respective cars to get there. When we got to our cars, it turned out that Gabe, being the fool that he is, had left his lights on during the show, and so his battery was dead. Also, no one there (there were three cars available) had any jumper cables, and so Ingrid and Shane took me to Jonathan's house to get my car, since I did. That was fun, though, since I got to know them better and such. They're definitely cool chicks. Of course, once we got back to Sacred Heart, we all realized that no one knew how to use jumper cables, and since we knew enough to know that mistreating them tended to blow things up, and none of us wanted that, I called my dad and had him explain to me how to use them. That was definitely difficult until we discovered the flashlight that my mother had left in my car from when she used it (bless you, mother) so we could figure out which part of the battery was positive, and which negative (hence, no explosions). Then we got the cars started without anything going boom, and headed off to Jonathan's en masse. We hung out there for about half and hour, before those of us with midnight curfews went home, and those going to the midnight movie went there instead.  Overall, I'd say the day was a success, especially since I feel like we never  do  anything on the weekend. I say that we should have similar adventures in the future. Or at least, we should go out and do something. Anyone else agree with me? Especially when our other friends don't have the PSATs in the morning and feel that they can join us as well. Silly juniors, don't you understand that you need to relax on the weekends as a counterbalance to the insanity that is your lives? Trust me, I was just there. 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Okay, this is one of the funniest conversations I've had on AIM to date, and it's all because of some miscommunication (which is ironic, if you think about it). I sent a message to Jonathan's mother (yes, I know her screen name) to try to find out what time he would be getting home tonight, and this is what happened (FYI for the uninitiated: Jonathan's mother's name is Susan, his father is Jack, and his sister is Eleanor):   me  (5:36:06 PM): what time is Jonathan getting home today?  Susan's sn  (5:36:29 PM): flight gets in at 8:50  Susan's sn  (5:36:33 PM): And this is your father.  Susan's sn  (5:36:36 PM): (snrk)  me  (5:36:39 PM): what?!?  Susan's sn  (5:36:51 PM): confuse-a-kid strikes again.  me  (5:37:02 PM): now I'm doubly confused  me  (5:37:03 PM): what's going on?  Susan's sn  (5:37:20 PM): Well, I was in the office and your mother isn't home yet.  me  (5:37:42 PM): wait, *who* isn't home yet?  me  (5:37:49 PM): is this Jack?  Susan's sn  (5:37:57 PM): YOUR MOTHER isn't home  Susan's sn  (5:38:10 PM): I identified myself as your father.  me  (5:38:16 PM): yes, but...  Susan's sn  (5:38:18 PM): Susan will have to judge whether I'm Jack  Susan's sn  (5:38:31 PM): I believe we are the same person  me  (5:38:39 PM): uh, right  Susan's sn  (5:39:13 PM): So this is Jack, Susan isn't home yet, and Jonathan should arrive home sometime between 9:30 and 10:00 tonight, if his flight's on time.  me  (5:39:21 PM): check  me  (5:39:22 PM): gotcha  me  (5:39:32 PM): it was the father/mother part that confused me there...  Susan's sn  (5:39:51 PM): Oh.....  Susan's sn  (5:39:55 PM): This isn't Eleanor  me  (5:39:58 PM): no  me  (5:40:01 PM): this is Elizabeth  Susan's sn  (5:40:01 PM): No wonder!  Susan's sn  (5:40:06 PM): Of course.  Susan's sn  (5:40:13 PM): Sorry about that  me  (5:40:17 PM): s'alright  Susan's sn  (5:40:24 PM): I just assumed it was Eleanor, withoug looking  me  (5:40:34 PM): yeah, I guess that's understandable  me  (5:40:35 PM): :-)  Susan's sn  (5:40:47 PM): It's been confusing for Eleanor when I answer on Susan's machine  Susan's sn  (5:40:52 PM): So I was playing that up  me  (5:40:57 PM): ah ha  Susan's sn  (5:41:08 PM): Though i did think she was being a bit dense  Susan's sn  (5:41:30 PM): which she would have been had she not been you  me  (5:41:36 PM): exactly   Now, while I do consider Jack and Susan to be parental-figures to me, I don't immediately think of them when someone says "your mother" or "your father". Go figure... 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Random thought: If the talk about "the birds and the bees" is about sex, then are the birds and the bees having sex  together?  And if so, is that how we get "birdies"?  And no, this didn't come out of my twisted mind. It came out of my sister's. 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Well, it's 4th period and we're in the computer lab looking up Stock Market reports on 6 companies, which takes about 5 minutes, but she's giving us 20, so I'm majorly bored. Hmm... This isn't as entertaining as Bun-Bun insisted it would be. Damn you Bun-Bun! 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Today I had a small interaction with one of the office staff members at Paly, although I'm not sure exactly who she was. Anyway, when she realized what my name was (she was passing out papers by name to a group of students), she said "Every time I read your name somewhere, I wonder if you were named after that Allman Brothers Song. Are you?" I explained to her that I was actually named after my grandmother, but I think she was a bit disappointed to hear that. Anyway, coming away from this conversation, I realized that there was this song floating out there with my name, but I had  no idea  what it sounded like, so I downloaded it this afternoon. Is it wrong of me to be disappointed by it? I mean, there aren't even any lyrics!  If any of you care about the song itself, it's  In Memory of Elizabeth Reed  by the Allman Brothers. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       *sigh* As if last night's rant wasn't enough, I'm back for more. The dude staying with us (I think his name may be Ron? I'll call him Ron) is definitely driving me insane this morning. Now, if I were less tired and I didn't think I was going to be late for class, I might be more reasonable and understand that he doesn't actually know that he's getting in my way, but he is, and so I'm pissed. He has been in my bathroom for over half an hour, which means that I cannot be in there. Now, it is the bathroom that he is supposed to be using, but  I have to go to school soon . Soon, as in I should be leaving right now to go to chemistry, and I still haven't been able to brush my teeth or put in my contacts. Or take a shower, but I'm going to have to live with that. grrrr.... 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Okay, so I'm not sure if all of you know that I go to church, but I do. Also, my church seems to go through an astounding number of organists, for a reason that I do not fully understand. Anyway, our current organist, who is cool, is moving back East to work at his dream job and so they had this big hunt to find a new organist over the summer. One of the candidates stayed at our house while they interviewed him (while I was at NYLF), and we overlapped by a few days so I got to meet him. My initial reaction was that he was a big nerd, and since this was directly after coming back from a  technology convention  if I can say that, suffice to say, he was nerdy. However, the nerdiness of an organist isn't actually all that important to churches, and I guess he was the best candidate or something, because they hired him as the replacement and he's in the process of moving here from... wherever the hell he came from.  Now my mother, being the all-too-kind soul that she is, allowed him to stay here again while his stuff was being shipped. So he has been around the house all weekend, and it has been grating on my nerves. Not only is he just a big nerd, but he's also really  loud . I don't think he really understands the concept of changing voice levels for different situations. Thank god he'll be out of here by tomorrow afternoon.  Sorry, end rant. 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       It's only early afternoon and I'm already exhausted. What's up with that? I spent my morning at church, working at a carwash at my church, driving around lots of cars because the majority of the members of the youth group can't drive yet. They also seem to be bad at washing cars. How hard is it to properly dry a car before the sun does it for you and makes it ugly? Silly young'ns. Oh well, I get the feeling that no one is really going to mind about some dried water on their cars. 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       So, I'm back, and the interview went well. Yay! 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Color me nervous. I am about to go to my MIT interview, in hopes of not making a complete fool of myself. Of course, they  say  that if the interview goes badly, they'll just disregard it, but still... Wouldn't a really good interview be nice?  Of course, I was also being thrown all over the place this morning when I was getting ready to go. As I started getting dressed, the first song I heard was Jimmy Eat World's  The Middle . Now, I'm not a superstitious person, to say, except when things point towards something good. So, when the cheerfull sound of their lyrics floated over to me, I relaxed a little. I mean, think about it:   Hey  Don't write yourself off yet  It's only in your head you feel left out Or looked down on  Just try your best  Try everything you can  ...  Everything, everything will be just fine  Everything, everything will be all right, all right    ...  Live right now  Just be yourself  It doesn't matter if that's good enough  For someone else    Of course, a few songs later, the radio decided to wrench me in the other direction with some... less peppy songs. Pariticularly of the  you're not going to do well so don't even try  variety. I'm blanking on specifics at the moment (I must have blocked them out), but suffice to say, I changed the station.  And then the person I'm interviewing with called to say she would be late, and so here I am, trying to stall for half an hour until it's time to leave. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Alright, this is my first 'real' post, I promise. Tonight my dad and I went to go see  Kill Bill , and it was utterly fantastic. I loved it! The only thing I wasn't terribly pleased about was the blood. It was definitely... spurty. I mean, I can handle gore like the rest of them, but this was... a lot. I understand that it was a stylistic thing, but...  *shrug* Such is life. The rest of the movie was so fantastic, I'll forgive him the blood. In fact, I'd sit through the entire thing just to hear the last line again. I won't go into any details so that the rest of you can go and enjoy it, but suffice to say, I'm eagerly awaiting the second half. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Okay, so I'm working on a comment system, in case anyone is actually looking at this thing. However, it's gonna take a little time because my entire website is being shuffled over to a new server, and I don't yet have a way to access the files to change them any more. So, bear with me people. Whoever you may be... 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       It's up! After  days  of hard work from... people other than me, my blog can now be viewed by other people. Satisfied, Bun-Bun? 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Okay, obviously this blog isn't going as smoothly as expected. Case in point: none of these posts are being seen by anyone except for me. Is it wrong of me to feel like a big loser? I thought not.  On a side note, during my adventures with getting this all to work, I found out that my Uncle Glenn knows one of the original creators of Blogger. How cool is that? This is how he met her:   urlLink http://web.0sil8.com/episodes/megway/home.html   Which is amazingly cool. I think we should all buy one. 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Okay, let's see if I can now FTP like I should be able to. If so, my Uncle Glenn rocks and my dad goes to bed too early. 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       So, with Bun Bun's advice, I now have a new blog. I don't really know what I'm going to put in it yet, so bear with me. This post is basically just to see if it works. I hope it does. How else am I going to blather on about nothing? 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       So tonight at MacKenzie's party, we watched  urlLink  Secretary  , among other movies, and I think it is fantastic. I won't go into why, because that isn't actually why I'm posting here. Anyway, I just went to see what else the two main characters have been in on IMDB, and I discovered that the leading lady,  urlLink Maggie Gyllenhaal , has the same birthday as me. Woot!  Oh, and pictures from the party will be forthcoming. 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Yesterday I saw the music video for Good Charlotte's  Hold On , which was also the first time I had heard the song (or at least the first time I paid attention to lyrics and such), and it gave me chills. It's not even like I knew Benjamiin Tachibana, or any of his family, or even Steven Wertheimer, and yet... why? Why did they feel the need to do it? And why is it affecting me like this?  And of course,  Hold On  makes me think of the Buffy episode  Earshot  as well. As Buffy says,    "You know what? I was wrong. You are an idiot. My life happens to on occasion suck beyond the telling of it. Sometimes more than I can handle. But it's not just mine. Every single person down there is ignoring your pain because they're too busy with their own. The beautiful ones, the popular ones, the guys who pick on you. Everyone. If you could hear what they were thinking -- the loneliness, the confusion. It looks quiet down there, but it's not. It's deafening."  
    
    
</post>

<date>26,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       So my mom's parents, her brother John, his wife Nancy, and their adopted son Brian are all visiting for Thanksgiving. It's definitely odd to see them, since I hardly ever do. I feel kind of bad about how disconnected I am from my mom's side of the family, but they all live so far away! Most of my father's brothers and sisters (and their kids) live here, as does my paternal grandmother, so I see them a lot more often than I do my mother's family. Also, the Reids (my dad's family) all very engergetic, lively, personable and interesting people, so whenever we  do  get together, we're having fun and doing stuff.  However, my mother's family is a lot more... toned down, I guess. I mean, I don't feel that I have as much in common with them as I do with my dad's family, and so we don't have as much to talk about. Also, they aren't necessarily really chatty, so awkward silences aren't in a terribly short supply. Heck, I keep on going back and forth between thinking that Nancy doesn't like me particularly, and that she does. It's all very confusing.  Also, their son Brian is 8, and I had only met him once before he got here, and that was only for an afternoon. So not only is he less than half my age, he also doesn't know me, and I have to constantly edit what I say around him (he's still in the "I am being taught to be a 'good boy', so I am not supposed to swear, be a bad sport, cheat, etc." stage (we were playing cards)). Altogether, this means that things while they are here are a little... strained, I guess. Now all I can do is see how the rest of the weekend plays out.   Oh, and Happy Turkey Day! :-) 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I thought I would post this, just because. I don't take quizzes very often, since they're usually very transparent, but this one was maybe a 7 on a scale from 1-10. Of course, the final determining factor: is it true?      You are Form 0, Phoenix: The Eternal. "And The Phoenix's cycle had reached zenith, so he consumed himself in fire. He emerged from his own ashes, to be forever immortal." Some examples of the Phoenix Form are Quetzalcoatl (Aztec), Shiva (Indian), and Ra-Atum (Egyptian). The Phoenix is associated with the concept of life, the number 0, and the element of fire. His sign is the eclipsed sun. As a member of Form 0, you are a determined individual. You tend to keep your sense of optomism, even through tough times and have a positive outlook on most situations. You have a way of looking at going through life as a journey that you can constantly learn from. Phoenixes are the best friends to have because they cheer people up easily.  
    
    
</post>

<date>25,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       In the further adventures of Elizabeth's locker...  Today I decided I was sick of looking at the message on my locker, so during my prep I decided to go hunt down someone to try to get them to clean it off. However, first I went to my locker to drop off some books, since I hadn't had a chance to earlier in the day. Guess what I saw when I got there?  That's right! My locker was once again lost among the masses, profanity-free. Anyone else find it ironic that it got cleaned off the  day  that I decided to find someone to clean it for me? Not that I really mind, since it saved me work, but still... 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I'm sorry,  urlLink this  just blows my mind! 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I just added a page with some of the pictures that I took around school this week. Please peruse them at your leisure. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I think I must have the only locker in school with graffiti on it  already . I mean, we've only had them for about 2 or 3 weeks now, and I've only been using mine for about 3 of those days (total). When they gave out locker assignments, I went to my locker and put my lock on it, and then promptly forgot which locker was mine. When I finally had time to hunt down where the list was kept in the office, it was Tuesday of this week. I headed over to it to check to make sure that it was really there and that I knew my combination, and when I arrived I was welcomed by the lovely sight of " F*ck you c*nt! Die! " in bright blue permanent ink.  Now, considering no one else knew which locker was mine, and I couldn't think of  anyone  who would feel the need to say this to me, never mind in permanent blue ink for all the school to see, I just assumed that it was a random (and extremely rude) tagging — probably from an underclassmen. However, when I returned to my locker on Thursday, I discovered a new message below it from a red ball-point pen reading, "Never!"  I guess this means that two people who I don't know are having anargumentt/insult fest on my locker. Why they decided to do this on  my  locker I couldn't tell you. I also couldn't tell you who was doing it, although I sure do wish I could... Anyway, I'm not sure if I should just ignore it and hope no one gives me any funny looks while I'm transferring my books to and from my locker or if I should try to have someone remove it.  Oi. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Has everyone seen the  urlLink latest Strong Bad email ? If so (or if you didn't notice this), once it is over I strongly recommend that you click on Trogdor's Arm (it's in the upper left corner of the news sign) for some wonderful grammar tips. It's about damn time Strong Bad gave some helpful pointers, and what better way to do it? 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       My party pictures are now officially up, if anyone cares. Some of them have even been turned into a story! 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Since there seems to have been some confusion, if I ever say that I am going to post pictures, I am going to put them onto my  urlLink pictures page  rather than my blog, because then they're more permanent. My pictures from Friday night are up there already, and I'm going to put pictures up from tonight's party there as well, although not quite yet (since I'm only just getting them onto my computer now).  Oh, speaking of my party, thank you to everyone who came. I had a lot of fun, and I hope you did too. For everyone who couldn't make it, I wish you could have. I might post a few of the pictures from the party here later, with silly captions (as seems to be the tradition now), although I'll still put them up on my pictures page as well. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       So tonight was the family half of my birthday celebration, with all of my local relatives here (except a couple cousins who couldn't make it). Man, I made out like a bandit! I got this really  urlLink kick-ass digital camera  from my dad/immediate family, excellent sunglasses from my aunt (which I had really needed, unbeknownst to her), and these two math books from my uncle that are first editions —  very  nice. I think I'm gonna put some of the pictures I took up on my pictures page, so look for some of them to go up in the future (possibly tonight, although not right away).  I must say, I do love my family. I don't have any of those embarrasing old uncles or anything, and we generally have a great time when we get together. It's blissful chaos, and I love it.  Of course, tomorrow should be an excellent party as well. I just wish I knew how many people were coming... it's easier to organize that way. :-) 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Triskaidekaphobia. How many people have we heard of with this rather odd disease? We see it in movies, hotels, and old fairy tales. It strikes when you least expect it, and among people of all intelligences. Maybe you suffer from this malady yourself, who knows?  And what is the meaning of this mouthful? Fear of the number 13. Cower in fear!!!  Who could resist such a cool name? I want Triskaidekaphobia! 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Well, I meant to post this last night, but Blogger wouldn't let me so I thought I would do it now. Last night I broke down and spent about an hour going through the "Insider's Guide to the Colleges" to try to figure out where in the world I'm going to apply. It was, as I always insisted it would be, not very helpful at all. Of of the schools sounded  exactly the same , and I had to revert to checking to see what types of majors were most common, what the SAT scores were, and as a final reality check I would skim a few paragraphs or the titles of subsections.  All in all, I'm about where I was before I opened the book. I know I'm applying to Amherst and Carnegie, and I'm pretty sure I'm going to apply to Williams, RIT, Rensselaer, and WPI, although those last three are all kind of the same, and kind of boring, but okay as backup schools, I guess. Oh, and I might apply to Harvard, I'm not sure yet.  I feel vindicated in my belief that such books are stupid and of almost no assistance, except in the way that they have a complete list of all of the colleges and helpfully organize them by location, which is a large part of my decision. Most schools have students who say that the work load is "rigorous", so that doesn't tell you anything, and other than that everything depends on which students they interviewed for the book. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I just edited another batch of handwritten Java programs from the Intro class. This one was  much  better than the last, which is probably a good thing. It certainly makes it easier to grade, although it is much less amusing in the long run. I guess it's a toss-up. Of course, there were still a couple of amusing situations in this one as well, so all is not lost.  Oh, and yes, I do know I'm a big nerd. You don't need to tell me. It's understood. 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       A random question popped in my head tonight, and now it's bugging me. If anyone could tell me the answer, I'll... give them a hug! Of course, depending on their location, it could turn out to just be a cyber-hug, but the principle is the same. Anyway, here's the question: How did they come up with Fahrenheit? I mean, Celsius was obviously created from the freezing and boiling points of water, and Kelvins are like Celsius only off by 273 so that it accurately represents absolute zero as zero, but where in the world did they come up with our Fahrenheit system?  Anyone know? 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I saw   urlLink Elf   last night with my cousin Dan. It was... amusing. However, I felt that it was more the movie you should watch at home so you can talk and joke about it while you're watching, rather than in the theaters where you... can't. And coming from me, that's actually kind of a big thing. When I'm watching just about anything, I'm pretty anal about wanting to hear everything that is going on, and I get really pissed at people who talk while I'm watching (especially if it's a movie I've never seen before). However for Elf I think that wouldn't really be the case. Odd... 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Well, I wasn't at school today because I was sick. I'm assuming the world got along just fine without me, though. It's odd, I am  very  rarely sick on a school day, so it was strange to think that I was missing classes. I just hope that the stuff I missed won't be too hard to make up... 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I guess this is one easy way for me to announce this, although I'll mention it around school as well. Since my birthday is on the 16th, and that is a Sunday, I am going to have my party on the 15th instead. Everyone who is able to come, should. It will be at my dad's house, probably starting around 6 or so. Things are very unorganized, as always, so we'll probably just hang out and watch movies and stuff. Also, if anyone has any requests or suggestions about movies, feel free to mention them and I'll take them under consideration. Oh, and if you could tell me you're coming, that would be nice too.  On a similar vein: presents. I'm guessing some of you want to know what to get me. This is a very good question, and not one easily answered. CDs are always good. I have many, many requests on my  urlLink Amazon Wish List .  urlLink Emotion Eric  or  urlLink H*R  shirts are also excellent, if of the cool variety. Anything with StrongBad or Trogdor would be excellent for H*R (including hoodies, etc.), and any of the Emotion Eric shirts are cool. I think Jonathan may have dibs on one of the shirts, but I forget which one so he'll have to tell people if he reads this and isn't too busy to leave a comment... and if he's actually getting me a shirt like he said he would.  I think that's everything. I could be wrong, though... 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Well, I just turned in my MIT application about an hour ago. Let the true nerves begin! Of course, they're not gonna  really  kick in until around December 5th, since that's about a week before I'll find out what their decision is. Oi. 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Furikuriban pictures are up! There certainly are a lot of them, though. I guess that's what I get for handing my camera around... lots of different perspectives on the subject. Gotta love it. Have fun... please. It took me hours to get all of the pictures put together. 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       So I just added a bunch of pictures from many years ago, on my trip to Chile. Admittedly, my disclaimer on the link is rather long, but if you just charge right in you might be surpised - both by the format, and by the suckiness of some (dare I say many?) of the pictures...  Anyway... yeah. I hope you all had happy holidays. 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I don't know how I survive Christmas each year.  I only started going out to shop today. I started at 5pm. I finished at 6pm, and that included going to the bank and getting gas.   How do I do this? , you might ask. It's simple, really. I only need to buy presents for 5 or 6 people each year, because I'm too lazy/horrible/don't think ahead enough to get presents for most of my friends. Also, my oldest sister Allyson is the organized one, and knows I "hate" to shop (I don't actually hate it, but I let this story perpetuate because I never know what to get anyone), so I just give her money and she deals with stocking stuffers and presents for my father and my step-mom. And since each year I have to buy a present for one of my three siblings (we have a drawing so we don't have to buy for everyone each year... the same goes for my extended family... but I'm getting ahead of myself) and this year I drew Nick (my one and only brother), Victoria (my step-mom, his mom) knew I didn't know what to get him and ordered sunglasses for him online for me, so all I needed to do was give her money. As for my cousin Garrett (the person I drew in the extended family drawing), I asked him what he wanted and he requested a laser pointer, and I, being the stingy and realistic person that I am, remember that I, too, had gone through a laser pointer stage and still had one of my old ones in rather nice condition, and since a good laser pointer would be somewhat out of the family drawing price range, I could just get some new batteries for it and give it to him instead. Furthermore, my mom hardly ever wants anything that requires buying (for example, this year she wants Vanessa and me to make her cds with music that she "would be unhappy not to recognize when they're on the oldies station in 40 years" *sigh* (don't get me started...). So that just meant I had to go buy some blank cds with jewel cases, to be burned tomorrow. Oh, and while I was there I picked up Shannon's present (yes, you know what it is, Shannon) since we always get presents for each other (feel special, dammit!).  And thus, I managed to survive Christmas once again with little or no shopping. Is it wrong of me to feel guilty for this? I think the hardest part was finding the right kind of batteries for the laser pointer. I think I cheated Christmas. 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Hopefully the final update in the MIT admissions adventure...  Today I finally got the "thick envelope" in the mail, but something I read in the letter amused me enough to post about it here:  "I also expect you to get right back to work and finish up the year with top grades, since we don't admit slackers to MIT and this offer of admission is contingent upon your completeing the school year with flying colors. (Because you've been admitted early, there will be many temptations throughout the rest of the year to keep you from your school work. Don't let that happen.)"  They don't shit around, do they? Oh well, I brought this upon myself, I guess. But bear this in mind, those of you who are telling me I don't have to work "ever again"! 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I got in!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  I think I'm still in a state of shock, though. Wow. MIT. Dude. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       On a more lighthearted note, for a number of years now I've only vaguely recalled the words to the "Nut Song". I remembered something along the lines of:  Dr. Pepper fixed him up and now we all drink 7Up , but no one could remember what in the world I was talking about. Then, a few days ago I realized how horribly stupid I had been being, and just Googled it. Thus, to celebrate my discovery, I thought I would share the words to it with you all (they are pasted from the first site I found them on, so excuse the odd rendition of how to spell the "clicky noise").   The Nut Song   I'm a little acorn brown,  Lying on the cold, cold ground  Everybody steps on me  That is why I'm cracked you see  CHO: I'm a nut tch tch (sort of a clicky noise) I'm a nut tch tch I'm a nut I'm a nut I'm a nut tch tch  I can sing and I can dance  I wear ruffles on my...  sorry, boys, guess again  I wear ruffles on my dress  Called myself on the telephone Just to see if I was home With myself I made a date Had to be there by half past eight.  Took myself to the movie show  Sat myself in the very first row  Wrapped my arms around my waist  When I got fresh I slapped my face   Grandpa's beard is long & gray, Growing grayer day by day, Grandma eats it in her sleep Says it tastes like shredded wheat,  Coca cola came to town  Pepsi cola shot'em down  Dr. Pepper fixed him up  Now we all drink 7up   Seven up got the flu  Now we all drink Mt. Dew  Mt. Dew went up the mountain  Now we all drink from a fountain.  
    
    
</post>

<date>17,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       No word again today. By this point, I think I'm more worried that they somehow didn't get my application (even though I did it online) than that I didn't get in. I know, I know, it takes time for things to be sent across the country, but still! Sheesh... 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       No news again today. Sorry to disappoint. :-( 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Right, since Max seems to think he'll have a heart attack if he doesn't have an update about MIT from me every afternoon: I still don't know yet. I certainly hope I'll find out tomorrow, though. I think that's a reasonable guess, right? 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Okay, today I heard a statistic that  blew my mind . Stanford accepts ~800 early applicants each year, and this year  5 percent  of all of the applicants they accepted early were from Palo Alto.  5 PERCENT!!!!  That means that for every 20 students accepted early, 1 of them is from within a few miles of campus! That's fucking insane!!  Oh, and I think 13 of them are from Paly. Possibly more. I'm not sure who exactly is on that list. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       The latest news on MIT (since everyone seems to be asking): they sent out the letters  today , so who knows when they'll show up? Soon, I hope. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Right. For those of you who are wondering, I still haven't heard from MIT yet. To repeat the familiar refrain, "maybe tomorrow?".  *sigh* 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Woo! My bookmarks are back!!! Thank god for my father. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       In case any of you are wondering, I haven't found out about MIT yet. Nothing came in the mail. Maybe they're shipping today and I'll find out tomorrow? If not tomorrow, hopefully by Monday.  You know, it's odd. I'm almost feeling calm about this. I'm sure it's only temporary, though. As soon as it's time for the mail tomorrow, I'll be climbing out of my skin. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Re: Colleges  "Is anyone else intimidated? Because I'm just expecting thin slips of paper with the words "no way" written in crayon." 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       You know what sucks? When your half-broken iPod (which you didn't realize was broken) wipes out all of your bookmarks and a bunch of your history when you plug it into your computer and makes your music program wonky as well. I don't think I can stress enough how much this sucks. It really really really really really really really really really really really really really really really really really really really really really really really really really really really really really really really really really really really really really really sucks. 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I just added a few more pictures to the school pics from November page, if anyone cares. 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Now, you all know I'm not the most...emotional person in the world. I mean, I don't cry easily, or anything like that. I think I've only cried at a movie once in my life, that I can recall. Or, more than one tear, maybe. Anyway, I know some of you (but certainly not all of you) know that I read a lot of stories online. It's how I waste an extremely large percentage of my time. Many of the stories are pretty crappy, since people write crap pretty easily, but there are a number of exceptionally good authors out there. Anyway, there's this one story that I read about a year ago, maybe a year and a half ago, and I just remember it being really good and really sad. I just re-read it again tonight, and my memory just didn't do it justice. I literally had tears streaming down my face for about 5 minutes. This  never happens .  I don't know why I felt the need to share that. 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Until tonight, I hadn't seen my nephew, Dwayne, for a few days. I think the last time I saw him was Monday or Tuesday, and since then I swear to god he's learned to speak in sentences. It's crazy. I mean, he could speak before, and he had a few phrases down ("auntie's car", "bye bye, dada", etc.), but tonight when I saw him he was jabbering away, "Bella has my ball", "Let's look at the pictures", "That's auntie's", "Bella is eating crackers". It was pretty mind-blowing. I mean, he's still talking in baby-talk, so you have to look past the lack of r's and s's and whatnot, but the sentences are definitely there.  It's crazy. *sniff* They grow up so fast. I can't wait until we can have actual conversations! Of course, that means we'll be getting into the "why?" stage... 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       So  urlLink I heard today  that a man in Germany posted a request online for a willing volunteer of a strong, able-bodied man to be cooked and eaten by him. Not only is this disgusting, but so is the fact that someone actually volunteered to do this. And it gets worse! Before the victim was killed, they both agreed to cut off part of his body, which they ate  together!    And I think the only reason they caught this guy was because he just posted another request online, since the first time was probably around March. He even videotaped it!  *shudder* 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Okay, this is a question for those of you who drive (or maybe just those of you who think). When you are driving and you want to turn left, but there are two left turn lanes, which do you prefer to go into? Because I have observed a strange phenomenon that makes me think that most drivers are complete idiots. There is a left turn such as I described that I take every day on my way home from school, and  every day , there are more cars in the rightmost left turn lane, and if a new car is just arriving, it is much more likely to go to the right lane rather than the left, even if there are more cars in the right lane. Now, this might make some sort of sense if the right lane were inherently faster, but it's  not . In fact, cars in the left lane have to travel less distance, and so actually go faster than the right lane, so why does this happen?  Any thoughts? 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Today in Sociology, which is (somewhat surprisingly) turning out to be one of my favorite classes, we were discussing social classes in America. Have you noticed how the  large  majority of people here in the United States refer to themselves as "middle class"? It's crazy.  But I digress. The real reason I'm here is to talk about me (sort of). We just finished watching this really interesting video about social classes, and the last part of it was about a high school in Austin, Texas, where the different social groups were very clearly delineated. The obvious parallel was that this high school was much like Paly, which people had already pointed out. However, that is always been something that has confused me about our school (and high school in general, I guess). Cliques. I just don't see them as being as all-powerful as they are always portrayed as being in high school. I mean, whenever people ask me what social groups there are at Paly, I am basically just like, "Um... well, there are the... people. And they... hang out, I guess." In other words, I don't really feel that our high school is entirely broken down into independent groups that function separately from each other. I mean, sure there are groups that tend to be a bit isolated and unwelcoming to outsiders (the people on the benches or by the Student Center being the main ones), but overall I don't really feel that I could pick a person and tell you specifically what "clique" they are a member of.  Anyway, I mentioned this to Mrs. Soutter (my teacher) while we were having group discussions, and she proceeded to give me what I feel is one of the better compliments I've ever received. She said (something along the lines of) that because I was such an understanding person, I was friends with people from all possible social groups and I did not view people through the lens of their social statuses. While that doesn't really sound like much when I put it here, the way she said it at the time made me feel really... good. I wish I could remember exactly how she phrased it. It made me feel all warm and fuzzy inside.  I just hope it doesn't go to my head... 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Well, since you said please... pictures from the party are now up. Enjoy. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Rabbit. Rabbit. Rabbit. 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Okay, here's a story, with some details withheld to help defend against my own embarrassment, because I know some of you know to whom I am referring (well you don't know in the sense that you know who I'm talking about, but you do actually know them... I'm just gonna stop talking here and get on with the story. You know what I'm trying to say... right?).  So there is this person who we'll call X, for lack of a singular gender-neutral pronoun. I greatly admire X. I think that X is intelligent, funny, nice, and cool. However, I don't have any real excuses to talk to X, so when I see X online, I know that if I were to try to talk to X our conversation would be pointless, and pointless conversations online drive  me  bonkers, and I do not want to inflict that upon X, in fear of making X dislike me (or like me less, possibly... hard to tell). (Wasn't that a lovely long sentence? ...but I digress. More.) However, today I was discussing my great admiration for X with some other people who I knew admired X as well (long story...) and they said that I should just tell X how I feel, not in the "tell him you like him!" sense... especially considering we don't even know if X is a boy, and we  do  know that I don't have a crush on X. This is strictly in the "I really admire you and think you are amazingly cool. I just wish I had more things to talk to you about. Now that I am done completely embarrassing myself, I'm gonna shut up now." At least, that was how I pictured the conversation going. So anyway, when I got home tonight, I got online and saw that X was signed on! So I gathered my courage, and initiated contact... but it turns out they weren't actually there! And now the longer I wait to do this, the more I think I'm going to lose my courage...  Anyway, there was no real point to this story. I just felt the need to share this potentially horribly embarrassing story with you all... 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I love scrimmaging against  urlLink Prospect .  I mean, they're good enough that it's not embarrassing that we're practicing against them, but they're bad enough that I was relaxed the entire time, and kicked some serious ass. Man, that's just... great. It leaves you in a wonderful mood, too. Overall today was just... great. I don't even know why. I mean, there was that, and the fact that Hanmer's Classics class was a hoot (he intro'd the Don Quixote unit with a lovely dress-up-as-Quixote-and-go-to-T&C-thing, which was funny), but other than that, it seems like any other day. I seem to be having a lot of good days, recently. Odd, considering how much work I still have to do...  *shrug* Who am I to look a gift horse in the mouth? 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I aspire to being able to wear  urlLink this shirt  someday. 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Oh, right. I need ideas for my senior profile. Help! 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So today I found out all of the grades I got for last semester for all of the classes that I was most worried about, and I did much, much better than I expected. So now I only have a B in chem (which was what I was *really* hoping for, but thought was a lost cause), and A's in everything else (in some form or other...also an achievement I wasn't too sure about in calc...).  Oh, and the two classes I picked up for the semester (both English) have really chill teachers, so I think that they shouldn't be too hard to deal with. Yay! Now if I could just get rid of the occasional obnoxious person in those classes... but then life wouldn't be adventurous at all, now would it?  Overall, I'd say that this day is a very good one. :-D 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This is the best day EVER. More details after school... 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I love it when my friends realize that one of my favorite shows is cool. This makes me very happy. 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, I'm now officially a second-semester senior. I don't think it's quite sunk in yet. Well, that or I realize that I'm still going to have a sizeable chunk of work left to do, so I'm not as excited as I should be... but still! Only a few months left until No More High School! I think that's good news.  Of course, I'm still not sure of the state of my first semester grades... we'll just have to wait and see, I guess... :/  On a more positive note, I got my Mock Trial sweatshirt today (finally)! It's pretty cool, although Christina was right when she said that they screwed them up. The quote on the back of it is on the lower back, so it looks rather odd... But such is life.  Hmm... I feel like I had more to say than this, but I'm drawing a blank now. Maybe I'll be back later. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I like tea. It's wonderful, especially when your sleeping schedule has gotten mysteriously shifted around, so you are exhausted all afternoon, and then perk up just in time to *not* go to bed at a reasonable hour.  But the tea is still yummy and caffeinated. Isn't that all that matters? 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So tonight instead of studying for my CS final, I went to see my Aunt and Uncle play at a small venue in San Jose with a bunch of my other family. It was a lot of fun (I finally got to meet my cousin Dan's girlfriend, who seemed cool), although it was rather odd hearing all of these songs that I usually only hear on CDs (and can therefore sing along with them)  live . Still fun, though.   Oh, and Margaret Cho has a  urlLink blog . Who knew? 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I spent all weekend cramming for my chem final tomorrow morning. I think I spent a total of *starts counting, grabs head in pain, and stops* uh... maybe 20 hours studying this weekend. Somewhere thereabouts, at least. However, I'm not sure if I feel I know any more chemistry than I did when I started. I  do  know, however, that my brain is starting to drain out through my ears.  "Fire bad. Tree pretty." 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So I went to see the Harlem Globetrotters with a handful of cousins, aunts, uncles, and a grandma. It was definitely an... experience. Also, it was rather blatantly a show, rather than a basketball game. I mean, I could even tell that the other team was one that went around with the Globetrotters and were the "other team". That, and the fact that they kept randomly stopping the game to do things with audience members... well, it was obviously a show. But I had fun, I guess. Some of the stuff they did was pretty funny. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Okay, I've come to a conclusion. Senior year is harder than junior year, I don't care what anyone says. Or at least, I know it's true for me. Junior year is just a lot of work, but it's all doable. One might even call it busywork, but it's not quite tedious enough for that. Senior year, on the other hand, has fewer classes, I admit. However, the classes that you do have that are hard are  hard . I mean, I only have 2 hard classes, but they're insanely difficult. Between AP Chem and BC Calc, I have more tests than I can make myself study for, more things to memorize than I could even if I were  able  to memorize stuff, and worse grades than any of my classes before. Ever. Well, more chemistry than calculus. So really this rant is mainly about chemistry, but calculus is included too because it's fucking hard and I get fucking confused too easily. This made so much sense last year. Hell, when we did the  same material  last year, it made sense, and when we did it this year, it didn't.  In summary, lots of work sucks, but getting demoralized because you can't do the work you have been given is 10 times worse. At least. 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       You know what I love? The fact that, not only is Little Nixa here, but she's here  early . w00t! 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Alright, the iPod is officically named "Little Nixa". I'm sure most (if not all) of you won't understand the reference, but in my mind obscure references are the only acceptable kind. However, if you  do  know what this is a reference to, 20 CoolPoints(tm) for you! 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       You know what sucks? Getting the flu. Today I barely moved from my bed for 24 hours, and I'm about to head back to bed again soon. blech. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Okay, okay. Hamletday pictures are finally up. However, before you go look at them you have to respond to my previous post, okay? Pretty please? I mean, I stayed up until after 2 in the morning on a school night getting these all together for you guys!  Oh, and while we're on the subject of pictures, do you guys want the bigger ones to be, well, bigger? I'm not sure why I chose to make them all 3x2, but it's not an issue for me if you want them bigger. At least that way they'd be better quality. As it is, I think they start out at at least 20 inches across or so, so it's not like they lack resolution...  *stumbles off to bed* 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Alright, I want everyone's opinions on this. I'm gonna get a new iPod with Christmas money (not the new mini iPods - a real one), but they're doing free engravings on the backs of them right now, so I thought it'd be fun to not only give it a name, but a cool one that I could engrave on the back of it. I was thinking something unique, rather than a normal everyday name, since if it were "Bob" or something, people might think it belonged to some guy named Bob instead of me (can't have that!).  Any thoughts? 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, I for one had fun at  urlLink Hamletday , even if a few of us did cop out and leave to go to Happy Donuts during the last half of Branagh's Hamlet. Of course, that was fun, too, so overall I'd say the evening was a success.  Oh, and I think the general consensus was that Hawke's Hamlet was the most fun to watch (and boy was it ever!) and Scott's Hamlet was the best for a "realistic" interpretation of it (or something along those lines... non-interpretational, more like), although I'm sure that some people would beg to differ.  I'll get the pictures up sometime tomorrow, probably. Not very many of them, though, since we were watching the movies for the most part, and I was afraid that if I took pictures during a movie, Jonathan would bite my head off, so... yeah. Pictures soon. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Arrogant people piss me off. I think this may be a problem in the future.   Oh, right. And I hope you all had a wonderful New Years. No, seriously. 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       And it's now 5-0, and we're onto semi-finals. No clue who's going up yet, though, or who we're against, but that's okay. We did well. Even if it was another  really  close match... 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So you know how I said we did well last night in Mock Trial? It turns out we did better than I expected! I thought we had lost by a small margin (which was good, because it was the team who won in our county last year), but it turns out that we actually  won  by a small margin, so we're one of the few teams in the county that is 4-0! It's very exciting... 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I realized something today that kind of surprised me. It's been a bit floody at school, what with this storm and all, and so the traditional puddles that fill half the parking lot (especially the one by the entrance to Town and Country) and the wooden things that they put between buildings so that we don't have to walk through 4 inches of water to get to our classes are there. Anyway, today I realized that I actually  like  having those things up. I mean, it's a pain in the ass to have to deal with, but for some reason a flooded Paly seems like Paly at its most... Paly-est. I can't even describe it, except that... I love it. I'm horribly tired right now, so it's hard to explain, but does anyone else know what I'm talking about? For some reason Paly when it is all flooded is what I feel I'm going to think back on when I think of high school, which is odd because it doesn't happen all too often...  Anyway, I'm tired. We did amazingly well in Mock Trial tonight, and now I'm fucking exhausted.   Oh, wait! Another side story before I go. One of the puddles on campus today was  steaming  and  boiling , I kid you not. It was right by the tree in front of the art classroom (by the glass blowing), and I think it was actually doing it all day. Someone said that they noticed it before school, and it was still going strong at lunch. As far as I know, no one knows what caused it, except I heard a rumor that Mr. Canmer dumped something there that was making it do that. Of course, that doesn't really make  any  sense at all, so who knows what was going on? All I know is that it was  fucking insane  to have a puddle boiling on a rainy, stormy day  while  it was raining. That's just crazy... 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Wee! Farscape season 1, here I come! Well, sort of... I have it, which is why I'm gleeful, but I can't really watch it yet, because I'm insanely busy all this week... man, I can't wait for this week to be over! Please, god, I'm almost done with mock trial, and then maybe I can actually  relax  a bit! 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       For some reason I feel very emotionally battered today, and I can't figure out why. It's very odd... 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm sorry, I couldn't resist...       Your future occupation by meteoric      Your name           Your future occupation    Ruler of the World      Yearly income    $731,758      Hours per week you work    49      Education    Up to 4 years of college             Created with  urlLink   quill18  's  urlLink  MemeGen 2.0  !      
    
    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Want to know how I spent my morning? Complimenting random people downtown. Yes, that's right, that was the  only  reason I was there. Well, technically I got some food while I was out, but that's beside the point...  So for Mr. Hanmer's World Classics class, we had this project that we had to do called "Chivalry is Not Dead". For this project, we had to go out and do some random chivalrous act - planned or otherwise - and write about society's reaction to it, as well as our own. So this morning Shannon, Sandy, and I went downtown and just walked around complimenting people. For the most part, no one really had a very strong reaction, but there was this little old lady standing outside of Longs holding a few flowers, which I duly complemented her on. She said that she had gotten them from a "public corner" (whatever the hell that is), and gave them to me. Being most pleased with my new flowers, I later encouraged Sandy to give them to  another  little old lady who we saw, who was sitting alone at a table, reading the newspaper. She seemed rather pleased with the flowers as well, so overall I felt that our adventure was a success. 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Will someone please explain what an RSS feed is to me, so that I can get one (since it seems to be a Good Thing...)? 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       No  way!  Did anyone else know that Mercedes McNab, who plays Harmony Kendall (yes, Eric, that's her last name) on Buffy, was also the girlscout in   urlLink The Addams Family   and Amanda in   urlLink Addams Family Values  ?  That just blows my mind. I mean, it's  Harmony!     ps. Yes, I do realize that some of my posts of late have been rather Buffy-cetric. Blame Eric; it's entirely his fault. 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Doppelgangland rocks. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I've decided that my sister is dead. Or she hates me. Or both. I haven't heard from her in  ages , so it must be one of those, right?  And yes, Vanessa, this is a test. Where the hell are you, and do you still read my blog? 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So the weather recently has been kind of perfect actually. It's been sunny (exceedingly so), but not hot, so I could wear "the sexy jacket" (so named because it makes  whoever  wears it "sexier" according to all of my friends) and my sunglasses. Also, I dumped most of my books out into my car at lunch, and so I was wearing my backpack like a messenger bag instead of by its backpack straps, which I can only do when it's emptier than usual. Anyway, while I was walking around like this, I had  three  teachers, all of whom know me well, comment on the fact that I looked "relaxed" or "like a college student" within about 30 minutes of each other. It was kind of amusing. Also, only teachers commented on this, not students.  I'm not sure if it means anything, though I did find it interesing. 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink This  amused me. 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       You know, I'm not sure if Mr. Hanmer's teaching style has changed since I was a Freshman or if it's just because I've had more experience in different English classes, but I'm really not enjoying his class this time around. I mean, I feel like he has his opinions about the book and the characters, and while he seems to encourage people's opinions on subjects, he only agrees with certain ones (even if he doesn't say anything... this is just a feeling I get). Also, he keeps on rambling on about how the "book reads you", which I understand, but he keeps saying it after  I  point anything out, which is a bit annoying after a while. Especially since I feel like he's saying that because he doesn't agree with me, even if other people express similar opinions.  Also, he really loves to insult math and science. I understand that he's an English teacher, so he doesn't necessarily excel at them, but does that mean that he has to insult them at every turn? I don't insult English just because it isn't my favorite subject!  I'm not even sure if what I just said makes it sound like how I feel things are going, but it really is starting to irk me... and it's only been like 2 weeks. I mean, there are good things about that class, but still... Grr.   Oh, and oddly enough, I had quite a nice conversation with Dr. Nick (of all people) today in the MRC. It was  kind of random, but she was very reassuring of the fact that it's not just the students who are afraid of Mrs. Lawrence... I don't know, there was more to it than that. Anyway, it was strangely nice talking with her. Even if she was being he usual, extremely talkative self... 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       What idiot made up the rumor that second semester senior year was easier? 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Success! I finally have proof! Just a few short hours ago, Eric said to me, "You're not Jewish."  I rest my case. 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So, generally I have gotten remarkably respectable grades over the years, with the exception of Spanish, which still wasn't too bad. My parents have always left me to my devices and been proud of me, etc. This year I pulled off respectable grades by the skin of my teeth (which I had already mentioned), so I was very pleased with myself. However, my grades arrived today and my dad asked, "what did you do to get a B- in chem?", and by that he meant, "what went wrong?" I'm not sure why I was so put out by that. I mean, that class is  hard , and he was basically wondering what I did wrong to get an A.  I guess I've just been taking my parents' chillness about grades for granted until now, because I've always gotten good ones. Of course, I could just be seriously over reacting and over analyzing what he said, because I'm very, very, very tired. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       My dad just got a new G5. *drools* 
    
    
</post>

<date>31,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm leaving on Friday to go to England over Spring Break to visit my sister (excitement!), and I realized today that I didn't want to lug all of my CDs around like I used to have to, because I didn't  need  to. Thanks to the glory of a 40GB iPod, I can carry all of my music in a very small space. Of course, first I needed to get all of my music onto my computer. I have all of these CDs sitting around that I had never really bothered to rip before, since I usually had some of the songs on my computer already, or I was too lazy, or I just forgot. So all evening I've been sitting in front of my computer and going through my CDs and ripping the ones that I hadn't ripped already. It's actually rather a lot of work but definitely worth it, I think.  Man, I had forgotten how good some of this stuff was. 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I think I need to apologize to Kelly, Claudia, and Eric for my rather angsy bit in the car last night. I was really pulling out all of the clichés, wasn't I? It was kind of amusing, in a horrifying sort of way... Oh my god, I'm an angsy teenager, with no real angst to talk about, or the ability to verbalize what the hell I'm talking about! 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Look! Fame and fortune for in Focus! Well, some amused Brits, at least.   urlLink http://www.thedarknessrock.com/guestbook/viewtopic.php?t=264  
    
    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       You know what I hate? The fact that my internal clock seems to be broken. I keep on getting really tired during the mid-afternoon and early evening (and I mean  really tired ), and then around 9:30 or so I'll catch my second wind so I can actually do all the homework I'd been working on all afternoon. Not only is it annoying, but it's a serious waste of time! 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm definitely tutoring three separate people in chemistry today.  Three!  Good thing this is for extra credit, or I'd think I was on crack or something... Well, two down and one to go. Hopefully now I'll actually know the chemistry when they ask about it... 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ha! I now have the script of  Angels in America  as well! *cackles gleefully* 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Oh, right, I made a wonderful discovery this week: there is a drink that I like at Starbucks, and it has  coffee  in it! Well, not much, but it's still there (it's the White Chocolate Mocha). Now I finally have something to get when we go to starbucks, instead of just standing there awkwardly saying "I don't like coffee". I feel as though I've finally joined civilization!  Oh, and my brother is home for an indeterminate amount of time. He banged up his knee, and so he's here to have Stanford people look at it. :-( Of course, being the spoiled brat that I am, I'm bothered by the fact that it's screwing with  my  scheduling habits (which is in part, I think, because he doesn't seem to be in any pain to speak of). So we'll see how that plays out... 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Okay, so I couldn't resist doing one of these "Song Memes" to which  urlLink MacKenzie  introduced me (and many other people):  The Idea and The Rules      * You have a name.      * Spell your name out with song titles.      * Use each artist only once.      * Use each song only once.      * This is pretty damn simple, people.      * Once again, make your mix under 80 minutes for a bonus. Depending on the length of your name, 160.      * For a supermegaextra bonus, use only song titles that include names.      * Have fun.   So this is mine (there's a list without my comments at the bottom if you want to jump straight there):  1. Every Morning - Sugar Ray (3:45)  This was the first music video I can ever remember watching, and the first song I heard on the radio where I knew all of the words.  2. Let Me In - Save Ferris (6:14)  This song just rocks. It's that simple. It's beautiful. Definitely my favorite Save Ferris song (10 Things notwithstanding).  3. I Know - Fiona Apple (4:55)  I subconciously picked up an affinity for many artists because of my sister, who has excellent taste in music (hi, Vanessa). Fiona Apple was one of them. She would play her Fiona Apple CDs, and I would hear them as I was going to sleep, and years later when I started listening to music myself (I was, quite sadly, rather a late bloomer in that department, but we'll get to that later) I rediscovered them while having the advantage that I already loved them, so I still have a soft spot for Fiona Apple, among others.  4. Zombie - Cranberries (5:06)  My favorite Cranberries song might be Dreams (it's debatable), but this song is quite excellent as well. Besides, how many songs do  you  know that start with a Z?  5. Almost Blue - Gwen Stefani (2:59)  This is the first song I heard that made me realize just how amazing Gwen Stefani's voice is. No Doubt is an amazing group, but sometimes I feel that her voice isn't stressed as much as it could be because of all the other things happening in their songs (not to say that she doesn't use her voice well in those, but you get distracted from the richness of it). Also, I think I downloaded this well before I thought to download any of No Doubt's songs, and it has such a different feel to it that it's always stuck out in my mind as being  just  Gwen.  6. Beautiful - Christina Aguilera (3:58)  This is the song that made me respect Christina Aguilera. While I enjoyed Genie in a Bottle, I had tried to avoid the pop scene as much as possible for quite a few years, but when I heard this I realized I was being silly for doing so on principle. She also has a  gorgeous  voice (I don't think I could stress that enough), and this song is beautiful both in the way it sounds, and what it says. Rock on, Christina.  7. Everything in its Right Place - Radiohead (4:09)  This song is cool. Radiohead is a cool band. There were quite a number of their songs I could have chosen for this mix, but I chose this one mainly for its strategic value (it took me a long time to figure out which songs I wanted to choose by which artist to make things fit as nicely as I could), although it's also here in its own right.  8. Thank You - Alanis Morissette (4:18)  Alanis Morissette has good music. This is one of her good songs, and one that even I picked up on when I wasn't listening to any music in particular. I think I might have Vanessa to thank for that again, but I'm not sure. Either way, I've always liked Alanis Morissette, as well as this song.  9. Hailie's Song - Eminem (5:23)  I love this song. I do. I mean, there are other Eminem songs that I like as well, but he's actually  singing  here! And it's a good song. What more need be said?   10. Gangsta's Paradise - Coolio (4:01)  Another song from my early childhood. I'm thinking my brother Nick is to thank for this one, but I could be wrong. This song is excellent. It crosses a number of genres, in my opinion, and it never really gets old. I've liked it as long as I can remember (although sticking this in here does make me wish that I had a "W" in my name, for Waterfalls by TLC, but that's another matter...).  11. Like The Rose - B*Witched (3:56)  I think it was the summer after sixth grade that I first began entering the music world in my own right. However, I kind of pushed myself into it and so I didn't have a chance to get my bearings before I bought 3 or 4 CDs. While most of them were only okay, or blatantly sucky, one of the ones I got was B*Witched's self-named first CD, and dammit I liked it! I still do, actually. Mock me if you will, but I'll stand by it. Anyway, this was my favorite song on that CD, and I'm still partial to it. I can still remember sitting in the front seat of my mom's rental car up in Maine listening to this song over and over as we drove to my grandmother's beachhouse with Mallory and Shannon. Good times.  12. Out Of My Head - Fastball (2:32)  This is a fun song. I'm not sure when I first heard it, or when I downloaded it, but it's along the same lines of some of the first songs that I ever downloaded on my computer ("The Way" by Fastball was definitely up there in the first 5 or so), which I listened to over and over until I had enough music to not run through all of them in an hour or two.  13. Runaround - Blues Traveler (4:39)  Another song that is just generally fun. I'm not really sure what else I can say about it.  14. I Fought The Law - Green Day (2:42)  This is a pretty new song, as far as I know. I think Max was the one who introduced me to it, and I'm a fan. I like it more than the original, even. Those boys know how to harmonize, which is always a good way to make me a fan (see: B*Witched, Blink 182 (below), and many others for more examples of this).  15. Aliens Exist - Blink 182 (3:13)  I have one Blink 182 CD (Enema of the State), and while this song was never one of their singles, I think it was my favorite on it. It's a fun idea, and they also do a really nice with harmonizing on a few of the songs that just make me happy every time I hear them. What can I say? I'm a sucker for harmonizing.   16. Graceland - Paul Simon (4:51)  Graceland was a CD that my mother has played for as long as I can remember (until my sister stole the CD and took it to school, that is *glares*). It's an amazing CD in general, and this song rocks. If you've never heard this CD, you're a heathen and you should go remedy this. Go!  17. Undenied - Portishead (4:24)  A calmer song than many of the ones just preceding it, but Portishead is such a cool group that there was no way in hell I couldn't include them. This song rocks. They rock. I remember Vanessa freaking out about the fact that we were starting to listen to the same music and saying "Just don't listen to Portishead when I'm around!" I certainly hope she blushes when she reads this and remembers that phase. Of course, I would be posessive of Portishead too, so...   18. Anna Begins -  Counting Crows (4:31)  Counting Crows is one of my favorite bands, and this was one of their first songs that I loved. There are many more, of course, but I always liked this one. It's bittersweet, but excellent. I've always been a sucker for romantic, but sad things.  19. River Valley - Moxy Früvous (3:27)  This is another group that my mother introduced me to when I was very young. Moxy Früvous is a very cool band (right, Jonathan? You know you're glad I introduced you to them), and this is the very first song on my favorite CD of theirs, so in some ways it's what I first think of when I think of them. Since we used to play this CD so often, the songs have kind of melded into each other so that when I finish listening to one, I can already hear the next one on the CD start, even if it doesn't. It's still a little jarring to hear this song and not hear "Stuck in the 90s" after it.  20. It Wasn't Me - Shaggy (3:47)  This song is amusing as hell, but I think I have it on here because it makes me think of my brother Nick more than anything. Let's just say that sometimes I call him "Shaggy" because of this song, and leave it at that.  21. No Angel - Dido (3:55)  I love Dido. I really do. She has a beautiful voice, and lovely arrangements. Her first CD, No Angel, was always one that my sister and I could always agree upon listening to, which helped prevent many a world-war over the years.  22. Only Happy When it Rains - Garbage (3:56)  Garbage is a fun band. This is a fun song. What mix is hurt by tossing in a little Garbage?   23. Return Of The Phantom Stranger - Rob Zombie (4:31)  Every time I hear this song I can't help but just get into it. It's just... fun. I like.  24. El Tango De Roxanne - Jacek Koman and Ewan McGregor (4:43)  I've become somewhat obsessed with this song over the past few months since I first saw Moulin Rouge. The main song ("the Roxanne part", as I call it) is nice enough, but I just adore the background part by Ewan McGregor. I'm addicted to it.  25. I Shall Believe - Sheryl Crow (5:34)  This song is beautiful. I like Sheryn Crow's music, but this one has always stuck out as beautiful to me. And it's just so  heartbreaking  (we all know I'm a sucker for that. I seem to be a sucker for a lot of things). Of course, in part that's because of an outside association I have, but that's a different matter.  26. Dark Angel - Blue Rodeo and Sarah McLachlan (5:16)  Sarah McLachlan is another artist that I call "a favorite", and while this isn't one of her traditional songs, it's beautiful enough for me to use it for her. This is a nice calming song which is good for the end of a CD, in my opinion. Everyone we hear here (not that I really know much about Blue Rodeo except that they sing here) have beautiful voices, and use them wonderfully.    And (in true copying-MacKenzie fashion), here's the unannotated copy:  1. Every Morning - Sugar Ray (3:45) 2. Let Me In - Save Ferris (6:14) 3. I Know - Fiona Apple (4:55) 4. Zombie - Cranberries (5:06) 5. Almost Blue - Gwen Stefani (2:59) 6. Beautiful - Christina Aquilera (3:58) 7. Everything in its Right Place - Radiohead (4:09) 8. Thank You - Alanis Morissette (4:18) 9. Hailie's Song - Eminem (5:23)  10. Gangsta's Paradise - Coolio (4:01) 11. Like The Rose - B*Witched (3:56) 12. Out Of My Head - Fastball (2:32) 13. Runaround - Blues Traveler (4:39) 14. I Fought The Law - Green Day (2:42) 15. Aliens Exist - Blink 182 (3:13)  16. Graceland - Paul Simon (4:51) 17. Undenied - Portishead (4:24) 18. Anna Begins -  Counting Crows (4:31) 19. River Valley - Moxy Früvous (3:27) 20. It Wasn't Me - Shaggy (3:47) 21. No Angel - Dido (3:55) 22. Only Happy When it Rains - Garbage (3:56)  23. Return Of The Phantom Stranger - Rob Zombie (4:31) 24. El Tango De Roxanne - Jacek Koman and Ewan McGregor (4:43) 25. I Shall Believe - Sheryl Crow (5:34) 26. Dark Angel Blue Rodeo and Sarah McLachlan (5:16)  total run time: 1:50:45  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm insanely happy that some (many!) of my friends are home for Spring Break. This is what sucks about having friends older than you are: they're off at college and you're left alone. I mean, last night I was out with MacKenzie, Bun-Bun, Kelly,  and  Laura! We didn't even do anything in particular, but it was still a lot of fun just because I hadn't seen most of them in ages, and when they aren't here I do even less (the whole "no one to do things with" problem...).  It made me happy to see them. 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Tonight my mother and I watched   urlLink Iron Jawed Angels  , which we had taped a while ago on HBO. It was actually pretty good, notwithstanding some rather anachronistic actions from the leading ladies (even for forward thinkers of their time, it wasn't appropriate behavior for the early 1900s) and extremely modern musical choices.  'What is it about?' you ask? Well, it's telling the tale of the women's suffrage movement over the 6 or 7 years before the amendment was ratified. Hillary Swank was Alice Paul, Frances O'Connor was Lucy Burns, and Anjelica Houston was Carrie Chapman Catt (although I think my favorite was Julia Ormond as Inez Millholland).  *shrug* I feel like I should have more to say about it, but that's all I can think of at the moment. Oh, and last night we finished watching   urlLink Angels in America  . That was  fantastic . 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Some people at school have taken to calling me "ElizabethReid". It's a little odd, and I can trace it to its origin, but it also seems to be spreading. Like, last night when MacKenzie, Bun-Bun and I were at Tower, I ran into some people from school who I had never heard call me that before, and they did too. It was odd.  It's a good thing I don't mind it when people call me that, or I might be upset by this. I just think it's kind of funny.  Oh, and I think I have the RSS feed working now! 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Vintage shopping is fun. It's one of the few ways to go looking for clothes that I actually  enjoy .  My cousin Mike (who's 24) is visiting this weekend for a job interview, and today we went to San Francisco with some other relatives to see China Town and The Haight. I hadn't been to China Town in ages, and I don't think I'd ever been to the Haight before. It was definitely a blast. I got this really cool hat, and a worn-in but not worn-out Coca Cola T-shirt for a total of about $40. Not bad, I'd say. Especially considering the hat was new.  Anyway, I had fun. The hat kicks ass. I guess I'll wear it to school some now, but I'll be interested to see people's reactions to it... 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am now the proud ownder of my very own copy of Campell Scott's  Hamlet . Yay! 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Alright, so we lost last night, which wasn't the best thing we could have hoped for, but we still did an amazing job getting to the finals themselves, so I'm happy. Also, the scoring attorneys were people like the Public Defender and the Assistant DA and the head of the Bar Association. Intimidating much? 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Wahoo! Guess who's mock trial team is going to county finals? Mine is! That's right! We are now the  only  undefeated team in the county, and the team we're going against tomorrow night, we beat last Wednesday. w00t! 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It's Eric's fault. Everyone go take  urlLink this quiz  about me. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Alright, this is driving me mad: which of our friends (if any) says "cool beans"? And if it isn't one of us, who is it? I had to have picked it up from somewhere... 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Sorry 'bout the lack of updates. I'm in the middle of pre-AP hell. HELL! 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Alright, let's see if I can figure out anything to say about my trip. I warn you, this is probably going to be   long   and boring, since we all know I suck at leaving out silly details, but I'll do my best (that's a lie... I'm not even going to try. This is going to be an annoying level of detail... unless I get tired of typing it all out, of course). If you want to skip to the end, I'll add some general comments which might be a bit more interesting for most of you.  I flew from SFO to London, Heathrow on Friday night, which is almost exactly 10 hours. The plane was a little delayed, and left about about 7:30pm (or something... probably a bit later than that), so we got into Heathrow around midday or so (their time). I slept for maybe 5 or 6 hours, I think. It was actually a pretty nice plane. It had the personal video things, so there were about 5 movies playing on a continuous loop (most of them sucked, though). I watched  Once Upon a Time in Mexico  (cool, but confusing) and slept, until about the time we landed. After we got through customs and such, I strided purposefully across the airport to the section where my next flight (to Leeds, which is in the north, whereas London is in the south) would be, which was about half a mile away or something (seriously). Once I got there, I got into line to check into my next flight, until I realized that you couldn't check in until about 2 1/2 hours before the flight took off, and mine wasn't until 10 that night. I got out of line and wandered around a bit, until I found this place to get some food. I ordered a sandwich (more so that I could sit down than because I was hungry), and chilled for a few hours. The sandwich itself was actually pretty gross... After reading for a few hours, and trying to get some code to compile for my CS class (it wouldn't), it was finally late enough for me to check in to my flight. I headed back to the check-in area, only to discover that the flight had been cancelled due to "technical difficulties"! As it turned out, the catering truck that was getting the food on the plane had  crashed into it , which I guess you could call a technical difficulty... However, they had organized a deal with another company to fly us all to Manchester (kind of near Leeds), and then put us on a bus to Leeds airport. The next flight was only about 25 minutes later than my original one was, but the bus ride would take about an hour or an hour and a half. I dutifully called the person who was picking me up from Leeds to let him know about the time change, and then checked into my new flight. I then got some really gross Burger King (hard to imagine just how they could make such overly-processed food  worse , but they succeeded) and worked on my stupid calculus work, which I had dutifully brought with me (I had to take notes on everything we learned all year - about 13 chapters worth, so I figured when better than while I'm travelling around with 10 hour flights and 9 hour layovers?) until the plane boarded. I remember there were these really amazingly ugly green chairs in the waiting area outside of the gate. They were kind of a neon green and probably were installed in the early-70s, if the color was supposed to be in style. The only odd thing about the flight was that when we were landing, the plane got about 50 feet (maybe less) from the ground, and then went back up again! It was pretty weird, and the pilot came on and said something about there being something on the runway (who can really understand what they say over the speaker system anyway?), but then we landed for real a few minutes later and it was fine. Of course, by this point it was about 11 or so, and I had only gotten 5 or 6 hours of sleep the night before, so I was kind of tired... and my luggage wasn't there. It turns out that the kind people of British Airways  left it in Heathrow  because they wanted a little extra fuel because of the headwind (although I didn't know this at the time... all I knew was that I didn't have any clothes). I dutifully filled out the little form they gave me, and trundled onto the bus. When we arrived at Leeds, I called to tell Dennis (the one picking me up) that I had arrived, and he said he would be there in half an hour. I then sat outside in the late, cold, rainy weather until he showed up (no clue why I didn't wait  inside , except that I wasn't sure whether he was planning on parking or anything). He got there around 12:30, drove me home, and I went to bed and slept for 10 hours.  The next day (it's Sunday by this point), my luggage still hadn't shown up like they said it would. So I gave Dennis all of the relevant information they had given me, and he spent the day tracking it down (god bless that man...). I basically just lounged about the house and such most of the afternoon, and chilled with Alex, the 23 year old son of the family (and he helped me get that damn code to compile). That afternoon, Anne-Marie (the mother) got back from her trip to Cambridge and mothered me a bit (which I was fine with). She's always been very nice. She was my mom's roommate at Stanford oh so long ago, and she and her husband moved to England a long time ago, and have 2 kids, Jennifer and Alex. I was crashing with them for the weekend because my sister (who was the one I had intended on visiting) was actually off with her water polo team for the weekend partying at the Isle of Mann. Anyway, Anne-Marie gave me some clothes to wear until my luggage arrived the next morning (thank you, Dennis), and all was well. Oh, and Alex and I seem to have similar taste in music, which we discovered as we compared collections and traded back and forth a bit between our laptops. He even uses a Mac!  The next day my clothes had arrived, which was nice, and I walked into the main part of town (Ripon) with Anne-Marie and Alex to run some errand before Vanessa showed up mid-afternoonish. We had dinner, and then Alex took Vanessa and I to a local pub for this 'pub quiz' thing. We met some of his friends and had fun and such, and picked up some Chinese food to snack on when the pub closed at 11, and headed back to the house. All in all, a fun day.  Tuesday morning, Anne-Marie and Dennis actually headed here to California to deal with her mother, who's in a nursing home in Los Gatos. Alex was going to play host for Vanessa and I, and take us to Richard III's castle that was nearby so we could play tourists, but he remembered that he actually had to go to a wine tasting for his job (he's a bartender), so instead he dropped us off in York and so we wandered about there for the day. We went to this crazy museum in a vague attempt to be good tourists, but it was so random that we just made fun of it instead. It had stuff like the bones of an old Dodo bird in the same room as a random old Teddy Bear and a meteorite. It also went into great detail about the history of some old Abby (St. Mary's) and had some dinosaur bones to boot! Overall, just an odd museum... After looking at it for a bit, we went shopping in the shambles, which was fun. Then we had some tea ("high tea") before getting on a bus back to Ripon, which followed a circuitous route about the countryside (we were half afraid that we were never going to get to Ripon and would have to call Alex and tell him we were "in some field"). There were lots of sheep ("are there? are there sheep?"). That night we went to a 'real' pub, and then when it closed we went to where Alex works and he made us some cocktails. Dear lord, that was... a night of alcohol. My stomach still churns when I think of some of those drinks. Anyway, then we headed home and eventually got to bed...  The next day (Wednesday, I think) Vanessa and I headed to Sheffield to visit her new boyfriend, Tom, for the day. We took the train out there and met his mother and saw some baby pictures, before he frantically got us  out  of his house, and we wandered about the town. We played some team pool with Tom's friend Alex (miraculously, whatever team I was on won each time, although I didn't really help. I suck at pool.) and had some lunch before heading back to Tom's house to watch Mallrats. Tom's mother made us dinner (which was good), before Vanessa and I headed back to Ripon for the night. Tom seemed very nice (yes, Vanessa, that's all I can really think to say about him).  Thursday, we headed over to Birmingham to visit another old friend of ours (well, more our mom's, since they worked together, but she's nice) who lives in England. We got in the trains in the early afternoon, and got there around 6 or so (they were pretty slow). We went out and got some Chinese food for dinner, and spent the rest of the evening just chatting, which was also fun. We talked quite a bit about school systems and accents, actually. Interesting stuff...  Friday Vanessa and I took the train to Oxford and got in in early evening. We went out and had some really nice French food for dinner (my god, that was good stuff) and spent the rest of the evening chatting with one of her housemates, Dan. He and I got along fantastically, since we seemed to be rather similar in many of our tastes, etc.   Saturday I took a bus to Heathrow, and got on the plane and came home. I got in around 5ish, and got home around 6:30. I collapsed in bed around 8, and slept for 12 hours.   Overall, it was a fun trip, although I spent the majority of my time in places other than Oxford (which was where we thought I was going to be). My sister and I got along quite well, considering we're sisters, so that was nice. Also, the entire time I found myself very aware of my American accent (when we were in public), and was self-conscious enough to not speak much (odd, considering self-consciousness is not usually a problem for me...). Also, when I was speaking with people (Anne-Marie and I had quite a few interesting conversations) I was hyper-aware of my grammer, which seemed much worse than usual. I'm not sure what was going on there, but I definitely wasn't speaking very well...  A fun time was had in general. And now that I've avoided my homework for an hour or so longer, I should probably get to work on that. *groan* Is it college yet? 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Home again from foreign lands.  So... I'm back. Hi! *waves tiredly* What time is it? 7 pm? 3 am? Somewhere in between? Damned if I know. I think I'm probably hovering somewhere over the middle of the Atlantic time-wise.   Anyway, the trip was a lot of fun. I'll try to type up a real report of it later, but frankly I'm fucking tired right now. I just thought I'd let you all know I was alive or whatever. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, I'm heading off to the airport in an hour or so. I hope everyone else has (or has had) a fantastic spring break! 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I think that's kinda cool. It's not the  most  surprising thing in the world, since both my mom and sister are O- too, but my dad's not so there was a chance I wouldn't be. I'm glad I am, though. It's cool. :) 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       One: I got my cap and gown today. Excitement! Coolness, no?  Two: I put up some pictures from school, although more will be forthcoming. Feel free to peruse any or all of them at your leisure. 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I just went with some friends of mine on the swim team to donate blood to the Stanford Blood people (I forget their official name), and it was a surprisingly fun experience. There were about 8 or so of us, so it took a while for them to get to everyone (even though a few people couldn't do it because their iron level was too low), and while I didn't know some people there, and I was nervous, it was still cool. Once I finally got in there, it took them a while to find a good vein (I think I have my mother to thank for that... hers move around or something). Once they did actually find one they liked, it turned out it was "deceptively deep", and so it only took me about 4 minutes to give the blood, which is kind of fast, although not outrageously so. The process itself wasn't too painful, either. I think the mild stinging in my arm right now is probably the worst of it, and I didn't feel dizzy or lightheaded or anything after I gave. I seem to be a natural.  So now I get to wait a few weeks for them to mail me the thingy that lets me know what type blood I have, and hopefully go donate again in July when I get the chance. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I just put up the pictures from the get-together last night at Eric's house. There aren't too many, but I think a few are quite nice, personally (and I didn't even take most of them!). Speaking of which, I thought I'd just remind anyone who cares that if they want a higher-quality copy of any of these pictures for themselves, feel free to ask me. The pictures I have up here are about 1/6 the size of the originals, and thus they lost some detail, etc. 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Eric was just over and we were being bored on my computer, and so we (I) decided to look up all of the nicknames of Elizabeth (since it has a  lot ). We found  urlLink a page  with quite a few of them, although I think my personal favorites were definitely Elspeth (and a few variations thereof) and Erzsi. Sadly, however, all of them already seem to be taken as screen names, and that's no fun.  So, who wants to call me one of those now? 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, I'm working on making my blog more presentable and blog-like, aka: actually have titles for my posts, and use their nifty new comment system. I have the titles working, as you see, but at the moment I'm not in the mood to attack my template code without my father around to fix whatever I screw up, especially since we've already made a number of changes to it in the first place that I don't want screwed up (or else I would just change templates entirely... now there's a thought).  Also, I'm too lazy (unlike  urlLink some people ) to go back through all of my old posts to add titles, because frankly I don't think they're worth it. 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am so  frustrated  with my family right now; I cannot wait until college starts and I am on the opposite side of the country. 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I just got my Big Packet of Info from MIT with everything I need to deal with between now and who know's when. While I'm excited (college!), I'm also nervous, and not looking forward to all of this crap I have to deal with. And the decisions to make! Oh, god, the decisions!  Oh, and I can now recieve email on my cellphone (in theory, I admit I haven't actually tested it out yet), which is exciting. The address is myfirstname.cell@mylastname.org (actual address changed as to avoid the possibility of spam... but you're intelligent people, so you should be able to figure it out. If you can't, contact me and I'll explain it to you and mock you at the same time). 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       You know what sucks? When you have to write an essay, but you're in such the  wrong  frame of mind, that to get each sentence out is like slamming your brain against some metaphorical wall -- slamming it HARD. And if you don't slam it hard enough, it's not enough to get the sentence out, and you'll have to do it again. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I don't think of myself as someone who's good with "heart to hearts". I mean, what the hell are you supposed to say when someone's having enough trouble with something in his/her life to talk to you about it? Clearly there's no easy solution, because if there were then it wouldn't be a problem, and usually it's something that he/she is going to have to decide for him/herself. From what I can see, the most you can really do is listen to them, and try to help them organize their thoughts. I don't approve of trying to make up people's minds  for  them, so what else can you really do?  God, I suck at this. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I just spent the evening with a few of my cousins over at SBC Park, watching the Giants play the Red Sox. It was a total blast, and I think I am now officially a Red Sox fan (and not just because they won 14-9). There was a ridiculous number of home runs throughout the evening (6 or 7, I think), and for some reason the section where we were sitting had an inordinate number of Sox fans as well (our theory was that it was becuase all the Giants fans had season tickets and, as such, better seats). There was even a taste of Fenway park with fights erupting and an obnoxious man saying the same things over and over again! Now I'm determined to go see them play at Fenway, but I might take my big hulky cousin Mike to protect me.  Oh, and there are pictures forthcoming. I'm just uploading them now, though, so it may take a while. 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Book Meme, courtesy of Eleanor (who got it from Eric...)  *bold those you've read *italicize started-but-never-finished *underline those you own but haven't gotten to yet *add three of your own *post to your livejournal   1. The Lord of the Rings, JRR Tolkien 2. Pride and Prejudice, Jane Austen 3. His Dark Materials, Philip Pullman 4. The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy, Douglas Adams 5. Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire, JK Rowling 6. To Kill a Mockingbird, Harper Lee 7. Winnie the Pooh, AA Milne  8. 1984, George Orwell  9. The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, CS Lewis  10. Jane Eyre, Charlotte Bronte  11. Catch-22, Joseph Heller  (I was going to finish, but Vanessa needed it... it's a long story) 12. Wuthering Heights, Emily Bronte 13. Birdsong, Sebastian Faulks 14. Rebecca, Daphne du Maurier  15. The Catcher in the Rye, JD Salinger  16. The Wind in the Willows, Kenneth Grahame 17. Great Expectations, Charles Dickens  18. Little Women, Louisa May Alcott  19. Captain Corelli's Mandolin, Louis de Bernieres 20. War and Peace, Leo Tolstoy 21. Gone with the Wind, Margaret Mitchell  22. Harry Potter And The Sorcerer's (Philosopher's) Stone, JK Rowling 23. Harry Potter And The Chamber Of Secrets, JK Rowling 24. Harry Potter And The Prisoner Of Azkaban, JK Rowling 25. The Hobbit, JRR Tolkien  26. Tess Of The D'Urbervilles, Thomas Hardy 27. Middlemarch, George Eliot 28. A Prayer For Owen Meany, John Irving 29. The Grapes Of Wrath, John Steinbeck  30. Alice's Adventures In Wonderland, Lewis Carroll  31. The Story Of Tracy Beaker, Jacqueline Wilson 32. One Hundred Years Of Solitude, Gabriel Garcia Marquez 33. The Pillars Of The Earth, Ken Follett 34. David Copperfield, Charles Dickens  35. Charlie And The Chocolate Factory, Roald Dahl 36. Treasure Island, Robert Louis Stevenson  37. A Town Like Alice, Nevil Shute 38. Persuasion, Jane Austen 39. Dune, Frank Herbert  40. Emma, Jane Austen 41. Anne Of Green Gables, LM Montgomery  42. Watership Down, Richard Adams  43. The Great Gatsby, F Scott Fitzgerald 44. The Count Of Monte Cristo, Alexandre Dumas  45. Brideshead Revisited, Evelyn Waugh 46. Animal Farm, George Orwell 47. A Christmas Carol, Charles Dickens 48. Far From The Madding Crowd, Thomas Hardy 49. Goodnight Mister Tom, Michelle Magorian 50. The Shell Seekers, Rosamunde Pilcher 51. The Secret Garden, Frances Hodgson Burnett  52. Of Mice And Men, John Steinbec  53. The Stand, Stephen King 54. Anna Karenina, Leo Tolstoy 55. A Suitable Boy, Vikram Seth  56. The BFG, Roald Dahl  57. Swallows And Amazons, Arthur Ransome 58. Black Beauty, Anna Sewell 59. Artemis Fowl, Eoin Colfer 60. Crime And Punishment, Fyodor Dostoyevsky 61. Noughts And Crosses, Malorie Blackman 62. Memoirs Of A Geisha, Arthur Golden  63. A Tale Of Two Cities, Charles Dickens  64. The Thorn Birds, Colleen McCollough 65. Mort, Terry Pratchett 66. The Magic Faraway Tree, Enid Blyton 67. The Magus, John Fowles 68. Good Omens, Terry Pratchett and Neil Gaiman 69. Guards! Guards!, Terry Pratchett  70. Lord Of The Flies, William Golding  71. Perfume, Patrick Susskind 72. The Ragged Trousered Philanthropists, Robert Tressell 73. Night Watch, Terry Pratchett  74. Matilda, Roald Dahl  75. Bridget Jones's Diary, Helen Fielding 76. The Secret History, Donna Tartt 77. The Woman In White, Wilkie Collins 78. Ulysses, James Joyce 79. Bleak House, Charles Dickens 80. Double Act, Jacqueline Wilson  81. The Twits, Roald Dahl  82. I Capture The Castle, Dodie Smith 83. Holes, Louis Sachar 84. Gormenghast, Mervyn Peake 85. The God Of Small Things, Arundhati Roy 86. Vicky Angel, Jacqueline Wilson 87. Brave New World, Aldous Huxley 88. Cold Comfort Farm, Stella Gibbons 89. Magician, Raymond E Feist 90. On The Road, Jack Kerouac 91. The Godfather, Mario Puzo 92. The Clan Of The Cave Bear, Jean M Auel 93. The Colour Of Magic, Terry Pratchett 94. The Alchemist, Paulo Coelho 95. Katherine, Anya Seton 96. Kane And Abel, Jeffrey Archer 97. Love In The Time Of Cholera, Gabriel Garcia Marquez 98. Girls In Love, Jacqueline Wilson 99. The Princess Diaries, Meg Cabot 100. Midnight's Children, Salman Rushdie 101. Three Men In A Boat, Jerome K. Jerome 102. Small Gods, Terry Pratchett 103. The Beach, Alex Garland 104. Dracula, Bram Stoker 105. Point Blanc, Anthony Horowitz 106. The Pickwick Papers, Charles Dickens 107. Stormbreaker, Anthony Horowitz 108. The Wasp Factory, Iain Banks 109. The Day Of The Jackal, Frederick Forsyth 110. The Illustrated Mum, Jacqueline Wilson 111. Jude The Obscure, Thomas Hardy 112. The Secret Diary Of Adrian Mole Aged 13 1/2, Sue Townsend 113. The Cruel Sea, Nicholas Monsarrat  114. Les Miserables, Victor Hugo  115. The Mayor Of Casterbridge, Thomas Hardy 116. The Dare Game, Jacqueline Wilson 117. Bad Girls, Jacqueline Wilson  118. The Picture Of Dorian Gray, Oscar Wilde  119. Shogun, James Clavell 120. The Day Of The Triffids, John Wyndham 121. Lola Rose, Jacqueline Wilson 122. Vanity Fair, William Makepeace Thackeray 123. The Forsyte Saga, John Galsworthy  124. House Of Leaves, Mark Z. Danielewski  (awesome book! go read it) 125. The Poisonwood Bible, Barbara Kingsolver 126. Reaper Man, Terry Pratchett 127. Angus, Thongs And Full-Frontal Snogging, Louise Rennison 128. The Hound Of The Baskervilles, Arthur Conan Doyle 129. Possession, A. S. Byatt 130. The Master And Margarita, Mikhail Bulgakov 131. The Handmaid's Tale, Margaret Atwood  132. Danny The Champion Of The World, Roald Dahl  133. East Of Eden, John Steinbeck  134. George's Marvellous Medicine, Roald Dahl  Or at least, I think I have. It would have been a while ago 135. Wyrd Sisters, Terry Pratchett 136. The Color Purple, Alice Walker 137. Hogfather, Terry Pratchett 138. The Thirty-Nine Steps, John Buchan 139. Girls In Tears, Jacqueline Wilson 140. Sleepovers, Jacqueline Wilson  141. All Quiet On The Western Front, Erich Maria Remarque  142. Behind The Scenes At The Museum, Kate Atkinson 143. High Fidelity, Nick Hornby 144. It, Stephen King  145. James And The Giant Peach, Roald Dahl  146. The Green Mile, Stephen King 147. Papillon, Henri Charriere 148. Men At Arms, Terry Pratchett 149. Master And Commander, Patrick O'Brian 150. Skeleton Key, Anthony Horowitz 151. Soul Music, Terry Pratchett 152. Thief Of Time, Terry Pratchett 153. The Fifth Elephant, Terry Pratchett 154. Atonement, Ian McEwan 155. Secrets, Jacqueline Wilson 156. The Silver Sword, Ian Serraillier 157. One Flew Over The Cuckoo's Nest, Ken Kesey 58. Heart Of Darkness, Joseph Conrad 159. Kim, Rudyard Kipling 160. Cross Stitch, Diana Gabaldon 161. Moby Dick, Herman Melville 162. River God, Wilbur Smith 163. Sunset Song, Lewis Grassic Gibbon 164. The Shipping News, Annie Proulx 165. The World According To Garp, John Irving 166. Lorna Doone, R. D. Blackmore 167. Girls Out Late, Jacqueline Wilson 168. The Far Pavilions, M. M. Kaye  169. The Witches, Roald Dahl 170. Charlotte's Web, E. B. White  171. Frankenstein, Mary Shelley 172. They Used To Play On Grass, Terry Venables and Gordon Williams 173. The Old Man And The Sea, Ernest Hemingway 174. The Name Of The Rose, Umberto Eco 175. Sophie's World, Jostein Gaarder 176. Dustbin Baby, Jacqueline Wilson  177. Fantastic Mr. Fox, Roald Dahl  178. Lolita, Vladimir Nabokov 179. Jonathan Livingstone Seagull, Richard Bach 180. The Little Prince, Antoine De Saint-Exupery 181. The Suitcase Kid, Jacqueline Wilson 182. Oliver Twist, Charles Dickens 183. The Power Of One, Bryce Courtenay 184. Silas Marner, George Eliot 185. American Psycho, Bret Easton Ellis 186. The Diary Of A Nobody, George and Weedon Gross-mith 187. Trainspotting, Irvine Welsh 188. Goosebumps, R. L. Stine 189. Heidi, Johanna Spyri 190. Sons And Lovers, D. H. Lawrence 191. The Unbearable Lightness of Being, Milan Kundera 192. Man And Boy, Tony Parsons 193. The Truth, Terry Pratchett 194. The War Of The Worlds, H. G. Wells 195. The Horse Whisperer, Nicholas Evans 196. A Fine Balance, Rohinton Mistry 197. Witches Abroad, Terry Pratchett 198. The Once And Future King, T. H. White  199. The Very Hungry Caterpillar, Eric Carle  200. Flowers In The Attic, Virginia Andrews 201. The Silmarillion, J.R.R. Tolkien 202. The Eye of the World, Robert Jordan 203. The Great Hunt, Robert Jordan 204. The Dragon Reborn, Robert Jordan 205. Fires of Heaven, Robert Jordan 206. Lord of Chaos, Robert Jordan 207. Winter's Heart, Robert Jordan 208. A Crown of Swords, Robert Jordan 209. Crossroads of Twilight, Robert Jordan 210. A Path of Daggers, Robert Jordan 211. As Nature Made Him, John Colapinto 212. Microserfs, Douglas Coupland 213. The Married Man, Edmund White 214. Winter's Tale, Mark Helprin 215. The History of Sexuality, Michel Foucault 216. Cry to Heaven, Anne Rice 217. Same-Sex Unions in Premodern Europe, John Boswell 218. Equus, Peter Shaffer 219. The Man Who Ate Everything, Jeffrey Steingarten 220. Letters To A Young Poet, Rainer Maria Rilke 221. Ella Minnow Pea, Mark Dunn  222. The Vampire Lestat, Anne Rice  223. Anthem, Ayn Rand  224. The Bridge To Terabithia, Katherine Paterson  225. Tartuffe, Moliere  226. The Metamorphosis, Franz Kafka  227. The Crucible, Arthur Miller 228. The Trial, Franz Kafka 229. Oedipus Rex, Sophocles 230. Oedipus at Colonus, Sophocles 231. Death Be Not Proud, John Gunther 232. A Doll's House, Henrik Ibsen 233. Hedda Gabler, Henrik Ibsen 234. Ethan Frome, Edith Wharton  235. A Raisin In The Sun, Lorraine Hansberry  236. ALIVE!, Piers Paul Read 237. Grapefruit, Yoko Ono 238. Trickster Makes This World, Lewis Hyde 240. The Mists of Avalon, Marion Zimmer Bradley 241. Chronicles of Thomas Convenant, Unbeliever, Stephen Donaldson 242. Lord of Light, Roger Zelazny 242. The Amazing Adventures of Kavalier & Clay, Michael Chabon 243. Summerland, Michael Chabon 244. A Confederacy of Dunces, John Kennedy Toole 245. Candide, Voltaire 246. The Wonderful Story of Henry Sugar and Six More, Roald Dahl 247. Ringworld, Larry Niven 248. The King Must Die, Mary Renault 249. Stranger in a Strange Land, Robert Heinlein  250. A Wrinkle in Time, Madeline L'Engle  251. The Eyre Affair, Jasper Fforde 252. The House Of The Seven Gables, Nathaniel Hawthorne 253. The Scarlet Letter, Nathaniel Hawthorne  254. The Joy Luck Club, Amy Tan  I read 1/4 of it in English junior year, but never bothered to read the other families 255. The Great Gilly Hopkins, Katherine Paterson 256. Chocolate Fever, Robert Kimmel Smith 257. Xanth: The Quest for Magic, Piers Anthony 258. The Lost Princess of Oz, L. Frank Baum 259. The Third Chimpanzee, Jared Diamond 260. Lost In A Good Book, Jasper Fforde 261. Well Of Lost Plots, Jasper Fforde 261. Life Of Pi, Yann Martel 263. The Bean Trees, Barbara Kingsolver 264. A Yellow Raft In Blue Water, Michael Dorris  265. Little House on the Prairie, Laura Ingalls Wilder 267. Where The Red Fern Grows, Wilson Rawls  268. Griffin & Sabine, Nick Bantock  269. Witch of Black Bird Pond, Joyce Friedland  270. Mrs. Frisby And The Rats Of NIMH, Robert C. O'Brien  271. Tuck Everlasting, Natalie Babbitt  272. The Cay, Theodore Taylor  273. From The Mixed-Up Files Of Mrs. Basil E. Frankweiler, E.L. Konigsburg 274. The Phantom Tollbooth, Norton Jester 275. The Westing Game, Ellen Raskin  Awesome book! Lots of fun... 276. The Kitchen God's Wife, Amy Tan 277. The Bone Setter's Daughter, Amy Tan 278. Relic, Duglas Preston & Lincolon Child 279. Wicked, Gregory Maguire 280. American Gods, Neil Gaiman 281. Misty of Chincoteague, Marguerite Henry 282. The Girl Next Door, Jack Ketchum 283. Haunted, Judith St. George 284. Singularity, William Sleator 285. A Short History of Nearly Everything, Bill Bryson 286. Different Seasons, Stephen King 287. Fight Club, Chuck Palahniuk 288. About a Boy, Nick Hornby 289. The Bookman's Wake, John Dunning 290. The Church of Dead Girls, Stephen Dobyns 291. Illusions, Richard Bach 292. Magic's Pawn, Mercedes Lackey 293. Magic's Promise, Mercedes Lackey 294. Magic's Price, Mercedes Lackey 295. The Dancing Wu Li Masters, Gary Zukav 296. Spirits of Flux and Anchor, Jack L. Chalker  297. Interview with the Vampire, Anne Rice  298. The Encyclopedia of Unusual Sex Practices, Brenda Love 299. Infinite Jest, David Foster Wallace 300. The Bluest Eye, Toni Morrison. 301. The Cider House Rules, John Irving.  302. Ender's Game, Orson Scott Card  My official "favorite book" 303. Girlfriend in a Coma, Douglas Coupland 304. The Lion's Game, Nelson Demille 305. The Sun, The Moon, and the Stars, Stephen Brust 306. Cyteen, C. J. Cherryh 307. Foucault's Pendulum, Umberto Eco 308. Cryptonomicon, Neal Stephenson 309. Invisible Monsters, Chuck Palahniuk 310. Camber of Culdi, Kathryn Kurtz 311. The Fountainhead, Ayn Rand 312. War and Rememberance, Herman Wouk 313. The Art of War, Sun Tzu 314. The Giver, Lois Lowry 315. The Telling, Ursula Le Guin 316. Xenogenesis (or Lilith's Brood), Octavia Butler (Dawn, Adulthood Rites, Imago)  317. A Civil Campaign, Lois McMaster Bujold 318. The Curse of Chalion, Lois McMaster Bujold  319. The Aeneid, Publius Vergilius Maro (Vergil) 320. Hanta Yo, Ruth Beebe Hill  321. The Princess Bride, S. Morganstern (or William Goldman) ( S. Morganstern is a fictional writer) 322. Beowulf, Anonymous  well, sort of... 323. The Sparrow, Maria Doria Russell 324. Deerskin, Robin McKinley  325. Dragonsong, Anne McCaffrey 326. Passage, Connie Willis  327. Otherland, Tad Williams 328. Tigana, Guy Gavriel Kay 329. Number the Stars, Lois Lowry 330. Beloved, Toni Morrison 331. Lamb: The Gospel According to Biff, Christ's Childhood Pal, Christopher Moore  332. The mysterious disappearance of Leon, I mean Noel, Ellen Raskin  333. Summer Sisters, Judy Blume 334. The Hunchback of Notre Dame, Victor Hugo 335. The Island on Bird Street, Uri Orlev 336. Midnight in the Dollhouse, Marjorie Filley Stover 337. The Miracle Worker, William Gibson 338. The Genesis Code, John Case 339. The Strange Case of Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde, Robert Louis Stevenson 340. Paradise Lost, John Milton 341. Phantom, Susan Kay 342. The Mummy or Ramses the Damned, Anne Rice 343. Anno Dracula, Kim Newman 344: The Dresden Files: Grave Peril, Jim Butcher 345: Tokyo Suckerpunch, Issac Adamson 346: The Winter of Magic's Return, Pamela Service 347: The Oddkins, Dean R. Koontz 348. My Name is Asher Lev, Chaim Potok 349. The Last Goodbye, Raymond Chandler 350. At Swim, Two Boys, Jaime O'Neill  351. Othello, by William Shakespeare  352. The Collected Poems of Dylan Thomas 353. The Collected Poems of William Butler Yeats 354. Sati, Christopher Pike 355. The Inferno, Dante 356. The Apology, Plato 357. The Small Rain, Madeline L'Engle 358. The Man Who Tasted Shapes, Richard E Cytowick 359. 5 Novels, Daniel Pinkwater 360. The Sevenwaters Trilogy, Juliet Marillier 361. Girl with a Pearl Earring, Tracy Chevalier 362. To the Lighthouse, Virginia Woolf 363. Our Town, Thorton Wilder 364. Green Grass Running Water, Thomas King 335. The Interpreter, Suzanne Glass 336. The Moor's Last Sigh, Salman Rushdie 337. The Mother Tongue, Bill Bryson 338. A Passage to India, E.M. Forster 339. The Perks of Being a Wallflower, Stephen Chbosky 340. The Phantom of the Opera, Gaston Leroux 341. Pages for You, Sylvia Brownrigg 342. The Changeover, Margaret Mahy 343. Howl's Moving Castle, Diana Wynne Jones 344. Angels and Demons, Dan Brown 345. Johnny Got His Gun, Dalton Trumbo 346. Shosha, Isaac Bashevis Singer 347. Travels With Charley, John Steinbeck 348. The Diving-bell and the Butterfly by Jean-Dominique Bauby 349. The Lunatic at Large by J. Storer Clouston 350. Time for Bed by David Baddiel  351. Barrayar by Lois McMaster Bujold  352. Quite Ugly One Morning by Christopher Brookmyre 353. The Bloody Sun by Marion Zimmer Bradley 354. Sewer, Gas, and Eletric by Matt Ruff 355. Jhereg by Steven Brust  356. So You Want To Be A Wizard by Diane Duane  357. Perdido Street Station, China Mieville 358. The Tenant of Wildfell Hall, Anne Bronte 359. Road-side Dog, Czeslaw Milosz 360. The English Patient, Michael Ondaatje 361. Neuromancer, William Gibson 362. The Epistemology of the Closet, Eve Kosofsky Sedgwick 363. A Canticle for Liebowitz, Walter M. Miller, Jr 364. The Mask of Apollo, Mary Renault 365. The Gunslinger, Stephen King  366. Romeo and Juliet, William Shakespeare  367. Absalom, Absalom, William Faulkner 368. The Sun Also Rises, Ernest Hemingway 369. Dreamhouse, Alison Habens 370. Hyperion, by Dan Simmons 371. Prospero's Children, Jan Siegel  372. Gaudy Night, Dorothy Sayers   373. Guns, Germs, and Steel, Jared Diamond   374. Enchantment, Orson Scott Card 375. Cetaganda, Lois McMaster Bujold  376. Beauty, Sheri S. Tepper 377. The Hour of the Star, Clarice Lispector 378. The Patron Saint of Liars, Ann Patchett 379. Sexing the Cherry, Jeanette Winterson.  380. A Wizard of Earthsea, Ursula Le Guin.  381. Assassin's Apprentice, Robin Hobb. 382. The Axis Trilogy, Sara Douglass 383. Peter Pan, J. M. Barrie 384. Sabriel, Garth Nix hells yeah 385. Neverwhere, Neil Gaiman 386. The Silence of the Lambs, Robert Harris 387. The Hot Zone, Richard Preston 388. The Dispossessed, Ursula K. Le Guin 389. The House with a Clock in its Walls, John Bellairs 390. The Wings of a Falcon, Cynthia Voigt 391. Gain, by Richard Powers 392. White Noise, by Don DeLillo 393. Koko, by Peter Straub 394. Death in Venice by Thomas Mann 395. The Persian Boy by Mary Renault 396. Maurice by EM Forster 397. Left Hand of Darkness. Ursula K. Le Guin 398. Slaughterhouse Five. Kurt Vonnegut  399. Martian Chronicles. Ray Bradbury  400. Thinking in Pictures, Temple Grandin 401. Reason for Hope. Jane Goodall 402. The Man who Mistook his wife for a Hat, Oliver Sacks 403. Lady Chatterley's Lover, D. H. Lawrence  404. Foundation - Isaac Asimov  405. Finnegan's Wake - James Joyce 406. Something Wicked This Way Comes- Ray Bradbury  407. Dragon's of Pern series - Anne McCaffry 408. Farenheit 451- Ray Bradbury  409.(The Romance of) The Three Kingdoms, Luo Guanzhong  410. Hamlet, Shakespeare 411. I Know Why the Caged Bird Sings, Maya Angelou  412. The Good Earth, Pearl S Buck 413. Youth in Revolt, CD Payne  414.The Chosen, Chaim Potok  Excellent book 415. Redwall, Brian Jacques 416. Farewell to Shady Glade, Bill Peet  417. The Lorax, Dr Seuss 418. Talking to Dragons, Patricia C Wrede  This series was my favorite when I was little 419. Tortilla Flat, John Steinbeck 420. V., Thomas Pynchon 421. The Blind Owl, Sadegh Hedayat 422. The Rubayyat, Omar Khayyam 423. A Game of Thrones, George R.R. Martin 424. Pigs in Heaven, Barbara Kingsolver 425. Memento Mori, Muriel Spark 426. Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf?, Edward Albee 427. Mrs. Dalloway, Virginia Woolf 428. Wind-Up Bird Chronicles, Haruki Murakami 429. Written on the Body, Jeanette Winterson 430. Sirens of Titan, Kurt Vonnegut 431. Breakfast of Champions, Kurt Vonnegut 432. Naked, David Sedaris 433. Maus, Art Spiegelman 434. The Mouse that Roared, Leonard Wibberley 435. Magician: Apprentice & Magician: Master. Raymond E. Feist 436. The Little World of Don Camillo, Giovannino Guareschi 437. Catch Me If You Can, Frank W. Abagnale 438. Ring, Koji Suzuki 439. Catfish and Mandala, Andrew X. Pham 440. The Sarantine Mosaic, Guy Gavriel Kay 441. Til We Have Faces, C.S. Lewis 442. Another Fine Myth, Robert Asprin  443. Sword of Truth, Terry Goodkind 444. Jackaroo, Cynthia Voigt 445. To Say Nothing of the Dog, Connie Willis  
    
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I don't care if it's been panned by the critics, or that it has a plot hole you could drive... the state of Texas through, The Stepford Wives was hilarious. I've seen it twice already, and it was just as funny the second time. I want to marry Roger (the gay man), or at least have his children. And if I could, I would get the "book club" scene and watch it a few more times, just for good measure.  Go see it. Really. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       My elementary school, El Carmelo, is the only one that got split between Paly and Gunn, so about half of the people I knew back then I haven't seen in 7 years. However, some people organized a little reunion for us, which was today in Mitchell Park. I took pictures (duh), which I just put up online. Peruse them at your leisure, if you so desire. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This is surreal. I still don't think it's sunk in yet. I mean, it's hard to imagine that I probably won't see a large portion of my classmates... ever again. Except maybe at high school reunions. Wow. That's a weird thought too.  I've decided that there are too many wonderful people who go/went to school at Paly. I mean, not only do I have some amazingly wonderful friends (some of whom I'm  so lucky  to have gotten to know better this year), but also there are a lot of people out there that I wish that I had gotten to know. There was just never enough time to spend time with all of them.  Anyway, now that it sounds like I just signed someone's yearbook, I should go to bed. Grad night is over, and the next step of life is that much closer. I miss everyone already! 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Or have any of you noticed that I haven't been online much recently? That would be because the internet connection at my mother's house has  died. DIED!  It's awful. Anyway, I'm over at my dad's for an hour or so tonight to check my email and the like, but I don't have time to get online. Hopefully I'll be back on on Thursday night, since tomorrow is graduation.  Oh, and I finished posting all of the pictures from the end of school, so go take a peek. Also, I'm working on putting up the pictures from the senior picnic, so keep an eye out for those as well. 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I have the spine of a jellyfish. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Harmony: "You know, I really wish we could have got to know each other better." Willow: "Me, too." Harmony: "I mean, you're so smart. I always wanted to be like that." Willow: "Thanks, you're so sweet!" Harmony: "I hope we don't lose touch." Willow: "No, we'll hang out. Oh, I'm gonna miss her." Buffy: "Don't you hate her?" Willow: "Yes, with a fiery vengeance. She picked on me for 10 years. The vacuous tramp. It's like a sickness, Buffy. I'm just missing everything. I miss P.E.!"  This has been my basic frame of mind the last few days in particular, minus the hating people part. Or the missing of P.E. And now classes are officially over, and all that's left are Baccalaureate, Senior picnic, and the actual graduation. I don't think it's really sunk in yet, though. I mean, I'm already missing everyone because I know I probably won't see most of them much (if ever) again, and that sucks because everyone is really cool. On the other hand, I don't think it's really sunk in yet that I'm not going to be going back to school at Paly next year. It's hard to imagine what college will be like, which I think adds to the feeling of detatchment.   On a side note, I've been spending the last few days scrambling to put together the present my chem class gave to our teacher. I'm actually rather pleased by the outcome, which is good since I dedicated more than a few hours to make it. The "it" to which I refer, of course, is a "Men of Chemistry" calendar, featuring all of the guys in our class. Copies of the pictures are posted in my pictures section, so go check 'em out. 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I just got my wisdom teeth taken out today. At the moment my jaw is still completely numb, so I don't know how much this is going to suck. Being knocked out for it was quite an interesting experience, though. Besides the fact that they nearly couldn't find a vein to get the IV into (that's a problem with me and my veins...), it went just fine. About 30 seconds after they put it in, I was out for the count. The next thing I knew, I was being walked into their recuperation area, where I stayed for I don't know how long (probably not more than about 15 minutes, actually), and then I was driven home by my mom (I have absolutely no memory of this after walking to the car, but I got home so it must have happened). After that, I basically fell asleep on the couch after about 5 minutes or so (maybe less) and I didn't wake up for about 3 hours. I seem to have completely recovered from whatever drug they used to knock me out, and now I just have the fun-filled job of entertaining myself without being able to talk.  Anyway, if anyone calls for me the next time I see you I'll smack you. 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So today I went with my sister while she got her hair cut to keep her friend Ria company and possibly get a "consultation" for a haircut of my own. (This is part of why my hair grows so long -- it's a huge thing whenever I do get it cut. It's kind of a horrible cycle, of course, but that's beside the point.) Anyway, while I was there one of the women was like, "oh, I can cut it now" so I got it cut. It was rather quick and painless, actually, which is just how I like it. Anyway, it's about shoulder length now, and the woman straightened it (which is, in a way, too weird for words) so it's pretty radically different. I'll get pictures up at some point, but I have to take them first.   
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Eric just brought to my attention a new movie called  urlLink Bandwagon  that I think we all should see. It stars Emma Caulfield as... Emma Caulfield. It's a mockumentary and — I really don't think I could do this justice, so just go to their page and look under "the movie" (the trailer actually wasn't as funny as I suspect it should have been).  Also, check out the  urlLink cast list . There are definitely a few familiar names there.   
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Anyone else notice how posting tends to seriously slow down during the summer? I would feel guilty, but nothing particularly interesting is going on, hence the lack of talking about it. I did just get back from a weeklong trip, though. That was fun.   
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So I just took  urlLink this quiz  and it actually had some interesting results so I thought I'd post it here. I have no idea whether it's really true, though.   You are an  SECL --Sober Emotional Constructive Leader. This makes you a  politician . You cut deals, you change minds, you make things happen. You would prefer to be liked than respected, but generally people react to you with both. You are very sensitive to criticism, since your entire business is making people happy.  At times your commitment to the happiness of other people can cut into the happiness of you and your loved ones. This is very demanding on those close to you, who may feel neglected. Slowly, you will learn to set your own agenda--including time to yourself.   You are gregarious, friendly, charming and charismatic. You like animals, sports, and beautiful cars. You wear understated gold jewelry and have secret bad habits, like chewing your fingers and fidgeting.  You are very difficult to dislike.  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       My new computer for school next year just showed up today, and I've been spending the afternoon getting things organized on it. For those who care, it's a 15 inch powerbook with 1.5 GHz processor, a gig of RAM, and 80 gigs of disk space. Good Times.  Oh, and no snarky comments about it, either. Yes, that means  you . You know who you are.    Oh, and any ideas for names would be welcomed. 
    
    
</post>


</Blog>