<Blog>

<date>11,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Life's Lesson number 274.  Never offer to share an apartment with your best friend's boyfriend/girlfriend... what happens if/when that boyfriend/girlfriend becomes ex-boyfriend/girlfriend?  If all goes well, life will be fine.  But when ever does all go well?  All this really does is put you smack dab in the middle of a relationship (that's not yours, mind you), hearing all the good and all the bad, without anywhere to just get away from it.  Suddenly all the little things that bugged you that you tried to ignore come roaring back and just leave you frustrated with the situation.  Plus there's always the possibility of the original friend not feeling able to visit.  Another bad thing would be if you really like your roommate.  Then it just gets bad for you, trying to have to juggle friends, and that is not a pleasant hobbie... trust me.  Learning Life's lessons... the hard way.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I have this weird taste in my mouth... like I'm afraid of something.  My heart rate jumped a little... and there's this warm-tingly feeling.  Why?  Spider-sense?
     

    
</post>

<date>09,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I have a friend who has written a lot about coffee today, and Starbucks.  Yeah, you know who you are.  Anyway, I saw a commercial on TV just now that made me think about her coffee exploits.  The commercial opens up with what looks like a marathon, but just on the peoples feet.  Noone is wearing tennis shoes, or running shoes.  There are a lot of high heels, dress shoes, doc martins, etc, then it shows a bunch of people all dressed up and running to work.  People are stopping by a coffee shop like marathon runners grab cups and bottles of water along the side of the road.  At the very end of the commercial is the best part, one of the gentlemen that had grabbed a cup of coffee was running with it.  He had a very determined look on his face.  Suddenly he takes the cup and splashes the coffee on his FACE!  Like runners do with water to cool down.  Now the reason I felt it important to write about it... is it seems very much like that.  People often grab their morning pick-me-ups on their way to work, and it works in essence like a runner splashing water on thier face.  Kinda strange.  I guess the whold point is: I'd rather have water splashed on me than coffee?
     

    
</post>

<date>09,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I need a hug.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      For sale:  Left Eye, color: blue, weak muscle on bottom side Left Pinky finger, crooked. Spinal Column, in the shape of an S. Heart, broken... barely used. Soul, empty.  Call for price. Will negotiate
     

    
</post>

<date>09,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I love music.  Music is one of my passions.  I love listening to music, and I love playing music.  I definitely love singing along with music.  I was in the youth choir at my church.  I played Alto Sax, Trumpet, and a variety of drums through the course of my High School career.  Over the past year or two, I've toyed around with playing the guitar.  I started out by taking two lessons while borrowing a friend's accoustic.  At first, I lacked the finger strength or dexterity to properly apply pressure on the strings to hit the fretboard... I became very frustrated, very quickly and I quit.  I had taken with me the knowledge of the most popularly used chords in Music... G, C, and D.  Later I picked up a friend's electric guitar that he had laying around.  I found it much easier to press down on the strings.  And the spacing of the frets and strings was much easier than an accoustic.  It renewed my interest.  After about a month playing on his electric, I bought an amp (since he didn't have one) and heard all this other GREAT stuff.  The amp had an overdrive switch on it, and I thought it was just the coolest thing... I could get a clean sound, or a variety of rock-like guitar sounds.  Shorty after I bought the amp.  I bought my first guitar.  A Fender: Squire... modeled after the Strat.  By far one of the best investments I have made.  It is such a great expression of one's self.  If I've had a bad day, I can come home and purge my soul for a few minutes by playing a few sad chords... "I guess that's why they call it the blues". Heh.  After a while, I got a little bored knowing just four or five chords... so I bought books, watched tapes, looked up sites on the internet to try to further and expand my knowledge base.  Then I learned Barre Chords... the staple of Rock and Roll... with these chords, you can take any chord and move it up and down the frets to make MORE CHORDS!    Okay, so that's where I was at as of two days ago.  So yesterday, I went in to my local guitar shop and purchased an effects pedal.  Actually, not just a single FX pedal, but one with a LOT of FX built in.  I plugged this mystical box in, and it was like the holy grail was set before me.  So many options to choose from, and it has built in drum rythms to play along to.  Now I can make sounds with my guitar that I can match my moods to, or songs to... and it's great!  I think I'll go play, now, while my roommates are out of the apartment.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Ever get the feeling you're writing your memoirs, and when you die, someone will stumble upon this website and publish your "works" and become rich off of some silly thoughts you had rattling around in your brain, and you decided to express them in text form.  I wonder what they'll call it?
     

    
</post>

<date>09,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Started: Thu Oct 09, 10:07:01 AM Loss is something I've dealt with most of my life.  It happens in many different ways, and none of them are easy to deal with.  I've lost friends due to distance.  Family due to illness.  Relatives from old age.  And more people than I can count due to time.  Losing someone is never easy.  And knowing how to handle it is even more difficult.  No matter how hard you try, you can never be fully prepared for it.  But how you deal with it will affect you for the rest of your life.  Deal with it badly... more than likely you will deal with most losses poorly.  Deal with it well... congratulations.  Knowing loss on a very personal level, I've given and been given a lot of advice.  Each piece of advice I give is usually tailored to the person.  Fortunately I haven't HAD to dish out advice or anything too often.  But today, I heard a really good piece of advice... or maybe more of a philosophy, than advice.  Where did I hear these upcoming words of infinite wisdom?  Well, the TV of course. heh.  From a show called "Charmed" it's a show about some witches, but they aren't bad witches, they're good witches... like Glinda of the North.  Y'know the one who hangs out with all the short people!?  Anyway, one of the sisters had to deal with Death in a physical form, and he gave her good advice.  Ready?  Here at last it is...  You grieve, then you move on.  BAM!  I know it sounds way too simple.  But this isn't like, "Okay, you grieve for two days, and then you should be over it."  NO!  Won't happen.  Anyone that you know that was worth grieving about will have you close to out of commision for a while.  You have to work through it.  If you had a really easy time getting over the loss of someone, then you're either a sad emotionless individual, or that person really didn't mean that much to you to begin with.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Bitterness.  It leaves a weird taste in your mouth.  The kind of taste that tastes... well, bitter.  Then once you taste it, it works it's way into your stomach, and from there spreads throughout your mind and body like the quickest and deadliest disease.  It eats you up inside, makes you angry.  Burn.  Fire.  Rip.  Shread.  You realize you're over-reacting to a simple situation... but a simple situation that has piled up on other simple situations, upon other simple situations... until the total mass of all the situations becomes this overshadowing, life consuming rage!  You begin to vent... letting off the built up steam... then the feeling begins to dwindle.  Mend.  Tape.  Ice.  Cool.  the feeling backs off, reversing it's course backwards through your veins and arteries and back into your stomach where, if not handled properly, a tiny piece is left behind, like nitro glycerine... waiting to be woken up and set off by some wrong move, bad step, or... another simple situation.  You go on through your day, unaware of this remaining tiny speck of your bitterness as the fog lifts from your mind.  You cool down, and continue on with life.  Laundry and late nights. 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I think God made babies and kids to be so cute so we wouldn't mind cleaning up their poop, pee, and vomit.  He sure is smart!
     

    
</post>

<date>08,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      You know what I like?  I like pie!  Coconut Creme or Warm Apple!  You know what else I like?!!?  I like drinks!!  I like Sidral Mundet!  Pepsi, Wild Cherry or Regular... and OVALTINE!  My posts were getting WAY too heavy.  Needed to lighten up a little.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I find myself very amused at myself.  Yeah.  That's exactly what I mean.  Not only at myself but at this phenomenon of weblogs.  This personal diary or journal won't judge us or tell us "that's silly" or anything like that.  Things that we may never actually speak aloud, we reveal to this virtual therapist.  What a society we live in, when we turn to machines for comfort...  I can't wait to think of something else to write.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      "Peace.  Hope.  Love.  "Dear Father, I need You, Your strength my heart to mend. I want to, fly higher.  Every New Day, again!  Man versus himself Man versus machine Man versus the world mankind versus me. The circles go on, the wisdom I lack, the burdens keep piling, up on my back, so hard to breathe, to take the next step the mountains are high, I wait in the depths, yearning for grace, and hoping for peace, Dear GOD INCREASE!  Healing Hands of God, have mercy on our unclean souls once again. Jesus Christ, Light of the World, burning bright within out hearts forever Freedom means love without condition without beginning or an end Here's my heart, let it be forever Yours.   Only You can make every new day seems so new!" 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Love is the strangest thing in this world.  Grown men that can take a two-by-four to the face and not flinch, would run from love.  Guys who have it all together, and never seem to cry, ball like a baby because of love.  Someone who is in the depths of despair and seeming like they will never work their way back up, seem to suddenly soar at the notion of love.  We were put on this earth due to one reason.  Love.  We were made in God's image, everything that we are, God is and more!  The only emotion I can think of that would lead a person to all kinds of actions.  A brother who loves his sister may beat up a bully, or "gently warn" a potential boyfriend.  A husband can love his wife so much that he would cry just watching her sleep.  My experiences with love have mostly been on the lighter side of things... mostly friendships.  But some friendships can become as emotionally intertwined as other relationships... sometimes even more so.  I, thankfully, have at least been blessed to have an amazing friendship with at least one person.  I feel sorry for anyone who doesn't have at least that one friend.  I believe that life would be a lot harder on me if it wasn't for that one person.  That one friend.  I love having someone to talk to, someone that's unjudging of me, and willing to listen.  I also enjoy the feeling of being needed.  It makes me feel like I actually have some sort of role or importance in this world.  What am I here for?  I'm not completely sure, but I have a feeling that at least at this point in my life, I'm meant to be here... where I am... discovering what I need to in order to live and to love.  I feel a part of my purpose at this moment is to be an outlet of God's strength for at least one person.  Thank you God, for your strength, and for the gift of knowledge of you, that I don't need to have ALL the answers ALL the time.  You'll give me the ones I need, when I need them.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Yesterday was a half-way decent day in my book.  Nothing bad really happened.  The best part about it was getting to see a friend and be somewhat of a comfort to them when it seemed like they may've needed it.  Truly, the best part was feeling the presence of God's guiding hand working to help me act as a tool for him, by helping one of his children.  There are things that can be explained, and there are things that can't be explained, but you can sometimes take a good guess at them.  I think I took a pretty good guess yesterday and came pretty close to the mark.  It is remarkable what you can do when you completely let go and let God take control.  Now why do I have such a difficult time doing that all the time, and in areas of my life that I definitely need more help in?
     

    
</post>

<date>08,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      One of my biggest concerns in life is the thought of being forgotten.  Now I'm not talking about those people in High School that everyone wanted to impress and hope that THEY remember you.  No, I mean FORGOTTEN.  Someone you love or someone who loves you just drifts away because they forget all about you.  It's kind of a passive abandonment... they don't actively try to forget about you, it just happens.  Why would someone forget about someone else?  One of the simplest answers is that one person simply ceases to be important to another.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I have been, shall we say, inspired, to begin making entries.  Here is a place and opportunity to jot down my thoughts and feelings and possibly events that occur in my life, or the life of others to stop them from banging around in my head and put them into some sort of physicallity to relieve stress or tension; to shout the praises of people, events, or things; to release energy of excitement, elation, happiness, anger, frustration.  To those of you who get to read this... it's the inner workings of my mind, a scary journey, if you ask me.... oh, and try not to wipe your feet on my medula oblongata... thanks.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hi.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      And with the sound of the squeeking front door closing... I am alone, again. Left with my longing for companionship. My want of laughter. A kind voice...  I  could go for a hug.  Cheesecake  Saturday  night.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      It's great how you can not see certain people for months at a time, but still feel like you're one big family, and not feel any kind of weirdness when you see them.  No "getting readjusted" to them or anything. You can pretty much just pick up where you left off... and you can act as completely stupid or as completely sane as you want.  That's how it is with my "family" from Jenny Wiley Theatre.  For instance, Brad (my boss) and I got into it several times this past summer when I worked there, but I saw him tonight, and after a few minutes, it never even occured to me that I had been upset with him at all.  I feel for the most part, I have made correct guesses as to who I invest myself into.  This is a group of people that I know I'll get a good return from.  We're not real deep, but that's cool.  I've got other friends to fulfill that need or desire.  It's just a lot of fun, with a dose or two of deepness.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I keep being amazed by God in my life.  I ask him for strength and he gives it to me... right up until the point that I don't need it anymore.  My best friend's father went to the hospital today, and wanting to help her out anyway I could, I went with her to visit him.  All the way to the hospital I prayed for strength... because I hadn't been in a hospital since   MY   father died when I was twelve (thirteen years ago).  I feel like such a failure sometimes when it comes to being able to say the right words or to be able to be there at the moment when someone is needed most, but today, I know that God granted me the strength that I asked for, and the strength that I needed.  I went into that hospital and I was fine.  Luckily her dad didn't have as many tubes, needles, and machines hooked up to him as mine did.  So it was a little easier than I thought.  I love her parents... they are some of the coolest people I know.  Her dad, especially, has a great sense of humor.  And I enjoy talking with them.  Well, my friend and I (and actually, her mom, too) hadn't eaten in a while, so we went to grab some food.  After we ate, I started to leave and my friend thanked me for just being there.  That meant to me that I was of some use in this whole scheme of things.. at least at this moment.  So I walked to my car, unlocked the door, climbed inside, closed the door, put the key in the ignition, turned on the car, and started bawling.  My time of strength was over.  All my memories of MY father came flooding back.  Camping, Christmas, dinners, every day events, learning to ride my bike, vacations, golfing.  Then... my dad lying on the couch with an oxygen tank.  The hospital.  Tubes coming out of my father, the strongest man I knew, lying weak in a bed.  Home; My mom helping my dad to just walk to the bathroom.  The ambulance in the middle of the night.  My mom forcing me to stay at home to go to school the next day.  The principal coming to get me.  Seeing my Priest and my Mom in the same room.  Then the years of hating God, and then the struggle of knowing God was right, but not understanding why it had to happen.  Seeing kids out with their fathers.  Fathers coming to see band concerts, tennis games, plays, award ceremonies, and graduation.  All this came back to me as I traveled home.  My strength gone.  Vanished with the turn of a key.  I cried most of the way home.  For my friend.  I'd go through it all again.  I love you, friend.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Who knew an offhand comment using a quote from some public service announcement could bring a smile into a day of misery?
     

    
</post>

<date>16,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Keeping in touch.  It's a tough thing to do.  But what really is the kicker here, is how people will send you a million forwards, but when you write them, it's too much for them to write back... takes too much time, I guess.  All I ask for is someone to e-mail me something with a little more substance.  Even superficial substance would be fine.  I'm not looking to be deep over the internet, just want to know how my friends lives are going and what they're up to and in to.  Too much to ask? The world may never know.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Love. Sacrifice. Laughter. Compassion. A hug. A kind word. These are the greatest tools of friendship.  Remember them.  Use them.    BE them.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Friday will be my day to catch up on all the movies my friends have gone to see without me.  Just me, Kill Bill, School of Rock, and an empty seat right next to me... just like old times.  This is going to be pathetic.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      A couple of links to check out.  urlLink News: Real 007 Dies   .... okay.... so upon further investigation... there's only one link to check out... currently.  Sorry.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Ooh la la! ------------  DOMONT, France (Reuters) - French high school students are up in arms over a drive by teachers to ban some of their most cherished items, ranging from cigarettes to G-strings. France's center-right government has declared war on the quintessentially French habit of smoking, angering many teenagers who fear a slip into a "no fun"-state as the popular thong has also become a thorn in the eye of authorities.  "We're not allowed to smoke anywhere on the school grounds any more. They treat us like babies," said Melodie Gambero, a 17-year-old student in Domont, north of Paris, who went on strike with fellow students last week against the new rules.  French law allows smoking at schools in designated areas, but the government, in its drive to crush the habit, is encouraging schools to become smoke-free zones.  "About half of all the students here smoke," said David Perochon, 19, adding a few hundred of the school's 1,200 students had participated in the one-day strike, which had not succeeded in changing the headmistress's mind.  The controversial smoking rules are being introduced in many schools as teachers are also trying to ban girls from showing off thongs and bellies above their low-cut trousers, provoking angry protests from fashion-conscious adolescents.  Hitting the same nerve, a French advertising association this month took the unusual step of ordering an underwear maker to withdraw a billboard campaign for its thong range, depicting three scantily clad pole dancers, following public protests.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Have you ever had one of those nights where it just seems like everyone has a life, but you.  The kind where you call 20 people, but everyone has plans, or is too busy.  Yep.  Well, that's tonight.  So here I am, sitting at my computer and typing in a journal on the internet instead of interacting with real people.  Life is great!  In actuality, this effin blows.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Nothing happened today.  Literally nothing.  Except the fact that I thought I was going to die at one point today.  Not really.  I was really scared, though.  Until I found out it wasn't too serious.  Then I was mostly fine... I was shaken.  My armpits hurt.  Really badly.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Cleaning your room can be quite theraputic.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      The laundry is done! Finally!
     

    
</post>

<date>14,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      ... but God is greater!
     

    
</post>

<date>14,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Technology is great.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      As you may be able to tell, I've been praying a lot lately.  What's on here is just the stronger-felt, and more passionate prayers and praises.  Well, I think tonight at around 15 after midnight, one of my prayers was answered... or maybe God is giving me the terms for answering my prayers.  I haven't been feeling too well the past few days, I've had some bowel issues... but that's all you need to know for me to continue.  So I was going to the bathroom, and I wanted to take something to read with me... so I opened up a box of comic books, and what did I see?  The bible I was given by my church for graduating high school.  Now, I haven't been able to find this bible since I moved to Richmond, and I haven't looked at any of my comics... can you guess?  Since I moved to Richmond. That was over three years ago!!  Last week at my connection/small group meeting, I was challenged to start diving into scripture, to really learn from it, but I hadn't actually taken the plunge, yet.  I don't know if I should take this as some kind of clue or not.  I'm really not used to getting signals from God or anything, so I'm trying to be semi-objective... but I can't help but think that my prayer actually did something... but God wants a little more from me before I'm ready, I guess, to recieve more of his gifts.  Today starts a new day.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      God, You give me such an energy boost!  I love it!  Please let it last!  Create in me a beautiful work of art.  But I know I am an incomplete work.  Fullfill my desire for completion.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Why?  How many more times is this going to be thrown in my face?  How many more times are You going to show me that people together are happy?  I know that.  I want that.  Please let me experience this!
     

    
</post>

<date>13,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Confusion: I don't understand what this is all for.  Why, when I've done so much to try not to worry about something, would You allow it back into my mind.  Why? Am I suddenly ready for this part of Your plan?  I want this so much. Relationships are what we were meant for, and I don't understand why I've been deprived of the second greatest kind that you created.  Please, give me understanding or let me forget this emptiness.  Your will is Your will.  But this is my desire!  To be able to completely connect with another human being, with no barriers, with complete comfort and safety.  To be able to completely know another, and for them to completely know me, the true me, and for us to be able to rejoice in that great gift that You gave us.  Why am I constantly and consistently denied this!?  I desire this connection.  It is not merely something I want, but it is something I NEED.  I want to buy a movie, I need food... and I need this.  I am not complete.  You in all Your wisdom, know this.  You did not create us to be alone.  Lord, as I am, I am only half a person.  If the other half of me is out there and ready for me, please make it happen, show them to me, reveal to me Your plan!  This is torture, Lord. I am not so nieve to think that all this doesn't have it's purpose, I just desire to know what it is.  I desire to know You and know Your purpose for me at this moment, at least. Anger: Why must people I care for suffer? Take the heart of my friend and that of her family, and wrap them up in a big warm blanket and give them the biggest hug you can.  Help them through their grieving, don't let them fight it.  You are God. The beginning and the end, and You love us... make that love shine more brilliant in their lives than ever before. Gratitude: Lord, You have given me many gifts, and blessed me many times.  I could have an incurable disease or come from a broken home... but You walked with me the whole time, sometimes I ignored You, but You were always there, picking me up if I fell, and I fell often.  You are the great and awesome Creator of Everything.  The warm sunny day with a wisp of cloud is Your work of art.  Thank You for Your greatness, for all Your gifts to us.  Thank You for the gifts I've received, especially for my friendships... or friendship.  But I think You and I are both realizing that I was making some bad choices with the people I let in.  You've shown me a place that I can be safe. Thanks, God.  A lot of those songs and psalms really know what they're talking about.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Dreams are a funny thing.  There are the kind of dreams you dream while awake, not like waking dreams, but "I have a dream!" dreams.  We can dream of a better life, or dream of one day getting that job, or that we'll win a very important prize one day.  Now the kind you dream at night tell us a lot about ourselves, if we can understand them.  Sometimes dreams are pretty messed up.  Last night I had a dream that I was working somewhere along side this girl... it's not anyone I knew, or recognize from real life... but I felt like I knew her in my dream.  She was cute, she had short dark brown hair and was apparently very attractive to me, and I guess I was to her.  We talked a lot, and we were talking, and talking, and it seemed that we had a lot in common, and at one point I just leaned over and kissed her, and we clicked.  MAN did we click.  I don't know if this was just my mind and my heart communicating and God telling me, "She is out there" or if it was just one of those tricks our mind likes to play on us because it's something that's been rolling around in there for longer than it should be.  It was nice, and real, and very comfortable.  And then I woke up, and I felt empty.  Like the one great love of my life had been taken away from me. And as I laid there half awake trying to remember her, a thought came over me.  You're never going to experience that, truly.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Doctors are probably my least favorite people in the world.  I've had a bad past with Doctors... I've recieved a lot of bad news from them.    "You're not a big enough dork, Scott, here's some glasses so the kids at school can make fun of you." - "Hey, Scott... you're dad has cancer." - "Hey looky there, Scott, your dad is dead" - "Okay, what we're going to do now is put little pieces of metal on your teeth, and then attach a wire connecting all of them... THEN once or twice a month for the next two and a half years, you must come BACK so that we can sit you in this chair and tighten them until you cry.  Oh, and not to mention the kids at school who didn't already make fun of you... well, heh, the will now!" - "Sorry Scott, but you have a floating eye... it's going to get worse as you get older, and we'll probably have to cut it out eventually, but Pirates look cool with those patches, right?!" - "Guess what, Scott!? Thanks to school, you've developed a crooked back, and developed what we call, you're "effed" syndrome, on the bright side we caught it right at the moment that there's nothing we can do about it."  But really the one that I didn't mind going to, was the eye doctor... it was the easiest... no needles, no pain, no touching me "down there" and telling me to cough!  I'm very thankful that there are doctors... a lot of people would die or live horrible lives without them... some of my family are even doctors, and definitely love them.  Anyway, I went to the eye doctor yesterday for the first time in about three years, and that was great.  I love being able to see, and I thank God that he gave someone the inventive mind to create contact lenses.  Contacts...Helping dorks blend in since 1945.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Taking a cue from a good friend of mine, here ya' go:  MOSCOW (Reuters) - A Russian man may wish he had stuck with having dirty trousers after an imaginative attempt to purge a stubborn paint stain on them destroyed his apartment. The unnamed Muscovite added a liter of petrol to his washing machine to help dissolve the stain, Itar-Tass news agency reported Monday, but the ensuing explosion wrecked his kitchen and demolished two internal walls.  Moscow police confirmed there had been an explosion in a south-eastern Moscow apartment, but would not comment on the cause. 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Stardate One-Zero-One-Three-Zero-Three Point Seven.  I've always wanted to do that.  yeah, I'm a dork.  Nothing really big to talk about today.  I had a great lunch with a great friend, we talked a lot, and she needed someone to listen.  I listened, and I tried to help with her problems... but I always feel like I'm just a waste of time, that I'm not really any help.  I really want to help and make her feel better, but I'm not always the best person for advice, and so when she comes to ME to talk, I feel very honored that she's seeking my advice, or comfort from me, or my ear instead of someone else's.  I pray for a lot of strength, compassion, and wisdom, just so I won't do more harm than anything else.  Okay, so there was something big to talk about today... but that's not big... that's just life.  Then I went for an eye exam.  It's been a while since I had one of those.... feels good to be able to see better again.  And then I was on my way to a meeting that was cancelled, no big deal there.  And now I'm back home, enjoying a nice relaxing evening while the apartment is empty... (sigh of contentment)
     

    
</post>

<date>12,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Why do I feel that if I don't spend a little bit of time writing in this blog each day, that it's like I'm neglecting a friend?  Maybe I'll have more to say tomorrow... or later.  Sorry friend.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Thank you, God, for keeping something in my life stable and constant.  It's really nice to go somewhere and have people genuinely happy to see you, instead of fake niceties.  Take my Life, Lord, and make it into something beautiful, something clean, something worthwhile, and new.    More importantly, use it for Your glory!
     

    
</post>

<date>12,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      In the next hour, I'll be leaving my apartment to go home.  No, I'm not going to visit my mom, I mean I'm going to church.  Since September, I've gotten involved a lot at my church, and I've met a lot of really great people.  People who I have a lot of respect for, and people (I'm finding out) I have a lot in common with.  I feel safer there, more than I do anywhere that I can think of.  No one judges me there.  At least I don't have any reason to believe they do.  I don't know what I would do if I ever felt unsafe or threatened in that environment.  I'm thankful for that place.  Thank you God, for giving us the gifts of friendship, compassion, and grace.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Why are my mind and my heart always at war with each other?
     

    
</post>

<date>12,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Shaking. Anger. Upset. Frustrated.... Fabric Softener.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Women are probably the greatest gift known to man.  God new just what we needed and what we wanted.  He knew there would be those men out there that would need help getting in touch with their emotional side.  That there would be rambunctious and rebellious men, that if they met the right woman, would calm down and be a great benefit to the world.  That there are men out there than need a fire lit inside them, and need someone to inspire a passion about something.  God made women soft, attractive, warm, smell nice, and blessed many with kindness, intelligence and a sense of humor.  Unfortunately for me, it seems like the ones that I meet with the intellegence are too smart to be interested in me... or I guess they think of me as a joke... a really bad joke.  So maybe they were meant as a torture device or punishment, as well.  Why can't I meet a woman who will love me?
     

    
</post>

<date>25,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Miscelaneous thoughts, sayings, feelings from today: ======================================  - He'll never give you a bigger challenge than you can handle.  - "I desire more desire"  - "Where's Stick!?  ...  STICK!!"  - Searching for a travel companion  - I need to read more C.S. Lewis  - "Why does everything have to be so complicated?"  - Burning Bush --- Burning Heart --- Burning Desire  - I've been given an amazing, peaceful, warm gift call the love of God, and of friends.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      After a rousing game of paper, rock, scissors, and a rest stop, I'm back to writing in my paper "blog", so I can type it out later.  The road is mostly smooth again, and I'm feeling much better.  This trip was the closest thing to rock climbing that I've ever done, and just being outdoors was amaing.  The group of people that I was with really made the day... especially since I was able to share it with my best friend.  I had one weak moment this afternoon where I would have likee to shar the moment with a significant other... but it was only a feleetign moment, particularly after I looked back around and noticed I was surrounded by loving and caring friends, and again looking nex to me to see my friend Stephanie.  God, You are truly amazing.  How great it  is to see all these people share themselves with you and each other.  Lord, thank You for EVERTYTHING. Thank you for sending these people into my life.  Thank You for Stephanie and Ben for pushing me, challenging me, helping me grow as a Christian, and getting me involved in this church.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      This has truly been an awesome and amazing experience.  I never really know what to expect on trips or events like these, but I definitely feel challenged, and peaceful, and even a little better about myself and life in general.  The overall package of this retreat was great.  Getting the chance to just personally reflect in nature with God set me up for the rest of the day.  I really enjoyed being able to get away and talk with these people outside our normal environments.  The walk/hike was amazing with some great moments of reflection and contemplation for me.  There were also plenty of opportunities to take great photos.  We had a blast with some of the rock formations and levels to create some interesting scenes.  Now three people are passing the time by playing paper, rock, scissors.  ... I think I'll join them.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      What an experience!!  That's all I can write until we hit straight level pavement.  Car Sick.  Not scared this time, though.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I don't know how well I can write in the car right now, but I'd like to say that this is the lowest part of this trip.  I am getting Sooooo car sick that I'm about to cry.  Winding curvy roads.  It sucks to be in the back seat.  We're on our way to the Gorge.  I can't wait to get out and hike and be with these awesome people and God!
     

    
</post>

<date>23,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      It's fun to imagine older people doing things you'd never expect of them.  Like wrestling... or mud wrestling.  Or doing backflips down a hallway naked.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      "I desire more desire."
     

    
</post>

<date>23,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hoedown Island... what a great name for a place!
     

    
</post>

<date>23,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Sitting in a peaceful and quiet place is a thing I need to do more often.  It is so much easier to reflect on your day and to admire the beautiful gifts God has given to us when we are not distracted by "things"; T.V., internet, games, CD's, etc.  I'm going to make it a goal of mine to take at least one day a week to just kind of get away, to sit some place quiet and reflect and think and pray.  Thank You, Lord, for this peaceful place, my life, my friends, and my salvation.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      As I was writing and reflectiong while looking over the trees and the lake and the hills, and basking in all their beauty, I came to a particular thought that just stopped me in my tracks.  I could go no further, I was blocked.  After a couple minutes of this blockage, a single leaf fell from a tree somewhere around me and it landed right on my knee.  Suddenly the wrote freely again.  I felt very much at peach.  It was kind of like a quick "hello" from God, and Him saying, "thanks for thinking of Me, here's a little something to remind you that I'm thinking of you."  ...Thank you, God.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Challenge: Dive into scripture!! Desire: Cannonball out of comfort zone; be who God intended
     

    
</post>

<date>23,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I love this church (Crossroads).  Especially how great the people are, and how welcoming and safe you can feel there and with them.  It's a feeling I've only felt on a very small scale before, and it's a completely freeing feeling and sensation!
     

    
</post>

<date>23,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      God is Great!
     

    
</post>

<date>23,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      What a beautiful day!  I was up earlier than I had been in a while.  I started my day before the SUN even clocked in.  The best parts up until this point were getting to see my best friend the first thing in the morning and getting to share watching the sunrise with some of the warmest and coolest people I know.  And the day has just started!
     

    
</post>

<date>23,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I've been very fortunate the past week.  But the past couple of days got me a little down.  I missed getting to talk with and see my friend.  I guess I'm going through withdrawal from her.  Luckily, I get another dose tomorrow!  I just hope I'm feeling somewhere between 75 and 95% of my full self for the retreat, I'm really looking forward to it!
     

    
</post>

<date>23,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      A new day is dawning in my evening!  The choirs are rejoicing, the angels are harking, and the hamsters are running!  I have the internet again after three days!!!!!!!!!  Ah, my poor blog, how you've been neglected by my irritation at this mass data transmission superhighway!
     

    
</post>

<date>23,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Being sick really sucks.  I remember as a kid being sick and watching the rest of the neighborhood kids play as usual through my front window.  Even if I was beginning to feel better, there was no way that Mom would've let me go play. "Too sick for school, too sick for play".  That was the one way my Mom kept me from faking being sick... she knew that I might be a little sick, but that I could probably tough it out, and if I did and felt really crappy when I came home, then the next day I wouldn't go to school at all.  My mom had me figured out.  The days I was REALLY sick, I would try to go to school and tell mom I was fine.  If I would try to convince her that I was sick, she would convince me to go to school.  The funny thing is, sometimes she went ahead and let me stay home.  She always seemed to know when I was faking something, but just because I needed a kind of personal day.  It didn't happen all the time.  I must admit, right around the time my father passed away, it happened more often, and later in life, mom asked me, and I told her how much I faked it, and she knew.  I love my mom.  But this story isn't meant to be about her.  It's about being sick, and how much you feel like you miss out when you stay at home.  I have a bunch of friends that I'm really missing right now, because they are all bowling.  I'm not just missing out on the bowling, but the forging ahead of relationships and friendships.  Now I feel doubly miserable.  And what's worse, the internet doesn't work right now (9:29pm) and so I can't even check my e-mail or anything.  I feel so cut-off right now.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      A very unusual couple of days for me.  Yesterday, I went to have lunch with my friend in Lexington.  It was great.  I always love having lunch with her.  Some of the best conversations I've ever had are with her.  She's such an intelligent person.  Anyway, I'm kind of straying from the point.  So, I had parked in a parking garage, like I always do when I visit her.  I was planning on grabbing some cash from an ATM in order to pay for the parking when I left.  Well, this is where the strangeness starts.  I try an ATM, my pin # won't work.  So I call my friend, and she doesn't have any cash and wouldn't be able to get any.  I ask her if there are any banks or businesses that might cash a check around there, she directs me to a few, so I walk to a couple businesses and noone will cash a check, not even with purchase or anything.  I go to two different banks and of course they won't cash checks drawn on another bank or they won't cash a check unless you have an account.  So I call my friend back.  And basically the plan was for me to just hang around in downtown until she got off work, and then she could drive me around the rest of the day, I could get some cash from SOMEWHERE and I'd ride back with her in the morning.  So that began my exploration of downtown Lexington.  I sat inside Starbucks for about 30-45 minutes, then I walked around and looked inside stores and the like.  I finally found a place to waste a good amount of time.  There's this nice Restaurant/Billiards Hall/Bar inside Heritage Hall called Yesterday's.  The atmosphere is really neat and nice.  They play a lot of blues and jazz music.  I was the only person in there other than the bar tender. Eventually playing pool by yourself just gets old, and by that time it was a little after four o'clock.  I started doing a little more exploring of downtown, and then my friend called me (she's super-sweet) to check up on me and see how I was doing, and to offer me a seat in the lobby of the office she works in.  Since there wasn't too much longer left before she was free to go, I went ahead and met her there.  After that, I went with her to see her father in the hospital.  And I had a very nice visit with her parents and her.  It almost didn't even feel like we were in a hospital, we were joking around and just talking about this and that... the only thing that kept reminding me we were in a hospital was the fact that a nurse would check in every so often to take his blood pressure, or to make sure his IV was still chugging along.  After that, she had rehearsal, and I tagged along.  After rehearsal she had plans to go out with some of her gal friends, and I tagged along there as well.  I felt kind of bad, because I know that people need to have their away spaces and times and that sort.  The whole night I felt like an old piece of luggage being drug around...  She made me feel like a jewel carried on a pillow, and displayed me proudly.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I find myself not as pleased or happy with a situation as I thought I would.  In my last 'blog' I mentioned getting a job that would last just over two weeks.  If I had been offered the job at the end of September or the beginning of October, I would have been thrilled to get it.  Now, I feel as if I might be shirking some duty that I've come to accept as a God led purpose for my life for the time being.  I find my mind and my heart in a tug of war between a selfishness and a friend.  I want to be here for my friend at this point in her life.  I don't want to feel like I'm abandoning her.  A thought that I'm very ashamed to admit to (Stephanie, please forgive me for thinking it) was, "Well, maybe he'll die before I have to leave".  I don't want him to die at all.  Who ever in their right mind WANTS someone to die?  Stephanie, and more recently, her family has begun to mean a lot to me.  I find myself very easily attached to a family, especially one with as much love and potential for love as hers has.  Her dad is almost like a dad to me, not that he's ever been like a father figure, or anything, but just he's always been very kind to me and joked around with me, and made me feel welcome.  I want to be around for Stephanie and her mom and her dad for as long as he's around.  Everything about these past few months feels like it's been leading me and preparing me to be available for her and her family.  And now, I get what I've been wanting for a while, but I feel uncertain.  I want to be here for them.  Do I not need to be?  What do You want of me?  What am I to do?
     

    
</post>

<date>21,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Today was a pretty good day, over all.  I got to see a friend that I haven't seen too much of lately, and we had lunch.  I got an e-mail for a job that will last for about two weeks and pay pretty decently, and pay for a couple of trips I want to take next year.  I also got to spend a couple hours with some of the greatest people I've gotten to know in a while... some of the most genuine and suprising people I think I may've ever met.  I feel so much better about everything when I'm around them.  I don't feel like some pathetic person, I absolutely feel like I matter.  I don't feel as if I fell off the planet, no one would miss me, or wonder where I was.  I feel like I'm wanted and loved and special.  It's a lot like how I felt the first time I ever experienced that kind of feeling, when I met my friend Stephanie... except now it's multiplied and greater than ever.  Unfortunately, I had to ask a question, that I don't think I was quite prepared for the answer.  I will NOT let this get the best of me, I will NOT let this send me down some dark road where I may have traveled in the past.  I will NOT turn away from Christ as I'm drawing closer to him, and I will NOT let my friends, or myself down.  Friend, I need your help.  I may need to talk a lot about this.  I KNOW I will need Your help, God.  Please keep me from stumbling backwards.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      A while ago I posted a blog that was very simple, but very important.  "Love. Sacrifice. Laughter. Compassion. A hug. A kind word. These are the greatest tools of friendship. Remember them. Use them.   BE them." - 12:06 PM, 10.17.03  Please Lord, don't let me falter in these... not now, not ever.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I just got an e-mail for a gig happening in November.  It would require me packing up and being out of town for a little over two weeks.  I kind of have been expecting this job.  But it kinda came to me out of the blue and without warning.  Now, I'm plagued with the thought of not being able to be at church for these weeks, especially now that I've gotten so involved with the service that I primarily attend.  I'm glad that a series is ending, but the new one seems just as appealing as the first.  I will miss THREE WEEKS of Sundays.  The series is only five weeks long.  I'll be here for the first and last.  It's a good job, a nice resume' builder, and I know it'll be fun to work with these people, I have no doubt about that.  Then what are you worried about?  That people are going to forget about you?  That you're going to miss out on a lot of opportunities to draw closer to God and to the friends you've made there? ... Yeah, kind of.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      ... on a side note, God.  Thanks for giving life to the creative and funny minds of those people who create, run, and update the website  urlLink HomestarRunner.com .
     

    
</post>

<date>20,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      God, I may not always realize what Your plan for me in the long run is. But I get what I need to be doing and just what I need to be, for right now.  I've never felt so peaceful about a choice I've made.  Everything I've done in the past four months, You've used for a greater plan than just my selfishness. You are wonderful, and amazing, and graceful, and forgiving.  And I'm glad that I know You, and that You have used me and grown in me and hopefully I've let Your awesome-nicity shine through in my day-to-day actions.  I trust You with my life, now more than ever.  So how's that girlfriend thing coming along?
     

    
</post>

<date>20,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I got to spend the day with THE coolest person on the face of the planet. No I'm not talking about Brad Pitt, or Jennifer Aniston... I'm talking about an even cooler person than that... and I'm sure much more friendly, and a hundred times kinder than anyone else you or I know.  I used to get to hang out with this person all the time.  But due to a lot of things, that's been a big hole in my life that no one else could fill.  That person would be my best friend in the world.  I'm so lucky to know her.  She genuinely brightens my day anytime I'm around her, whether she realizes it or not.  She has a huge heart, and I'm just grateful that she has made a little corner in it for me.  This corner is warm and welcoming. Thanks for the home, friend.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      More Dreams:  I don't remember the actual events in my dreams from last night, I just remember the feelings associated with them.  I felt afraid, and sad.  I also felt nervous and worried.  I wish I could remember more.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Women: When I created the heavens and the earth, I spoke them into being.  When I created man, I formed him and breathed life into his nostrils. But you, woman, I fashioned after I breathed the breath of life into man because your nostrils are too delicate. I allowed a deep sleep to come over him so I could patiently and perfectly fashion you. Man was put to sleep so that he could not interfere with the creativity. From one bone, I fashioned you. I chose the bone that protects man's life. I chose the rib, which protects his heart and lungs and supports him, as you are meant to do. Around this one bone, I shaped you....I modeled you. I created you perfectly and beautifully.   Your characteristics are as the rib, strong yet delicate and fragile. You provide protection for the most delicate organ in man, his heart. His heart is the centre of his being; his lungs hold the breath of life. The rib cage will allow itself to be broken before it will allow damage to the heart.    Support man as the rib cage supports the body. You were not taken from his feet, to be under him, nor were you taken from his head, to be above him. You were taken from his side, to stand beside him and be held close to his side. You are my perfect angel.....   You are my beautiful little girl. You have grown to be a splendid woman of excellence, and my eyes fill when I see the virtues in your heart. Your eyes......don't change them. Your lips -- how lovely when they part in prayer. Your nose, so perfect in form. Your hands so gentle to touch. I've caressed your face in your deepest sleep. I've held your heart close to mine. Of all that lives and breathes, you are most like me. Adam walked with me in the cool of the day, yet he was lonely. He could not see me or touch me.    He could only feel me. So everything I wanted Adam to share and experience with me, I fashioned in you; my holiness, my strength, my purity, my love, my protection and support. You are special because you are an extension of me.    Man represents my image, woman my emotions. Together, you represent the totality of God.   So man......treat woman well. Love her, respect her, for she is fragile.  Love, God
     

    
</post>

<date>19,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      CARACAS, Venezuela (Reuters) - A group of Venezuelan prisoners sewed their lips together in a grisly protest to demand a transfer to another jail, officials say. The protest at El Rodeo jail west of Caracas took place amid a spate of prison shootings this week that killed four inmates in the South American country, national prisons director Col. Carlos Alberto Sutrun told Reuters.  "A group of prisoners sewed their lips together. They made a stitch with needle and thread," he said Thursday.  Eleven El Rodeo inmates had sewed their mouths up Monday and eight had not removed the stitches as of Thursday. They were demanding to be returned to a jail from which they had been moved this year following a riot. Sutrun said that authorities had agreed to the move.  Sutrun also said the protesters could still eat and drink "through the corners of their mouths."  Venezuela's overcrowded jails have a reputation for appalling conditions and violence. 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I can't get over how much at home I feel at this church.  You know how sometimes you meet people, and it's just really neat because it's something new, and so after a little while, you and the people don't click any more... well, it doesn't seem to be letting up at church.  The people there are genuine and kind and loving.... thank You God, for keeping two of my good friends on my back to get involved with this place.  You've answered a really big prayer for me.  Now... let's talk about that girl that You want for me.  Where is she? Huh?  I'm here for Your glory, but it would make it easier to give You my whole being, if I had the other half of me.  As I am... I am incomplete, without You and without her.  Lead me to her.  Show her to me, God.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I have a really amazing friend. One who doesn't even know it, but she's cheering me up and giving me more confidence as I type this.  She is an amazing person, but unfortunately, no matter how many times I tell her that, and reassure her of it, one person can come along and in one swift motion make her doubt most everything about herself.  I love my friendship with her, because even as I help her, she (unknowingly, more than likely) is helping me along the way.  Experience is a great teacher, but there are somethings that I'd rather learn from others experiences, and so I look to my friends, especially this one, and ask questions and just observe her in life.  If I could, I would totally and completely learn everything for myself and go through the pain if it meant that she wouldn't have to. She is kind, honest, caring, funny, beautiful, intelligent, compassionate, and loving.  I love her.  She is my sister.  She is inspiration.  She is an asset.  She is my confidant.  And she is my best friend.  I wouldn't want to be walking through life without her right now... or ever.  I thank God for the great gift of her presence in my life... and through her I can see Him working in so many glorious ways.  God is an amazing sculptor of my life... and thankfully he put us somewhere in the kiln together.    I never want to be without her friendship.
     

    
</post>

<date>31,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Definitely the worst part of being single is not having an outlet when you're horny.
     

    
</post>

<date>31,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Why God, when everything is going fine, does something have to go wrong, or does somebody or something have to mess it up?  This sucks.  I'm NOT happy with it at all.  I'm shaking.  Why, when someone begins to redevote their life to yYou, especially in the middle of bad times when doubting is much easier, would you allow another to do the emotional equivalent of hitting someone head on in a car to that believer who is just trying to get a grip on things?
     

    
</post>

<date>30,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I was at church at 8:30am today.  It was great.  There was no worship going on other than that of two creative minds trying to bring glory to God through 70 feet of steel trussing, 30 feet of chain, and ten ETC SourFour ParNel lights.  By three o'clock, we had created a masterpiece.  There was one large 30 foot section and two smaller (only slightly) 20 foot sections.  The larger section was suspended in air at an angle of 20-30 degrees from horizontal.  The other two sections intersected that one... one on the left suspended by one end at an angle of around 70-80 degrees.  The third section was on the right and was suspended at an angle of around 45 degrees.  We hung the ten lights on the trussing sections and aimed them AT the trusses in order to actually light up the trussing and paint it like a canvas for lights.  We used an awesome blue called Zephyr Blue and an excellent green color, along with lighting it from the top with a Salmon color to give it some "heat".  When we were done, we tested it out.  This structure gives the feeling of a cold, desolate industrial kind of area, with a touch of heat, but not like warm-happy-good-feeling heat... a nasty, hot, sweaty, yukky hot heat-ness.  Satisfied with our job.  We praised God and left, thankful that He has given us these awesome gifts, and grateful that we are able to use them for His Glory!
     

    
</post>

<date>30,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I recently read a blog that puts the female gender in not too good of a light.  I'd like to make an adendem to my prayers for a girlfriend.  God, when I meet this woman that You are preparing me for, please allow her to fit almost seamlessly into my life.  Please give me the strength to be my own person, and allow me the knowledge I need to combine my "worlds".  Also, please remind me to not forget about my other friends and hurt people as many have done to me in the past, present, and I'm sure will happen again in the future. Grant me peace in knowing that one day I'll meet her, and that it will be a joy for You to see two of Your children bonded on a deep level.  Thank You for this day, and for all the blessings in my life, especially those that I may not recognize and take for granted.  Your loving servant, Scott.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I have found that certain people can affect your mood.  Not so much mood, really, as affecting your feelings.  I have this one friend, and it never fails that if I'm in a bad mood and I talk to them, I usually end up feeling better or at least my mood has lightened a little bit, and the opposite is true.  When this friend is sad or depressed, I experience it, too. Not quite to the same degree or level they are, but I shift a little bit.  Maybe it's something like sympathy pains or that sort.  Or maybe it's just because I care so much about this person and have so much invested that I really feel what they're going through.  My friend is the greatest.  I sometimes want to be selfish and keep this person to myself, but that's not right.  I hope everyone in some way or another has a friend like mine.  Here's to you, friend!
     

    
</post>

<date>30,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Good things happen to those who wait.  But sometimes you have to help it along.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Update: I've talked about a job in a couple of blogs over the past couple weeks.  Well, I just want to say that I am looking more forward to the job as each day passes.  My only sadness is that I won't see my church family for two weeks. Bummer.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Think about these for a moment.  - No man or woman is worth your tears, and the one who is, won't make you cry.  - Just because someone doesn't love you the way you want them to, doesn't mean they don't love you with all they have.  - A true friend is someone who reaches for your hand and touches your heart.  - The worst way to miss someone is to be sitting right beside them knowing you can't have them.  - Never frown, even when you are sad, because you never know who is falling in love with your smile.  - To the world you may be one person, but to one person you may be the world.  - Don't waste your time on a man/woman, who isn't willing to waste their time on you.  - Maybe God wants us to meet a few wrong people before meeting the right one, so that when we finally meet the person, we will know how to be grateful.  - Don't cry because it is over, smile because it happened.  - There's always going to be people that hurt you so what you have to do is keep on trusting and just be more careful about who you trust next time around.  - Make yourself a better person and know who you are before you try and know someone else and expect them to know you.  - Don't try so hard, the best things come when you least expect them to.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Music is a window to the soul.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I feel great today.  I don't really have anything to do, but it doesn't really matter.  I woke up this morning, and went back to sleep... and then I didn't wake up until almost noon.  Something I haven't done in a LONG time.  I usually wake up around nine o'clock, and get out of bed to at least feel productive.  But I guess my body was trying to tell me something, trying to tell me that I went from zero to sixty in 0.34 seconds, and that it wasn't quite ready for that.  I'm gearing up for a really busy two weeks, so I think that makes me enjoy the regular lazy days a little better, and not feel like I HAVE to have something to do.  It's nice to have stuff to do, but it's more fun to have people to do stuff with!  Ah, Thank God for today!
     

    
</post>

<date>28,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      It's hard when someone you care about is hurting and you feel like you have an emotionally helpful equivalent of two left feet.  I want to do more, friend!
     

    
</post>

<date>28,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      To edit a friend's blog a little:  It's hard when someone you care about disappoints you ANY time.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Quinten Tarantino has been watching WAY too much Anime lately.    I got the chance to watch Kill Bill today, practically had the theater to myself.  Thankfully, and unknowingly, a friend of mine had warned me about a certain part of the movie, that I definitely would not have wanted to see.  I kind of guess from the situation that that was where the particular event would occur... so I averted my eyes until I heard the slashing sound and a cry of pain from a man's Achilles tendon being severed.  I very much agree with the same friend on the movie.  I think it was very well written, and the characters were developed very well, but it was like I was looking at a painting... something people say, "That looks nice" and "I love the (insert what you love here)."  I haven't seen many of Tanatino's movies, but I've heard that he really likes to show movies out of order (in a sense), and I know that other movies that have been like that I have sometimes had a difficult time following the plot lines.  But in Kill Bill, I often found myself going, "OOOoooHHhhhh..., I get it."  I was a little sad that Lucy Liu's character died in this volume, I would've loved to see that Nurse chick get it in the stomach, and let Liu live on to the next movie.  It was a good escape for a couple hours.  I can't wait for Volume Two!
     

    
</post>

<date>27,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Sometimes people stumble, and when that happens we shouldn't say, "You always do that", we should say, "here, let me help you up, and find a way for you to not trip like that again."
     

    
</post>

<date>27,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Today really is mine.  Today, I am selfish.  Today, I am making ME happy.  Sorry world, solve your own problems, today, I don't care!
     

    
</post>

<date>27,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      God, give me understanding.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Good morning world!  I have something to look forward to today!
     

    
</post>

<date>27,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hey God, I'm working on my part... how about you?  Any progress?
     

    
</post>

<date>27,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      One of the saddest truths about people, is that they forget.  One instance of forgetting is that of a friend who becomes involved with someone and suddenly they don't have a lot of time for their friend.  I've witnessed this more times than I can count, and I've experienced it more times than that.  It's hurtful.  It makes you feel unimportant in others lives.  God, if this is a lesson, I think You've taught me well. Please don't allow me to put any of my friends through this if I meet someone.  I want to incorporate that person into my life, not neglect my life for that person.  I want to add on to my life, not replace it. Forgive me if I've hurt others in this way, and please grant me peace in this area.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I really enjoyed having things to do this past week.  Things to keep me busy, people to talk to.  Mostly I really enjoyed being out of my apartment, and with people.  Right now, all I have is the TV.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      ... awww, who am I kidding, I'm just going to waste my day around my apartment until something better comes along.  I hate this part of me.  The part of me that won't allow myself to call and ask someone to go do something because they may say that they're busy, which will just feel like rejection.  So I just sit and wait until someone plans something and invites me... or until my regular weekly events happen.  What a sad part of life.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm getting out of here.  Today is mine!  I would like to direct your attention to a blog posted on Friday, October 17, 2003 @ 12:30am, and then at 12:30pm.   ===== "Friday will be my day to catch up on all the movies my friends have gone to see without me. Just me, Kill Bill, School of Rock, and an empty seat right next to me... just like old times.  This is going to be pathetic." -12:30am ===== Love. Sacrifice. Laughter. Compassion. A hug. A kind word. These are the greatest tools of friendship. Remember them. Use them.   BE them. -12:30pm ===== Well, I feel I've done one of those things, but not the other.  Time to do the other, unless of course it becomes necessary not to in order to do the other one again...   and I would do it again, without thought.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      The mixed feelings I was talking about yesterday... well, I can't say that I'm happy, but I'm not really sad.  Just in an even kind of mood, I guess.  When you've been really happy for a few days in a row and had plenty to do, even an even kind of mood feels bad.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Worried.  Not to the point that it's debilitating, but enough that it's usually in my mind somewhere.  Quiet times... it's the worst.  Distractions are a good thing, but only for a short while, eventually I need to deal with my worry.  Needless to say, I'm worried.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I have mixed feelings about tomorrow.  I want it to come, so I can see what great things can happen in my life and in others lives.  I don't want it to come, because I've had such a great weekend, and I don't want it to end.  I wouldn't be surprised if I have some withdrawal symptoms tomorrow.   As you can tell, Saturday I went on a retreat to Red River Gorge with some of the most awesome people I know and have met.  We spent all day in prayer and contemplation and community.  And then we went rock climging and hiking.  Then today, I got to spend some more time with a great friend of mine.  We saw a musical called "Bat Boy".  One of the coolest shows I've seen, by far.  It's one of those shows you really just need to see in order to understand... and then we went to eat, and then I went to church and was supposed to answer a question pertaining to what we had gotten out of our small groups on Tuesday night.  I listened to all the other people answer their questions, and they all sounded eloquent and passionate and great... then it was my turn, and I just felt like a big idiot... I don't know if I even made any sense, or if I was even putting whole thoughts together in any kind of order... but I really enjoyed the service, the music was especially great tonight.  Then I stayed to help take down the environment and some of went out to eat, and I had a lot of fun.  It may not seem like I'm portraying the intensity of this weekend or the amount of postive vibes that I received, but it was incredible.  So I think I may be a little down tomorrow.    I hope I'm wrong.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I cried. I wept. I blubbered.  I wish I had done that twelve and a half years ago... or even ten and a half years ago.  But I didn't.  I am now, and will... I have a lot of time to make up for.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Unfortunately, this will be one of my last blogs for a couple of weeks.  I'm going to a place where I have very little access to the internet.  I'm going to continue to keep an offline log on my computer so I'll be able to continue to share my experiences.  So, until we meet again!  See you soon.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Thank You God!  For helping me to realize that something was broken and needs mending.  Thank You for overwhelming my heart today as I left the funeral home, and thank You for my heart.  Thank You for my loyalty and my devotion to helping out a friend when they really need it most (or at least appears to me that they need it).  I couldn't have been who I am without You.  Or with out your help, friend.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Overwhelmed.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Too many things to think about.  I can't seem to focus on one thing and get that accomplished.  I'm thinking about everything at once and I'm just spinning my wheels.  GRRAAAARRRRRGGGGGGHHHHHH!!!!!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Day 4.  Temptations come and go.  Easier when people are around.  Tough when I'm by myself.  Hanging in there.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      - "Love.  True Love.  Love is what brings us together today." - Love.  Isn't it grand?  Isn't it lovely?  Isn't it wonderful?  Doesn't it just make you want to sing?  Doesn't it feel like you're floating?  Just when you feel like you've gotten away from it, and you're used to being alone... that stupid baby in a diaper with the little bow and arrows shoot everyone around you BUT you.  Doesn't it just make you sick?
     

    
</post>

<date>04,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm an aweful friend.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Guilt.  I don't like it.  It's worse when it's something you bring upon yourself.  Please, God, ease my soul.  And please keep pumping me full of your strength.  I'm going to need it more coming up soon.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Day 3.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I just ran out of gas again for the third time in my life.  What a moron.  I had just left my friend's house on a quest to run a few errands.  My gas gauge read about an eighth of a tank... the idiot light had not turned on.  I was driving down the bypass when my car wouldn't quite pick-up-and-go.  It started to kind of sputter, and suddenly a couple of lights lit up on my dash console, and it became difficult to apply pressure to the brakes and to turn the steering wheel.  The realization hit me, I was out of gas.  I had the forethought to scan the road really quick and see how far away any gas stations were.  I had just passed three and was coming upon a fourth.  Fortunately, I had enough momentum to be able to coast into a Shell station on the right.  God was really watching out for me, because there was no traffic between me and the station.  I coasted up next to the pump perfectly, tugging at the steering wheel for it to obey my command, and mashing down on the brake pedal as hard as I could to make my car completely stop.  I don't think anyone was the wiser, so the experience wasn't as bad or embarassing as my other two times had been.  THe only bad part is I knew how my gas gauge works, and I ignored it... I tried to push my car to the limits, and it finally gave and I did NOt triumph... except that I made it to the station before it completely stopped moving.  Would't that be funny if I had to call my friend who I've been comforting and being with, to come and help me now... how worthless would that have made me feel... heh.  Life cracks me up.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Day 2.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Lord, about 30 minutes ago, you eased the pain of one of your children and welcomed him into your arms.  Show him around, and help to ease the pain of those that remain.  Don't leave them, now. Lord, please.  Stay with them.  Wrap your huge loving embrace around the Seales family and squeeze with all your might.  Please continue to help me through this time as well.  It kills me to see my friend sad, although I know it is a normal part of this process.  Give me strong arms, a strong heart, and a wise mind.  Lord, You are great.  I know Steph's dad is up there cracking jokes with my dad, and having a good time.  Tell them that a lot of people miss them, and that we'll see them soon.  Dad, take Melvin and have a great time... tell him about time the snake that grabbed your leg.  I bet he'd appreciate that.  Lord, we know this should be a happy time, and a time of rejoicing, but it's difficult for us to think of it that way.  Our selfish hearts don't want to let go of people as the leave this world.  Jesus, I just ask you to ease their hearts, and help Stephanie and Doris to remember the good times and think of him when he was full of life, and not cry because it's over, but smile for the time they got to spend with him.  In your loving name.  Amen.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      My friend tonight told me that she was impressed with me.  I was kind of taken back.  Later I asked her, in a joking kind of way to explain, and it was just how I was facing a lot of fears by being there with her for this particular instance.  She said she was proud of me.  That means a lot to me.  God really knows what he's doing, I guess.  He takes the most unlikely things and uses them for His glory and to help us through things, or for us to help others through things, and by which, we gain unrequested rewards ourselves.  I'm glad that it's happening, but even if it didn't, I'd still do what I've been doing.  I don't know what else to do, but I AM going to be there for her.  She's an amazing person, and I want to see her soar.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Tonight, for the first time, I cried with my friend.  Not about her, or for her, or around her... but with her.  I've always felt like I had to stay strong for people, but tonight in the midst of prayer and seeing and hearing her cry, I bawled my eyes out.  I felt very clensed afterwards, and a little foolish.  This isn't about me, and I felt like I needed support instead of being support.  When I got into my car on the way home, I drove in the rain, but of course no one else was getting wet, just me... my eyes were pouring.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Guess what... still helpless.  Why can't I just take and realize my own advice?  I know no matter what profound and inspiring thing I may come up with, it won't mean a damn bit as much as me just being there.  That's all I can do, or at least that's all I know to do.  I'm sorry I can't do more, friend.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Helpless.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      They say it takes 40 days to make or break a habit....  Day 1.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Why must I be tainted by life?  And why do people see something that I don't seem to.  "Full of energy"  "Full of life"  "A treasure"  I guess I don't get it.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Today was a very awesome day.  I woke up, got breakfast for a friend and I, took it to her, and hung out with her for a little bit.  Then some more people showed up and we all spent the day raking leaves at her parent's house.  Her father is very sick and her mother has been too preoccupied with him to be able to take care of their yard (understandable).  Then we came inside and had a little bit of a dinner, and I came home to shower so I could meet up with a friend of mine from High School (Jason) and his wife.  We've lived in the same city for about a year now, and this is the first time we're getting together... sad, huh?  Well, we had a blast.  When I got there, Kat (short for Kathryn) had made taco-type stuff for dinner, so we enjoyed that while talking a little bit... then the games commenced!  We played cards like crazy, and like it was going out of style.  We played an interesting game called "Unexploded Cow"... you really have to play it to understand it, and then we played "Spoons" and then Egyptian Rat Screw, which I had not played since High School in band class on days our director was sick or decided to give us a break, etc.  Then we watched a movie to enjoy his new surround sound system.  The second Matrix movie.  Unfortunately, by this time it was 11:00 and I was a little tired from the days events so I dozed on and off during the movie... thankfully, I'd seen it before.  The movie ended, I said my departing good-byes, and came home, and here I am now, typing in my blog.  Good blog.  Safe blog.  Well, gotta go to bed to get some sleep.  Tomorrow's another busy day.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I don't want to be a "man's man".  I don't think I even want to be a "guy's guy".  Sometimes I don't want to be "the guy who is fun to have around sometimes, and is sort of okay".  I don't want a girlfriend, I want something deeper, something more substantial.  I don't want to be the guy who meets someone and drops off the radar to everyone he cares for.  I don't want to be a bad friend.  I don't want to be a bad son.  I don't want to surround myself with negative people.  I want to be able to look at someone and know that they care, to be able to see it in their eyes, or in their body language, or to just hear them say it.  I want to know that everything is going to be all right, or at least it's on the right track.  I want to feel like I'm me, no matter what I'm doing or who I'm with.  I want to touch someone's soul with merely a word or maybe two.  I want to make a difference in the lives of the people around me.  I don't want to be forgotten.  No. Nothing's wrong.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I only have time to say one thing, but it's the most important thing to me.  I miss my friend.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Just wanted to apologize for not being about to blog as much as I want to... but starting Sunday, that all changes!  And look for a special "come-back" blog of immense proportions!  or at least it's gonna be long.  I've been saving up all my stories, rants, and raves for you, and can't wait to share them.  Bloggers... soon.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Yes, the sensation that is sweeping the blog-nation... I, too, have the ability to receive your comments.  I now have THAT power!  MUH ha muh HA... muh ha ha ha ha haaaaa.......  No longer shall I be left in the dark about how YOU feel about my blog.  Now the power is in YOUR hands as well as mine!!!!!!  Viva all of blogdom!  So feel free to browse the past blogs as well as the future ones and give me a little feed back.  Thanks!  Too over the top?  Surely not.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Ahhhh......
     

    
</post>

<date>16,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      No sleep, only a few minutes to jot down a couple of my thoughts before I need to work some more.  I felt like I wanted to cry tonight.  This job is SO incredibly difficult.  Anyone who thinks they can do it better are welcome to try, and I'm sure they'll succeed.  I suck at this.  I'm no good.  If I could equate a smell to how badly I stink, it would be the middle of a sewer surrounded by skunks drinking curdled-past-expiration-date milk.  Please God, PLEASE!  Get me through this.  I know it will be great, in spite of me.  Please watch over us as we go through the show tomorrow morning and all week, and help ensure safety and peace amongst the company.  And give me patience.  With everyone... especially now that I've been running on very little sleep for the past three days... and I hope that people I may have talked to realize that I'm under a lot of pressure and frustrated, and aren't too hard on me for some way that I may have treated them.  I just want to do a good job, and have a little fun while doing it.  njbfdhgjb .... sorry, my head hit the keyboard, but I can't go to sleep because I don't think I'll wake up in time, or I won't be worth ANYthing.  ARGH!!!!!!!  Restless days, and sleepless nights.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      This sucks.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Crunch time.  Waking up at 9:00am and working until 1:30am.... what the heck am I thinking everytime I work in this business.  The week before a show opens is crazy and more hours than there are in a day are required to get the show up and running.  Now I'm trying to find a tiny bit of social time.  I think there's something about this business to make you forget the bad times and remember the good times, or think the bad times ARE good times... or something else, I don't know really.  Fortunately, I love it.  And I'm very much looking forward to Tuesday.  The show opens and there's nothing else to be done.  I'll be finished.  Then I can relax and enjoy the rest of my time here and enjoy the company.  Now, I'm trying to unwind a little bit before I can go to bed.  But, I don't think I'll be getting much sleep tonight since I need to be up and working by 9:00am.  SUCK.  Anyway... at this particular moment, I'm pretty miserable.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Hair Update   It's growing on me... no pun intended.  okay, partially intended...  well, mostly intended.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Seeing family is great, especially around the holidays... the best just seems to come out in everyone.  It makes my heart ache, though.  I wish I could be closer, so I can see my little cousins growing up, and to be a bigger part of their lives.  It also really makes me want to be at the poing where I'm married and settled down and have a kid or two that when they bump their head, they look to me to see if it's "supposed to hurt" or not, and if they realize it's supposed to, then they come running to me with arms open wide for comfort.  Someone just running up to me and saying, "daddy".  Yeah.  That would be nice.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       The true testament of friendship #3.   Someone "senses" you might be lonely or bored and makes an excuse to come see you or to call you.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       The true testament of friendship #2.   A friend calls you in the middle of a performance to make sure you're alright.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Alright, here's a list of just a few things I'm thankful for... feel free to comment with your own!  Salvation My family My best friend Crossroads n' Gang! My friends Health When I allow it ... my happiness
     

    
</post>

<date>26,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       The true testament of friendship #1.   Acting like a jerk and an idiot, and they forgive you and overlook it.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Eulogy for a PC   My computer has been on the verge of dying over the past week.  The motherboard aparently is the problem.  It's been moving a little bit slower than it used to.  It can't run or play as much as it had.  But I will remember all the good times.  The jokes we used to share.  The tears, the pain.  The countless hours of e-mailing.  And even blogging.  Yes, my computer was a dear friend, and before it goes... I would just like to say...  WORK YOU STUPID PIECE OF CRAP!  Thank God for warranties and tech support! ...and roommates' computers.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Re: Previous Blog   Sorry, I just needed to get that out.  I tried to say something a couple times yesterday, but couldn't due to interuptions. I'm not saying I don't care how I look, I like looking nice.  I love it.  I like getting compliments and stuff, that's all well and good.  Here goes:  School... all of it.  Scott not a popular guy.  People who mostly make fun of him and put him down... the trendy people... the "cool" people.  Scott didn't want to become like "them".  And change can be a scary thing.  I'm a fan of change to a degree... I find it exciting a lot of times, but people just have to understand that changing how I look after I've basically looked the same for 25 years.. is a big deal to me.  I know to some people it's not a big deal.  It kind of makes me feel self-conscious to think that people think I need to change.  Whether it's a good thing or a bad thing.  So please don't think that the previous blog was some maddening rant... it was not.  Oh, and about the "forget girls" part... I'd like to take that back.  I want peace in my heart and in my mind, AND girls.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      When did I become one of those people that cared about how I look?  Who am I really trying to impress?  Does it really matter HOW I look if I'm not comfortable with myself?  Shouldn't be who I am that attracts people to me? (not necessarily meaning in a male-female dating kind of thing)  I don't know.  I just started becoming moderately comfortable with who I am... and now I'm changing.  [sigh]    Forget girls, I just want peace in my heart and in my mind.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Looking forward to tomorrow.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       JWT/MAC gig:  ADDENDUM    A couple days ago, I had to kill an actor.  I gave him a line note, and he just refused to say "THANK YOU" like you should always do after given a note by the director or stage manager.  He ticked me off.  And I snappend.   This entry brought to you in part by Patrick Drury 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Actual Date:  Sunday, November 23, 2003  Actual Time:  2:13am     Final entry from JWT/MAC gig.   Our final performance was tonight, and we struck the set and props and costumes afterwards while the actors went to eat.  From the sound of it, it wasn't a GREAT deal of fun, but I don't think it was horrible.  I really enjoyed my time here, one way or another.  I met some really cool people.  This is the part of this business that I dislike most of all. Saying good-byes to people I get to know and enjoy spending time with.  I'm almost sad to go back to the real world.  Not only have I made some new friends, but I've really connected and feel like I have some friends that previously were only bosses and supervisors to me.  I have enjoyed their company immensely.  I have really enjoyed working and feeling like I am doing something to work towards a goal, with a team.  This show was something I was pretty proud of.  I enjoy doing this.  I'm tired of college.  I can make money doing this, and I'm making contacts left and right.  ARGH!  Any advice?  Any thoughts?   No?  That's right, you're a computer.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Actual Date:  Saturday, November 22, 2003  Actual Time:  4:27am     5 hours, 3 Doc Otis, and 28 games of Bullshit later    I had a great time.  I need friends that I can just sit back and relax with every once in a while.  I love going out and doing things, but Im a very high-strung kind of person, and I need to really break myself out of that, its not a big turn-on for too many people.  I really need to find people I can just sit back, shoot the bull, have a drink, and hang out with.  Where are you?   11:56am  I had a wonderful dream last night.  I usually have really weird dreams that I remember or seemingly abstract or something absurd that is a reflection on whats going on in my mind at the time and this could be one of those dreams.  But it was very straight forward.  I had sex with this girl.  It was very passionate I dont remember if I knew her or not (in real life), or if she was just some amalgamation of my subconscious.  It was one of the best dreams I can remember having, and as I was in that fog moving from sleep to awake, I remember having this feeling of closeness with someone.  Then as I came out of the fog I looked next to me guess who was there!?  No one.  Not saying that I want to have sex right now or anything just that Id like to be with someone who cares as much about me as I do her.  I know I have friends, and one really great one in particular, but I cant get what I feel I need from them.  Friendship goes a long way, and I believe that all relationships should try to build that first before making it anything else, but I guess I just want more of an intimacy with someone than I feel I can get from a friend or am getting from friends.  I dont even mean in a physical sense, I dont know, its a very abstract thing Im trying to describe, but I can tell that its there and theres a desire for something MORE.  Well, until then  Sex dreams are the next best thing to actually doing it. 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Actual Date:  Friday, November 21, 2003  Actual Time:  11:54am  The shows went much better yesterday than they did on Tuesday.  In the evening I went to eat with a couple people at Applebees.  The more times I come back to this theatre, the more I realize that the people here are kind of like my extended family.  These people that work here arent JUST my co-workers and supervisors and bosses, but they are my friends, too.  And, I think that people look forward to me coming back as much as I look forward to being back.  I know someday that Ill have to venture out and work other places, too.  But Id definitely like to think that Ill always have a home here, at least as long as the current people are in charge are here.   11:55pm  Tonights show went well.  We had a first act pre-show entertainment mini-stravaganza, where a few people sang Christmas songs and then a group of us did a small sketch and then performed a song and dance.  The song was Bruce Springsteens version of Santa Clause is Comin to Town it was great fun.  People in the audience seemed to enjoy the cheesy background dancing and the overall package of the song.  For tonight, my seven and a half minutes are gone tomorrow is another day, and then, unfortunately, Ill go back to being one of the unseen, unsung heroes of theatre.  I just wish 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Actual Date:  Wednesday, November 19, 2003  Actual TIme:  6:58pm  What a great day!  I slept until noon, watched a whole disc of FRIENDS episodes, went to rehearse a sketch for an hour, bought a few groceries, and then came home.  NO WORK INVOLVED!   7:45pm  Ive really been enjoying my time here well, for the most part.  Ive not been miserable by any means, just been losing sleep.  Ive met some really cool people and Ive enjoyed visiting with some old friends.  I miss people and things back home, though.  Which brings me to a very scary thought.  What happens when I graduate?  Am I trying to hold on to school because I dont want to leave my friends?  The comfort and assurance, the confidence and strength Ive gained from these people is enough to get me through tomorrow, and knowing that Ill see them soon, re-energizes all those things in me.  I want to be me, no matter where I am, and know that I have a support group of some sort to be there for me when I need it.   11:19pm  I meet all kinds of neat, fun, smart people.  People who I have a lot in common with (but not too much). But why with all these people can I not meet her? 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Actual Date:  Tuesday, November 18, 2003  Actual Time:  11:15m   People miss me really?    I always envisioned that, if my life were a T.V. sit-com, I would play the part of a minor character, most likely comic relief and the kind of character that just kind of tagged along with the main characters and made a joke every now and then.  Its nice to feel wanted.  I like that feeling.  I hope it happens again. 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Actual Date:  Friday, November 14, 2003  Actual Time:  11:22am  I HATE DOING PROPS!  I love working with them on stage but being a properties person is NOT what I want to do.  Its okay for a little while, but I get REALLY bored of it REALLY quickly.  Im SO tired of shopping.  ARGH! 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Actual Date:  Thursday, November 13, 2003  Actual Time:  10:34am  I havent written anything in the past couple of days.  Nothing good has really happened.  Nor has anything bad so I guess Im thankful for that.  The best thing was that I finally got to talk to my friend.  I have this weird empty feeling inside me.  I cant describe it other than that.  God, help me to fill this weird empty feeling. 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Actual Date:  Monday, November 10, 2003  Actual Time:  12:45am  My friend called me a couple of times today.  I missed her call.  I miss her.  She sounded half-way between good and not-good.  When I say that, I mean I think she was trying to sound brave so I dont worry about her too much.  My phone dies after two phone calls here where Im working.  Im in the mountains and signal is kind of a hit or miss situation.  Man, when I heard her voice, it was SO awesome.  I couldnt help but smile, even though Im worried about her.  So, now, Im sitting here, watching Friends, thinking of my friend, and writing in my blog (which wont be published until I can get a hold of an internet connection).  I hate being away during this time.  Let me clarify Im not having a bad time here at all I just really miss my chosen family, and my church family and my best friend.  I missed it especially yesterday I didnt get to go to church.  Wow.  I really love church, and I love going to church, its not a chore like it used to be for me when I was growing up.   1:10am  I feel like Im running away.  I feel like I had a break-through with a past feeling (or lack thereof) and now Im nowhere near anyone who I feel comfortable with to help me or talk about it.  I dont want to bother a particular friend, because they are going through a rough time right now.  I feel like Im back-peddling.  Ive come so far with my emotions and with myself and how I feel, that I dont want to mess any of that stuff up and I dont want to disappoint anyone by backsliding and slipping.  Im a very happy person right now, and I dont want to ruin it.  I may be sounding like a Im speaking a bunch of non-sense, but this stuff is all kind of jumbled in my head.  Anyway, I need to sleep.  Hopefully, I will.   9:45pm  Went to see Brother Bear tonight.  I enjoyed it, but it was lacking.  When the movie was over, I didnt feel like anything happened, it felt a lot like an extended music video for three or four Phil Collins songs with the some comic relief Moose plopped in.  Disney is starting to reach and theyve used their same formula for way too long.  At least this one wasnt a tired love story where boy meets girl, but girl doesnt like boy, or is out of reach of boy, or is evil.  Then girl meets boy and falls for him, but then something happens to make one of them think wrongly of the other yadda yadda yadda.  It wasnt a complete waste of an hour an a half, but Id wait for it to come out on video, if I were you.   9:55pm  Friend where are you?  Im using my powers of telepathy to urge you to call me.  No reason other than to talk.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Actual Date:  Sunday, November 09, 2003  Actual Time:  11:08am  I had to exert some authority yesterday in rehearsals.  People in the hall were being REALLY loud while we were working on a quieter scene of the show.  I had to go out FIVE TIMES to tell them to try to keep it down.  Not the fun part of this job at all.  Other than that, it didnt go too bad.  We were missing a couple of actors due to conflicts, and started about 40-50 minutes late due to an actors late arrival, but Scott did a great job of making up the time, and we were out of there on time.  Not too shabby.   11:22am  I miss my friend.  I hope shes doing okay.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Actual Date:  Saturday, November 08, 2003  Actual Time:  1:50am   Day One:  Started working today, my first order of business was to call all the actors to remind them of rehearsal and where it was.  Man I hate phones.  I dont mind talking to people on the phone, but I hate trying to get a hold of 25 different people to make sure theyll be somewhere at sometime.  Other than that, we had a production meeting, and then had the first read through all the actors arrived on time.  The read through went well, and some of the cast were going to Applebees to eat (and drink a little) afterwards.  We hung out and had a great time.  But alas it is now time for bed too bad I have to do some paperwork first.  Maybe Ill get some sleep.  Anyway, Im outta here.   11:45 am  I cant help thinking about my friend and how shes doing.   11:50 am  I need this time away.  Im glad Im here.  I needed to be around some people who arent in the middle of some kind of struggle.  I feel bad for feeling that way but I know its something I needed.  Sometimes I think God doesnt really have a particular schedule for things, and sometimes, I think He plans everything out to the last detail.  I wouldve felt even worse if it had happened while I was here.  Im glad He let me be there for her.  Well, thats all the personal time I get for today, time to work. 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Actual Date:  Thursday, November 6, 2003  Actual Time:  11:58 pm  Christmas Carol Gig  Arrival Well, Im all settled in here, at my home for the next two weeks.  I arrived at about 4:45 and got to see some old friends.  Scott B. and I talked a little about what Ill be doing, and we took a quick drive over to the MAC to check out the set.  Then we went back to the office and I headed to the housing.  This is really going to be weird, Im used to the housing being packed with people but only one of the three cabins are being used at all.  And theres only going to be 7 people living here.  Four are actors, one is me, and the other two wont arrive for another week.  Very odd.  On an interesting note, I got to visit with a friend from two or three years ago, Beth Brandel.  We talked for a couple of hours just about all kinds of things.  It was fun.  I went grocery shopping and believe that I bought enough food for the whole two weeks that Im here.  Tomorrow I start work, Im a little nervous.  Ive Stage Managed before, but that was a college production, and it was cake, nothing to it.  Well see how this rates in comparison.  Good night.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Stay tuned for the Christmas Carol Blog-fest that happened while I was away!
     

    
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Tonight didn't go exactly as planned.  Church was fine, I felt I did a great job with the lights, but the whole movie thing... I felt... out of place.    Maybe I should have stayed in Prestonsburg.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      ... and that's a good thing.  I saw a production of "The Fantasticks" tonight at  urlLink Studio Players .  I have a friend in the show, and she was incredible!  She played the lead female role,  urlLink Louisa .  Now, I've known  urlLink Stephanie Seales   for almost four years, and I have always known she was extremely talented (even when she doubted herself), but I was really blown away by her performance.  The whole package was there.  Her acting was amazing and precise and flowing and natural.  Her voice was strong and yet portrayed fragility.  And, let's not forget that she was  HOT !  An actress that can sing, act, and has such beauty is a force to be reckoned with.  More than this, I cannot say.  I don't have the words to express it.  I don't think they exist.  I'm sorry to say that it's only running for two more days.  More people needed to see this show, and I would've definitely liked to see it again.  I can't help but be incredibly proud of my friend.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      It seems like the city of  urlLink New York  is sick and tired of hearing them complain, too
     

    
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      To create a link to e-mail:  &lt;a href="mailto: youraddress@yourdomain.com.org.net"&gt; E-mail me&lt;/a&gt;   -to automatically add a subject line of YOUR choosing format it like this: ADD:  ?subject=My%20Blog    -use the character %20 to add spaces. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      8.  I've been watching  urlLink Smallville  on DVD, and the guy that plays Lex Luthor ( urlLink Michael Rosenbaum ) would be perfect for one of my buddies at church,  Ira Duncan .
     

    
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Colymbosathon ecplecticos  does.  This fossil has it  ALL !
     

    
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      In Spain or Mexico, is it pronounced:  VA - HINE - AH ?
     

    
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      So if you ask someone out, and add the byline "as friends"... is it still considered a date?
     

    
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Curse Japanese animation!   ... and curse  urlLink Cartoon Network  and it's  urlLink [adult swim]  for feeding my addiction!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I've worked on the blog for the past two days to try to make it somewhat more visually appealing.  Hopefully it's not too "busy".  Just wanted to get everyone's feelings on it.  Also thanks to Patrick, some of his questions spurred me on to find answers to other questions.  And the result is... well, you're looking at it.  Enjoy, and send some feedback.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Movies with  time travel  give me a headache.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I went to the bank this afternoon, like I do at least once a month for a specific type of business.  All the ladies there know me by name.  Wow, this sounds really bad, but I must continue.  I have EE Bonds that I cash in to survive while I'm in school.  And they know if I come in at the beginning of the month that I'm there for that reason.  So I'm waiting to get into my deposit box and one of the ladies says hi to me from across the room.  And brilliant ole' me says loud enough for most of the bank (filled with women, mind you), "Yep, it's that time of the month!"  "Hmm..." I thought to myself, "that maybe sounded wrong out of context."  So I say back to her, "That didn't sound so good, did it?"  The whole bank of people just about roared with laughter, as did I.  I brought attention to my mistake, and brought smiles and laughs to over a dozen people this afternoon.  That's gotta be  some  kind of productivity for the day.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      6. Y'gotta have Mel.   urlLink Mel Gibson  would play the part of my friend  Jon Adams .    7. His wife,  Erin , would be played by  urlLink Michelle Pfeiffer . 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I had a pretty good time tonight.  I haven't had just a relaxing time hanging out with anyone since that Saturday night at JWT sitting around playing cards and having a drink... and before that... sheesh, who knows?  Yeah, it was great, but I still need to find some single friends where I don't have to look at, think about, or talk about significant others for a bit.  I'm very glad that people are happy, I just want that for myself, too.  When you don't have that, but you want it, your heart aches... and sometimes you just need to take your mind off of it.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Another possibility to play yours truly would be  Seth Green .  I had not previously thought about this one until Stephanie mentioned him to me, neither of us could think of his name at the time, but she told me the character he played in the Austin Powers movies, Scott.  Coincidence?  I think maybe it definitely probably could be.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Geez, that hurts...   Just finished watching an episode of friends on TV.  One from the first season.  In this particular episode, Ross realizes that the day is the anniversary of his and his lesbian ex-wife's consummation... which was his first time ever.  Later on Chandler and Joey are let in on this and they tell Ross really nice things about "how special that was to wait" and that sort of thing.  After he leaves, they call him a freak.  Now, as you may or may not know, I am a virgin.  Yes, yes, I am.  I'm not ashamed of it, but it's not really something I go around shouting to the hills and so-forth.  Just makes me wonder about the times I  have  told people and they say nice things and sweet things and how it's going to be special and all that, if when I leave they say, "wow, that's really weird, I can't believe there are weirdo's like that around" or other possibly worse scenarios.  My time is not yet, and I'm not looking to rush it, but I don't want to be considered a freak due to something I haven't done.    ANYhoo... that's a bit of a downer, and kind of a shot to the gut.  I need to get my wind back now.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       LEO   It surprises you to find out that some of the opinions you had up to this point might not be as set in stone as you previously thought. It isn't your intention to get into a political, religious or otherwise controversial conversation, but for some reason, you seem to draw people to you who are interested in doing that very thing. The strange thing is, once you take some time to digest their point of view, you find yourself agreeing with it despite the fact that it's the opposite of how you used to feel. You may not change your mind wholeheartedly, but there is definitely room for compromise.   The "stars" really don't know me at all, do they? 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Not good.  Not good at all.  Don't  encourage  this guy!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I wonder if  Duane Hurley  realizes that he's going to have to share.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Playground Treated To Hot Pug-On-Pug Action  PROVIDENCE, RIChildren playing on the swingsets at Waldo Street Tot Lot were treated to a raw, uncensored display of hot pug-on-pug action, sources reported Tuesday. "First the one doggy got behind the other doggy," said Andy Haupert, 6. "Then the first doggy tried to get on top of the other doggy while the other doggy tried to run away. It was really funny." The canine copulation has been the most talked-about animal-related playground incident since June, when a pigeon crapped all the way down the slide.   Bacon Good For You, Reports Best Scientist Ever  ROCHESTER, MNBacon, long believed to contribute to heart disease and obesity, possesses significant health benefits, according to a study released Monday by Dr. Albert Gruber, the best scientist ever. "My research has found that three strips of crispy, mouthwatering bacon every morning can actually reduce cholesterol and help slow the aging process," the awesome Gruber said. "What's more, the bacon's positive effects are enhanced when combined with milk shakes and/or marijuana." In 1997, Gruber, a Mayo Clinic cardiologist, was awarded nine Nobel Prizes in Medicine for discovering that frequent oral sex with models cures cancer.   Rookie Trucker Always On CB To Mother  LUBBOCK, TXTwo weeks into his new job driving an 18-wheeler for the Harper Red Line, trucker Billy Ray Coogan, 23, still talks frequently with his mother on his CB radio. "Breaker 1-9, Mother Hen, this here's Red Rooster, come on," said an obviously nervous Coogan. "Are you sand-bagging, Mother Hen? 'Cause the boss man's got me hauling a dead-head to Abilene, and I'm a little nervous. I...I could really use some company, 10-4." Coogan went on to say that if his mother would just say the word, he'd do a flip-flop and put the hammer down to be back home in the short-short, in time for dinner. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm thinking of changing the casting of my best friend  Stephanie Seales  from Jennifer Connelly to  urlLink this girl .  The reason, I have just come to find out that she likes the smell of skunk.  Any questions? Good.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Yes. I'm definitely ready to be done with college.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I ripped this from a friend's blog... if you've already seen  this , sorry, but I think it's worth repeating.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      When you're with someone, they seem to always be on the phone or getting calls or making calls.  But when you try to call them, you can't get a hold of them. Why is that?  Another of life's confusing mysteries.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      4.  urlLink Keanu Reeves  is the closet in appearance to my friend  Josh Paugh .  And he's softer spoken much like many of Reeves characters.  5. Friend,  Brian Stocks  would be played by  urlLink Vin Disel .  They're both bad-a$$es and Brian kinda looked like Vin when his head was shaved.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I just got a call from the Artistic Director from  urlLink Jenny Wiley Theatre .  He called to ask about my interest for the up-coming summer season.  He wanted to know if I was interested in Designing one of the shows.  Of course I said, Yes.  Unlike my designs in the past, this one will be the first that I'm actually paid specifically for.  I'll be getting a designer's fee on top of my pay that I get for being the Master Electrician.  Very exciting times! Very exciting!  The summer is too far away.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      We had a production meeting today for  Other People's Money , a play being produced by  urlLink Studio Players  in Lexington.  I feel like such a professional.  This is actually going to be my first full design that's completely mine.  I've designed lights previously at  urlLink Jenny Wiley Theatre  for Children's Productions and a talent show.  My first design that I'm really proud of came this past summer when I was given the opportunity to design for a cabaret-style show called, "Hooray for Hollywood: An Evening of Song in Film".  The number that brought down the house was the most fun to light... a song from the musical, "CHICAGO" ... the  urlLink Cell Block Tango .  JWT even put it as a  urlLink publicity shot  on their website.  But for the cabaret, I used someone else's light plot and worked with that.  For Studio Players... it's  urlLink all mine !    I'm really excited, but my only question is how do I express that without sounding like I'm bragging or too proud?  I don't think anyone else will be as excited as me, and a lot of people don't quite "get it" I guess.  Maybe someone will and will pat me on the back a bit.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hey everyone.  It has been brought to my attention that some browsers may not view my page correctly.  800x600 screen resolutions will put half of my Left Side Bar stuff below the main post section.  So, scroll on down to the bottom to check the rest of the stuff out, or change your screen resolution.  Sorry, I don't know how to fix it any other way.  Hello and thanks to everyone who's been commenting, and for everyone who's been reading.  I hope you continue to enjoy.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Today dawns a new day... well, definitely tomorrow, I need today to adjust!
     

    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      tired... but... can't sleep.  Must.... blog. .. . ..zzzzzzzzzz
     

    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      3. Roomate  Brian Ink  would be played by  urlLink Jim Carey .  Two reasons... one: some of the faces Brian makes could only be accurately  urlLink re-inacted  by Jim Carey, and two: I think Jim could play just about  urlLink anybody  at any given time.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Okay, so I'm going to jump on the band wagon and try to cast my life as a movie. Here goes:  1.  urlLink Ron Howard  would play  yours-truly , I get the most comments that I look like him, especially when I need a haircut and start wearing my hat all the time.  Of course, he'd have to get a hair-piece.  And that guy he's talking to would play "that one guy I talked to that one time".  2. My best friend,  Stephanie Seales  would be played by one of the most beautiful and classy actresses that I've seen,  urlLink Jennifer Connelly .  Hey, I even found one with us  urlLink together .  Okay, so it would have to be a slightly younger Ron Howard.  I'm stumped, any ideas for someone to play me?
     

    
</post>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Hasbro Pledges Additional 30 Marbles For Hippo-Hunger Relief  PAWTUCKET, RI - With global famine worsening, Hasbro pledged an additional 30 white marbles Monday to hippo-hunger relief efforts. "To see those starving, starving hippos just lying there, not knowing if they will ever get another chance to click and clack for life-giving marbles it's too much for anyone to bear," Hasbro spokeswoman Lisa Reiderer said. "We cannot stand idly by while these sweet plastic creatures slowly die. It is up to all of us to get the most marbles for our hippos."   Couple Always Like This  QUINCY, MA - Longtime couple Scott Pfaff and Lisa Baumgartner have pretty much always been like this, sources close to the pair revealed Monday. "This is definitely no news-flash," said mutual friend Stacie Pritkin, who recently hosted a party during which the pair was at it as usual. "You hang out with those two, you learn to expect that sort of stuff." Said Pfaff's friend Mark Dohn: "I was at the mall with them once when they started getting like that - right in Radio Shack."   United States Toughens Image With Umlauts  WASHINGTON, DC - In a move designed to make the United States seem more "bad-assed and scary in a quasi-heavy-metal manner," Congress passed a bill Monday changing the nation's name to the United States of America. "Much like Motley Crue and Motorhead, the United States is not to be messed with," said Sen. James Inhofe (R-OK). An upcoming redesign of the American flag will feature the new name in burnished silver wrought in a jagged, gothic font and bolted to a black background. A new national anthem is also in the works, to be written by composer Glenn Danzig and tentatively titled "Howl Of The She-Demon." (this one's not quite the same without the umlauts.. check it out  urlLink here .)  
     

    
</post>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      How would you like to work  urlLink here  with this guy's job?
     

    
</post>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Arby's must be running out of ideas.  I guess there's really only so much you can do with  urlLink Roast Beef .
     

    
</post>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       An hour and fourteen minutes.   Pretty good for someone who really doesn't like talking on the phone.  And the conversation never felt dull.... until the end.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       UPDATES, UPDATES, UPDATES!!!   In an effort to feel more comfortable with giving my blog address out to more people, I'm "lightening up".  Also, I'm working on the layout and different things to make people  want  to come back and check it out.  For pure and unmatched intellect and cleverness, visit Steph's or Patrick's blog (if you have the address).  Maybe I'll come up with something good every now and then, though... you'll never know unless you come back. [GRIN]
     

    
</post>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      "It's like butter and chocolate syrup."  - -Greg Chandler (describing how performances were good, just not good together)
     

    
</post>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Announcer:  Yes, ladies and gentlemen, YOU TOO, can look and feel cooler in less than seven days!  That's right folks, in less than a week, you can feel on top of the world.  All you have to do is rush out and get a truly awesome friend like this man has.   Scott:  [obviously reading from a card] I am not an actor, I am an actual person who has an extraordinary friend.  My secret is Stephanie Seales.  What's  yours ? [smiles a really big, dumb smile and looks straight into the camera]   Announcer : So go out, NOW, and hug a friend and thank them for showing you the error of  YOUR  ways.  
     

    
</post>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       The true testament of friendship #5.   They keep a couple of your favorite drinks stocked in the fridge, just in case you come over.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      At times I wished I had a sibling or two, so I could be "uncle scott".  One of my little cousins called me that over this past weekend, and it made my heart feel all warm inside... of course, I'll never be an uncle.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Thanksgiving:  getting "stuffed" at dinner, grabbing some floor to watch the football game/take a nap, and then wrestling around with the little cousins.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       The true testament of friendship #4.   If you call in the middle of the night and wake them up, they say, "It's no problem, I was already awake."
     

    
</post>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      TV theme songs get stuck in my head all the time... so it spawned this post:  1. Friends 2. Greatest American Hero 3. Gummy Bears 4. Cheers 5. MacGuyver 6. Charles in Charge  Any that I missed?  I'm sure there are!  Send me some!  Maybe I'll add them to this list!
     

    
</post>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Nov 26, 8:16 am ET    MIAMI (Reuters) - Fighter jets were scrambled at Miami airport on Tuesday after an elderly woman threw a fit on an American Airlines plane and flight attendants thought she would attack them, police said. Reports said the woman was aged between 69 and 79.  "They said old," a police spokeswoman said, adding she could not confirm her precise age.  The pilot of flight AA-2133 with 126 passengers on board announced an emergency as a precaution shortly after taking off for Caracas, and fighter jets were scrambled to escort the plane back to Miami international airport.  The plane landed safely.  ::: What is the world coming to when the elderly can't throw a simple fit on an airline any more!?! I mean, what happened to respect for the elderly, huh?! 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      My two month blog-aversary is coming up.  Maybe we'll do somthing nice. :)  Any thoughts?
     

    
</post>

<date>13,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Thanks to my roommate and friend, Dustin, I am beginning to get in the Christmas Spirit.  I had been off to a slow start, but tonight, we put up a Christmas Tree and decorated our apartment while listening to holiday music.  It was really a lot of fun.  I took a few pictures of our tree, and I'll try to get those up here in a day or two.    There's only one thing that would make this holiday season better right now.  (it's not the obvious "gee, I don't have  a girlfriend" answer) 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      IT'S SNOWING OUTSIDE!!!!!!  "We could go outside and build a snowman...." "Walkin' in a winter wonderland..." "Rock the casba, rock the ..."  (wait, that one doesn't really go.) 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Small Life to Big Screen - Casting Project   It has been said that I look similar to three people... I'm putting it up to you to vote (via the comment section) who would be better to play me.   1.   urlLink Ron Howard   (younger - more like Richie Cunningham age)   2.   urlLink Seth Green   (as cast by my good friend, Stephanie)   3.   urlLink Clay Aiken   (also, if my movie became a musical, he could play me then, too)   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Distance:  It can be a good thing or a bad thing.  Por ejemplo: Distance between my face and someone's fist, the more the merrier.  Distance between friends, bad.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Went bowling last night for the first time in a bout a year.  Broke a hundred both games I bowled.  Also bowled one of the better games I've played, scored a 124.  Not the best I've done, but definitely not the worst.  It was good.  Went to eat at Denny's afterwards... oh the memories of Denny's.  My town got rid of their Denny's and put in a Liquor Mart.  What crap.  I miss the Moons over Myhammy, the Grand Slam, American Slam, and French Slam breakfasts.  Their cheese eggs were some of the best.  Ahhh... late night at Denny's. [sigh] The good old days.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Want  urlLink FREE MOVIE tickets ? Sure you do!
     

    
</post>

<date>12,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I have recently made a bad decision. I won't let it happen again. 'Nuff said.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Woman:  So when do I get to know you?   Man:  What do you mean? You already know me.   Woman:  No, I mean in the biblical sense.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       I was introduced to this list in college and thought it was the funniest thing I've ever read.  Hours of entertainment.  I hope you find it at least mildly entertaining.    Ghost Poopie  The kind where you feel the Poopie come out, but there's no poopie in the toilet.    Clean Poopie  The kind where you poopie it out, see it in the toilet, but there is nothing on the toilet paper.    Wet Poopie  The kind where you wipe your butt fifty times and it still feels unwiped, so you have to put some toilet paper between your butt and your underwear so you don't runie them with a stain.    Second Wave Poopie  The kind that happens when you're done poopie-ing and you've pulled your pants up to your knees, and you realize you have to poopie some more.    Turtle Poopie  The kind of poopie that pops out a little and goes back in a few times before it finallly comes out    Pop-a-Vein-in-your-Forehead-Poopie  The kind where you strain so much to get it out, you practically have a stroke.    Lincoln Log Poopie  The kind of Poopie that is so huge you're afraid to flush without first breaking it into little pieces with the plunger.    Gas-sy Poopie  The kind where it's so noisy, everyone within earshot is giggling!    Drinker Poopie  The kind of Poopie you have the morning after a long night of drinking. It's most noticeable trait is the skid marks on the bottom of the toilet.    Corn Poopie  (Self explanatory)    Gee-I-Wish-I-Could-Poop Poopie  The kind where you want to Poopie, but all you do is it on the toilet and fart a few times.    Spinal Tap Poopie  That's the kind when it hurts so badly coming out, you swear it was leaving you sideways.    Wet Cheeks Poopie (aka The Power Dump)  The kind that comes out of your butt so fast, your butt cheeks get spashed with water.    Liquid Poopie  The kind where yellowish-brown liquid shoots you of your butt and spashes all over the toilet bowl.    Mexican Poopie  The kind that smells so bad your nose burns.    Upper Class Poopie  The kind of Poopie that doesn't smell.    The Suprise Poopie  You are not even at the toilet, because you are sure you are about to fart, but, OOPS---a Poopie!    The Dangling Poopie  This Poopie refuses to drop into the toilet even though you know you are done poopie-ing. You just pray that a shake or two will cut it loose.   Fisherman's Bobber Poopie   You are in a public restroom with two people waiting on your stall, you poopie and flush two times, but several golfball pieces are still floating above the water line.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      All  urlLink crooks  should be this honest.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Dec 12, 9:39 am ET   BUDAPEST (Reuters)  - Hungary moved Thursday to stop users of new camera mobile phones from taking and sending snapshots of people without their permission. Hungary's data protection ombudsman ruled that mobile users transmitting pictures of people who are unaware of being photographed could be liable to prosecution -- as could the mobile service providers.  Ombudsman Attila Peterfalvi said he started an investigation after one of Hungary's three mobile providers ran an advertisement saying: "If you see a good-looking girl or guy on the street, don't hesitate to share the aesthetic experience with your friends via MMS."  Mobile phones, kitted out with small cameras used in multimedia messaging (MMS), are selling fast in Hungary, where mobile penetration is a high 75.2 percent.  "...taking and transmitting recordings without legal or personal accord is unlawful data handling and can lead to civil, or in some cases penal, responsibility," Peterfalvi said.  Regulators around the world are trying to get to grips with the spread of camera phones and their invasion of privacy.  The phones, with their tiny, discreet lens and ready access to the Internet, have prompted fears that voyeurs could take advantage of this new technology.  South Korea's telecommunications minister recently decreed that all camera phones must emit a beep of at least 65 decibels when taking a photo, even when the phone was in silent mode. 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Take full account of what excellencies which you possess, and in gratitude remember how you would hanker after them, if you had them not. - Marcus Aurelius
     

    
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well, that was hardly worth it.  Just a little bit of patience and it's better. So now I'm back to the old Comment tool.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Sorry folks, it seems that  urlLink CommentThis.com , my previous comment host is having technical difficulties.  For the meantime, I've switched to  urlLink BlogSpeak .  As soon as I can tell that CommentThis is back up, I'll switch back, I really like them better than this one... but BlogSpeak works.  Thanks.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      The best portion of a good man's life is the little, nameless, unremembered acts of kindness and love. - William Wordsworth
     

    
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Okay, I was walking through Wal-Mart tonight when I happened upon a very disturbing sight.  I'm sure all of you are familiar with how boxers (the underwear, not the hard-hittinglook and function... with the verticle slit in the front that serves as a fly where there may or may not be a button to keep it together.  In Wal-Mart there was this freak of nature that disturbed me greatly, I can't even imagine wearing it.  It was a boxer short with a pocket on the front.  Right in the middle.  It looked like a pocket that goes on the back of pants normally, but it was dead front and center.  Of course you can't keep change in this pocket, because there's a hole in it!  It's a penis pocket.  Reach in looking for your car keys... no no... there's something else in there!  It's just WRONG, man!
     

    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       MANILA (Reuters)  - An irate Filipino housewife sliced off her husband's penis while he slept after she discovered text messages from another woman on his mobile phone. A local radio station reported the woman rushed her husband to hospital in Manila Thursday when large amounts of blood flowed from his wound, but that she forgot to bring the severed piece of flesh.  Doctors were able to restore his manhood after she raced home to collect the missing piece. The man, a welder, told the radio station he had forgiven his wife.  Callers to the station, reacting to the news, offered helpful hints to wayward husbands such as never sleeping on their backs and always keeping mobile phones tucked under the pillow. 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I made some small adjustments to the blog tonight.  Check them out, and let me know what you think.  Questions? Comments? Suggestions? Snide Remarks?
     

    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Okay, so there's one thing to talk about.  The Smoking Ban in public places in Lexington went through and if my sources are correct, it goes into effect tomorrow!  YAY!  No more coming home smelling like cancer sticks!
     

    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Zero.  Nope.  Nothing to tell today.  Sorry.  Today's been a pretty boring day.  Woke up.  Had lunch.  Tried to blog, and this is all I came up with.  Maybe tomorrow.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       ... One Giant Kick in the Nuts for the Not-so-good-looking.    urlLink Sad days  in the life of mediocre looking males everywhere.  The  urlLink Average Joe  didn't get picked, the hot n hunky man was the choice.   urlLink Good looks  won out over  urlLink personality .
     

    
</post>

<date>08,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      A friend senses something is wrong, and somehow knows just the right thing to say.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Ahhh.  Nice relaxing evening at home.  Haven't had one of those in a while.  I've been home, but it's not been relaxing, usually.  My roommate got a new couch, it's nice.  Vegged out on that most of the evening and watched TV.  It was great.  I'm glad I have something to do tomorrow, though.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Okay, I'm done with the numbering it was giving me a headache.   My other roommate and longtime friend  Dustin McClain  would be played by  urlLink Breckin Meyer .  And his girlfriend,  Katie  would be played by  urlLink Chyler Leigh .   Rose Colem ... wait, no, she's married now, to Josh  Paugh .  Wow, what a slip up!  Anyway,  Rose  would be played by  urlLink Jodi Foster .  A good friend of mine that lives WAY too many miles away,  Bethany Hayes , would be played by  urlLink Reese Whitherspoon .  Just imagine blonder and curlier hair.  My friend and her fiancee  Mark Smith , would be played by  urlLink Paul Gross .  
     

    
</post>

<date>07,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Love.  What a powerful four-letter word.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       BERLIN   (Reuters)  - A German vicar inadvertently supplied his parish with dozens of hard core porn films in an unsuccessful bid to teach people about the life of Christ. Frithjof Schwesig, vicar in the southwestern town of Lampoldshausen, had ordered 300 copies of a video film portraying the life of Christ as told by the gospel according to Luke.  "In a first batch 20 to 30 videos were distributed and we immediately got a reaction from five to seven people saying we must have given them the wrong film," he said.  "It was a real porn film. Within an hour our staff had collected all the videos. Really, all were withdrawn."  Schwesig said there had been a mistake at the Munich video copying plant and his staff established in a viewing session that night that 200 of the videos were pornographic.  Undaunted, Schwesig said he was pressing ahead with the life of Christ video campaign.  "It's extremely successful," he said. 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      ... No, I'm not talking about phone sex lines.  I'm talking about those random phone calls that you get from friends just out-of-the-blue.  Those are some of the best conversations I've ever had.  When a friend just decides that they want to talk to you and possibly for no other reason than to say "HI" and "I was thinking about you".  Now, I don't usually get those kinds of calls from friends.  They always have a purpose behind them, not malicious or anything, but usually it's to solidify plans or ask a question that I may know the answer to.  Today, I had TWO such phone calls... quite a record, I believe.  The first from a great friend of mine, and then the second a couple hours later from a new friend.  Just makes me feel all warm inside... kind of like a big gulp of a hot vanilla chai from  urlLink Live Wire  (a coffee place down the street from where I live).  I think I'll go get one and keep up this really neat feeling.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      A good friend and one of the ministers at my church,  urlLink Steve Edens , would be played by  urlLink Rob Thomas  from Matchbox Twenty.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Tonight... better than I thought.  Had a nice relaxing evening at home.  Did a little bit of  urlLink work .  Cleaned up a little... and now I'm off to bed.  Good night, world, see you tomorrow!
     

    
</post>

<date>18,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I fully endorse and support this  urlLink half-time  event.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      The worst part about hanging out with good friends in a bar, is after you step out the door, but before you arrive home.  About 5 minutes after you get into your car, you realize you smell like shit.  That is, if shit smelled like cigarette smoke.  If it did, I'd never want to take another dump for the rest of my life.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       [holding up a chair, lion-tamer style]  Whoa, back, back I say!  There's too many of you... one at a time!
     

    
</post>

<date>16,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well, it's official... we're  urlLink f#@ked .
     

    
</post>

<date>15,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Upon reading a friend's blog, I stumbled upon this website.  I found myself very captivated and feeling very good generally speaking afterwards.  I encourage everyone to take a few minutes to check out  urlLink this website .
     

    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      "Love is patient, love is kind. It does not envy, it does not boast, it is not proud. It is not rude, it is not self-seeking, it is not easily angered, it keeps no record of wrongs. Love does not delight in evil but rejoices with the truth. It always protects, always trusts, always hopes, always perseveres. Love never fails."        I Corinthians 13:4-8a (NIV)
     

    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Neurosurgeon Heckled From Observation Deck  HOUSTONDr. Martin Kenneth Rinjipur, a neurosurgeon at Methodist Hospital, was heckled from the observation deck Monday after removing a cancerous tumor from a patient's occipital lobe. "You call that closing an incision?" the unidentified man shouted. "I could make a cleaner suture with 15 centimeters of frayed chromic gut and a pair of barbecue tongs. Go back to Johns Hopkins." Rinjipur did his best to act like he had not heard the comments.   Drunken Episode A Repeat  PARMA, OHSunday's episode involving drunken house-party guest Philip Welz was a repeat, guests reported. "I couldn't bear to watch it again," Robert Joffe said. "Sure, some parts, like when Phil pees in front of everyone, or when he pretends to have sex with the pets, are sort of entertaining the second time around, but on the whole, it was pretty tough to sit through twice." Joffe left the party early in order to avoid the episode's final moments, when Welz pukes on himself and passes out.   Baby Boring  TAMARAC, FLMichelle, the three-week-old daughter of area residents Sue and Allen McKay, is "unbelievably boring," sources close to the couple said Monday. "Sue's always raving about how amazing Michelle is," friend Elena Jacobs said. "But then you meet her, and she barely moves. Who knows? Maybe Michelle is an incredibly charming and engaging little mastermind during the 20 minutes each day that she's awake and not crying." Jacobs added that Michelle must have been born with her mother's eyes and her father's total lack of personality. 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      For those of you who don't already get  urlLink enough .
     

    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      This  urlLink explains  a lot.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Think  you're  bored?  I thought I was too, until I read  urlLink this .
     

    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      "I can't change the world, but I can try to change myself."
     

    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      The Bengals are actually making a  urlLink good run  this season. ... huh... guess sticking with a team through the bad times really pays off... eventually.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Yeah, we got  urlLink him ... so what now?
     

    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Ever wonder what your ratio of doing things  right  to doing things  wrong  is?
     

    
</post>

<date>23,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      What does it mean when you get a big goofy grin on your face every time you think about a particular person?  I've got a big goofy grin on my face, right now.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      My last post before I head out onto the road for the holidays is this one.  I saw this on a  urlLink friend's blog  and I guess I just want to drive that point home to anyone that reads both of us.  "Invest in things that matter and enjoy every second of every day." 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Season's Greetings!   I'll be stepping away from my blog for a few days ( the crowd applauds loudly ) as I'm heading off for the holidays to do the family thing.  This is one of my favorite times of the year... I have a really big family, and it keeps expanding.  I love the feeling of such togetherness during this time.  It is amazing how close you can feel to people that you only see once or twice a year compared to people you may see once a week or more.  (If you're reading this, I'm more than likely not talking about you, so rest your fears if there were any)  But what this post really is all about is my wishes to all of you to have a very merry, happy, and safe holiday!  May God bless you through your encounters and keep you safe on your travels, and may you all keep in mind what Christmas is really about.  It's about a celebration of a life that was brought into this world that would one day save us all.   God bless you all, and have a Merry Christmas! 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Why am I so incredibly happy when I feel like there is nothing really to be incredibly happy about?  I don't get it...  ...but I like it!
     

    
</post>

<date>21,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      For some reason, I've been a little off-kilter for a couple weeks (more-so than usual).  I feel like I'm working my way back to "me".  That makes me happy.  So I'm making myself happy.  No one else has done it.  At least no one on earth.  I can't take complete credit.  Sometimes I need to listen to my heart more than my mind.  I need to open up, and not be afraid to get hurt.  There's no way to actually shield myself completely from that, anyway, so why try?  At least with friends, the healing can happen quicker than if I keep myself closed off.  Also, the last Well service that I'll be able to attend happened tonight, and afterwards, a Christmas Party that we had prepared.  I think it went really well.  To me, it was part funeral, part celebration, but total dedication and thanksgiving.  That service is what got me involved at Crossroads, those people are the ones who pulled me into their lives, and those lives that gave me a home when and if there was no other.  I know that I'm going to have to let it go... and like dealing with a lost loved one... I'll mourn and then I'll move on.  I had a couple people come up to me tonight to express their excitement that I was a part of that place, and that my skills and energy were looked forward to being integrated into the regular weekend services and the church as a whole.  This was all originally thanks to two people: long-time friends - Ben Stewart and Stephanie Seales.  Without their encouragement, I wouldn't have come as far as I have, as fast as I have.  Thank you.  Now that just has to give you the feeling that something is going right for you.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Situation: You invite someone (in this case, a girl) to go do something.... say, a movie.  Then she asks if she can bring a friend along.  What should you do?  Advice?
     

    
</post>

<date>02,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Hypothetical Conversation   Guy: Hey, let's go out tonight!  Girl: Okay. What do you want to do.  Guy: I was thinking maybe a movie.  Girl: Sounds great!  Guy: Yeah, so... can you pick me up, I don't have car.   [How romantic]   [Portions of this conversation have been made up] 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Okay, for those of you who don't know (or actually care), my car's transmission has been on the fritz for about a month now.  I was finally able to take it in to get it worked on this past Tuesday, and they said it was possible it would be ready the next afternoon.  Great!  I call Wednesday around noon, and they said the transmission was being put back together, then they'd take it out to test it, so please call back around 2:30 - 3:00.  So I do.  When I do, they tell me that one of the parts they ot in was bad (just a part that should've been a reject off the line) and my car wouldn't be ready until Friday... today.  So I call around 11:30am to ask about my car, and theytell me the truck with the part on it never arrived, so it wouldn't be ready until Monday.  Recap: Been without a care since Tuesday, having to bum rides from people everywhere I go.
     

    
</post>

<date>31,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm having a tough time deciding if the New Year is starting off well or not.  I really enjoyed where I started it, and who I started it with.  So for that much, it's going great.  Let's just say,  questions  and  doubts .
     

    
</post>

<date>31,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Okay, I may not have much, if any, experience with dating and girls... but I do know that  urlLink THIS  is  not  the way to go about winning the heart of a woman.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Several circumstances negated my plans for tonight. But tomorrow's outlook is full of goofy grins.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Okay, so my holidays (so far) have been great!  I had a blast visiting with my family (even more-so than usual), I got to talk to an awesome person almost everyday on the phone while I was gone.  I learned that Bailey's Irish Cream goes really well with Eggnog.  Chocolate Cookies with Peanut Butter chips are STILL my favorite.  It truly doesn't matter what or how many gifts you receive.  I missed getting to experience the Christmas Eve service at my church since I was away visiting my family.  I got to see two really good friends (who are about to become one great friend - so to speak... they're getting married in April) and found out that they are moving to the area in August or September!   My Christmas List:   A cool new doo, to impress the ladies Seeing my all-time favorite Christian band's farewell tour A cool "lego"-type set of Optimus Prime An awesome see-thru deck of cards Another deck of awesome cards that are long and thin! Star Wars: Jedi Knight - Jedi Academy game for XBOX A set of Legos 264 leather CD case Small wooden figure of my Grandfather's business in the town where my mom grew up A little black waste bag for my car A nice long sleeve shirt (heather blue) a phantom of the opera ornament  and   MONEY!    There may be a couple things I'm forgetting, but that's pretty much it, I think.  It was great.... and my holiday season isn't over yet!  New Years Eve is just a day away!  I'm SO looking forward to that!
     

    
</post>

<date>29,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      It's amazing how much one post will change the "holiness" of your blog.  Before the last post, I was somewhere around 51% EVIL... that's right, talking about infatuation (not to be confused with flatulation) dropped me down to 49% GOOD... now, right before this post I'm up to 85% GOOD, again.  Well see how this post affects it even more!
     

    
</post>

<date>29,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      My head feels like it's swimming in big dumb goofy grinning thoughts.  Yeah, I just talked to her.  I may be wrong, but I think I just asked her out on a date.  The word date never came into play, I just asked her to go see a movie with me. Is it a date?  How does this all work? Am I doing it right?  WHAT'S GOING ON HERE!!!????  I could really get used to this dumb smile.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Big, big, BIG goofy grin.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Alright... we know how smart we are, but HOW are we smart?  Take  urlLink this test  to see!   The Multiple Intelligences Test    Scott, you're smartest when it comes to visual/spatial intelligence   Others may take their environments for granted but not you. Because of your visual/spatial intelligence you really see the world around you. This strength often helps you better appreciate the beauty and detail in everyday things. From shapes in nature to the structure of a fine automobile, a countless variety of things hold your interest.   Having this particular kind of heightened awareness can allow you to form accurate mental images of existing places and objects. In extreme cases, one might call this strength a photographic memory. Being visually/spatially intelligent also means that you likely have a vivid imagination that can be put to use in a variety of creative or professional endeavors.   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, that didn't take nearly as long as I had figured, and kind of had hoped.  Everything looks good though... at least without actors on stage.  Tomorrow night will be the real test.  But for now... I'm bored.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Apparently no one knows how to answer a phone, so I'm at home... bored.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
       (to see what was up previously, visit Tuesday, December 02, 2003)   I'm almost finished with the design aspect of the show.  I hung, focused, and gelled the final lighting instruments I need for  urlLink Studio Player's  production of  Other People's Money .  Tomorrow at noon, the director and I, along with the stage manager and a stray actor or two, hash out how the show will flow lighting-wise.  I'm really excited about seeing what my first full design project is going to look like in the context of the show with people on stage emoting and such.  It's just not the same just staring at the set with lights turned on.  Now I want to see what people look like underneath the lime light (which there is none of actually in this show).
     

    
</post>

<date>08,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      New Visual Stimulation on the sidebar. Enjoy.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Bored and Lonely.  Now accepting entries for something to do.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      MXC, also known as Most Extreme Elimination Challenge, has GOT to be one of the most hilarious shows on TV.  It's a great show for a bunch of people to sit around, watch, and laugh at.  The SPIKE network has done an incredible job with their programming geared for men.  And thank you for running three straight hours of it during card night at the apartment!    Cards, friends, junk food, and Japanese people humiliating themselves on TV for who knows what or why, is the best way to spend at least one night a week!
     

    
</post>

<date>08,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "All you can eat. Don't use your hands."   This is an "advertisement" that I heard on mXc last night. Cracked my s**t up!
     

    
</post>

<date>08,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, to all TWO people who I know regulary visit my blog  (Thanks Patrick and Stephanie)  this one's for you!  Yeah, sorry, there's still very little to be told that I haven't already.  Starting Jan 15, 2003,  urlLink Studio Players  is producing a show called  OTHER PEOPLE'S MONEY .  I have designed the lights for the show, and I'm very excited about seeing it on it's feet.  I'd also love to see a lot of people in the audience that I know to see my first full-fledged lighting design.  Spread the word.  Other People's Money at Studio Player's in Lexington.  January 15 thru February 1. 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Sorry folks, I've got nothing.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A few things:   1.   For the first time in my life, car repairs have actually cost LESS than I was quoted.  2.   I feel like a giant in my little Chevy Cavalier compared to the nice roomy interior of the 2004 Honda Accord that I was renting.  3.   It's good to have my car back.  4.   No more having to explain why I don't want to drive somewhere.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I just called about my car, and they said they'd have it together in about forty-five minutes!!!  Then they'd test it, and (hopefully) it'll be MINE AGAIN!!!!!  I can't wait... stay tuned, true believers!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The past two days have been filled with lighting, chili, friends, and goofy grins.  It's been great, but there's been a slight emptyness.  Something that wasn't there that usually is.  But I've plodded on, and continued to be happy even in the face of this void.  The big goofy grin saga continues.  I had a lot of fun yesterday.  I just enjoy being around her.  Right now, those are the only words I can put to it.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Okay.  So finally on Friday I went and rented a car from Enterprise.  I reserved my car online and my roommate took me in to pick it up... pretty easy.  When I got there I saw an old friend... and he happens to be the manager of the place.  I haven't seen him in a while, and I don't think he ever knew my last name or anything, so when the reservation came in, he didn't recognize my name.  When I got there he immediately recognized me and my roommate (although he still sees him on a more consistant basis).  He gave me a hard time and stuff like friends do, and then he cut me a really sweet deal.  Instead of driving around in a Geo or another Cavalier, he set me up with a too sweet 2004 Honda Accord... pretty loaded, too.  I tell you, as of right now, driving hasn't been much sweeter.  I even took a drive on I-75 one night just to drive it.  It's been a great time, and I'm not looking forward to Monday anymore (which is when I get my car back, supposedly).    Y'know, actually, if my car is working the way it should when I get it back... I'll love it!   (and for $1500.00, it better!) 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I love it.  A bigger dork than me.  Check it out  urlLink here .  By the way... I wouldn't be caught dead driving it.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Just think , you're here  not  by chance, but by  God's choosing . His had  formed  you and made you the person you are. He compares you to  no one else  -  you are one of a kind. You  lack nothing  that His grace can't give you. He has allowed you to be here at this  time in history  to fulfill His special purpose for this generation.   How  thankful I am  that He has allowed me to be here at the  same time  you are!
     

    
</post>

<date>15,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have to laugh at myself sometimes because on the way home from the show tonight, I caught wiff of fresh pole-cat.  That's skunk.  Now the first thing that comes to my mind isn't, "Gee, what an aweful smell".  No, the first thing that pops into my head is that a friend of mine told me that they actually liked the smell of skunks.  I'll always think of you, friend, when I smell skunk while travelling down the road.  God love ya'.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I really hate the first day of classes.  My stomach works itself up into knots, and I feel semi nauseous most of the day.  Today's not starting out much different.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Cast in the name of God.... Ye Not Guilty
     

    
</post>

<date>14,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Feeling a bit "blah" today.  I'm going to be missing out on a certain someone's Birthday festivities tonight because of the show I'm involved in.  It really bothers me.  I really get into birthdays, probably to make up for usually having really crappy ones myself.  I have some really good presents for her, too.  I'd hate to have to give them to her later than her Birthday.  I really hope she likes them.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This was a  urlLink good time .  This is what I like to remember.  Not right now.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I grabbed this from a friend's  urlLink blog .  "Enjoy life.  The world could end tomorrow."
     

    
</post>

<date>12,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well due to a SNAFU in the scheme of things. I won't be starting classes until Wednesday.  "Why?" you ask.  Because I have a hold on my records that won't allow me to register for classes, and the person I need to contact about it has been in meetings all day today, I would've started tomorrow, but that won't happen because I'm not registered for classes.  If I didn't want to be done with school with something to show for it so badly, I'd just stop and hit the road with all the skills I'm going to learn about my profession at EKU.  I have no more major classes, all GEN ED.  Health Class, Literature Classes, Biology... CRAP CRAP CRAP!  I'm almost out of school, and I don't have any debt (which is a very big accomplishment in this day and age) and I want to get to the living my life part.  It's all very frustrating.  Stupid 20/20 hindsight.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Worry burdens my troubled mind.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Alas, Sunday morning is my last day to sleep in since classes start Monday.  Man, I'm am SO dreading classes.  I'm dreading not knowing ANYbody in any of my classes even more.    This is going to suck.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Narrowly avoided a completely fun-free weekend, thanks to a friend of mine in Lexington. Grin!
     

    
</post>

<date>24,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I did it.  Not really though.  I mustered the courage, my left nut dropped, and I called... and I got the voicemail.  Never was I so dissappointed in my life.  As an after thought, I should've gone ahead and asked via voice message, but nope... I didn't.  On the bright side, it should only get easier.... right?
     

    
</post>

<date>22,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I think my left nut has formed, or I'm just tired of putting myself (and I'm sure all my friends to a degree) through hell.   When  I talk to her tomorrow, I'm going to lay it all out... see where I can go from here.  Either way it turns out, I will do it.  I'm not ashamed to say that I'm very nervous and may have a difficult time sleeping tonight.  I know this kind of thing is old hat to many people (probably most people), but it's not to me.  I can't wait for tomorrow... and I'm dreading it.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Lord what have I done...   There's no fallout from the phone call last night.  Either it was all really muddled or she's ignoring it.  Either way, it makes me feel a little better.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Let me explain my last entry.  My roommate's girlfriend (Katie) says the ability to ask someone of the opposite sex out lies totally in the left testicle.  So for a couple days we've been joking (only partially, though) that I need to grow a left nut.  Fast forward to tonight.  My roommates and I generally have some random friends over on Wednesday nights for what we call "Card Night".  In case you're way too simple-minded, card night is where we get together and (wait for it...) play cards and just get together and have a good time.  Well, one of my roommates decides to do some drinking tonight, and since I haven't done so in a while, I figured what the heck.  Fast forward.  So around 10:00 (10:11pm to be exact) I decide to do my first ever drunk dial (not really drunk, but feeling good [two shots of   Montezuma Tequila, and a Doc Otis later]).  The person I decide to call was a certain someone that I'm interested in (No, it's not Patrick's mom)...  Besides she had asked me to call her later if I got the chance, and as soon as her voice-mail picked up, I realized what time it was [note: she goes to bed fairly early, and turns her phone off when she goes to bed].  I was leaving a message and held the phone up to have everyone say, "HI [insert name here]" and my friend Rose said, "go out with Scott!".  I ended the phone message and we all had a pretty big laugh, I was pretty impressed that she did it, and wasn't upset at all that she did.  Thus, that is how Rose became my left nut.  Fast forward.  Talking with Rose a little bit later, she gave me a couple of tips about if or when she brings it up or asks about it.  So that was good... but she basically said, "don't read into anything too much, and still you need to just ask her out"  Fast forward.  Now that everyone has gone and I've had a bit of quiet time to myself... I'm a little nervous.  This big giant boulder that's just been sitting here and getting bigger has been getting increasingly more difficult to get moving... but I think that Rose put some TNT under it, and now it's got a little bit of momentum and all I need to do is give it that shove and see where it goes from there.  It basically is really making me step up to the plate and get ready to throw myself in front of the bullet (too many analogies?).  Well, one thing is, I'll know one way or the other, and if it's bad news, then I can get to feeling sorry for myself and get that part over.  If it's the way I'd like it to go, then I can finally get on with enjoying my time with her even more.  Any advice?  Comments?  Snide remarks?  I'm really nervous.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Rose (Coleman) Paugh is my left nut.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I hate a particular 5% of who I am, How I am, and what I will and will not do.  As my roommate and his girlfriend put it... I need a left testicle.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Cast in the name of God  Ye Not Guilty    One of my favorite anime titles right now is The Big O.  I just bought it on DVD a couple days ago.  Stupid Cartoon Network's [adult swim] got me hooked on it.  The first season is really great... there's a lot of weirdness that goes on in the storyline and most of it is interconnected to make you want to try to figure out what's going on in the whole scheme of things.  Quick breakdown: Takes place in a city called "Paradigm City".  The city of amnesia.  Approximately 40 years ago something happened to make everyone lose their memories.  No one knows what happened.  Bits and pieces surface every once in a while to give them glimpses of their past.  Fortunately people remembered how to use electricity and machines and that sort.  ANYway, check it out, it's fun.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm not one to fish for compliments, and that's not what I'm going for here, either.  I'm very proud of my lighting design for Other People's Money, and since behind-the-scenes kind of people don't get a lot of recognition, I'm going to brag on myself a little bit by posting a couple pictures from the show.         
     

    
</post>

<date>19,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, what a waste of time Eastern Kentucky University has been today.  I've had three classes and none of them have gone anywhere NEAR the full time (which normally, I would love, but since I live relatively close to campus, I've been going home after class).  I had an 8:00am LAB that met for 15-20 minutes.  Awesome since it's scheduled for two hours.  So went home to wait for my 11:00 class.  It only went 10 minutes.  What a crock.  I just got out of my 12:30 class at 1:05 (supposed to go to 1:45).  This time I'm killing some time in a computer lab instead of making the 10 minute trek back home.  I only pray that my last class of the day doesn't make me feel like I've completely wasted my time.  I'll let you know.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Cock-blocked.  Learning life's lessons... the hard way.
     

    
</post>

<date>31,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I did something last night that I swore I would never do.  I left a friend high and dry for a girl.  While I now understand the other end of the spectrum and how it's easy to do something like that, I've made myself into a hypocrit.  I am an ass, and I feel really bad about it. I wish I could go back and correct it.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "you'd think this life would make me bolder but I'm running scared is all..." "well you got to think with a girl like that any love at all, is better than nothing... is better than nothing" - Matchbox Twenty - girl like that   "If it were up to me, she would know that she'll be the one, when I'm dead, will use my bed and she'll spend her life, thinking of us and making a fuss." - Rooney - If It Were Up to Me   Yes, you read correctly, I DID IT!  I asked her out.  She came to Richmond this morning on business and we went out to breakfast, and then I rode along with her to one of her clients.  When she dropped me off, I asked her.  I'm pretty sure that it can't be misconstrued as anything other than what I meant it to be.   [Important excerpt from conversation]   Me:  Y'know, I always have a great time with you.  Her:  I have a lot of fun with you, too.  Me:  I may be going out on a limb here, but I'd like to take you out sometime.    [plain, simple, to the point, right?]   Her:  That sounds great.  Yeah, we'll go out sometime. [big smile]  [end of important dialogue... not direct quotes, general gist of conversation]   So there you have it.  My heart is pounding, my pulse is racing, and I feel as if I'm out of breath.  But I love it.  If nothing else, this is a mountain I've climbed and conquered.  Hopefully it'll be easier if I ever have to do it again.  Is this the end... or is it merely the beginning?  I can't wait to find out!
     

    
</post>

<date>29,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Telemarketers Start Transmitting Caller ID Information   Starting today, if you have Caller ID, you'll know when a telemarketer calls you.  Telemarketers must transmit Caller ID information in order to comply with the Federal Trade Commission's Telemarketing Sales Rule (TSR).  Prior to the new requirements, most calls showed up on your Caller ID as "out of area."  Now the name of the company or firm calling must be displayed along with their phone number.   urlLink Full Story 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Alright, to all of those who have been reading my blog for the past month or so... it all comes down to tomorrow.  My big goofy grin days will either be numerous and plentiful or be snuffed out like a candle in a huricane.  I'm going to have lunch with  her  tomorrow.  I've been given a lot of good advice that I can and can't use.  I've been encouraged by so many people, and it really makes me smile to think that people are rooting for me and cheering me on in a respect.  I'll actually get one last psyche up tomorrow if I need it... and I probably will.  In approximately 11 or 12 hours, I (along with everyone else) will finally find out if this waste of energy has been worth it or not.  I have a good feeling about tomorrow.  No matter which way it goes.  I'm actually looking forward to it.  That hasn't happened before.  Usually I've dreaded it, or been really nervous about it.  I feel anxious, but not nervous.  Do you think I stand a chance?  Feel free to give any kind of feedback on any part of this post.   Lord protect my heart. 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Do the numbers...   In the past two months (November 29 - January 29) the following number of blogs have taken place:  Posts about any girl - 7 Posts about a girl I like - 25 Posts about friends - 15 Posts about an event - 6 Posts about a TV show/movie - 9 Posts about school/classes - 5 Posts about a job - 7 Posts about worries - 12 Posts with quotes - 4 Other posts - 13   Some posts counted as two things... and the news articles I didn't bother counting.   A very interesting couple of months.  Thanks for everyone for all your advice, support, laughter, and patience.  Especially for your friendship! 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Another fun-filled card night... not as much alcohol this time for me.  I took some pictures this time, though.  Wish you were here.     Loyal Participants in Card Night - Group Shot   From Left to Right.  In front: Rose and Josh Paugh; 2nd row: Scott, Angela;  back: Brian (roommate), Brandi, Katie, Dustin (roommate) Not shown: Jason and Kathryn Bowles      NERTS! anyone?      Setting up for another hand. 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
        A friend of mine happened upon this comic and gave it to me.  Intriguing.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
       The talk of the town ?  ... Apparently.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Just when you feel like life is out to get you and all the odds are against you... life stops by and seems to apologize and give you a pat on the back.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Do what I do...  Go to Wal-Mart at 2:00 in the morning.  Why?  Why  not? 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A friend is one who sees through you and still enjoys the view.  - Wilma Askinas 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      In order to discover new lands, one must be willing to lose sight of the shore for a very long time.  - Anonymous 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, due to an ice storm that passed through central Kentucky this morning, the show for today has been cancelled.  The only thing I had planned to do today, and I can't do it.  I'm only mildly dissappointed, more-so that I won't be heading into Lexington today than anything.  Maybe the weather will lighten up a bit and I can get out for a little while this afternoon/evening.  I don't mind staying at home, but I don't like to HAVE to stay at home.  I like the freedom.  But for now, I'll enjoy my time, and maybe continue rearranging my room a bit.  For anyone that's out and about, I hope they are able to make it to their destinations safely.  I wouldn't want to lose anyone that's special to me.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Dallas Nelson Glascock.    My father.  Died on this day in 1991.   I feel like I barely knew him.  I wish all my friends could have known him.  What little I can remember of him was the "running tabs" he kept for my friends when they came over for dinner or spent the night.  He would alwyas tease them about paying their bills before they left.  He was a fun man, I think I got a lot of my humor from him.  I look a lot like him through most of my photos.  When I look at photos I can definitly see a lot of him in me.  My favorite images of him in my head are all of him smiling or laughing... he had a huge smile, and probably as big of a laugh... maybe that's where I got mine from.  He was a great dad, played with me, tickled me, loved me, laughed with me, made fun of my mom and I for crying at a happy or sad movie.  He was an amazing man from all accounts that I've heard.  I don't think anyone who met him didn't like him.  I mean who wouldn't?  He was my dad.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I remember why I chose not to worry a whole lot about girls and dating in High School, and the first few years in college... it's because relationships can really cloud up your judgement on so many things.  I also withnessed so many failed relationships or unhealthy relationships or relationships that took my friends away from me that I didn't want to get involved in that.  I think I've had more "second hand" pain from relationships that most people have had first hand.  It's kind of like second hand smoke... you're not smoking but you're still reaping the unhealthy consequences.  With relationships, you get to see all the aftermath of the heart-ache, bad-blood, break-ups, fights, etc, without any of the good stuff.  I hate seeing people hurting from something someone else has done.  It's even worse when it's something I've done.  I feel like atlas some days being able to bear the weight of the world on my shoulders, and some days I feel like I'm nothing but this thin clay shell that will break if the slightest pressure is applied to it.  Sometimes I can't take the pressure and just want to leave everything alone and not watch, because I can't bear the pain of seeing someone hurting.  And other times I feel like there's never enough I can do, because I want to help bear someone's pain and hurting.  I feel so very selfish.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Some days you just wake up feeling like crap.  Well, yesterday and today have been those days for me.  Today, I just feel like laying in bed all day... but I know that's bad... so maybe I'll just lay in bed half the day.  Company and phone calls seem to cheer me up and make me feel better... or at least it takes my mind off of it.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Kind of a bad night for card night, I guess.  It was still nice for a bit.  A couple people had to work, and one participant was sick so she didn't stay too long.    My roommate made me nervous most of the night by having needles and his medkit out (he's a medic in the National Guard).  One person was a brave soul and let him practice giving an IV.  I couldn't watch.  I have a sensitivity when it comes to needles and blood.  Mostly, Card Night went well, but it was a bit of a let-down.  I wish a couple more people would've been there or something.  Oh well.  Next week will be better, hopefully.  Couldn't be the lack of alcohol.... could it?
     

    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hooray for Card night tonight!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Okay, I just want to take a small poll.  Those of you who read this blog, encourage readers of your own blogs to vote on this poll.  I'm sure most of you are aware of the stunt where Justin Timberlake exposed one of Janet Jackson's breasts.  So...   Do you think that:  A)  It was truly an accident thanks to too little or no rehearsal of a movement that was to take place during a performance. or  B)  It was a publicity stunt to get their names into the press.   Short and sweet or long and drawn out... leave your comments and votes....   NOW  ! 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Kindness and coutesy will only take you so far... eventually you have to kick ass and ask questions later.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, the show at  urlLink Studio Players  is finally over.  The weekend nights are mine to do with as I please, again!  Ahhh... the feeling is... amazing!
     

    
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Lord, please protect my heart.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Not being able to sleep really blows.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hello everyone, in case you hadn't notice (and it would be really difficult not to), my blog has changed looks.  It was about time for an overhaul, and I'm kind of restless tonight, so I decide to undertake it.  I mean, if you can't sleep, find something constructive to do,  right?   Well, enjoy the new look and layout of my blog.  I'll try to keep it interesting for you.  Any and all feed back is appreciated.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today, I want to put my foot through the TV.  But since I don't have the money to replace it... I'll just turn it off instead.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "All You Need is Love" - The Beatles  Well... that's all I'm asking for.  I want love.  I want intamacy.  I want closeness.  I want love.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Move over Karaoke... here comes  urlLink Movieoke .
     

    
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      To alcohol... The cause of, and solution to, all of life's problems. -- Homer Simpson
     

    
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
       It's been a while since I've been home on a friday night... even longer since I've been alone on one.  Now before I get the "it's okay to be home" and "it's okay to spend time by yourself", I do that during the week plenty, it's not about being alone for only 5 minutes with nothing but my thoughts to keep me company. At any rate Friday nights alone suck. Maybe it's just this one, since Valentine's day is tomorrow, and I hate even the thought of that holiday... of love, of people being sweet to each other, of couples looking into their partner's eyes and knowing they are safe.  So it's just me, the TV, Doc Otis, and an empty apartment... except for me.  Here's to friday night's alone.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Some days I just shouldn't get out of bed.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Feeling kind of down today.  Not sure why.  Just in a "blah" mood, I guess.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I know this may sound very "guru" or "spiritualistic".  But I feel like I've been filled with a lot of positive energy in the recent months of my life.  And today I was able to "feel" or observe what kind of negative engery I had been filled with until that point.    I met with a good friend of mine whom I hadn't seen in a couple months, our schedules just never seemed to work out.  She was meeting with some people for a few mintues (some I knew and some I didn't) and invited me along.  When I got there and was sitting in their company, I felt really rediculous and out of place.  I could feel somehow that these energies (mine and theirs) were not in cooperation with each other.  Have I grown that much?  I don't feel like it.  But I do feel that I've changed to a degree that I'm very happy about... and these people that used to be "friends" of mine, well, I don't miss them (except the one I wanted to see in the first place).  I don't know.  Parts of me sometimes think back to the "good old days" and miss them... but the more I think about it... my memories only fill in certain people in them any more.  Do I need to fill in the blanks? No. Do I want to?  Nah.  Thank God for the positive and faithful people and friends in my life.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Just when everything's going well, some kid throws a stick into the spokes of the bicycle of life. 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Many of you may know (and just about as many of you may not care) that from August to December, I took a semester off from college.  A very healthy one, in fact.     A quick run down of the past few years of my life  [until this point]  would look like a lot of depression, hate, anger, hope, more depression, funks, crashes, loss, gain, more loss, and some good moments.  Starting in October of 2003, I became really involved with  urlLink Crossroads Christian Church .  There I re-learned what friendships and grace and compassion were, and that they do exist in more than just two people.  Thanks to a lot of people that I met there, I've learned a lot about myself, been given a lot of good advice, and am able to make it through my day without feeling like there's some impending doom around the corner just waiting for me to walk by so it can beat the crap out of me. Stephanie, my ever-faithful, beautiful, and loving friend has seen it all, and helped me through most of it.  Some of the folks from Crossroads that took me in or taught me some well needed lessons about life were some of the same people that I know read this blog.  For one, Patrick.  Thanks man, and sorry for the crap I pulled... I am an ass.  Aside from those two... Dave, Jon, Matt, Eric, and Ira have all been really awesome and helpful along the way.   Back to the story... EKU Theatre was a big part of all this crap... not the department, or the professors, or the classes, but the students.  Negative, negative, mean, bitter people. I started working this past week at the theatre for financial aid... federal work study.  It's great, I get paid for doing what I enjoy doing.  I haven't talked with many people around the theatre except the technical professor (my "boss").  I get a unique view of things going on in the actual theatre space while people are working because I'm 35 (or more) feet in the air above their heads on the catwalks working on the lights.  Nothing has changed... no body has any degree of a work ethic... people just goof off and flirt (I'm all about flirting, but if it keeps the job from getting done or people being ANY amount of productive, it's too much.  It makes me laugh SO much to think that I used to really care what a lot of those people thought about me.  I'm very glad I'm not in rehearsals with them, or in classes with them.  I'm very excited at how my life has changed, how much I feel I've grown.  I love my friends.  I love my life.  I love my God.  Because through my friends and through me, he has made everything possible.  And there's a piece of me that anytime I see some of the people there, I think... I've done this "out there", I know I can make it, will you ever make it?  And a small part of me hopes not... a bigger part of me feels sad knowing that most of them won't.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      There are two things in the previous post that are   NOT   true.  Which do  YOU  think they are?
     

    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I figure enough time has passed since the last time many of you have seen a post like this, so I'd give it a try.   acted like a fool in front of a bunch of girls  worked backstage for a show  designed lights for a show  watched naked women running around  worked in a pharmacy  acted like a fool onstage  designed a webpage  stage managed a show  sold myself  got good grades  did yard work  worked in a "pharmacy"  drank water from a storm gutter  designed and built props for a show  cleaned bathrooms  sold my soul  bagged groceries  pushed shopping carts  designed business cards and letterhead for people/businesses  laid down in the middle of a street for 15 seconds  sold my possessions  hung by my pants from 40 feet in the air  been burned  been shocked  took shots
     

    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ah.  The weekend was awesome.  That free-time-stealing-not-getting-paid-for-my-hard-work show is over, and this weekend was my first real taste of the freedom.   Friday night  was fun.  I got to spend some time with a great person, and I went rock climbing for the first time at The Stadium.  I had been hiking before, but nothing with real vertical walls, and the possibility of really falling.  The Gorge had a few scary possibilities, but I wasn't worried about it.   Saturday  was a fun day.  The first part was mostly lazy, and I burned a lot of CD's for someone who - for the first time, I feel - is taking a little bit of my musical taste with them.  My friends have always kind of rubbed off on me with some of their tastes in music.  But very few people have I ever musically infulenced before, so I'm helping her out a bit.  The rest of my Saturday afternoon involved visiting the "fabulous" Richmond Mall and hitting Wal-Mart.  That night, I went over to a great friend's house and hung out, watched TV, watched a movie, and watched SNL.  Too much fun. I had one of the best times I'd had in a while.   Sunday  was another fun-filled day.  Woke up and headed out to church.  After church, I stayed for a class in the basics of sound and running sound.  Very educational, and I'm really into gadgets and electronics, so I loved it.  After that, I went to help a friend move some stuff into her new house.  Then that evening I drove to Georgetown to visit with three of my good friends.  I love my friends, but that's a rough drive!  I'm always glad I go, but the drive back always is  WAY  too long  (about 40-45 minutes!) .  I came home to find one roommate asleep and the other not home (probably at his girlfriend's).  I made myself some left-over Arby's sandwhiches and talked one of my friend's home from Georgetown.  I fell asleep watching the movie UNDERWORLD.    Today is a new day, and I can't wait to start hating school again!  The weekend can't arrive too soon.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Watching Saturday Night Live tonight, I have discovered that Megan Mullally is a genius.  I knew she was talented, and I'm not talking about her role on the Sit Com "Will and Grace".  She has some great comedic moments on the show (W&G), but I'm more impressed with her talent on the stage... the legitimate theatre.  I grow more impressed with her the more I see.  (minds out of the gutters, pervs)  I hadn't seen SNL for a while, for some reason or the other... and it was good to come home.  I still miss the good ole cast of the days of yore, but... every once in a while the combination of host, musical guest, and sketches just all seems to come together to put on a really great show.  It also helps that I shared it with good company.  :)
     

    
</post>

<date>08,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Two Words.  Huggies Thong.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Setup and Ran lights for the first time for what had been called by some "big church", in other words, the regular weekend services (when TheWell was still around).  The setup seemed a lot better or more organized, or maybe there were just more people there to help... but after the setup, I felt very helpless and very nervous.  I feel like it was the worst job I've ever done running a light board, and yet, I still got compliments... I don't know what I was doing.  I wasn't even this nervous when I ran lights the first time for TheWell.  I guess for TheWell, I had a lot more free reign.  There are more constraints on what you can, can't, should, and shouldn't do for the regular services... maybe that got me all flustered, who knows.  Hopefully tomorrow morning will go better.  Please, God.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      What happened to the friends who were ready to do anything at just a whim?  Where are you guys?  Am I the only one left?
     

    
</post>

<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Most of you who read my blog know what kind of business I'm in, but in case you don't, here goes:  I'm a Lighting Technician/Designer for stage productions.  I've worked professionally for three summers at Jenny Wiley Theatre; worked for money, credit, and for the pleasure of it at EKU Theatre; worked at Studio Players for the experience (free); worked for minimum wage and free food at the Center for Rural and Economic development in Somerset, KY; and give back to the One who has given me these wonderful gifts, talents, and tools by giving my time to Crossroads Christian Church.  I've had to work in different conditions and environments.  I've dangled by a harness from over 35 feet in the air, I've kept myself from falling from such heights as well with just the use of one hand.  I have NEVER been afraid of the heights I have worked in.  Growing up, I was fairly phobic of high places, but overcame that through working in theatres.  This semester, I've been working in the theatre department as part of a work study program (financial aid).  I was working today, and I had to go up to an area of the theatre called the grid. It's usually the highest point of the theatre, directly above the stage where all the pipes (batons) are hanging from.  All the lights were out on the grid, and I had to grab some cable from up there.  I climbed over 90 feet to the grid, and when I got up there, my heart started pounding wildly, my pulse raced, my mouth became dry, and I felt a little light-headed (which isn't good at heights).  I made my way back down to the ground and just laughed at myself... fear is so irrational.  There was no point to my fear.  I was perfectly safe, there was very little chance of my falling over 90 feet to the stage floor.  The steel slats were spaced apart just wide enough that your foot WON'T fit through it.  There are a couple of larger spaces that only someone half as skinny as myself would fit through, and even then, it'd be VERY difficult to fall through them.  Nonetheless, I was frightened.  I told my boss/professor about it, and he went up, and y'know... everything looks different when you put in working light bulbs and everything is lit up.    I was able to go back up and complete my job without any anxiety.  Proving to myself that it was a VERY irrational fear.  And I remain undaunted.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I shouldn't be allowed around people.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I haven't had a haircut in almost three months (a lot longer than I usually wait) and my hair was getting a bit long.  Here I am  [on the left]  before the hair cut (photo is right after a shower)... and yes, I am completely naked at time of photo.   And thanks to my good friend,  urlLink Stephanie , I was introduced to Johnny at  Studio V  in Lexington.  I  urlLink resisted  the new hairstyle at first, but eventually I got  urlLink used to it , and eventually even really liked it.  I went back to Johnny on Tuesday, and got another great hair cut, and he's a pretty cool guy to talk with too.  So here's the "now" shot  [on the right] : 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's hard not to feel happy when you see a peaceful, bubbling fountain.  It's hard not to pee, too.  Actually, it's hard not to feel happy when you pee.    Feel happy.  Pee.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      To do the useful thing, to say the courageous thing, to contemplate the beautiful thing: that is enough for one man's life.  - T.S. Eliot 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "What the hell is wrong with me? Don't fit in with anybody How did this happend to me? Wide awake I'm bored and I can't fall asleep and every night is the worst night ever  "I'm just a kid and life is a nightmare I'm just a kid I know that it's not fair Nobody cares 'cuz I'm alone and the world is having more fun than me tonight."   "I'm Just a Kid" by Simple Plan 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Why do I seem to attract all the girls I  DON'T  want, am not interested in, or would not be good for me, but  don't  attract the girls I  DO  want, am interested in, or would be good for me?
     

    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm having some long-time internal struggles... God, please give me a sign.  I give it up to you.  Love, your servant, Scott
     

    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I believe that everyone goes through cycles, some people's are more pronounced than others.  Women go through a very noticable cycle every 28 days for much of their life.  Men go through cycles, too... just maybe not as noticable.  Through my life, I've gone through cycles.  My emotions are definitely on a cycle, not necessarily on a monthly cycle, but they are on one at any rate.  Early on in life the ups and downs were about even, I had just as many "down" days as "up" days.  They were mixed in together pretty well and they changed gradually.  As life went on, the "up" days out numbered the "down" days.  Sometimes I would hit a down day and flop right back up the next day, others would take me a day or two.  Now in my life, I'm noticing that the down days are feeling even fewer and farther between.  There are certain issues that I still struggle with, but I'm not down in general.  I've also noticed that it's gotten easier for me to come out of down times.  Sometimes I make myself, some times someone else will snap me out of it, other times it just happens.    Well, it "just happened" today.  About two and a half hours ago, actually.  I just found myself laughing and smiling and cutting up like normal, and I just felt GREAT!  It happened where it usually happens... at church.  I can't tell you how great of a feeling it was to just feel like I snapped out of it.  In retrospect, I think a lot of my down days are because I try too often to put on an air of happiness even when I'm not... so suddenly I'm unable to keep it up any more and my mood just breaks down.  Sometimes we need a down day or two for no reason... and sometimes they help us to really appreciate things better.  All I can say is that I really needed tonight.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Is it worse to have to censor yourself or have someone else censor you?
     

    
</post>

<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      For those of you who watch what you eat. Here's the final word on nutrition and health. It's a relief to know the truth after all those conflicting medical studies.   1. The Japanese eat very little fat and suffer fewer heart attacks than the Americans.   2. The Mexicans eat a lot of fat and suffer fewer heart attacks than the Americans.   3. The Japanese drink very little red wine and suffer fewer heart attacks than the Americans.  4. The Italians drink excessive amounts of red wine and suffer fewer heart attacks than the Americans.   5. The Germans drink a lot of beers and eat lots of sausages and fats and suffer fewer heart attacks than the Americans.   CONCLUSION: Eat and drink what you like.  Speaking English is apparently what kills you.  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Have you ever just felt incredibly grateful for knowing someone?  I have... and I do.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I made my first attempt at making a new dish tonight.  Chili.  I kept it pretty simple so that I had some basis to go off of for next time I make it... so it wasn't too hot... just hot enough.  It actually could've been a little bit spicier.  But it tasted great, and it turns out that it can be made pretty quickly, too.  (took me about 45 minutes, but that's because I didn't exactly know what I was doing, plus I made cornbread and waited for that to be done).  I actually made it with ground turkey instead of ground beef, and it was great.  I can't wait to make some again sometime!  I would like to thank the following people for introducing me to - and encouraging my love for - chili...  Jon Adams Erin Adams Amber Henry  That is all. Thank you.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Last night a friend of mine was baptised.  I'm extremely proud of her.  After that service, she and a bunch of our friends went out to eat.  Now, I haven't been eating out or doing a lot of stuff because money is REALLY tight for me right now.  I went to eat with everyone but I was just going to have water and just go and hang out.  My friend and her new roommate conspired and bought me food without my knowledge.  Now, it was actually the roommate (who I barely know) that I later found out actually bought my meal.  I had tried to keep it low key so as not to attract any special attention or anything... I didn't want (and I didn't want anyone else) to make a big deal out of it.  I thanked her greatly.  On the way home, my eyes actually watered up a little bit.  No one has ever shown me that brand of kindness and caring before.  I barely knew her, and she paid for my dinner without a thought.  I guess what I've been brought up thinking really is true... God will provide.  She was just an instrument.  Thanks God, and thanks to my friend and her roommate.  Bless you both.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I feel a LOT better after today's services, I got a lot of compliments.  Lisa Moss, the head of the lighting team, came up to the booth after the first service this morning and told me that I did an excellent job and that I did some really neat things for the service and during the songs.  She praised me pretty highly, and I must say that I was extremely pleased with the end product.  I was able to fix a couple things this morning before the services and it made life so much easier.  I had a great day, except that one person who I really would've like to have been there... wasn't.     I understand that I'm not the center of this person's world, and understand that they have a life, though... and I'm not mad, and my day wasn't ruined.  It just would've been nicer for that person to have been there. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
        [03-27-03]   Oh Happy Day!!!!  (Oh Happy Daaayy!!)  When Jesus washed...  (When Jesus washed...)  He washed my sins away... Oh Happy Day!!     I hope you had a good day at class. I don't like you always having rehearsal every night. I liked hanging out with you all the time   Sing with me now....  Oh Happy Day...
     

    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Had my last classes before Spring Break today.  Came home, chatted to a couple people, made a couple phone calls, went to work for about an hour, came home and have done jack-squat since.  Kinda depressing way to start of my Spring Break.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I get a tip-of-the-day kind of thing in my e-mail. Here's what I got today:  "In a recent study, people who had at least one close friend appeared to have as much as a 30 percent lower risk of periodontitis, a dental disorder that can lead to tooth loss. Researchers speculate that the connection may be due to the stress-reduction benefits that friends offer; stress is associated with poor oral hygiene."   Thanks friend, for doing things neither of us realized. :) 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      No real details.  Just through my life, that's the way it's been.  Even if I've asked a girl out, it's been the same story, just a different line.  But somehow girls that I don't have ANY desire to get to know any better are the ones that seem to "throw themselves" at me.  Maybe it's a matter of the amount of energy you put into someone.  But I look at other relationships, and that seems to work on some girls but not on others.  I've tried different things.  And not to get down on myself, but the only thing I see differently between me and the guys that girls seem to go for is the looks.  I guess I just don't have "it"... whatever the heck "it" is.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      What I wouldn't do to take away her burden.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Copy cat?  -  Yeah, maybe, but who cares... it's cool.   Check out the new stuff on my sidebar - I figured out how to send photos to the internet and display them on my blog... cool, huh?
     

    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
       ::::  Warning : This post is about disappointment, so some of you out there might find it depressing or a "downer".  Sorry, if you don't like it, don't read it.  At least it's something meaningful. ::::    On the way home from a botched attempt at celebrating St. Patrick's Day, I did some thinking.  I've decided that my energy doesn't work well with planning things, or work well on it's own.  My excitement needs to feed off of someone else's in order for it to be effective.  I can be excited about something on my own, but eventually I run out of juice if no one else is excited with me.  Such was tonight.  Plus the fact that the plans slowly were falling apart around me.  The original plan was to go with about 7 or 8 people, and one-by-one they petered out or changed their mind at the last minute or had made other plans or had conflicts.  It's kind of a shot to the old self esteem.  I keep telling myself, "this one's going to work out!" and then it doesn't.  I would just love to plan something and it be fun, and everyone have a great time (or at the very least - show up).  I think that's another reason why my friend Stephanie is so important to me... we can feed off of each other's excitement (and sometimes she can jump-start mine when there isn't much there to begin with).  Oh well - such is life.  Just a string of disappointments until you get lucky and something works out for you.  I can't wait for it to finally work out for me.  PS - I'll get over it, don't worry about me.  I'd just like something like this to go well for me for once.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "Well, it's all for me grog, me jolly, jolly grog... It's all for me beer and tobacco... For I spent all o' me tin, with the ladies drinkin' gin... and across the western ocean I must wander."  That song is off a Traditional Irish group's CD called MOLLY'S REVENGE.  I bought that CD two years ago on Saint Patrick's day out in California while visiting Stephanie on my spring break.  Since then we've kept up the tradition by going to an Irish Pub on St. Patty's day.  Sadly, this year may be different as she may not get to go.  One a lighter note - I got to see a really awesome Irish Band out of Canada called Slainte Mhath (pronounced Slawncha Va) yesterday on campus.  Check out the photoblog on the sidebar to see 'em.  They blend traditional Irish music with modern beats and songs.  The actually played, "That's the way I like it" yesterday... it was too cool.  And of course, there's a girl in the band, and she was HOT.  She plays the fiddle and this traditional Irish-type drum - it kind of looks like an oversized tamborine without the little cymbals all around it.  I think I'm destined to be with someone who - on the lowest level - really enjoys music a lot, or - to the hightest level - plays an instrument, sings like an angel, or totally gets wrapped up in the emotion of a song and sees the things in music that I do.  Instruments and voices for girls just really turns me on, I guess.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So, I was diagnosed with an eye infection and given some antibiotic drops to put in my eye four times a day for the next week.  What a pain in the butt.  This was also the day I decided to get my eye glass prescription updated.  I went down to eye glass world...  BUY ONE GET ONE FREE!!!     Awesome!    The only thing is that I've never bought new frames without having someone there to help me and look and tell me if they looked good/bad on me or not.  Well, I didn't have that this time.  I was left to the mercy of one of the sales associates, I tried on about 15 different pairs of frames, but I couldn't really tell how I looked in them because I didn't have contacts in, and the frames just had clear glass in them.  I was totally at his mercy.  He helped me pick out two sets of frames, and I decided to make one of them a pair of sunglasses.  They'd be ready for pickup the next day. (fortunately and unfortunately - I would be in Nashville the next two days).  As the time to pick up my glasses drew nearer, I became very nervous about how they would actually look on me.  One friend said I was being silly.  Which I probably sounded like... but it was a lot of money gone down the drain if I didn't like them... and since I hadn't ACTUALLY seen what they looked like on me, it was a big worry.    When I got back in town, I went and picked up my glasses.  I put the sunglass pair on first... BAM! I could see amazingly well... I looked in the small mirror on the counter and was amazed at how great the frames looked on me!  I set that pair down and went for the regular ones, BAM! once again I could see perfectly!  I looked in the mirror and thought WOW!  I look AWESOME!  Now, anyone that knows me, knows that I'm pretty modest when it comes to my looks, and my own self image isn't always the best either, so when I say that I look TOO sexy in these glasses, you'd know what a big deal that is.  With these glasses added to my cool hair cut (thanks again, Stephanie), I'm one step closer to being a babe magnet.    I've always been told that I'd make a great boyfriend and that I have an awesome personality, I just need to hook someone with the "look factor" so they have the chance to see the charming, chivilrous, loyal, I'd do anything for you, senstive, loving, with a hard-candy shell - me.  That and I need advertising!  Help guys!
     

    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Sunday Night  (March 7, 2004), I was hanging out at my friend Steph's house... the usual - watching TV, talking, writing angry e-mails, y'know... what we do every time we're hanging out (well, everything but that last bit).  She has a two cats and I normally play with and pet them.  I used to be severely allergic to cats, just being around them would make my eyes water and begin to swell, and my nose would run like a faucet.  As I grew up, I grew out of it to an extent... I could pet them, just as long as I didn't rub my eyes with my hands afterwards, and I had no problem being around them... but sometimes I get absent minded and do something stupid.  SO while I was writing an e-mail, my eyes began to water and itch a little bit.  I figured it was probably my allergies and just suffered through it.  When I got home I looked in the mirror and realized that it may be more than allergies when my entire right eye was blood red.  Taking my contact out was a bit scary as the fear of a detached retina came screaming through my head.  I went to sleep that night and woke up with my eye glued shut from eye-boogers (or eye crispies).  My eye watered a bit when I woke up and they disolved enough for me to open my eye and clear off the rest from my lashes.  I went to the eye doctor (after donning my old glasses) to see what was up.   (to be continued) 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, life must be back to normal for me - I can't sleep. 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Check out some of the graphics I've created for the page.  Tell me what you think about them.  (por ejemplo: the title banner and the post it note)  - more will be coming soon.  I just don't want to add graphics just to add graphics.. i want them to blend in and compliment the blog.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Well, as you may have read, my Spring Break didn't start off too well.  It just so happened that I chatted with friend of mine the next day and we both decided I should go down and hang out with him in Nashville for a couple days.  So my Spring Break wasn't going to be a total lack of some sort of adventure, after all.  Anyway, he moved to Nashville several months ago and began working with a traveling youth ministry called  urlLink Inlightened Ministries .  I know he runs sound for them and that he handles a lot of their web site and graphics and technical aspect of their ministry, I'm sure he helps out in other ways, too - he's a pretty handy guy - but I haven't learned what else that is, yet.   Anyway, I jaunted down to Nash-Vegas (as Ben calls it... oh by the way, his name is Ben Stewart - he's far right in the photo above), which is a solid four hour drive.  I listened to Butterfly Boucher (whose CD I had bought at the Barenaked Ladies Concert) twice going both ways plus some other CDs of mine.  Anyway, I get down there and we hang out and do some sight-seeing.  Unfortunately if you're not too into Country music, there's not a whole lot of sight-seeing to do.  We ate at a couple of cool places, hung out at a Starbucks for a while, drove around downtown, and just chewed the fat and enjoyed each others company.  Oh, and thanks to him and my best friend Stephanie, I'm totally craving Sushi about 3 or 4 days of the week.    While I was down there we ate at two kind of unconventional buffet restaurants.  The first was a sushi buffet.  We stuffed ourselves SO much.  The buffet only cost us $10, and we had two full plates of sushi each, some clear onion soup, a salad, drinks, and some hibachi chicken.  WHAT A DEAL!  So sushi buffet? Okay, yeah, I can see that... not much different that a Chinese buffet, right? Okay.  So the second buffet, I was a little leary about... it's REALLY not the kind of thing you would really think about going through a buffet line for... MEXICAN.  Like burritos and chimichangas and quesadillas.  It was some of the best Mexican food I've ever eaten.  And like I said, we drove around downtown a little bit, and I grabbed a bite to eat and a T-shirt (and one for a friend) from the Hard Rock Cafe there.  Later the next afternoon, after hanging out and just talking for a while, I hit the road to come home, where I had a meeting to get to and then a bed to attend to.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey everybody! (Hi Doctor Nick!)  Okay, now that we're done with that, I just wanted to say I did a couple of quick edits to the page so that it will look basically the same no matter who views it.  The proportions will all be the same for anybody.  People with higher screen resolutions will just see more blue to the right side of the sidebar than others.  Hope you enjoy reading every now and then, keep coming back, you make it all worthwhile.  I'll get more  Past Weeks  events posted soon.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
       On  March 5, 2004  - five (plus two makes seven) people journeyed to the far reaches of Lexington, KY, to Rupp Arena.  There they saw an amazing, live, upbeat performance by some of the greatest musicians around... Barenaked Ladies!   This concert was incredible.  It started off with this girl (Butterfly Boucher) playing guitar and singing... she was awesome, and she had an accent.  Talking with one of my friends, I said that the fact that she's holding a guitar, and has an accent makes her 50 times more attractive than most girls.  Up next was Howie Day... he was pretty good too.  I remember liking his music, but I can't - for the life of me - remember any of the songs he played or what kind of sound he had... I guess I was still thinking about Butterfly Boucher, or maybe I was distracted by other goings-on... who knows.   And then the creme de la creme, the band we were waiting for arrived onstage.  Those guys are so energetic, lively, and quick-wits abound.  A couple of my favorite moments from the concert were ( moment 1: ) when they did an adlib song about Lexington, KY, and Steve talked about how KFC was changing it's name to Kitchen Fresh Chicken (which is dumb)... and that apparently we now lived in Lexington, Kitchen.   And then to begin his adlib, Ed busted out "You lost the chicken, but you still got the bourbon."   Moment 2:   They have a song called Shopping, which talks about... gasp.... shopping.  They did some shopping-cart-ography for this song and the screens switched to an overhead camera view and the guys were doing faux synchronized swimming... it was awesome!   Moment 3 : The guys did an acoustic set which included the hit song One Week, and a song called Roadrunner (which IS about THE famous roadrunner and coyote).    And I wouldn't be a very good person if I didn't mention that the LIGHTING for the concert was incredible!  Everything fit with the songs, and it really added to the experience.  Not one disappointing moment for me from this concert... well, I can think of one, but it wasn't about the bands.   But one of the best parts of the whole event is who I got to share it with.  And I'll never trade these memories for anything.    
     

    
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A lot of stuff has happened over the past week, and I've been WAY too busy to jot it down as I went... and I'm crashing now, so look for updates coming up this week.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I say "Thank Gawd" for the SPIKE network and all those japanese contestants on Takashi's Castle (or whatever it's actually called in Japan) for giving us the glorious gift of mXc - Most eXtreme elemination Challenge.  I have seen some of those episodes at least five times, and I cannot help but laugh at the pain and suffering of those people as they attempt some really crazy obstacle course like games and contests.  It always seems to brighten my Thursday night.  So once again, I say Thank Gawd!
     

    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      We've all heard the saying " What doesn't kill us, only makes us stronger ", right?  Well, if you haven't... you have now.  The others of you, perhaps you use it as a daily reminder that nothing too tough can happen.  Or maybe you've heard it, but just think it's a big joke.  This is one of my favorite sayings.  I just received an e-mail from a friend of mine, and I came up with another use for this quote - in friendships.  I'm pretty sure that most of us at one time or another has been involved in a friendship that you thought was really great, but sometimes you had really bad fights or arguments... but you came out of those arguments even better friends than before, because you learned something from those arguments.  Or perhaps you've just lost touch with a friend over time or distance and got the chance to reconnect with them.  Well, that's my new use for that phrase - " what doesn't kill a friendship can only make it stronger ".  Sometimes it just seems that no matter what you do, a friendship is destined to be.  Sometimes friendships take some work, on both sides, but if it's meant to be - you will always be able to work through whatever problem(s) or issue(s) you have.  Or you will always find a way to reconnect to that "long lost friend".  And I'd say that nine times out of ten, that long lost person and you will have a stronger friendship for it down the road.   Challenge:    Call someone you haven't talked to in a while.  Someone you may have lost touch with.  Or just call a friend and let them know that you haven't forgotten them.  Or call a current friend and remind them that you care. 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      After doing some thinking about my life and when I've been happy and when I've been sad or depressed... I realize that there are three things in my life that whenever at least one of them is around, I am truly happy.  Number One - God.  And when I say God, I mean Him and the church and everyone I've met through there, everyone tries to help build each and every person up and help them to realize the greatness that, with your help, they can do.  Number Two - my best friend, Stephanie.  She is the most amazing person I've ever met. She is funny, warm, intellegent, kind, and has one of the biggest hearts one person would ever hope to have.  Number Three - the theatre. I always feel at home in a theatre.  Thank you theatre.  For giving me a creative outlet and letting me get paid for something I actually enjoy!  Thanks for shoving me down into the deepest dark pit of my soul so I realized I couldn't live without God.  And thanks for introducing me to the greatest friend I've ever known.  Thank you Stephanie.  For all your encouragement - in our friendship; in my faith and journey; and in that crazy theatre world.  Thank You God for those three things.  It's thanks to You that I'm alive.  Thank You that through You my friendship with Stephanie grows stronger everyday, and thank You for my creative gifts and for allowing me the ability to share them with You and the world.   [ Disclaimer  -  this is the second time I've written this out.  The first time - blogger messed up on me and it didn't post and I lost the whole thing.  Sorry if this doesn't sound very eloquent or flow very well, I tried to reconstruct it the best I could.  All the sentiments are there, I just hope all the heart is still there, too. ]
     

    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Life can be really complicated sometimes.  One day everything is going great - the next, you feel like you've been crapped on.  And on those wonderful occassions, you get both those wonderful feelings wrapped up into the great package of one day.  Those are the days when you don't know if you'll make it out alive.  Y'know the days I'm talking about - they're the ones where you wake up feeling great, you look outside and it's an absolutely beautiful day outside.  Then you get a phone call, or an e-mail, or a letter (or you DON'T get that phone call, or that email, or that letter)... and your heart sinks.  Then maybe later, you hear your favorite song on the radio, or you get a phone call from a close friend, or an e-mail from someone you haven't spoken with in a while.  Then later that day, something again, may cause the sun to not look-so-shiney, the sky to look not-so-blue, and the day to look not-so-great.  Life is full of disappointments, of sorrows... but it's also full of joys, excitements, and wonder.  I think sometimes it's all who we look to for support... when we look inward or to the wrong people, we stumble, fall, and fail.  When we look up to the heavens and embrace the One, the Almighty, the Creator, the Father... we realize that nothing matters but how we treat people around us, and that we live our lives to the fullest, without regret, without anger, without bitterness... with compassion, kindness, caring, friendship, and love.  ... it's amazing how the word of God will change everything in a heart-beat.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've realize that I have slightly more interesting posts if I don't try to post just for posting's sake.  Then I don't post: "I scratched my big toe today, because it itched."  I know you will all be saddened by not being able to keep up on every single detail of my little life... but you'll get over it. :)
     

    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
       As I see it at this moment ; the only thing worse than coming home and seeing everyone all happy and cuddled up with someone - is coming home to an empty apartment ... on a Saturday night ...  at 7:30pm.  This blows.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, April 1st has come and gone - alas this year I did not pull any pranks.  The only ones I kept coming up were really mean, and could be quite a bit distasteful.  So instead, I watched the 14 hour marathon of MXC on Spike TV.  A couple of the "pranks" I thought about were:  - calling someone and telling them their refrigerator was running, then hang up.  - call someone and tell them I was from the clinic and that their test came back positive... then later when they were getting worried, double check what their name was - when I found out - I would apologize and tell them to have a nice day.  - call someone I know - have a normal conversation with them (while sitting in my car).  Then at one point I would yell out something like, "Oh My God", or "Oh Shit"... fumble the phone around a second and then hang up like I was in an accident.  There were others, but I'm not up to writing them down right now, and plus, they really just got meaner from there.
     

    
</post>

<date>31,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Question:   What do you get when you cross two parts insomnia, one part thirst for knowledge of CSS/HTML, a dash of experimentation with Adobe Photoshop Elements, and basted in boredom?    Answer:  You get the newly designed (from the ground up) blog.    No more blogger templates for me.  No sir.  Thanks to some sleepless nights, the fact that I have no girlfriend, my friend Ben Stewart, and my insatiable thirst to be better at something than I already am, I've made a variation on a theme, the basic layout and the information is all still here, it's all just formatted differently.  This is actually the first step in creating a whole website. Phase one - initiate new design into blog!  I'm still working on the actual website, and you'll hear it here, first when it's launched!  Anyway, kick back, grab a cold one (whatever that may be) and let your eyes feast on some candy.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      As some of you may know, pretty much every Wednesday night, my roommates and I have a few friends over to play cards, hang out, watch a movie, or whatever else makes us happy.  Yesterday was a good friend of mine's last card night.  Alas, she (Rose) and her husband (Josh) are moving to L.A. in about a week.  There were very few of us there last night (in fact, just me, one (out of two) of my roommates and our friend.  So we decide to make it a tequila night.  Now I realize that this may be a side of me most people don't know about... but I actually like the taste of tequila.  It's definitely my liquor of choice (on the occassion that I drink). So we have a couple of shots of some crappy tequila to finish that bottle off, and then decide to walk to the liquor store right down the road from my apartment to get (duh duh duuuuh) the good stuff, Jose Cuervo.    A few more shots later and her husband was finally able to come over, and we watched this REALLY weird Anime movie called Wicked City.  Now, I like anime, I'm not hardcore into it or anything, but I've seen my fair share.  Vampire Hunter D, Akira, and most of the series that's been played on Cartoon Network's [adult swim].  I don't know if it was just that I was tipsy or what, but that movie was one of the wierdest movies i've ever watched... it was also difficult to follow since I probably zonked out once or twice.  I'm going to miss them.  Rose is a good tequila drinkin' buddy.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I just realized what time it is.  I kind of got sidetracked experimenting with some CSS... working on making a webpage totally out of it, and I kind of lost track of time.  I'm going to bed now...   I must sleep.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey gang.  I just wanted to give everyone a quick heads up.  I've got an almost completed webpage up and running that runs alongside this blog and this blog has been integrated into.  Feel free to check it out - there are navigation links to it at the bottom of the blog posts.  Feel free to send me some feedback on the pages and all that jazz.  Enjoy! - [  urlLink skipthehero.com  ]
     

    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      if you do nothing else today - goto:  urlLink www.homestarrunner.com .  It's a website made entirely with Flash and Flash Animation and it gets updated pretty regularly, usually once a week.  I suggest you start out by clicking on the button that says "First Time Here" and then go directly to the Strong Bad E-mails.  Some of the best to start out with are the ones titled:  sibbie; dragon; guitar; lures & jigs; i love you;  and  trevor the vampire .  Make sure you have sound on the computer you're viewing it - otherwise it looks kinda silly... y'know... like little characters just kinda bouncing around on the screen... and stuff.    So.. Check it out.  I mean... y'know, I like it.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A Look at the trends that shape your world.     image from theonion.com 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yep.  It's 3:30am.  I'm up, and awake... unfortunately.  All attempts at sleep have failed at this point.  Normally, I wouldn't mind AS much, except my small group is going hiking/climbing tomorrow... or correction - today.   I have to be awake in three hours in order to make it to church by 8:00am.   I just wish my body would work with me here.  I've been getting up fairly early to try to impede the progressively later and later nights.  I've stopped drinking a lot of caffine, and I exercise during the day.  I just don't understand.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
         Josh Wilhoit ... Then - actor/singer/musician.  Now - Agent Smith.  This kind of thing almost makes you wonder if we really are inside the matrix or not.  And if Josh actually is an agent or not.  Could that explain some things?
     

    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I found this link on Dave Barry's blog... check it out, it's a  urlLink japanese commercial .  I sure would love to know what they're advertising... any guesses?
     

    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      10 seconds of awkwardness... with  Mr. T.  ...  ...   ... Genius.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Okay, so I've had my first official day in New York.  What a beautiful city!  Today, I visited Rockefeller Center, Central Park, and saw CBS and NBC Studios.  Pretty cool.  I don't really feel like writing too heavily in the blog for the next few days or so, but I will be taking pictures and posting them to my PhotoBlog, so make sure you check it out to see what I'm up to on kind of a day-to-day basis while I'm away. And look forward to a really big post when I get back with better photos of my time in New York.    Miss you all... well, not really.  ... end transmission.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have some really great stories and pictures to share with everyone from this past weekend... unfortunately, my computer doesn't like me right now, and I can't do anything with it.  I'm on my roommate's computer right now, just so I can check my e-mail and give this quick update.  By the time I have my computer back in working order, I'll hopefully have even more great tales to retell.  Here's some things to look forward to:  - Hiking/Rock Climbing Trip to Red River Gorge - Holocaust Remberance Day (this one's a bit tricky) - Trip to NY for a Wedding and Site-seeing  Hopefully DELL will be able to help me get up and running quickly.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      After an hour on the phone with DELL, the determination was that my hard drive has errors on it.  They're sending me a new one and it'll arrive in two days.  Until then, thanks to my roommate (Dustin) for the use of his computer.  And now a moment of silence for all the programs lost due to my fallen hard drive.  Oh yeah... and let's not foget all the porn. (j/k)
     

    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I know a few people who have the very popular iPod made by Apple.  I also plan on purchasing one in the next couple months.  I recently read an article that gave some tips to maximize the life of your battery for not only the  iPod  but any other device that uses Li-Ion (lithium ion) batteries for power such as  laptop computers .   Tip #1: Leave some gas in the tank.  Letting a Li-Ion batter run all the way down is a bad idea. It reduces the overall life of the battery and can trigger a protective cut-off circuit that may prevent the battery from being recharged at all.  It is ideal to discharge 80% of the battery's capacity before re-charging and to recharge frequently.   Tip #2: Store at 40%.  Never store fully charged Li-Ion batteries for any length of time.  The self-discharge of lithium-ion is about 5% per month.  Once the charge level, cut-off circuitry kicks in, and the batter goes to sleep and quite often cannot be woken up unless you have special equipment. For Notebook computers - it's recommended that the user removes the battery from the system anytime the machine draws power from the wall socket, other wise the battery stays in a less-than-ideal 100% charged condition at all times.  Only top off the batter before you go on trips, when you know you'll need the extra juice.   Tip #3: Keep your cool.  Hot temperatures can significantly reduce the lifespan of a Li-Ion battery, and exceedingly hot temperatures can cause the battery to leak or even explode.  Keep your battery packs or iPods in a cool place (59' F or lower) when ever possible. [ note from Scott: so don't leave them in your car on a hot day, after all they're made to be extremely small and portable, and chances are that your pocket or purse will be much cooler than inside your car ]  For products with removable batteries, take the battery out whenever possible when using them on AC power to avoid heat and over-charging issues that can reduce the lifespan of the batteries.   Tip #4: Beware of old age.  Because of their chemical makeup, Li-Ion batteries deteriorate as time passes, and there is nothing that can be done to prevent this process.  Over a period of 18 months to three years, the capacity of the battery slowly diminishes until finally it won't accept a charge, at which point there is no way to resuscitate it.   Tip #5: A couple of solutions.  - 1) If still under warranty  urlLink AppleCare  only charges $29.95 for shipping and handling.  Out of warranty: Apple's Battery Service costs $99 plus a $6.95 S&H (total of $105.95).  - 2)  urlLink iPod ResQ  - cost $79.  Service: ship a padded box to customer via overnight with prepaid overnight shipping back to the company, technicians switch out the battery that day and box it and send it back to the customer via overnight.  - 3) Two others to check out:  urlLink PDA Smart.com  and  urlLink iPod Battery.com .  The Article Recommends:  Use Apple or iPodResQ   Websites to check out for further research and information:  urlLink iPod's Dirty Secret   urlLink CE Tips.com   urlLink Cadex Electronics   urlLink Battery University   Hope this is useful to everyone.  Send feedback!
     

    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm home from NY, but my computer is still on the fritz... so you'll just have to wait for the whole story. Sorry.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yeah, I haven't had the chance to do an update everyday.  I've been going and going and going, and then I get "home" and I crash... hard.   When I return home, I'll make sure I post a bunch of pictures for your enjoyment.  Until then, I post pics in my PhotoBlog in the sidebar, and you can click on the images to see larger images, so go there until I return!    Exploring a new place is tough work.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Since april 19th I've been having issues with my computer.  I call Dell Tech Support and they fix one problem, and then another pops up.  I have wanted to change my template for a while now, and prior to the unfortunate state of my laptop, I was working on one.  Now, I've switched back to one of the lame template presets that you can get from blogger (they're nice and all, but I'm just not content with them anymore) until I can upload my new page.  I just got tired of looking at the other one, really.  On another note, I leave for Prestonsburg, KY, in 5 days.  Podunkville, USA, as I affectionately call it sometimes.  It's a really beautiful place, but I miss everything about a larger city when I'm gone.  The blog will probably be put on haitus (sp?) for a couple months since I may not have access to the internet.  I know all three of you who read my blog will be distraught and heart-broken (yeah, right) but it can't be avoided.  Please pray for patience, sanity, health, and safety for me while I'm away.  Thanks. :)
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Congratulations to my Big Brother - Kelly (Bub) Cox, and his BRAND NEW WIFE - Jamie!!!  I wish you two all the best!
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm beginning to see the side of those people who oppose the smoking bans in certain cities around the country.  I don't think the government should have ANY control over business owners.  They shouldn't have to worry about making a building safe for people to enter the premises.  After all, it's their choice if they want to step inside a condemned building.  I definitely think that health inspectors should stay OUT of kitchens in restaurants.  Who cares if there are a couple of rats running around the kitchen... it doesn't bother me if an employee doesn't wash his/her hands after using the bathroom and then handling my food.  What's a couple of hairs in food between total strangers, right?  The government regulates all kinds of things, things that we take for granted every day, things that we wouldn't think of changing... all for public health and safety.  If you're a smoker.  That's fine, I'm not telling you not to smoke, just don't smoke around me.  An hour in a restaurant WON'T kill you to be without a cigarette.   Second-to-Last thought:  I think an exception to the ban should have been made in the fact that if someone wanted to open an establishment especially for smokers (aka - a smoking bar or a cigar bar) that should be allowed.   Last thought:   Being a person who has been VERY affected by the horrors of cancer and other diseases due to smoking, I totally agree with the ban.  NOT going through with the ban is like sentencing everyone to a slow and ugly death.  If you disagree with me, feel free to take it up with my father - wait, you can't - he died from lung cancer caused by smoking almost 13 years ago.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I hate packing.  Therefore I'm not doing it.  I leave tomorrow and I'm only about 1/4 packed.  Packing is the worst part of taking a trip or moving... I mean, UNpacking is even better than packing.  It's more fun.  Almost seems like a treasure that you've just discovered!  Anyway.  I'm procrastinating.  I guess I should go make another attempt to pack SOMEthing at least.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm very overwhelmed by the people from my church.  As many of you know, I'm leaving on Wednesday for Jenny Wiley Theatre to work for the summer.  Now, I've worked there for four years, now, and each time I've left, I have just had a friend or two say goodbye to or to "see me off".  Tonight people are actually getting together to have kind of a send off get-together for me.  Never has anyone ever done that for me, and it just really makes me feel like part of a really awesome family.  I'm really going to miss a lot of the people from my church, and especially people from my small group.  I suppose I've gotten by before, but I'm just a little bit sader to leave this year, even though I know I'll have a good time in Prestonsburg.  On another note, Blogger just launched it's new site and they've got a blue zillion new templates, so I figured I'd try one out.  They've also got a whole slew of new features to try out.  Too bad I won't have a lot of time to actually play around with them before I leave.  Oh well.  Thanks to all my friends and "family" for your presence in my life.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've been in Prestonsburg a little over a week, now.  I'm getting all buff and tan and sweaty.  We're doing a lot of great things and everyone's working really hard.  Here's a quick run-down of some of the highlights:  - arrived and it felt like a family reunion ( the good kind ) - cleaned 150 lighting instruments and uncoiled over 5000 feet of cable - hung a pipe grid and created a makeshift truss - played basketball - played ultimate frisbee - ate lots of good food (5 meals a day) - had lots of laughs with new and old friends  That pretty much sums it up for the moment, folks, except for some specific stories that I don't have the time to go into right now.  I hope everyone that reads this is enjoying their summer to some extent.  I know I am... I mean what's better than doing something you absolutely love - AND getting paid for it!?  over and out
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      To those of you that want to know.  I'm not dead. :)  Sorry to those of you who wish I was... looks like luck's on my side today!
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Summer Nights - from Grease!  Key Lyrics:    Summer loving had me a blast Summer loving happened so fast ... Summer dreams ripped a the seams  But oh those summer nights   The Luckiest - Ben Folds  Key Lyrics:    And where was I before the day That I first saw your lovely face? Now I see it everyday And I know  That I am I am I am The luckiest
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Another quick post from JWT...  Today I helped rig up the flying track and mechanism to make Peter Pan and company fly for our production of Peter Pan.  It's another great resume builder experience.  When we were finished the "Fly Guy" - the man from whom we're renting the gear and who's teaching the flymen and actors how to do everything thing - asked me if I wanted to fly.  Of course I said yes, and I flew like Peter Pan, Wendy, John and Michael.  It was really cool and a lot of fun, I was basically the guinea pig for the guys learning the ropes before the actors came in.  I guess I'm more expendable than the actors are or something ;).  Anyway, I'm having a blast when I can... my part of putting up the shows is almost over (at least the tough part).  A lot of late nights are happening right now, but in the end, it'll be worth it.  Love to all!
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      1) it sucks when people you care for just don't seem to "get" you  2) loneliness is more bitter when it's not shared  3) all work and no play really does suck  4) blowing stuff up is cool and exciting   5) i'm doomed to a single life  on a lighter side... Into The Woods opens tomorrow night and then I switch roles from Master Electrician to Lighting Designer and my job becomes ten times easier - ten times harder - and I get paid more for it.  Man - I hope I don't F#@$ it up.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Probably THE coolest thing that I've done so far [at Jenny Wiley] is to create flash pots and other pyro effect delivery devices, and design and build the firing mechanisms for said devices.  More on this later... if you're lucky.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today is a day of celebration!  Today marks my 400th Post.  It also marks the end of the build at Jenny Wiley Theatre!  All of our shows are up and running.  We opened Legend of Jenny Wiley last night to a huge house.  And it was very well received.  My first paid lighting design looks amazing... even I'm impressed with myself, and people have been fairly encouraging.  One person commented that it is the best the show has ever looked. I'm very proud of that design.  Well, it's not much of a post... but it's the 400th... isn't that swell?  Keep checkin' in... who knows... maybe there'll be 400 more.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>