<Blog>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      With their tanks and their bombs And their bombs and their guns, In your head, In your head, they are dyin'....  Poor buggers, dunno whats up in my head at the moment but it feels like something up there is dying. Maybe its me. But who is me anyway? Meh. I think I need a hug. My little bit of imaginary tipsyness has worn off and the world is colder on this side. Or it was always cold and someone stole my jumper. This may appear as nonscence, take it as that if you wish, but it is really some of the thoughts flying though my head..... 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ROBYN IS THE BEST! Sorry doing 'tomorrow when the war began' in english and I thought I would share my opinion. Mr Marsden sir, you are a genius. *two thumbs up* YAY! Even though I've read it b4 its still a very exellent book. The only exception is the work we have to do with it. Meh, oh well.  OH YEAH! And Congratulations!! (Why?) 'Cause You Aught To Be, Congratulated! 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OOOOHHH WAAAHHH! (MacDonalds "Dory" Toy). www.thesurrealist.co.uk/slogan  Yes well, If you've noticed I'm in a better mood now, no one gave me a hug though :( I STILL WANT MY HUGS DAMIT! Oh Well how were they suposed to know. READ THIS DAG NAMIT! I'm pouring out my heart! Well not really, I don't want a half empty heart, or would it be half full? :D:D Sorry, love playin' with the minds of others MUHAHAHAHA!  yes well, i'm done now, bye! :o thers no nonesence!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay there are just a few things that annoy me and stealing the idea off B I'm making a hit list. Muhahaha! Yes well she did steal my poem and no I'm not talented. 1. Teachers who give you work to do that they don't even understand (SOSE!) and when you ask them what it means they say "I already went though that" even if they haven't 2. That make-up brand "Be Yourself" No offence but how exaclty is layering make up on your face being who you really are? 3. People who disrespect others. Like okay, if you feel the need to make fun of someone in that joking way turn it back on you and see how you feel. 4. People who continually say "I'm fat" or "I'm ugly". Sorry to state the odvious but you're not ugly or fat you're beautiful and should be proud of it. 5. Okay, people who dis my freckles. Its not sun cancer and there aren't any mapped constlations on my arm!  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah, why am I writing if I have nothing to say, or maybe I do and just can't get to the point. My brain thinks it's going to explode, but shouldn't, so don't worry, it won't splatter brainy goodness on your nicely clean shirt. Meh, who really cares anyway. No one else does so why should I? bang bang maxwell sliver hammer came down on her head, bang bang maxwell sliver hammer we're sure she was dead... in you head, its in your head.....I want the world, I want the whole world, I want to lock it all up in my pocket, it's my bar of chocolate, give it to me now!!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yeah well, me not so happy, don't know why. even twang has lost it's charm.... myeah, well, if you see me I'd really appreciate a hug, or two. or one really big hug.... hmmm... 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      FOR ALBY Alby, you are one of the smartest, funniest guys I know and if that shit school melbourne high can't see that then they don't even deserve to be in your presence! You aren't a pile of turd either!! (I wouldn't hug a pile of turd). So Alby, this is for you....  Today's the day,  where I disappear and fly away. Can't they see, that their words are slowly killing me. My hopes, my dreams are getting tired. This moment feels so shiiat. But i won't give in, I'll live to win. And they'll regret, That we only met, and they,  let, me,  go.....
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *drum roll* . . . . . TA-DA!! ITS MASKING TAPED HAND GIRL! YAY!! WOOHOO! Yeah I got bored and found this massive roll of masking tape and it is now noticably smaller, but my hand bigger :D 89264!! 89264! Translation TWANG!!! YAY!! Sorry i need that happy word to keep me going. When the world shuts me down, when my friends throw me out of town, when a lone rice cracker becomes my only friend, you'll run back for me in the end.... I hope, I wish, I dream, for everything not to turn out as it seems...  yeah well, twang....
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      horseriding+rain+me=AWESOME TIME + sore bottom. ohhhh my sore bottom, how it hurts! My horse was the coolest. GO CHICKO!! TWANG! True happiness cannot be described to its full extent, only experienced. Hero of the year. I loooove being a turtle! mmm pizza. itza itza pitzza and its very yummy! eisykalt ist coca-cola, coca-cola eisykalt. Well something like that, I've only ever sung it, so I don't know how it's spelt. Some german thing we did in P.S. about ice cold coca-cola with a following verse about egg and ham snadwitches. It was fun, lol no sarcasm intended. German has changed since primary soooo much it isn't funny, maybe coz our teacher has a huge attetude problem and everything has to be her way or no way and ooooh lets all sympathise how hard her life must be! She is quite annoying but she gives me good marks so I can't really hate her. ARRG! SHE'S ANNOYING! Yesh well. Be careful as you go, coz little people grow, and little people know, when little people fight, we may look easy pickings but we got some bite!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hands are really quite perfect things. Okay, have a look at your hands. LOOK AT THEM! I know you're most likley not but I shall continue. Each didgit has its own little unit of nerves and can be moved individually by a series of perfectly balanced muscles planned exaclty where they are needed to move your hand where you want to. How is it possible for atoms to group together and just change or evolve into such a pieces of complex, balanced, pure brilliance? Even over a matter of zillions and zillions years it still seams unbelievible in my opinion,..
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Please excuse the last entry, I guess I was being over pesimistic, sorry, nothing comes from complaining. Which brings me back to nonesence! It is something but means nothing! Its brilliant and I love it. Quotes are good too. They're a good thing to help get out of shifty questions that you really don't want to answer like "Soooo, what did YOU do on the weekend with your hot hunk of spunk? eh??", e.g. relpy "How do I know I can trust you?" And do the shifty eye thing with the moving of eyebrows. It either scares them and they move on or they start to believe that something happened and ask more questions in which you laugh (tehehe) and skip away smiling and singing "I know something you don't know and I'm not going to tell you". Yes or that would just be one of those plans which are fun to think about but you'd never actually do. Well I dun have a hot hunk of spunk atm (the one hiding in my closet found the secret passage to Narina and never came back) so I don't think anyone would ask me that question in the first place =S.  Well, yes, I will be going now... But beware, WE KNOW WHERE YOU LIVE! WE LIVE WHERE YOU LIVE! HAHAHAHA! (go Joe's Apartment cockroach dudes!)
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes, it is sad. It is 8:25pm and where am I??? Hidden away in the computer room. Yep, I have no social life, so here I write into cyberspace that will never listen or respond. Its a wonder why people even bother publishing things on the net, they say "to hear their message heard", but you know what? NO ONES LISTENING!! Its a huge, deep, dark pit were the thoughts of meaningless little people spin around and around only to be picked up by mistake and tossed back into the horrible void it came from. I have no idea why I even write here. AHHH! man! I don't like this! Its seems I question everything with a reason, and if it doesn't then I question it even more and its no fun on the brain waves man, its no fun. Maybe I shouldn't question at at all, maybe I should just toss it back into the deep pit of cyberspace....    
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Don't you just  HATE  it when you do a big poop and the person before you only left one or two pieces of toliet paper?? It is very annoying. My advise, always check the roll first. Also don't wear black socks on hot days 1. because black absorbs heat ur feet get hotter, 2. if you feet are hot they sweat more which = smelly feet and 3. it leaves black pieces of fluff stuck to your foot which gets right inbetween your toes. TOE JAM! yummy. Rubber Ducky, joy of joys, when I squeese you, you make noise. everyday when I, make my way to the tuuuuubbbbbyyy, I find a little fella who's, cute and yellow and chuuuuuuuuubbbbbbbyyyyy.  Ernie is the best!!! WOOOHOOO!! Berts okay. Doin' the * * PIGEON!!  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah I thought I'd put abit more poetry/depth in here. maybe I'm just bored and have to get this stuff outta my head. meh, i don't know....   the weakening spirit, of a girl that is lost, in all of her days,  and in all the miles she's crossed, she thinks she's never found love...  she cries out,  for the kindness of any,  no one helps,  though 'round her are many,  she'll never beleive in love...  huddled in a corner, wrapped in all that she owns, eyes squeezed shut, she prays, wishing she had a home, somewhere where she could love...  the night grows cold, her breathing lenghtens, she knows who she is, but keeps on forgetting, that she has someones love...  the day begins, she thanks the sun for shining, her eyes are red and puffy, u know that she's been crying, hoping for someones love...  she keeps hoping and wishing,  never getting, but giving, hope to all around her. she smiles so weakly, not harshly, a little sweetly, her hope beams a little brighter.  because she remembered love...
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Good evening fellow bloggers, tehehe that sounded funny. Yes, well. AHHH! again with the "yes, well"'s, I'll have to think of something different. hmmmm. Anywho, nah, anyway, nup, oookaaaaaayy moving on now, nope, WHO REALLY CARES ANYWAY!! oooh! I like that one! well, I'm not going to say well, yes anymore except for that one occasion. Moving on, hey, what about the day! Forever and ever you'll stay in my heart and I will love you, forever and ever.... sorry my sister was singing. No the original of coursem the one of "my best friends wedding", yes, I have mixed opinions on that movie.... "don't push the red button" "wah?" "The red button!" "Oh!" *push* "AAAAHHHHHHHH!!!!", push the button, don't push the button, push the button, don't push the button, trip the station, change channel. yes wanywho, funny, honey, honey hmmmm tasting good, tasting fine, funny, honey, honey, you know your on my mind! But then there is always that stray chocolate thought, or that ice-cream that I just bought, but oooooh funny, honey, honey, you taste so sweet to me. THAT IS ACTUALLY ABOUT HONEY! Not some love affair I have with some sexy beast with rippling muscles and a huge personality hiding in my closet. Aww man got to stop watching day time soapies when I'm home, they really polute your mind. Yes well theres alot of emtpy space in my mind so it shouldn't matter that much. Brad! I'm mad, for you too... Ohh! I have to go check my sexy beast hasn't escaped!  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh! Badger, Badger, Badger, Badger, Badger, Badger, Badger, Badger, Badger, Badger, Badger, Badger, Badger, Mushroom, mushroom! YAY! Ah its a snake! yes, well that is off a little animation on the net about badgers. Its really funny and gets stuck in your head quite easily. www.badgerbadgerbadger.com! yeah! badger, badger, yes okay, I'll stop. TWANG! tehehe. Today, if you live in the forest hill - burwood area, you would of noticed the torrential rain between 3:30-4:00 and then a little to follow later. Guess who was walking home at around 3:30?? MEE!!! I greatly sympathise anyone else who got trapped in the rain, but it was actually quite nice. I haven't been that wet with clothes on since I was 10! That didn't come out right, I'm not a bare-bottom rain dancer, ahhhh.... I think I'll say no more and hope no one ever reads this. I would just delete it but these are thoughts and you just can't erase thoughts. badger, badger, badger....sorry, impulse. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Poopsie-Apple Shorts! AHH!! If you just came from B's Blog hello! (If not, hers is http://monkeypants73.blogspot.com.) I Am Poopsie-Apple Shorts! I didn't know she was going to tell people my blog. I thought it was going to live in cyberspace for all its exsistance and never be read, but hey, nice to see you! Well, no exacltly see you, I don't even know if you're really reading this, are you? AHH!! Yes, well, I say that alot, well, don't read the thing about eating reused human flesh if you are eating. Well its not that discusting, its just disturbing. well I thought I would warn you.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Chicken atoms, chicken atoms, chicken atoms in my apple! AHH! somethings in science you don't want to know about, like how the atoms and energy for dead animals and their poop end up being reused by trees, which includes trees thats bare fruit which we eat! If someone was buried next to an apple tree, after the decomposers did their work, the apple tree would take up nutients and atoms and energy from the dead body and use it!! WE COULD BE EATING HUMAN FLESH!!! AHHH!! I'M A CANIBAL!! Well maybe not to that extreme. But did you really need to know that? No, but its not nonesence!! NOOO!!!! OOOHHH!! One fine day with a woof and a purr a baby was born and it caused a little stir, no blue buzzard, no three-eyed frog, but a feline-canine little catdog. CATTTTTDOOOOOOOOOGGGGGG! CAAAAAAATTDOOOOOOOGGGG! Alone in the world is a little catdog!  We could be heroes, forever and ever! We could be heroes just for one day! ONE MORE DAY!! Optimistic! Me like! I got the joy, joy, joy, joy, down in my heart, where?, down in my heart! where? down in my heart! I got the joy, joy, joy, joy down in my heart, where? down in my heart to stay! YAY!  Anywho, to who ever may read this, (well to everyone really, who would read this??) I LOVE YOU! MWAH! And if you're a complete stranger I don't care! I love you all! WAH!!! HUGS FOR EVERYONE!!! *hug**hug**hug**hug**hug**hug**hug**hug*  If you smile, just for a while, other people too, will smile back at you! :D:D:D
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ONE MORE DAY!! ANOTHER DAY, ANOTHER DESTINY! Yes, *cough* well we're doing Les Mis in music, its pretty good, it's a musical with depth! :o surprising!(not sarcasm) yeah well I thought it was very inspirational. WEll yes so thats wat I'm going to write today, somethig with depth, but don't you fret, nonesence will be back! Yes well here is something written by me, it has depth but is incomplete so yeah hmmm.....  Frozen in my shoes.  But what have a really got to lose?  A life in which no one cares?  A life in which it's truth who dares? They can go on living, I'm getting tired of giving, They can go on looking up there nose,  On those who opose,  The way the world spins,  How only the lucky ones win. I'll go on drowing in my place,  Where I'm the only1 without a face,  Forgetting the memories of why,  Maybe I'm just getting tired, Someones yelling in my ear, But I don't want to hear, Shut their mouth, shut them out, What they got to complain about? Drowning in air that keeps them alive,  Have they felt the quench to die?  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Who you gonna call?? GHOSTBUSTERS!! or me! call me! Well if you already have my number please do, I'd appriciated it. Hi my name is Frances and I haven't used the phone in around 3 days now. Yay! No radiation going through my head!! Tell all my friends I'm dead....
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      TWANG! If you say it right, you smile, if you don't say it right you don't deserve to smile! Sorry but if you do say it right the corners of your lips go up and yeah, start the craze!! TWANG TWANG!! yay! :D yes well, first entry. Hmmm, how much wood would a woodchuck chuck if a woodchuck could chuck wood?? well? 4? that all? ok, thats a pretty lazy woodchuck then. Lazy, lazy, lazy, lazy, lazy, lazy, lazy Jane. She wants a drink of water, so she waits and waits and waits and waits and waits for it to rain. Awww, anyone do that in primary school? TWANG! 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Jingle bell, jingle bell, jingle bell rock. Jingle bells swing and jingle bells ring. Snowing and blowing up bushels of fun. Now the jingle hop has begun.  December tomorrow. Hmmm. I GOT A VENUS FLY TRAP FROM MY BESTEST BUD KATE! yay! it is soo cool, but all of them are closed coz ppl were playing with them and seeing if they would close on their fingers. Its the coolest and some of them look like they have red lips. Rebuilding bridges in your mind, your eagerness now is on the line. Sorry, listening to radio, sometimes good, sometimes bad. Too many ads. Kelly just got back from netball, they lost the semi final. bother. Oh well, I think they still got another chance, hmm. Consider this, consider this, the hint of the century, consider this, the slip that brought me, to my knees failed, what if all these fantasies, come flailing around, now I've said too much....  You like potato and I like potarto, you like tomato and I like tomarto, potato, potarto, tomato, tomarto, let's call the whole thing off. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yep, I am obsesed with this blog. Its just so luscious and bewildering. Call it an addiction, I'll try and get over it, and only do it once a day or maybe once every two days. But its just so boring otherwise, well its boring still but i'm typing, lalalala dooo bop bop bob the tomato, larry the cucumber. The same, insane, brain waves are rocking through my head. Someone signed in MSN "Up YoUrS jIvE tUrKeY". wow. how now brown cow. 'Update save file' reading screen. 'Retry' 'Level Select' 'Watch Replay' 'Quit'.  Well I had my first being pissed off mood swing today for a very long time. Can't they just turn around if i'm in a bad mood, oh "Sorry I'm so social" I'm sorry buddy, but is it possible for you to say 'sorry' with out being so sarcastic? And when did you start wanting to talk to Pete anyway. And thats my anger outletting done. Grrrr.  I have now successfully failed History SOSE, whoopdee doo. Its been and gone and I'm over it. Why do we need to know why the English settled Australia? I mean its all good and well that they did and yippee, rejoicing in the streets, but why do we need to know that? And why do we have to make up someones diary but still keep to the facts? It could either be called creative writing or plagiarism. None of these arguement a valid though, all wrong, all could be counter attacked. The debate is lost, just like all our other school ones, Wendy, you so should of gotten best speaker for that last one, you kicked ass, and Alice all I can say is pure brilliance. And to Jo who gave it up because of soccer, and was on the bus that hit me, well done in getting out of it early. And to stupid teachers who say congratulations when we lost, one point three times in a row is still a loss, accept the fact that the school sucks.  and now i'm actually done. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I slowly burn, From the inside out, No one cares, They just want to know what its about.  Suddenly hot goes to cold,  I start to freeze,  now frozen over,  could I just have one hug please?  But if you can't be bothered, Don't mind me, I don't care, I'll go on pretending to be happy...   
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Laughing at the sky Shapah doo daa, and continuing with the vocal solo with the pah dee da dooop. While the sun isn't shining, the whole world is whineing, but me, I'm singing. I don't like being the only year 9 on music camp, it sucks. Its now that part of the show where Larry sings a silly song. Oh Barbara Manatee, you are the one for me, sent from up above, you are the one I love. i don't like peas. The Queen of hearts, she made some tarts, all on a summers day, the naive of hearts, he stole those tarts and took them right away. or some variation. I would like an e-mail, and e-mail pLAease! Anything from politics to your favourite type of cheese. or you could tell me to shut up and stop watsing my time trying to make everything rhyme. that one was a mistake. and I'm done.      P.S. How funky is your chicken? How funky is your chicken? How loose is your goose? Our goose is totally loose! hurrah for pointless chants!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      . . . dot dot dot don't know whats up, so don't bother askin'. The Jean Genie lives on his back. The Jean Genie loves chimney stacks. He's outrageous, he screams and he bawls. Jean Genie let yourself go! Shmeh thought it was a comitment to write so I did, and now I'm gone. Thats the time you must keep on trying, Smile, whats the use of crying, You'll find that life is still worthwhile, If youll just Smile... Its Jaskson Michael not Michael Jackson
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What am I doing anyway, I don't really know, So I will go, So away I shall fade, Into the lies I made, Into the time that will be yesterday.  It took me awhile to tear, At the seems, For all it means, I'll remember you there, As you were, At the time you cared.  Woof, woof, meow. Run slow run fast, Forever it'll last Burning legs, sweating brow, Got to keep up no matter how, Run, run, fly away now.   So now I disappear, Forget me, You never met me, Into yesterday, into yesteryear, I'm not fine but have no fear, Only thing left will be my tear.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      its five to 3, someone is bored and that person is me....
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, the new heading I put on stuffed up, so it is back to the old, boring one. But Quixotic Gnome is still here. OH! And I have links, I'm so very proud of myself, go me.  It be a new day. Saturday. Sat (on) ur (arse) day. A day for nothing. Well, I have homework and its my own bloody fault except I want to blame someone else but that wouldn't be right because it is my fault.  Wow, one of my friends signed in with this name,  "people are like sausages... its whats under the skin that counts.... so poke them with a fork periodically"  I like it, so be careful if you see me with a fork looking all shifty eyed and cunning, not to say that I'm usually not. MUHAHAHA, why does this always end up about me? What about me, it isn't fair, u've had your turn now I want my share, can't you see, I want to live, but you.... just... take.. more... than... you give.... what about me.... Excuse the singing outburst, although there may be various more just ignore them, or sing along. My dad picks the fruit that goes to... and I'll stop there as I shouldn't sing adds. Wic-a-wic-a warrenator. If you love life, then lets have a love life.  I'm stuck on pain 'cause pains stuck on me! and yeah, well... What I don't get is why people can't except that you can change your mind if you want. It shows that you are thinking and not a programable robot. I'm most likely being a bit hypercritical here but meh, so is everyone else so I shall join he club (yay clubs, maces work better). Changing your mind means you've thought it over more and have seen more outcomes, pros and cons. Well thats me being all unrealastically logical so I shall stop pretending Im someone I'm not. I really couldn't bother thinking about what the outcomes could be. and I'll stop now because its about me again. what about me...   OH HAPPY BIRTHDAY NAOMI!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Somebody come and play Somebody come and play today Somebody come and be my friend And watch the sun 'til it rains again  Somebody come and play.... today  Somebody come and play Somebody come and play today Somebody come and smile the smiles And sing the songs, it won't take long Somebody come and play.... today  Joe Raposo
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ross is a hole (in tassie) with faulty toilet doors. (its also my brother lol)
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I never want to go in another bus ever again. I have come to the conclusion after approx. 24hrs in a bus over the last 5 days that I hate buses and believe that those bumming scientists should hurry up and build me a molecule relocation device so that I don't have to go in a bus again. By the way, Tassie was okay. BUT I HATE BUSES! the one we had the floor got really hot because the motor was underneth and so I burnt my foot. and there was heaps of gum everywhere because people are lazy slobs and can't put it in the bin so i just goes everywhere else. RAAAG!! I like jet boating and chocolate but I'm sorry I can't stand buses any more, I pity those who have to catch one to school everyday. If I had wings I would fly away, to where there is no light of day, so I could hide in my own dismay. Paha. pathetic rubbish made from the bus angered mind of... wait for it... CECIL! Yes, according to kaitlyn, I am now cecil.  And I found out that people are jealous of me. Of what is my question exactly. It's amazing what you find out on camps and taking photo's of people who have fallen asleep on each other in lesbian posses on the bbdhbvjkads is hilarious. Suposedly I'm lucky that I don't hate anyone, they don't have to hate someone because they did something, if you do they be even more bumming annoying and you'll loose another friend to talk to. I like talking, but about nothing, if you havn't noticed from my blogs. I'm not one of those everyones my friend person, just, I don't hate them I don't act like I hate them so I give no reason for them to hate me and I should really stop talking about myself, maybe just alittle more. Waving is good to. especially crazy waves, and the mocking of the queen (good for her) waves.   and when is this shakespeare concert?? I want to go dammit, I won't know anyone there but I want to go. It was probally yesterday, just to spite me. ggrrrr, I don't like top bunks on the spirit of tasmania either, (Kaitlyn got the bottom bunk again and its not fair!) but it could be tonight, and if it is tonight I most probally wont be able to go anyway or I will and wont be able to get of my bbdhbvjkads riding, sore, pittiful huge bottom and spend generations at this computer with this as my only connection to the outside world. I moved from the point again. I WANT TO GO! and I'm done.  Well seeing I've been away for 5 days I thought I'd make up for lost space in this magical world of the blog. A worm can roll and stone, a bee can sting a bear, a fly can fly around versilles coz flies don't care, a sparrow in a hat, can make a happy home, a flea can bite the bottom of the pope in rome. Awww memories,  GO STEPH GO! It was all you. noicely done. yes, well, I'm still percrastinating (bad spelling) about my music project. Meh, whats the point anyway? To show the skills that you have? Its been done in every other class except history and thats because she has a mental problem where she can't recognise logic. Why do we have to hand in a copy of our good copy in hand writing? How does that show we didn't copy it of the internet? RAGG!! BOBBA! Oh, I was meant to stop that, and saying hurrah, it "doesn't suit me", it doesn't but I like saying it anyway. just coz it doesn't suit me doesn't mean I can't say it, check out fashion for example. no don't, its a scary world where it contradicts itself by saying "retail" and "be different" in the same sentence. Tasmainian radio is bad. I like fudge. I'm writing to Mr No One, do you think his address is in the middle or on the east side of nowhere? paha damn deforming mind of mine, killing me and killing time.  I worked out that it was blogger that was making my computer act like it was on speed , but its easy to fix just by reseting or by just waiting. It just stopped being all speedy!! yay! Wow I feel special.  Its the chocolate!! the chocolate!! LAURA YOUR SHOES! (long story) I had to keep away from coke and chocolate all week, well i tried, after a day of full on yummy junky (lunch was yuk) food my head decided to explode, defying me of any social practices on the first night. People pretending they care is funny, its always "are you okay?" and if you say no its usually "awww, hope you feel better" and then they walk off. And I'm very sorry Jo for walking off on you near that terrible music, party boat, but I thought when you turned your back you didn't wish to be in my presence, so I disappeared.  Plenary: complete in every respect : absolute, unqualified. I don't understand that meaning how can it be absolute while being unqualified, wouldn't it be fullyqualified?? Or is a plenary person soo good they don't need qualufacations? And why do I ask so many retorical (I don't think thats to word) questions?    THIS PROGRAM HAS PERFORMED AN ILLEGAL OPERATION AND WILL BE SHUT DOWN.    p.s. I don't like salad and ham rolls/sandwitches either   p.s.s. jealous of me?? I don't get it!  p.s.s.s. I just wanted to write a p.s.s.s.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, happy birthday to me, hurrah, I know I'm excited.... yeah its pretty boring. CAMP!!! CAMP!!! 1 hour til we leave in a bus. WOW yeah, just though tI would wirte to say good bye. I'll miss you for a whole week, unless I get really lucky and scab a computer or get really sick and come back home =(. hopefully not. well catch ya's.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Shmell my feet! Why do so many people do gardening on hot days??? Blood and bone (fertilizer) + sweat + dirt + flys = annoying, smelly, unnessecary work that could of been done on an overcast day. My idea if you have one of those biggish freezers is take everything out and put it in the fridge (just in case of selmanella or how ever you spell it) and sit in it with head phones on. Another idea is beach but I'm not a beach person 1. coz I don't like sand for various reasons 2. I'd be burnt to a crisp even with sun-cream. and 3. too many people go to the beach. and so I rest my case. To people how enjoy the beach, good for you, I'm just not a beachy person. I'm more outdoor walking/hiking person. I like trees, trees are cool. There are no trees on the beach. Salt water, yeah I don't like that either.  Yes, well, off the beach. Tasmania tomorrow, birthday tomorrow. I said tasmania first because I'm more excited about that than my birthday. Birthdays are cool but they make me feel alittle greedy. Well, thats me anyway, well part, the other quarter is going "GIVE ME PRESENTS DAMN IT". Meh, another confusing aspect of me. Ahuh. AHHH! computers on speed again, maybe it'll just run out and go back to normal.  Slurpin' on a peach. Dragon, dragon, rock the dragon, dragon ball Z YA! Ol' man on the back porch, old man on the back porch, old man on the back porch, and that old man is me. Who lives in a pineapple under the sea? SPONGE BOB SQUARE PANTS! Absorbent and yellow and pourus is he! SPONGE BOB SQUARE PANTS! If naughtical nonsence is something you wish SPONGE BOB SQUARE PANTS! Then jump on the deck and flop like a fish! mmm water! need water. H2O, H2 NO. Tune out with TWIX. PAT-ATO CHIPS, no more mr nice guy. Was Pat Rafter every really nice? Like yeah he wasn't ever a mean bastard, but nice guys are usually really nice, not average nice. Well, I don't know, e-mail me your ideas at gday2u88@hotmail.com. yep, well. And in reading brigie's, sinead's and LE's blog (monkeypants73.blogspot.com) I think the ugliest part of the body is the gaps between your toes, but thats just me. Congrats to everyone who aught to be congratulated, hurrah, and you don't have to read mine to say thanks if you don't want to. Not to say that I'm ungrateful to who ever might read this, I'm just saying.... I have no idea wat I'm saying so I better stop. It's been swell, but the swellings gone down. (love that line). check ya's
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OH!! FAR OUT! I repeat that add yesterday!! I REAL DO WANT MY CLOTHES OFF!! (um well yeah) IT'S IS SO HOT! I'm boiling in my skin, so you can wear the dormio grin. I went outside with a think layer of sunscreen for 20mins or so and I still got burnt!! grr. This isn't my week. And now my computer is acting as if it's on acid and going really fast, the clock is going wack. 1 real min = 5 wacked on amphemenines mins. But who cares, even computers need alittle fun. So I shall keep on writing! hurrah! You aught to be congratulated. I'm lovin' it but my thighs aren't. I better go reset my computer b4 it blows up. ADIOS AMEGOS 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i want my...clothes off! i want my...bath tub! and the water! i want my....mr matey!!  awesome little ad, man, advertising's changed.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I am NOT PLEASED! I've had a migrain like everyday this week and it might mean I don't go to Tassie!! NOT HAPPY JAN! I wanna go to tasmania, even though its quite a hole, but still. GO AWAY MIGRAINS I DON'T LIKE YOU!! They probally don't like me so why don't they go away? Enough of my complaining, I'll proabally get to go and have lots of fun and throw ppl off the spirit of... I mean lots of fun throwing rocks at... Ahhh not throwing anything or throwing up. Yes, well having fun, and buying lotsa chocolate and eating it all in a giant feast with everyone. mmmm chocolate, wait NO! not good for migrains! DAMN YOU MIGRAIN!! *shakes fist in the air*
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pajama Giraffes. They are my giraffes not yours, being all splodgie as they are. purple background. Me want milk and cookies. Well not milk, I dun like milk, maybe if its chocolate milk. mmm cookies, cookies are good though espesically subway double choc cookies. Boy, I could eat them all day, not with a sub aswell though, otherwise I'd be sick, and thats never noice. Even more if its avacardo sick, its like pea soup thats... well you get the picture, not very pretty. well, COOKIES ARE YUMMY! C is for cookie that good enough for me, C is for cookies thats good enough for me, oh cookie cookie cookie starts with C.      little dune buggy in the sand, little dune buggy in my hand. wow, my bro Jason is so cool (ross is cool too but yeah), he GAVE me his Presidents of the usa albums, both of them! Now I shall take the rest of his CD's! muhahaha! they will be mine! Nah I wouldn't steal them, maybe borrow them without his knowledge, but I would return them eventually. with his fuzzy little toey-oh-oh-oh. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I feel so proud, I have met all challenges with flying colours, I can make a rhyming poem out of anything. But most of them are crap, but they still rhyme! and yeah, the best was about a pineapple that came from a tree.  Hello, Mr Pineapple why are you up so high? Don't you know you belong on the ground? I don't know how you climbed up there, We're missing you, so come back down.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hangin' out, down the street, the same old thing, that we did last week.  WOO HOO! "I'm so excited I think I need the toliet"  Happiness is like peeing your pants: Everyone can see it but only you can feel its warmth. "If peeing your pants is cool consider me miles davis" (lady from billy madison) Back to school! Back to school, to prove to Dad that I'm not a fool! I got my lunch packed up, my boots tied tight, I hope I don't get in a fight!  My Mama says that alligators are ornery because they got all them teeth and no toothbrush. Once you can accept the universe as matter expanding into nothing that is something, wearing stripes with plaid comes easy. (good ol' Albert Einstein) Life is like a box of chocolates. You never know what you're going to get.  Frankly, my dear, I don't give a damn! Look, it's been swell, but the swelling's gone down.  If I'm not back in five minutes... wait longer! I got to disappear now.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Yellow matter custard, dripping from a dead dog's eye, crabalocker fishwife, pornographic priestess, boy, you've been a naughty girl, you let your knickers down .  Do you know what thats from? the chorus should give it away, and if you still don't know you need and injection of musical culture.  I am the eggman, they are the eggmen, I am the walrus, Goo goo g'joob.   Many people think it is "coo coo ca choo", although it may sound like it, it is not, and you shouldn't change lyrics to one of the greaters in music unless it is a parody I which you change everything or if it is already a parody, cause then it would probally end up like the original and that would be weird. Misjudgement in philosophy, Messing up the mind of me. Defying laws of gravity, Withstanding the water of the sea. Changing everything as it seems, Only to realise they were waking dreams....
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      go brigie, go brigie, go, go, go brigie. Tell those stuffed up, putter downerers to go away rudely! I would but its just one of my morals with those kinda o whatever.  FUCK OFF YOU CREEPS AND LEAVE BRIGIE ALONE!  You shall be poked in the kidneys for ever more! tehehe! i mean MUHAHAHA!! yay! well I showed them with my bold letters posted on the internet. and I think if any does choose to start up my fan club they have to change the name to the mystic spiral caral club, cause they rock more than me, and its a caral. Oh bobba, I've written 3 times in one day. LOOK AT MY LIFE! and I actually did stuff today. Which is quite strange, but no fear none was music homework due in friday, i mean friday week..... and i'm going to start up the "go brigie" rant again coz its cool and she rocks! YAY! go brigie, go brigie, go, go, go brigie. me feel happier now and I really couldn't damn well care if you noticed or cared. peace out people of the generation.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      not happy jan. I'm sorry but I can't deliever nonscence at the moment. not in the best of moods. can't people just not catgorise others? Are people really that shallow? So what if they are different from you! You're different from everyone else. did you ever think of that? Appearance isn't anything. If you're head is going to explode because you don't want to do something because of how it would look who seriously cares? What happens if you're head explodes? YOU DIE! death appearance. hard to weigh up eh?    Far out, I'd really like a hug.  You saw the red, You saw the blue, Inside my head, Confusion grew, I closed up, but you still saw through. Don't leave me coz I'm different,  Stay because you are too....
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I apologise for the last couple of days for I promised noncence and did not deliever. I want chicken, I want liver, meow mix, meow mix, please deliver! If knowledge is power, and ignorance is bliss what are we meant to do in life? twidle your thumbs? skim rock on a lake? dominate the world? create your own blog? happy, happy, joy, joy, happy, happy, joy. YAY! hey for anyone who may every read this I'm planning on making FREE custom made, braclet, wrist-hugging, fabic thingys. and they shall be free... conditions apply. So if you want to know what on earth I'm on about contact me saying "WANT ON EARTH ARE YOU ON ABOUT" and I'll understand and smile and nod my head and go "thats nice dear" . No I'll reply properly and possibly make you one.  patchwork made at the hands, forming something within the strands, it was once nothing, now something, just strange and interesting. ha i reread that and I realised how lame it sounds. oooh man, do all my others sound as bad as that? oooh bobba. Oh well. Hugs and prayers out to anyone who ain't feeling too special. YOU ARE SPECIAL AND YOU SHOULD BE DAMN WELL PROUD OF IT!! If anyone owns a bible, please don't stone me for saying this, Psalm 91 is a good read if your not feeling your best.  When the rain comes it seems that everyone has gone away, when the night falls you wonder if you shouldn't find a place, to run and hide, but hidings such a lonely thing to do.... THIRD DAY! luv yas mate.  if you feel like hiding come hide with moi! "so we can be all steamy and thriffty at the same time". no, not really, sorry guys. Yeah, hiding is pretty lonely, join me so I shall not be lonely, but then I'll probally not be hiding if people knew where I am, unless you're playing sardines, but thats a completely different matter...
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      a b c d e f g h i am go ing to scream. I scream you scream, we all scream for ice-cream! mmm ice cream. one of the rewards in life at the moment. LOVE ME DAMNIT! green balloon? Oh well, a blue balloon is a maybe, maybe, maybe not. pick my nose, yellow snot. sorry msn convos mmixing up in my head. I feel better now if anyone cares, excuse my last impulse, on-the-spot poem. It is actually quite gloomy.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      what happens when the mind shuts down? when the gun goes off splattering guts on the ground? drowning in your own blood, whats the cause of death? just because someone hated you at your best....  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      and so I shall soon fade into the past...
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      blog blog blogging blogg-e-dy blog. spot spot spotty spotty spot spot. repeat repeat.  YES I'M EXTREMELY BOREDED!! Although I feel special cause i'm talking to 4 people at once in proper conversations. not just the "hi""hi""how r u?""good and u?""yep i'm good""thats good" NO!! down to 3. Jo left. but thats still three!!no! 2 have stopped! aww no one likes me. Atleast Alby still talks to me. HI ALBY!! HOWS IT DOING HOTTIE!! lol he'll never read it. heap of yr 8 girls he's known for like a week are asking him out. His reaction is hillarious. OHh g2g now have to set the table.  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Continuing with my hit list. B, u r a genius, this is a great idea and a good waste of time. =D=D Not like you'd read this lol! ha thas funny. Oh! and thank you Jo for waking up so we could watch movies!! Its was awesome!  6. People who have every conversation all about them. Okay, for people listening who aren't also talking about themselves it is pretty boring, open your eyes and look around. THEY ARE YAWNING!  7. Those people who think they're being nice when they say hello on msn and dont say another word. 8. Me, cause i just annoy myself and others sometimes by inconsiderant things that come out of my mouth. Even though people say I don't, I do and I notice it. 9. People who say I should swear more. FUCK OFF! is that enough for you? Now I shall refer to my "sugars" and "far out"     
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Easy for you to say! You didn't just eat 4 poisoned waffles!"  "WOW!! I mean wow what a funny joke!" Yes, we are watching the Daria movie again. ahhh goodness, it so good.  "Isn't golf for old people who dress funny?" "Do you get to ring the bell that goes ding-a-ling-a-ling.... a-ling?"  =D TWANG! HOLIDAY! DAY OFF! TWANG! =D  Its fun! I'm doing nothing! Hopefully someone would wake up or atleast get out of bed!! I'm all alone, nobody is here, besides me..... 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Daria Movie is probally the only decent video we actually own, well the labrynth is pretty cool too, tehehe Davie Bowie is a ledge in those tights. anyway, daria movie, seeing it is the only decent video shining in it's pure brilliance, my sister and I have watched nearly 15 times in the last month. "yo ho ho jolly green babe!". "Oh Kevy! You're so spidery!"  moo ha ha, briliance. I like it.  OH!! And I got a hair cut and I love it! Its like 15cm shorter and is around chin length and is longer at the front than at the back and yes. Its short. My mum is soooo talented!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Brilliance, pure brilliance mate. Nothing to say today, awesome party friday night for Halloween. And now I shall submerge into my homework and become a hermit. what a change! lol. Maybe I could actually get it done, but then wat would happen to my perfectly planned percrastination? I think I spelt that wrong but 'meh!'. Forget the words, forget what was said, I'm just the messenger between you and my head. Sorry, but I need an outlet for my creativity (If thats wat you call it) and this is the place to do it. Yes and to note, teachers don't appreciate art, neither words nor pictures being outletted on tables. Its not graffiti! and if it passes on alittle smile then what trouble is it causing? NOTHING! Despite all my rage I am still just a rat in a cage, then someone will say what is lost can never be saved...  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      -The last few weeks have been a bit weird, I kept getting these blocks of bad stuff in my head. Neither relevent or real but it just really gets grabs of your emotions and throws them against a wall. Like a fake life or maybe and interpretation of how someone else is living. Its not a nice feeling but it opens your eyes to somethings like God. God is and awesome god and he will always be there and always love you. I guess I was missing this point when I went down the river of another life. So if anyone out there isn't feeling too crash hot just remember that and I send out all my hugs to you *hug**hug**hug**hug**hug**hug**hug**hug**hug**hug*!! :D:D Nonscence may be back, most likely will, but I just thought I'd share it with all of who read this, lol, the only one is me.     
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today is the last day of 2003. Hurrah, within the next 12hrs I will sit down on a couch and go "wo ho another year" very unexcitedly.  Nature knows nothing of evil, nothing of violence, Nature knows nothing of death, nothing of silence. Pow, pow, pow! Onguard, toshay! Bang bang. Me bored, what else can I say? Au mein koft tut wei! (KITTY KAT! aww man my first published short story, published meaning in the school mag, lol funny, well actually lame.)  And they smile as if all is good and well, But inside the pressure starts to swell. They're no longer effected by what happens outside their head, They focus on the confusion instead. And then they realise that it isn't what it was. And start the whole mind-numbing circle again, just because... Depression is just anger without enthusiasm. Or something of the sort.  Song of the day:  Their tears are filling up their glasses  No expression, no expression  Hide my head, i wanna drown my sorrow, no tomorrow, no tomorrow  and i find i kind of funny, I find it kind of sad  the dreams in which i'm dying are the best i've ever had  I find it hard to tell you, I find it hard to take  when people run in circles its a very, very mad world.... mad world... 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I love you, you're better than ice-cream.=)=) Sorry, but its catchy. Speaking of catchy, the mexican hat dance! Ben and I were singing it, even though it has no words though knox and I think we were starting to annoy Shayesta. We saw LOTR, second time for me, the ending is soooo corny! Give me a bucket I need to throw up, and I didn't even eat any avacardo. Bleh! Tehehe Mr Depp is bald!! haha, what movie am I watching? You'll have to guess. Do do dooo-de do, ba ba baa-da ba. Hmm. etc. etc. and so on. KABLAMO!  Have you ever seen, A body of a dead man, Perished in the heat, half buired in the sand.  Ching-edy ching ching ching-edy. TING! =) Song of the day: Good morning starshine, the earth says hello, You twinkle above us, We twinkle below, Good morning starshine, you lead us along, My love and me as we sing, Our early morning singing song,   It was on Simpsons the other night. =) I bring you looove!  Mist and shadow, cloud and shade. All shall fade, all shall fade... Adios Awesome Air-guitar Amegos
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      RAH RAH RAH RAH RAH RAH RAH RAH RAH RAH RAH  Sorry, chatting to me mate Alby and that got stuck in my head.  Who me? Yes you! Couldn't be! Then who stole the cookie from the cookie jar. Whats funny is that we actually have a cookie jar and I ate the last cookie!!! TEHEHE!! *skips away giggling*  *comes back*  I love you, you're better then ice-cream. I love you, you lovely lovely dream. Oh you gotta see it, i think i'm obsecesed, or maybe I'm in love. Nope, I'm just obsesced. Funky chunky monkey. Dancing like a star. And I've given up on the story, it was crap and was going nowhere.  CHEESE WAS NEVER UNCOOL!! (except those hairy/mouldy ones) Writing about milk products... What did the first person to milk a cow think they were doing?!? Oh I just going to pull and this cows udder, wow! its drinkable and yummy! Okay, I just grossed myself out. I hope i grossed you out too. MOOOOOOOOOOSE! GOOOOOOOOOOSE! MOOOOOOOOSES! geese Ohh, I finished the Ellie Chronicles 6 days ago. AND IT WAS BRILLIANT!! BLOODY BRILLIANT!! AND AND!! OOOOH! I want to tell you people who read and who don't, but stories aren't the same if you know how it ends. So I'll just say this.... HA I'M NOT GOING TO SAY ANYTHING! READ IT YOURSELF! And be prepared to read pure brilliance. thANk yua John Marsden! I love you, I really really do.  Song of the day: (I would do the ice-cream kitten but i did that yesterday)  Its got the zip that makes you flip and thats what really counts In the Whoop-de-Dooper Loop-de-Looper Alley-Ooper Bounce!  Now, half this bounce is 90 percent mental If ya calculate the specific Tiggerjectory of yer Stripecelleration Diviferous by the Square Boot of yer Rebounce, yer Vertical Situituation should Riccatica-chet yer Hydraulific Fu-silly-age into an Accelerometric De-orbit!  Any questions?  (yeah I couldn't remember all of it so I used the net what a handy thing it is) well thats all from me! Adios Apple Antidote Amegos
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I love you  I really really do I love you  I hope u love me too I look in ur eyes  and I think that you are great stick with me for a while  and I'll always be your mate  you know I'll always be your mate I love you you're better than ice-cream I love you you lovely lovely dream I fall into your arms  and everthings ok  you are my sunshine and my love  on a rainy rainy day  on a rainy rainy day you know I love you I really really do you know I love you I really really I really really do...   GO THE SINGING CAT. MEOW!! I love you, I really really doooooo!!   WARNING PENERTRATION BELOW! 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ching-edy ching-edy, at moi mates kawtes house. Alex is here too, he's on the phone to nick. And playing spank the monkey, tehehe jk.  http://www.funnyjunk.com/pages/spank_the_money.htm Everytime we get over 200 it plays spesh music and we dance and its great. WE spent a day in the city and searched around town for a disposable camera so we could take a picture of a sign that says "penertration below" at melbounre central food court. It was awesome fun and gave us something to do. MUHAHA!  Nothing really to say, oh song of the day, myes, something of sorts: http://www.funnyjunk.com/pages/ice_cream.htm  you know I love you, your better than icecream... yeah give it a listen, thats the song =D=D I really really, I really really dooo!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      G'days maties. Contiuning my story. =S.   Ann was already waiting outside when Jodie submerged from her house.  Good morning! Ann said cheerily. Ann had an unusual amount of optimistic enthusiasm around her and was always very bubbly. She was one of those people who seemed to have everything yet be modest at the same time. Ann and Jodie had been friends since primary school and theyd started walking to school together every morning when they moved on to high school that was only two kilometres away. Mornin Ann Jodie replied still half asleep. What you get up to on the weekend? A bit more of your get down and boogie partying? Ann asked. Nah, just the usual. Bummed round the house. Walked around quite a bit. Finished that bloody English project. How bout you? Jodie replied, taking a breakfast bar out of her bag.   Oh, whod you bum this time eh? Im sure its that Brian you keep talking about Ann joked wittingly.  Jodie hit her on the head with the bar and laughed. Now come on! I dont even know what he looks like! Hes just got different views to most people.  Ohhhhh really? Ann paused and decided not to take it any further. Fair enough then. I got up to lots of mischief with police, you know stealing and hotwiring an old Toyota.  Yeah sure, Ann without an e. Im pretty sure I saw you at the station with that young, handsome, well-spoken George. Im sure you had fun in the city  And what would that mean? Ann said cheekily playing with her hair. Nah, you know how my head works, we went shopping! Hes actually going out with Sarah we met up with her at the next station. Ann continued, almost with a sigh. Hmmm, well now its the really journey! Ms Dontilson first period, my head is already throbbing. Ann laughed, Yeah, I dont think if weve ever had a class with her without her lecturing us about how easy we have it. Theres always room for a first! She laughed again and they entered the gates of Killstone High.    I think its getting worse, Ohwell, Adios Arista Cat Amegoes
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah, well I said I'd write something during the holidays so here is the first bit of something I've been writing. If you think its crap send me an angry letter so I can turn her into black ninja and set it in Canada just to make it more interesting. Well yeah here it is.  Darkness crept over the sky. To the east some stars had started to shine dimly. Jodie finally got up out of the long grass and sighed, she wanted to get away from her life. But the only way she would be able to do that was fly, and that wasnt going to happen anytime soon. Meeting up with the path out of the reserve she took a left and cut across some bush until she reached the fence. Making sure not to tear her jeans on the wire she climbed over it. She reached her house, sighed again and prepared her ears for the blasting from her father. Opening the front door she headed straight for her room, hoping to avoid all glimpses from her family. It wasnt that Jodie had a bad life or that she hated her family, she just felt empty. Like she could do more than her parents and the world would let her. She wanted to explore past the boundaries. She wanted to break free. But everytime she got a chance she felt like a dog tied to a tree, just out of reach of food. Like a moon, destined to orbit the same planet for eternity.  What world are you living in that you so long to escape from? The boy on the other side of the country asked. I dont know, Jodie typed back But its just, oh I dont know, what kind of life do you think I could complain about? Well living as an orphan in total poverty and having to look after your seven younger siblings  Its not that bad! Man, you make me sound like a complete whinger! Jodie answered a little insulted Compared to that its nothing, just mental bullshit that I cant control. Yeah well, thats my story. What your problem? Well my names Brian and Im an alcoholic. He said jokingly. What gives you the idea that I have a problem? So youre completely happy? Not having a problem doesnt have anything to do with complete happiness Jodes! What mind set have you been living in?? Oh the world is shit so lets dwell in our miserable thoughts for all of our lives You need to seriously chill out! WOAH! Sorry! You didnt need to completely crack it, I was just asking. I didnt mean to upset you. Jodie replied, shocked by Brians sudden outburst. Ive g2g now, talk to you later. Brian said after awhile. Ok. See you later alligator Jodie said, hoping for him to relay the joke back. Bye Brian signed off. Jodie signed off too, no one else worth talking to was online. She shut down the computer and checked the clock, 2:30 am, time for bed.               
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      MERRY CHRISTMAS!  tehehe cat outside, his name is esky. He's usually really lazy and is very garfield like but he can hear something, maybe the sound of me typing, so he's all like "HMM!! something is moving! maybe I could eat it, oh! what was that?" Oh wow Cocoa is there too now, she's black and very, lol! Esky just chased her up a tree! wow, Cocoa went skits and ran under the house.  MERRY CHRISTMAS! Lunch at my aunty Petah and uncle Geoff place, and boy were we spoilt! no more prawns! Aww prawns, not shrimp. I believe its a prawn not a shrimp! Yeah, the cousins weren't as, LOL! Esky just jumped through the window next to me, he's done it before when it ws closed, quite funny. pestulent as usual, maybe everyones in the Christmas spirit, maybe coz its Christmas, but I don't think thats the reason. But James, he's around 7, if you are playing with something, like the KBall my bro got, he'll grab for it going "give me a turn" even though he just took the bionical (is that wat its called?) off another cousin. Meh, maybe its me thats being selfish but he started it!  MERRY CHRISTMAS! Rethinking yesterdays thoughts, they were irrelavent pieces of info that don't mean a thing now, so meh, stuff the dying thing. I AM IMMORTAL! Well, yes, yes I am actually. And so are you! Just look at the little train that could and Peter Pan. And I'm done because there are many comebacks to that statement where I would just go "I'm not listening la la la la laaa" or "IS NOT! Santa and... and the toothfairy and his little brother Fred who lives in my top drawer are real!!" Erhem, yes well, I'm in a little kiddy mood, I WANT A PONY! Don't ask about Fred, please don't. MERRY CHRISTMAS! Now its time of the blog where Larry sings... a silly song. Oh Barbara Manatee! You are the one for me.... =D Yeah its time for song of the day because I've written enough. Its not going to be a carol, they are just annoying.  Song of the day  She's a killer, queen, gunpowder, gelatine, dynamite with a lazer beam, guaranteed to blow your mind, recommended at the price, insatiable an appetite, wanna try?  (Mum got the Freddie Tribute DVD and I'm in the mood.)    
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, this is my blog and as I have made up of thoughts I guess I have to put this one in here because it is a special thought and I don't know where else to put it. Ahhhh, nope, i'm chicken, this thought stays in my head, I might as well delete this blog, meaning post, but thats silly. Wait, THIS is silly. ARG! just write it. I keep on thinking I'm going to die young. Like I'm going to have an accident and not pull though. I know this is like. WOOOH! Pesamistic Princess on her way, but its really buggin me. Its like I keep on having these dreams where I'm in a classroom and suddenyl everyone else disappears and its just me so I run outside to look for everyone else and get hit by a bus. and the bus doesn't stop until it runs into bright yellow wall and then I wake up. and just to top it of I think I'm falling in like with someone who I've been friends for ages.  oh well, not dead yet. Adios Airboarn Axy Amegos
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      And now I shall blog. I must be alittle behind the times, its Christmas tomorrow!! WOW! thought it was next week for some abscure reason, even though I'm well aware of the dates. It doesn't feel like Christmas. Oh well. MERRY CHRISTMAS DUDES AND DUDETTES! You sunk my battle ship. *guitar rip* =D Bill and Ted. thank you. This shall be my thankful blog, so its gonna be alittle long, and if you don't get thanked send my and angry letter asking why you weren't thanked. Well better get it started. Thanks blog for all the memories you are storing Thanks MSN for the many hours I can spend talking to many people at once without using the phone. Thanks Alby for all the hours you spend on MSN with me, and making me smile when I feel really crap. Thanks scoll button on my mouse, it makes scolling so much faster. Thanks Amy and Kate for all those interesting, out of the subject coments that turn into a beautiful conversation of there own, pointless but soo much better than the original topic. Thanks Jess for always caring and listening even though you ask "whats your problem now?" Thanks Rachel for just being a awesome person to talk to. Thanks Alex for being my first bloody brilliant boyfriend. Thanks Kathy for being a kick ass friend who always signs in when I have to leave. Thanks Squashy for all your internet sites and conversations. Thanks Jo for all those video memories, teo dollars and fifteen cents. And even though you don't have internet anymore, thanks for all the hours on msn. Thanks Brumby's for your seasame dinner rolls Thanks Brigie, LE and Sinead for all you wonderful entertaining blogging. Thanks REM, Third Day, Queen, Bowie, Presidents and Don McLean (is that his last name? for all of your brilliant songs, and the writer of "Billy Don't Be a Hero" Thanks to the maker of bouncey balls and making the 20c ones so cheap =D  Thanks everyone for not being on MSN at the moment, lol. Thanks Laura for always saying poo in the middle of our conversations, it got annoying but it was humourous.(is that how u spell it?) Thanks people who can spell my name correctly. Thanks IMesh for all your downloadable downloads. Thanks Alice, Alby and Alex for doing the Christmas card walk with me. Thanks to everyone who was home so we could deliver your Christmas card. Thanks holidays for exsisting. Thanks siblings and mummy and dad for a great non-argumental year Thanks Alex for just signing in!! YES someone to talk to. Thanks GOD for everything you have blessed me with. And finally thank YOU! yes YOU for reading =D Adios A4 Paper Ageing Amegos 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I forgot the last two days of songs of the days so here they are.   December 22nd   Everyone around love them, love them Put it in your hands Take it take it There's no time to cry Happy happy Put it in your heart Where tomorrow shines Gold and silver shine    December 23rd  Cannot find the words to say I'm sorry Don't know how to show You I was wrong Wasted all that You had given me Now I'm left with nothing and no one And I find it's my fault I'm the only one to blame For the tears and the pain I don't know what I can say Or would it matter anyway 'Cause I don't know how you could still forgive me For all that I have put You through Is there anything that I can do   Shiny Happy People by REM and I don't know by Third Day. Peace out leaders of today Adios Angry Alligator Amegos  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm sorry soylent green ppl. When I said "remove this blogs exsistance" I meant just the post I wrote for it was somewhat meaningless, I didn't mean to say that what u guys were writing is crap and u should get rid of it because it isn't, its pure brilliance and reading it just makes my day. And I shouldn't of broken in like that in the first place. oh well cheery-o 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ching Ching, money money money must be funny, in a rich mans world. Wow, I have money, step aside Bill Gates I got $100!! YAY! Its a voucher though, but me having money at all is pretty special and now I'll merge into the real world and realise that $100 can't buy alot that isn't meant to be eaten. Ohh, imagine all the PEZ I could buy with $100. do they even sell PEZ at MYER? well if it is "My store" then it should. Wow I'm excited, and I know you're most likely laughing but $100 is still a big deal in my eyes, and I just got it for chewing gum for 2 years. It tasted bad but. WOW! I just wrote all of that really fast and I think I'm on a high and I had to sign for the envelope aswell because it was soo special. and I had to rewrite every second word in that last sentance. I'm done boasting about all my lovely money to people who have more.  I watched 'Girl, Interupted' last night. It was very, a word the english lanugage hasn't invented yet. So I'll have to make one up. Ahhh. This is alot harder than I thought. Underplex. It sounds kinda dirty. Under being for understandable and plex being for perplex. But they contradict each other so it has to be a new word. Like it was understandable but it had that little bit where you go why? and yeah ooh maybe english does have a word for it but I just can't use a dictionary properly. I actually liked it quite alot. Yeah I might end up there, or at the top of the best of peoples who do stuff, or a lazy, self-absorbed bum. Or all of the above. The life cycle of the Francesca Butterfly, but I dunno if it every reaches past it's lava stage. meh, I never really liked butterflies anyway. Wow its holidays, gonna see LOTR return of the king on boxing at 1:30, anyone else going then??  querky realities  Adios Air-cooler Avocardo-eating Amegos 'ave a good one! or two, or three or how ever many you choose. =D=D  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well little bubble-popping pals I haven't done any irregular nonsence of the strange kinda lately so thats what I might do. But it might end up making sence so no lifetime guarantees. Yeah I don't get "lifetime guarantees", is it your lifetime or the appilances lifetime? Well it's not gonna work forever. shmeh to confusing of the bad kind.  Smorgy's, eat, eat, all you can eat. food turns to fat now where are my feet?  Hey kids, where are you, no body tells you what to do. baby... do do dooo waaa shabopedy doo eeeeooooo. Blue pen, black pen in a blue casing. Maybe your crazy in the end.  Why do the White Pages pages turn yellow after a while? take it, take it, there's no time to cry. Hey kids rock and rock, nobody tells you where to go. No blue buzzard, no three eyed frog but as feline canine little cat dog. It looks as if our two will never be one, something must be done. Gnomey man living at the end of my yard, we don't bother him much, his life was hard, living trapped in a concrete shell, never showing if he was sad or swell. Either eIther, neither neIther. Need each other soey.   So I can't aford to faulter or slow. Orange light, red light, stop. Green light beep your horn at the car infront. Bass, treble, balance, tone, banana. mmm banana split. His poor wife. Oh out on the roof to enquire the sky. Welcome to me very own show, I'll introduce my friends to you, oh no its ninny poo. I just wish you'd let me explain to you...  Crashed car speeding, wounds are bleeding, You know you know the victim, Luckily its not Mum. This goes out to the one I left behind. OH!! I got While I live! Step out of nonsence for alittle. Ellies parents and Mrs Mackenzie get killed!!! I know I just wrecked the first 2 chapters, sorry, but far out! What they'd already been through, to have that. I'd just freeze over, sorry nobody home. Everybody hurts, sometimes... And I felt stupid coz I forgot who Gavin was. If you don't know either he was the leader of the kids in the town with the hearing problem. Its such an awesome book I got to quote one bit that wont give away anymore. But it'll have to be short, otherwise I'm just a party pooper.  " 'Mrs Samuels, call the Coucil, will you, and see what's happening about application. You're Ellie. Come in, Ellie.' I wa glad he'd told me who I was. It's a relief to know who you are " Wow. I love it. Continuing... That suger cane, that tasted good. They just stared at the weight of the world and pretend not to feel. Come on, come on, no one can see you cry. Anyway, cherry-o. Hope your holidays are ol' good 'n' well.  Lotsa Love'n'Hugs (I wrote that so many times in my Christmas cards, its a trad now) Peace is hopefully my future reality. Adios Shiny Happy People, love you guys who read, still love you guys who don't. =D=D
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah, I've been bored so I was reading a few of my october posts and those poems are so negative it isn't funny. Come on with the monty python "Always look on the bright side of life"  =D well, I'm going to have to write a more happier one now. Its probally not possible without making it cheesey, but I like cheese, especially melted on toast. ah... yeah....  Puppy doggy,  Wheres your lead? Are you a loner ranger? Have you been freed? Free from your boundries Released from your cage Able to run wild To start a new page Moving in your own direction Walking your own way Don't worry puppy doggy This is your day  And I think I'll stop there....erhem, well thats pretty mediocre is not further down the road. Chess set. Check and mate. You sunk my battle ship, awww noice bogus adventure. OH! buy a Christmas tree!! PLEASE! I loathe them so that if you don't buy one I'll have to burn them and that means no profit for the group. PLEASE BUY THEM! they are $26 except for the ones marked as $30. AHHH! I said that way too much today. 10am-6pm, come buy! come buy! please! And let me tell you, you do not want to do a pick up of 40 decent sized trees on a hot day. pine needles get in ur clothes and the sap gets all over ur hands and clothes and if you get poked in the eye it stings like burning wire, well i don't know about that but its close. Enough of my complianing. Cheery-o then =D=D i love it really, just don't say you like the smell of the pine or I'll have to stick a tree up your bottom.  Adios Abundat Not-your-average Amegos! 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Her I am again, writing to you and your little minions. Wait, do you even have minions? I want some minions, wait, no I don't, I want to lift up self-ruling. Glad I'm still thinking even though school has ended. ahuh, and that is me.  And as you most probally well know, I have a very small social life so as nothing will be happening in my life I shall spend my time writing a short, very short storys/ies. YAY! It won't happen but I'm trying to make it interesting by making it bad. That sentance made sence when I wrote it but no longer does so just ignore it.  OH! and I heard from my lovely brother's even lovelier girlfriend steph that if either of the too new girl aren't up to scratch that I'd get an interveiw. Wow and then I'll have or atleast tried for a job.  "Well after I graduate I plan on getting married" "And then?" "And then I'll be married" Mona Lisa Smile. Hmmm dunno what I think of the previews but yay for female independence. nah nah nah nah nah nah LEADER! Oh yeah, I'm a peer support leader for next years little yr 7s. I hope they are all nice little children that have no access to nuclear warheads. I'm most likely with Tom, Zohair or Hsein, because I really couldn't care who I was with and neither did they. All of the other peer support ppl chose their partners.    and Alby got his plate today, one day off freedom and now to the less attatched plate. I found my old one, its quite disturbing, I put it back in the draw and ran away as fast as possible before it jumped into my mouth.  Let me, ooooh, entertain you. Here we are now entertain us.  And I'm done.  Song of the day:  the concrete broke your fall to hear you speak of it I'd have done anything I would do anything I feel like a cartoon brick wall to hear you speak of it you've been so sad it makes me worry why not smile? you've been sad for a while. why not smile?
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      YAY! we got our reports today, nothing that was unexpected. Dad hasn't seen it yet and he's gonna crack it hardcore when he finds out about history, shmeh he'll get over it. All the ones I wanted to do good in were excellent so I'm very pleased, and everyone contradicted Ms Caserta (hist teach) in their comments so I felt very proud. And alot of them say I'm capable student, but does that mean I use those capabilities?  Oh well. YAWN! Pheobe's been texting and flirting with people she never met, but the slightly disturbing thing that went with this is what my brother said she should write, "I want u to fall down the stairs so I can nurse you back to health only to break you neck while passionatly fuking u" Very disturbing but also quite humourous in a very twisted way. Strange things are happening to me, song off toy story.  welll I'm done for the day.  Song of the day: Rebel, rebel, you tore your dress, Rebel, rebel, your face is a mess, Rebel, rebel how could they know? Hot tramp, I love you so.   
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      and here I am writing again with nothing to say so I'll just keep this window open and when I get some insperation I'll write.  Ohh! Alby got his braces off! and I get to see them tomorrow, I'm so excited! On his behalf. =D. Ahhh...   Everyone keeps going "brb" on me and not coming back, I know I've been complaining about it lately, but it really hurts. Or if they say "hi" and don't say another word until I say "I think I'll join the quite club too" like 10mins later and then they crack it at me and I end up apologising.  Hmmm, I think the brain should be detatchable, then I could sleep without all these strange dreams. But you'd have to leave the brain stem (i think, was I paying attention in science?) so that you could still breathe and circulate blood. Ohh and all those blood vessels would bleed. Maybe it'd be easier if you just turn certain (I know its the wrong certain) sections off.  I'm so addicted to MSN its not funny. Well not to the extent that I ring people up and go "hey go on msn tonight!". But I'm always on it, the really question is do I have a life. The big answer is unknown but mine is no. I sooo don't.  WOOOHOO! Alby and I are rejoicing in the hyperthetical streets!! WOOYAH! He's going crazy and accidently ran crutch first into a mis-placed pole, acording to him not me, i must of been too busy "partying" HAHA!  And rachel says she isn't high on sugar or other substances but none of her sentences make sence. Or mabye they do and I'm not making sence. Or I misinterpret too many things all at the same time. NOOOOO! Alby's gone =(. awww, Frances rejoicing in the streets no more, isn't fun with anyone else. =(  AHH! not this song again. Okay its an okay somg but 5 times in 2 hours?!?!? Take me away from here! I'm feeling it! Grr... and I think I'm done with only the coment that times are a changing, but I'm still staying the same, still staying sane. Or is that insane if your living in the past? 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      That is no orc horn... Here come, here come, here come the badgers. aww those dudes are brilliant.  Stapler, address book, pencil, pen, mouse, floppy disc. Suddenly I have nothing to write, maybe my veiws are becoming too discriminating to put on here. here come, here come. sorry impulse. GRR! Jess did it to me again! saying hello and then signing off once I reply. And alby keeps, going away. Man I am really bad company. Yep, so now its down to my song of the day, it was played at the bowling alley and is stuck in my head.  Song of the day: Love is in the air, in the whisper of the trees. Love is in the air, in the thunder of the seas. And I don't know if im just dreaming, Don't know if I feel sane, But it's something that I must believe in, And it's there when you call out my name.   Have you ever sEen the littLe hints People give? PeopLE usuAlly miSs thEm.  YOU don't HAve To say it out loud, i undErstand what you MEan. Can yOu thiNk only Find yoUrSelf In anOther dead eNd? toDay just like evErydAy, you just walkeD by. toTally ignOring whaT sHE Wanted tO say, Ruining her hopefuL Dreams... Silence followed the awfUl crack. Inside i Cried, as the outsIDe would nEver know... 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think I write tooo much so instead of publishing another I'll just add onto this one. =) Hmm, now I have nothing to say. Its not funny coz its true, its funny co its not you.... Song of the day:  When your education x-ray  Can not see under my skin I won't tell you a damn thing  That I could not tell my friends Roaming through this darkness I'm alive but I'm alone Part of me is fighting this But part of me is gone  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just signed in and saw this little tick box under the sign in box. It says "Remember Me [?]". Do I really want to be remembered? What would I be remembered as if I was? Ohh sugared beets, I really don't care. forget me forget me you never met me.  Wow there was this soccer player on TV and his mouth was really wide open, I'm surprised a fly didn't fly in. Why can birds fly but flys can't bird? I don't know why she swallowed a fly, perhaps she'll die. hopefully not but just going along with the nursery rhyme.  I had a dream. It was pretty disturbing too. Someone pushed me out of a plane and as I fell to the ground my leg got snagged in a tree and ripped clean off. But suddenly I was plunging into red water. when I hit the water, I started swimming upwards but couldn't reach the top so I just kept swimming and swimming. But then there was nothing it was like there wasn't any water and I fell again. I dunno what that was about but hmm. weird "I'm sorry, goodnight"
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      And they started singing and grooving to the melody, not reliesing that the punch bowl had been spiked, slowly people began to get entangled with each other as more and more punch was consumed. hmmm do I want some punch. my brother had some Coke in the fridge and I was thristy so I poured me a glass, a full one, and sculled the lot, but lol its quite funny, it had i think it was rum in it. I dunno how diluted it was but yeah, I like ordinary coke... I HAVE A PAPER PHONE. RING ME!! its a samsung.  Thanks for the conversation jess, I just love it when people say hi and sign off. its a nice feeling, really.  Depression is anger without enthusiasm.  Twenty four gallons on my head, might be twisted glue instead, not making sense but no one minds, just a way of spending time. green elephants flying though my home, happily sings the dancing garden gnome, purple swirly swirls indeed its me you need to feed rocking out to the beets  tuning hard to the roots  sorry spur of the moment... I dun like beetroots... My head wont stop bobbing... tehehe, no I'm not tipsy, the rum was yesterday, i'm not trying to be tipsy either. bob bob bobbing head tehehe doggy
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Who? Is that that girl from gym class? No, that's me. Ew... Who is she and why does she have her own song? Did someone take my lunch?  Pepper Ann, Pepper Ann, Marchin' in her own parade. Pepper Ann, she's like one in a million! Pepper Ann, Pepper Ann, Much too cool for seventh grade. No one's cooler than Pepper Ann! She's her own biggest fan Pepper Ann! Catch 'er if you can, Pepper Ann!  That is my favourite saturday morning programe, well it depends what else there is, like sorry, but I can't stand buzz lightyear of star comand or tarzan. And don't even start on Tabaluka if thats how you spell it. "oooh a mood ring"  yep. we got school activities today, I'm doing 4 periods worth of indoor and two of rock climbing and I have a feeling no one else is, oh well, continuing being the little individual who complains about doing too much indoor soccer but will happily do it instead of staying home. Meh, if I stay home Kelly stays home and I don't know if I want that... Nah my sisters cool, sometimes, when shes not kicking me while I try and sought out the stuff/junk/rubbish/treasure (depends on who you talk to) under my desk that happens to be under my bunk. yes well erhem me done now, adios armadillo amegos!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yep, on my rollercoaster. But the last two days have been sweet and now I'm just antisipating the fall, come on, come on, ruin my day. Well thats just me, okay, get rid of that mind set. No more one step forward two steps backward shit. No more antisipating the down side come on.  Last night was awesome. JT (Church, yep i see ur disappointment) had a "Looking Back" thingy for the yr nine coz this was our last year, and all of the Godly vibes just got to me. God, He is soooo cool. Man, come on in the faith.  And today Albert and I went a walkin' and a talkin' down the street singing doobadaybe... well actually delivering the Christmas cards to all of my firendly friends that have known addresses. And Alex, (our second stop) joined in which was awesome to have another buddy along. And so we walked around 15-17km bouncing my $2 bouncey ball, talking and stalking Frances. Rachel wasn't at her mum's place and we think we woke her mum up, it was 11:30 so sorry but fair enough.  Wendy wasn't home but left cANday canes in her letter box for us. (my comps on speed again) then to Vermont Sth where Laura had strange people over, 'watching disney' but it seemed too orgy-like to stay. ahh, who was next? Kathy, we didn't even get to her house coz we saw her crossing the oval yelling my name.  We went to the Time Saver petrol place thingy and all three of us got these cool limited edition pepsi bottles. I know coke is better but presentation was just to high on the scale, excuse my shallowness. Then to malcolms but we were to scared of his grandma so we just put it in his letter box, yes we are wimps. then we went to Amys and I think we got her in trouble because when we went walking up her drive Amy's dad and her evil stepmother fiona drove up giving the idea that amy invited us over while they were out. Well fiona can't really give her any more chors as she's basically but amy into slavery.  We had alittle trouble finding zohairs street and alex and alby started ducking off and pretending to stalk me, and I got plum juiceage in the hole in my shoe, but we eventually found it and gave him his card. He just got back from cricket and his hair was all funny. then we went to michelles who when we asked if she wished to join said "no" very quickly and blankly.  Afterwards we went to K-Mart plaza, I think it was around 1:30ish and thought to had lunch but played on some on the equipment and rolled down hills and played with the elavator and bounced my bouncy ball down the stairs. THEN WE GOT MORE BOUNCY BALLS! I got two and alex got one. We checked out Brumby's but B wasn't onduty so we went and said hello to Santa and off to Alice's.  We stood around the corner of her house and rang her mobile and she came out looking for us. She joined and then we went to Jo.L's house in which she was not home!!! GRRR! Her front door was open but the fly screen (where we stuck the card) was locked and not being American curious trespasers that go into other ppls houses we moved on to Jo.F's house who was working at McDonalds so we just handed her card off to her sister. Then we planned to go to Dats, but Alby rang him first and found out that he had family over and would rather us not go to his house, so of course, we didn't.  So we shortcuted past 7-11 Ably being the gentleman buying us Slurpees we went to Jess's house. Rachel was at Jess's house and they were.... er... i think cooking, if you call it that. Their muffins were golden syrup flavours and didn't have and baking power (not baking soda) in it so they were pretty flat. And their cookies had way too much flour. They admitted to this, and Jess dogs also agreed that they weren't the tastest of snacks, but they were very edable, the food not Jess or Rachel or the dogs. Then we went half way to Forest Hill chase and sat down on the sidewalk. Alice decided to go home so we got up and continued to Forest Hill chase.  Firstly we went to Big-W to see Alex's sister Fiona (not related to evil stepmother Fiona) in the entertainment department and organised his Christmas pressent from her, talk about convenience. and then we went down the Harris scarf to find tom working (tehehe) and found that its a small world after all, Alex knowing Jaqui from primary school, who I know from scouts and Tom knowing her from work and tom alex and I all going to the same school. Alby kinda stood there going "wah?"  We tried out KFC to see if Emily was working (Pete's in sydney) but as I found out later she was at Luna park and... the beach (shiver). So we went to Hungry Jacks and saw Zohairs brother and said hello to him. And then Alby went home and Alex came to my house and Alex got dropped home when Mum had to take Kelly to a sleepover party and I love adverterous day where I acctually do stuff, with people I love so very much. =)=) And now I am the happy little munchkin full of happiness and joy.  Merry Christmas Dudes and Dudettes, ave a good one! And OH HOW MY LEGS HURT!  How many dogs barked at us? 9 How many dogs did we see? 15      
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I lost my reasons, To live through all the seasons, Bash my head, And go to bed, Why isn't this pain easing?  No reason to feel the pain, But my life isn't the same. Just need a day, to run away, turn the flour back to grain.  Need a reminder to remember, If its June or December, I want to stop it now, I don't care how, To this hurt I must surrender.  Tomorrow will be the day. That the voices will get their way, Slit my throat, Bleed and choke. But thats still a day away....
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm sorry but I'm in one of those everythings a peice of poop mood and you can't stop me. Nothing happened to bring it on, it just is so there. I now you must hear about it in detail, but there's nothing to say so I won't say a thing, no thing at all, this is the last you'll hear from me here! Stuff your stuck up nose up someone elses bum coz i'm not in the mood to have my mind mucked around by the likes of you!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You wake up in the morning at seven twenty-three, you don't need to poop and you don't need to pee, you write a blog, bloggy bloggy, blog-edy blog, you write a blog, bloggy bloggy, blog-edy blog... So that is what I am doing, woth the computer on speed and everyone fast asleep. Anyone got any bashing saucepans? Icy cold water? Warm water to make them pee themselves? Shaving cream and a feather? No? Well I guess they can stay asleep as I wish not to use my vocals, even though their sound is sweet, lol laughing at myself coz no one else is around. I finished all the Christmas card covers for people, they are rockin' now I just have to write in them. 14TH OF DECEMBER!! CARDS TO YOUR DOOR! If you're one of the lucky 15 you will get a christmas card delivered to your door by FRANCES!! =D and Alby might be there too coz he's awesome and we needed a reason for a walk. The square that we shall be delivering in will between Canterbury and Highbury, Terrara and Middleborough. YAY! Well yeah... Adios, I don't like you I think you're gross! Not really.  Song of the day: Tell all my friends I'm dead, I'm leaving you, this time its for good, tell all my friends that I'm dead, it won't be long before you forget my name...
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We return to the life of our famous (well not that famous), little (well not so little) character Frances. Being the bored girl she is she decides to walk up to K-Mart Plaza to obtian some 20c bouncy balls to add to her collection. So she picks out all the 20c peices in her wallet and sets off into the wilderness of the bitumen Blackburn road, well the footpath of Blackburn road. So she continues along this road and incounters a half-naked, middle-aged man talking to a lady she asumes is his wife. She keeps walking, feeling the eyes of the man and lady following her and sees a girl jogging on the opposite side of the road. "Wow" she thinks to herself "I wish I had that much determination, I couldn't run for more than 2 minutes at the most" She shrugs off the thought of being and unfit, not so little juvinile and looks ahead, nearly running into a man with two really cute, black dogs. She apologises and keeps walking. Walking, walking, walking. Up ahead she can see a little girl, the little girl looks at her and picks up a pine cone that had odviously fallen from the tree on the fence line. "Ahhh, I hope she doesn't throw that at me. And if she does well..." she picks off a gumnut from a passing tree and holds it in her hand "..I'll throw this at her." It was alot smaller, very much so being about the size of a 5c piece, luckily though the little girl didn't throw the pinecone so Frances didn't have to throw the little, pathetic nut. Walking, walking, wlaking, living in Blackburn it is alot of walking to get to K-Mart Plaza. A lady with a dog. A girl walking from work, possibly K-mart. She stops at the lights at the intersection of Blackburn Rd and Burwood Hwy to hear some unintelligable, quite blind, young hullagens yelling from their car "IS IT REAL?" at her. She is quite puzzled as there isn't anything that could be even questioned as fake. So she just ignores the young hullagens and crosses the road finally reaching K-Mart Plaza. Nearly knocking into another person she skips onto the path and walks past Brumby's. And to her surprise she see her good, ol' (well kinda new) friend Brigid. YAY!! "Maybe I'll buy a dinner roll" she thinks "hmm" She enters the shop and says "hello" or some variation as most people do when then meet. To her dismay there are no dinner rolls. "AHH!!" she screams half-heartedly inside her head. "Oh well". After a conversation about Frances', B's and Jo's beautiful, completely awesome, hair cuts she has to come to the conclusion of what she should buy. "hmmm" our not so little character thinks "Yes, we have no bananas". So she ends up saying something about having no idea and that Brigie should chose. So chose brigie does. A nice, delicious, chocolate covered crosaunt/pastry that was odviously over $1.60, but thats what Frances paid to the very nice girl at the counter by the name of Brigid. and that was her day! hurrah!!! Besides being home later than expected nothing mentionable arose to the mind of Frances... except for how many people pick their noses in their cars at the lights... but thats another story....
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am VERY disappointed with you fellow bloggers!!! I said I would write less but thats because I wrote too much. Just because I write less doesn't mean you can. WRITE DAMN IT!! I NEED TO BE ENTERTAINED!! I probally write the same anyway, but just because you have more of a life than me doesn't mean you write less. Aww I dunno, I have no valid reason to yell at you, good on ya for having a social life. I'll just hide away in my little dank, dark cave living off the moss that grows off the walls. Will you visit me? Will you save me if the walls cave in?  Song of the day:  Stop in the name of love, Before you break my heart. Baby, baby! I'm aware of where you go, Each time you leave my door. I watch you walk down the street. Knowing your other love you'll meet...   
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If your looking for a name you wont find one here. Just coz I wear pants doesn't make me queer. *shakes fist* I am not perfect but at least I'm trying, to change something in the world that won't stop buying.  Cd stuffed up so no music for talk, got an awesome spring wobbly clock from my KK (Thanks ALEX!!=D)got hit by a puck hit by Zohair it didn't hurt but it left a red line that looks like a 'J'. for Jelly cup that I eat everytime I go to 7 11. wibble wobble wibble wobble jelly on a plate. My mind is in a fragile state. Please excuse my lameness today, it was the last day of 9B Fellowship :( shattered, we wore black arm bands and 9C copied. Next year will be all over the place, still don't know electives yet GRR get orginsed school or i shall have to kick you, or bag the school terribly when I have to talk to the future year 7 on monday!! MUHAHAHA  song of the day:Silly songs with Larry (the cucumber!) Larry: If my lips ever left my mouth, Packed their bags and headed south, It'd be too bad,  I might be sad. Doctor: It'd be too bad? You might be sad? Larry: It'd be to bad.  If my lips said "Adios" "I don't like you I think your gross" It'd be too bad I might get mad....
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Being on blogger and have this bumming song in my head I thought I would have a second song of the day, making up for the days that I didn't.  second song of the day: Forever and ever you'll stay in my heart and I will love you forever and ever thats how it must be, to live without you would only be heartbreak for meee-ooo-eee-oo-ee oh. I run for the bus dear, while riding I think of us dear, I say a little prayer for you, at work I just take time, all during my coffee break time, I say a little prayer for youuuu-OOOHH, forever and ever ....
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You wake up in the morning at a quarter to one and you feel like having a bit of fun, you brush ur teeth cch cch chhchh chh chh chhchh. I had to let those dentisty people attack my teeth again today! get out of my mouth!! grr oh well, after 3 years of chewing that gum we get a $100 myer voucher. We're in the money, la la la. Well! isn't that Swell! erhem, yes, bordem is my second middle name, my first middle name is Renee, but thats besides the point. and now I past the bordem virus to you! MUHAHAHA!! ITS CONTAGIOUS! spelt wrongly of course and I think i'm done for the day.  adios enchalada amegos  song of the day: Did you write the book of love? and do you have faith in God above, if the bible tells you so. Do you believe in rock 'n' roll, can music save your moral soul, can you teach me how to dance realllllll slow? and I know that your in love with him, coz I saw you dancing in the gym, you both kicked off ya shoes, man I dig those rhythmy bluesss Ooooh, I was a lonely teenage bronken buck, with a pink carnation and a pick up truck, but I new I was outta luck the day... the music.... died, we started singing....
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Good day people that are and aren't really there, Its been an average day in the life of me. I got to play Pete's shocking roulette and got shocked twice, damn electric currents. It feel likes someones pinching your finger. Its quite an interesting concept. And now I continue into the part where I start talking as if someone, possibly you, is still reading after they relised what a waste of time it is reading this. DO YOUR HOMEWORK! Lets go fly a kite, or fly a kite, or attack people with pointed sticks. I have a dream... Ohh, ok, lately stuff in my waking dreams have meant something to someone and one thats been puzzling is "Why did he read them?", if this applies to you. Well, I had a dream about you, *winks and smiles slyly*. how you doin'.  WELL!! *cough cough*. this big vein in my foot pops out when its hot, its all like squishy. Yes, we have no bananas. My arm isn't flaking as I thought it would after the encounter with melted candle wax falling on it making my arms look all crusty. Well I'm done, but in honour of my special song blog, I shall have a song of the day everyday.  Song of the day: Billy don't be a hero, don't be a fool with your life,  Billy don't be a hero, come back and make me your wife.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You've got the music in you, Don't let go, You've got the music in you, One dance left, This world is gonn pull through, Don't give up, You've got a reason to live, Can't forget... we only get what we give....  Today shall be my special, music blog as I want some special music and I want some NOW!!  It's like you're always stuck in second gear, When it hasn't been your day, your week, your month, or even your year, but I'll be there for you, When the rain starts to pour, I'll be there for you, Like I've been there before, I'll be there for you, 'Cause you're there for me too...  Another turning point, a fork stuck in the road, Time grabs you by the wrist, directs you where to go. So make the best of this test, and don't ask why. It's not a question, but a lesson learned in time. It's something unpredictable, but in the end it's right. I hope you had the time of your life...  Little darlin' I feel the ice is slowly meltin', Little darlin' it seems like years since it's been clear, Here come the sun, here comes the sun, And I say it's all right, Here come the sun, la la la laa, here comes the sun, It's all right, it's all right...  I'm laughing at clouds, so dark up above, The sun's in my heart, and I'm ready for love, Let the stormy clouds chase, everyone from the place, Come on with the rain, I've got a smile on my face, I'll walk down the lane, with a happy refrain, Just singing, singing in the rain...  Good morning, it's a lovely morning. Good morning, what a wonderful day. We danced the whole night through. Good morning, good morning to you. I said good morning, see the sun is shinin'. Good morning, hear the birdies sing. It's great to stay up late. Good mornin', good mornin' to you...  First I was afraid, I was petrified, Kept thinking I could never live, without you by my side, But I spent so many nights, thinking how you did me wrong, I grew strong, I learned how to carry on...  Well there's a pretty girl servin' at the counter of the corner shop, She's been waitin' back there, waitin' for a dream, Her dreams walk in and out, they never stop, Well she's not too proud, to cry out loud, She runs to the street and she screams: What about me? It isn't fair, I've had enough, now I want my share, Can't you see, I wanna live, you just take more than you give, more than you give...  And as we wind on down the road, Our shadows taller than our souls, There walks a lady we all know, Who shines white light and wants to show, How everything still turns to gold, And if you listen very hard, The tune will come to you at last, When all are one and one is all, To be a rock and not to roll...  Woe oh oh oh oh oh.....  And she's buying a stairway to heaven...       
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Migrain is finally gone and all is good and well inside the head of our famous, little character Frances. Chilling to some Duke Ellington she smiles and wonders about that person who she wonders about when she wonders. Or about wondering about wondering, one or the other or both. Apart from the ocassionally reply from MSN buddies she is undisturbed. Reading though her resume again, seeing if she should add more or take somethings out. Laughing at the fact she had to put her gender because of her name, she coasts through the rest and places it down.  "Those Bakers Delight people better love me, if not I shall become a Brumby's gal and there shall be a baker's war in which I throw my first attempt of bread at their heads." she thinks to herself. "Then no one will be able to stop the rath of ME! moohahaha!"  Focusing off her world domination plan she continues to wonder about that person she wonders about when she wonders. Or about how stupid she was to give Pete her answers as Alex is in a bad situation without any at all.  "Great! Why do I always help the annoying ones and let my friends down" she proclaims annoyed at herself. "If I hadn't had a migraine I would of been able to get the questions back off Pete and give them to Alex. DAMN YOU MIGRAINS" she cries shaking fist in the air. She cools herself down by turning up Ella Fitzgerald's and Louis Armstrong's  'Let's Call the Whole Thing Off'  and she starts to sing... "So if you like pyjamas and I like pyjahmas,  I'll wear pyjamas and give up pyajahmas, For we know we need each other so we, Better call the whole thing off, Let's call the whole thing off." She breathes a sigh of releif and continues to wonder about that person she wonders about when she wonders. Or at her terrible history outcome. How could it come to this? A fail? Frances Hatcher of B plus ville? The one given the highest expectations as if she would succeed? No wonder why she always lets people down. She remembers a time when this was not so. She was a bossy, arrogant, stuck up, know-it-all, little grade 4er who treated her friends like second grade poop. She runs her fingers through her hair and sighs again. "Guess I'll never know" she says, quite out of the subject. Maybe she was wondering about that person she wonders about when she wonders after all.      
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      DAMN YOU MIGRAINES! And now I understand very well that November has 30 days not 29 =S. My head isn't happy and this computer isn't doing much good, I'm home alone with my head going "Ohh! I want this side to burst! Wait what about this side? oh! oh! idea! how about both!?!" Well its my right side at the moment right near the temple, no ora though which is good. I feel no pity for those how had to go to school for their head are not exploding, and if they are, well then I do. Ahh! ora coming on must leave computer.  Love ya's, not migtains, mate!  P.S. HEAR MY SCREAM!! RAAAAHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHGGG!! *head throbs*
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I want to say "I hate you" continuosly over and over again but it'd be a lie and just a reflection of my sad mood thats gone sour. I talk too much about nothing. Its a good and a bad thing. Well I dunno. Okay better mood. I shall bang my head on the table until stress is relieved. Yes me happy now. Oh yes, want to read about my strange encounter with music? Well if you don't stop reading. =S  Right, so, I was listening to ghosts by gary jules, a real ledg, and then I started reading a post by brigie and she was writing about those annoying, stupid ppl ruining the awesomeness of mad world and then suddenly the song started on my playlist and, wow, yeah I was quiet startled.  And then something happened in which something else was said that upset the stomachs of the brass players in the marching band who spent the next 2 weeks cleaning their instruments. not quite sure where that came from. How do you define a fault in a persons personality? I don't believe it is so. Maybe there's some stuff about them that really ticks you off, but that doesn't make it a fault, on either of ur behalfs.  In the eye of the beholder stuff again, sorry don't mind me. Being opinuated but pretening not to take sides. Adios Ant and Apple-eating Armadilo Amigos. Its hard to believe, that he was laughing at you, poor jeremmiah weed.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm never coming back, I'm never giving in, i'll never be the shine in your spit. I disconnect the act, I disconnect the dots, I disconnect the me in me. And you're mistaken, It's you that's faking, living and breathing and dying too, this message is for anyoine who dares to hear a fool, you can't bring me back, you can't bring me back. Cause I give it all back to you, thru sacred alleys, the living wrecks, wreak their havoc upon this world. The disenchanted, the romantics, the body and face and soul of you is gone down that deep black hole. Destroy the mind-destroy the body-but you cannot destroy the heart, and you, you make me so I need to disconnect, and you make it so real. I don't need your love to disconnect. To runaround kids in get-go cars, with vaseline afterbirths and neon coughs, galaxies full of nobodies, giving us the farewell runarounds. I took a virgin mary axe to his sweet baby jane, lost my innocence to a no good girl, scratch my face with anvil hands, and coil my tongue around a bumblebee mouth and I give it all back to you. No way, I don't need it, I don't need your love to disconnect, and you make it, so real, I don't need your love to disconnect. No way to disconnect and you make it so real, I don't need your love to disconnect, no way to disconnect...
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      7 people!! 7 people! Only 7 bloody people, all girls for that matter, in yr 10 german. out of 108 or something, only 7!! And its with bumming frau moore, or conner or hore or watever she is nowadays. Man she shits me up the wall. At least they aren't annoying people, but the frau sure makes up for that. AND IT WAS SO QUITE! It was scary. You could hear people writing and thats not normal for a class, not right at all. and WAHH!! =( AND AND! just to top it off, I can't do yr 11 pysc' cause it clashes with maths. But it seems alot of people missed out on there yr 11 subjects because it clashed with maths. WHY MATHS?? At the end of last year 2D art was in block A, and that would of been fine, but nooooooo they had to change maths to block A. AND what annoys me more is that 10D and 10E don't have maths in block A! AND ARRRG! If they didn't want us to do it they should of just said so, snobby bloody school that suposedly has lots of money except doesn't spend it. OH! AND AND! We can only have the talent quest or the musical. WTF is that about? We have talent quests every year, its a fund raising thing. And I don't think money is a problem because we only have musicals every second year, dispite what teachers say to the yr 6ers coming up every year. AND AAAARRGGG!! I wanna do the musical because rumor is that it is Grease and that is one of the best musicals ever in my opinion, but then I wanna do this act thingy we've been planning for the talent quest and grrr! I don't like you forest hole! VOTE FOR JUSTICE! VOTE FOR ME!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I started a joke, which started the whole world crying. But I didn't see, that the joke was on me, oh no. I started to cry, which started the whole world laughing, oh, if I'd only seen, that the joke was on me.  Yeah, hi people. The lack of something to say is overwelming. But I don't exsist today, so it doesn't really matter what I do say, cause it wouldn't exsist if someone had not said it. Pulsing under my skin, the blood within, the veins that may, be released someday. What do you see, when you look right through me? mohahahaha. I give you a hug. You look like you need a hug, so I'll give you a hug. =] Nobody said it was easy, no one ever said it would be this hard, oh take me back to the start. soo, yeah. Adios Apricot-Flavoured Amigo's (the A adjective today was brought to you by the letters H, Q and the number 5.)  I looked at the skies, running my hands over my eyes, and I fell out of bed, hurting my head from things that I said. 'Till I finally died, which started the whole world living, oh, if I'd only seen that the joke was on me...
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tehehe, sleepy, been up alll night on sugared goodness, like erkil. Watched some alright movies with some brilliant friendies, like erkil.  mooohahaha, only to wish to open my mouth full of slimey, green, jaggered teeth and close them slowly around the tender flesh, just to hear the statisfying crack of its spine and slurp of liquids as I rip open its neck like a present on my 8th birthday.  Whats that about I don't know, I HAVE... I was about to say hands or a dream but I think thats not very original. soooo. I HAVE THE URGE TO STOP SOON! I got to urge, she got the urge for herbal. boooo wa! Coz I'm free! to do wat I want! Any ol' time. Love me! Hold me! Hold me! Love me! Cause I'm FREE!! CAW CAW the raven cries, showing its disapproval of the way the world is going, running 'round in circles on a broken track. When people run in circles its a very, very mad world... Adios Addictive Amigos, hope your holidays were shiney as we move into the dark days of school starting. I hope the mist clears soon...
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have been talking names with my good ol' mate Alby, so then I thought "hmm" and asked everyone else on msn their favourite names. And yes we all know it would be funny to call people by kitchen appliances. Frances| Girls: Lorelei/ Boys: Frederic Alby| Girls: Kristin/ Boys: Lucas Laura| Girls: Ruby/ Boys: Jack Rachel| Girls: Emma/ Boys: Sam Andy| Girls: Aribeth/ Boys: No Idea Emma| Girls: Chloe and Zara / Boys: Jedd A Luke person I dont really know| Girls: Aleisha/ Boys: Calleb Will| Girls: Jodie/ Boys: Cain Alice| had too hard of a time deciding, and didnt want to be part of this. Haha, too late.  Ross (brother)| Girls: Penelope/ Boys: Sebastian   Wendy| Girls: Heidi/ Boys: Daniel  Janine| Girls: Tiffany/ Boys: Scott   Well hurruh hurray! Moohaha. Yes well, I think thats enough of me being bored. da da da da lade dee. yep Adios Alpha Amigos
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In the morning when I woke up, he was sitting on the edge of my bed, with his brother whose name was Fred, he'd bought him along to sing me a song. Right, let's hear it here, what's that clicking noise? That's Fred, he's a "metrognome", haha! Ha ha ha, hee hee hee  "I'm a laughing Gnome and you don't catch me" Ha ha ha, hee hee hee "I'm a laughing Gnome and you can't catch me"  tehehe, early Bowie, you have to hear. Laughing Gnome. tehehe. aww brilliance. So what are you people doing today? like chicken tonight?  *steping* Do do do de do *right kick* *steping ther way* do do do de dooo. *left kick* tada. yes as per usual when writing on this little blog of mine, I am bored. but not completly.   Own up, I'm a gnome, ain't I right, haha "Haven't you got an 'ome to go to?"  No, we're gnomads "Didn't they teach you to get your hair cut at school? You look like a rolling gnome." No, not at the London School of Ecognomics  tehehe. ahhh. so good, is not good. Adios Arrowed Apple Amigos!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes. It is. Very much so. Completely and utterly so. What on earth I am talking about, no coment, you'll have to talk to my lawyer.  We got a new scanner, ahuh ahuh, we did, we did. and its so cute and tiny.  And suddenly I have nothing to say. Quite a rare thing actually, well. 5 days until I find out whether I got into year 11 psychology. Excitement, or mabye just more work. Yep, well, this posting is very empty of enthusiasm. meh. tired. bored. laking amusement. la de dee la de daa. Shawing, ting ting ping, twang! zoip! and a giggle giggle te-he-he. yanky doodle went to town, a riding on a pony, stuck a feather in his hat and called it macaroni. Ohh, so many versions of that. WELL! erhem, adios amigos.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "...but I know I can't talk to that guy for more than about 3 seconds before I start thinking that gnawing my own leg off might be a more better way to spend my time." Strong Bad. You are my hero. Scroll, scroll, da button, du button, scrolling so smooth like butter on a muffin. http://www.homestarrunner.com/sbemail.html You shall be-dazzled in all its dazzlement. OHH! AND CHECK OUT TEEN GIRL SQUAD! I met a possum. Lets get youghurt. MSG'D! Weirded out! yes, I might have further references to them so you might want to have a look. And amy, I'm sorry I made a big deal out of you asking for my help and then not waiting for a reply. It was silly. but then that goes very well with the general stuff that goes on. SILLY BILLY! tehehe. billy don't be a hero, don't be a fool with your life. billy don't be a hero, come back and make me your wife. And thats all from me, tune in next time to hear Larry sing, everyones got a baby kangaroo, yours is pink but mine is blue... Adios Another A-Starting Adjective Amigos!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Amy you rude little girl! "Oh thanks Frances", I didn't even get that! Well grrr, not happy, you can stick your pictures up your bottom for all I care, I spent ages typing it so u could actually read it. "Oh I know how to do links now" blah blah blah. *shakes fist*. Thank you sooooo much for your gratitude. Aww, I do love you Amy but sheesh. Caw the raven cried. My hypothosis, all ravens are black or an equal hypothosis, all non-black things are non-ravens. So a pen being blue prooves that ravens are black. Confused? 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well Amy, you vant my help, eh? how do you put links on. Hmmm I do not know. MUHAHAHA of course I do know, because I know everything!! MUHAHAHA EVIL CACKLE!! Yes well, first you put your right arm in, your right arm out, no, wait you don't. Ok, you sign in. You go to the page where you write stuff, and click on TEMPLATE!! oooh speshical little bear, er icon thingy. and then you put something like this: (p)(b)(font face="Hobo" color="#FF000 0") PUT HEADING OF DESIRE (/font)(/b)(/p)  For a heading. Don't you love the font? and then you do something like this: (p)(b)(font face="Arial")(ahref="PUT ADDRESS HERE!") PUT NAME HERE! (/a)(/font)(/b)(/p) Except you know, you put like all the right stuff were it says "PUT BLAH BLAH HERE" And replace the ( and ) with  . ooh i do not know whether this will come out properly, bummer. hope it does. Oh but oh! First you have to find a spot on your template thingamajig that says something about links, but you have a different template than me so I dunno, and put the bogus    stuffy stuff under that. hope this helps and if it confuses u. GIVE ME YOUR STUFF, and then I can do it for you. I just read over it and it was very confusing, well, it wasn't when I first typed it so maybe it won't be when you first read it. MEH! hope it helps. OOOOOH Jessica's blog eh? the true, one and only angry shoes? have to check it out.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well hidey-ho there people of the internet relm. How are we all? I and completely and utterly bored, thus I shall continue to right to you as I have nothing better to do. And I said, "What about, breakfast at tiffany's", she said "I, think I, remember the film line, yes I recall, I think, we both kinda liked it" and I said, "Well thats, one thing we got" and then, some, one else said, something 'bout grammer, and I said, "that is, quite off the plot"  Errhem yes, well maybe I am very bored, and it is ruining this lovely blog so I shall stop for this kind of writing only makes it worse and what on earth am I talking about?!?! AHHH! damn electrified, barbwired poles. And who wrote about the Cebu yesterday? coz it wasn't me although it is a pretty good point. Sad cebu is rowing and crying, a boo moo moo, boo moo moo, moo moo. Adios alphabetical amigos. C is for coookie thats good enough for me...
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sick cebu is rowing and sneezing achoo moo moo, achoo moo moo, moo moo! 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Good Day. How are we all on this lovely Friday? Hope you are good, good, gooooooooooood. The love we've all been in before, a million ways to burn. Do do dee do da, yep I'm bored. shawing! ting-ting-ping TWANG! tehehe. Yeah random lyrics is the go. Oh I am what I am, I'll do what I want, but I can't hide. Hello, I'm your mind giving you someone to talk to. HELLO! Howdy Partner. Yo, yo, yo my bro-ther. How YOU doin'? wink-wink nudge-nudge how's your father? EEH! Damn poles (not polish people, they are cool) think they can stand anywhere. Wasted thoughts broken hearts, love was not acknowledged. Hmmm, soooo, you put your left arm in, your left arm out, your left arm in and you shake it all about, you do the hokey pokey and you turn around, thats whats its all about. WOOOOOAAHH, a hokey pokey, WOOOOAAAHH, a hokey pokey, WOOOOAAAHHH, ahokey pokey. Thats what its all about. Well not really. Jellyman, offspring, offspring, jellyman. You have some serious trill issues dude. WOAH RIGHTIOUS RIGHTIOUS! Dude, Mr Turlte is my father, I'm Crush. And he is a ledg. Give me some flipper, noggin. *thonk*  Let it ring a long, long, long, long time, if i don't pick up, hang up, call back, let it ring some more. "birds! birds!" is all we heard before she flew away, and the more I've been thinking, the more I know, know I'm living alone... Thats all folks! Adios Awesome Airforce Amigos
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      AHHH!! After all this time i've been spelling it wrong!! its not amego, its amigo!! AH! what have I been saying? Bye amego? What is amego? oooh well. I apologise for calling you all amegos instead of amigos. It might just be one letter, but one letter makes a whole difference, like duck and buck. they wouldn't know whether you were talking about a bird or a mammal. Or some other social practise. or um... I have to think about this. Belgrave or Belgrade. You wouldn't know if you were near the Dandenongs or in Serbia. I think its Serbia. Well near Yugaslavia. Yeah and I'll stop there, I've made my point. Thats it from me. Adios Auspicious Amigos
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You had the confidence of one, Who didn't fear the pain. One who pushed at all the boundries, And didn't mind being called insane. You were determinded, You knew you were destined for much more, But something happened, Suddenly you weren't so sure...   Thought I'd just let you know, I still beleive you can rule the world. You can do it! You can do it allllll night long!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Shaaawing ting-ting-ting "WAH!" shing wing ting-ting-ping tap! "GRR" ting-ting-shing shawing thud! Wow, I should fence more often. on guard! toshay! peray and thrust. tehehe thrusty. *cough cough* erhem. just smile and nod. Well Phillip Island was gooooood. Not like you were wondering, but I'm back, and to be back I had to of gone somewhere.  The roof, the roof the roof is on fire... we didn't start the fire, it was always burning since the worlds been turning. Anyone see that Billy Joel thingy on the ABC? Yes well... hmm... sha-wing-ting-ting pow! thonk! zap! bang! plonk! zonk! smash! crack! "ahhhh! my nose!" And the written violence will be stopped. So shall the post.  Adios Armored Aniseed Amegos
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      And they called it puppy love...Where on earth did that orginate from? Meh, probally some guy who bred dogs, or a singer, or an actor who just recited what the script writer wrote. No offence to actors or dog breders or garbage dudes. THANK U GARBAGE DUDES!!  I rediscovered my Gary Jules downloads hiding in my D:/ drive. just hidding away. It's really awesome feeling getting excited all over again. Running on the rocks of the river... and I'll stop. I don't know if I write too much or I don't write enough. I WANT SOME BUMMING FEEDBACK! GIVE ME SOME FEED BACK!! ARGG!! *smiles sweetly* paweease! if you don't know my e-mail its gday2u88@hotmail.com now you know it you have no excuse!  come in and try to wake her up, I can always sleep standing up.  Well, well my pretties it is the new year, and isn't it exciting, it's only 5mins old. aww the year is just a baby. Coochie coochie choo! Poor years, they only live for a year, then they die like yesterday.  Did you write the book of love and do you have faith in God above, if the bible tells you so. And do you beleive in rock'n'roll and music save your moral soul and can you teach me how to dance reeaaalll slow...  Noo Moo Foo Yoo. Too Coo Foo Schoo, and i'm done with that idea. they just stared at the weight of the world and pretend not to feel...  and good ol' boys were drinking whisky and rye....  singing this will be the day that I die...  this will be the day that I die....  *starts jazzy rhythm* *clicks fingers in beat intervals* (to "it don't mean a thing")  Musical culture, has grown alittle flat, the good ol' rhythms gone, the bass drum is getting too fat. The beat has gone, completely out of wack, come on you've gotta, bring that groovin' jazz back!!!  And that is my song.  And that is my blog.  And this is my name. But I forgot.  Yeah, happy new holden... I mean year... it's getting alittle repedative...
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      oooh, and it makes me wonder. ohhh, your head is humming and it won't go in case you don't know, the piper's calling you to join him, dear lady, can you hear the wind blow...  It is the day of sun, a sunny day. I don't get to go to smorgy's with friends, I get to go to my grandma's with family. Dunno if thats a good or bad thing, I don't like smorgys but I like friends. Meh. I .... just lost my train of thought. Bummer. I have to do home work now, apply for work experience at the coroners court. I wrote to 4 different forensic places and all rejected me. Because of the "nature of their work". Well I don't like them either. Anyway, cooling off, adios
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When we left the movie show the future wasn't bright, but came the dawn the show goes on and I don't want to say good night! So say good morning! Good MORNING! Well actually good evening, but hey, no technicallities.  How are we all? I'm very good after my hour and a bit of patchwork therapy. Its really good, as long as you have different colours and good music. Very good music. Yes. My patchwork is now around 30cm by 15cm or so. And not its not quilting patchwork its patchwork patchwork as in scrap stuff, unfortuantly no florals. Damn. Well yes, lacking things to say.  awww esky wants to get out via the window. He reached up for it and meowed really cutely. Aww he's gone away now. And I think to myself, what a wonderful world. GUY SO RUINED THAT SONG! You can not beat Louis Armstrong so don't try and ruin his songs. Yes, well I know you know the way to San Jose.      I found a way, a way make, a stand...
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      35/36 for our drama improvisation assesment. I feel so good about that. I got to be a two faced, snobby, shop assistant; a sexist, sleazy guy on a double date who hit on the the other couple of lesbians while his girlfriend was next to him; and the good guy in a western that dies because the bad guy cheated, but then she got shot too by the indian. Tehehe, in the western all the girls played male roles and Pat, the only guy, played the damsel in distress.  OH! The double date in the restaurant was the best.  tehehe funny, but I had to be soo sexist. It made me feel unclean. "I think I want some chicken brrrreast".  Yeah well, hmmm, how are you today? Yes I am asking you. Well I had double german to start off today, so that dragged down my morning but brought me to make a new song. That mainly consisted of "Gemse" 9 times then "Obst" and then "Sissigkeiter" to finish it off. But I couldn't, pronounce that sissig one. anyway, tennis training g2g now adios
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My box of one-way mirrors. I can see out, but they can't see in. All they can see is a reflection of themselves, fat or thin. They strike a pose and smile,  and pick at their teeth for awhile. They don't know I'm here, having to live through a life that isn't my own. Wishing for a brick to shatter my cubic home. The glass would break and fall, scraching scars in me, but it wouldn't matter because I'd finally be free. But then people would be able to see the differences in me. Is that what I really want?  Just to be another subject for people to taunt?  Not about me, although its written in first person.  Don't be the one too afraid to fall, that lives life like watching TV.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Good Afternoon Ms Bloggedy-blu, how are we all on this wonderously cloudy Saturday? All the stranges came today, and it looks like that they are here to stay. Hope you're mentally, phsyically and emotionally happy. or at least one of the above.   Theres an opera thing on TV, and I've never really been intrested in opera, but it gains my interest now because of the translation, the lyrics are awesome.  I showed Naomi my little book of my... erm, poems? and she said it it was really surprising coz she didn't think I had a "suicidal streak" or dark side. Both of which I argued with. I don't think its that dark, is it? Well Its not ment to be, so it shouldn't. The only really dark one was that one about ripping out someones neck flesh and that wasn't in it. awww, I'm not suicidial damnit! I just write more about the crappyness then the goodness, because the goodness deserves to be lived not written about, and noone should have to go through the crappyness. Yeah, well, or something along those lines. awww. Don't ask me whats going though my head, I honestly don't know, well maybe just not at the moment. Me go now. Byezybyez   I know a girl who waits, all her life, she's been waiting in shame, anticipating a change she can't explain. Don't let me seem so, don't let me feel so... down. Theres a better way, theres a better way...
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The question is: How can such a good day make me feel so crap? The Answer? It doesn't exsist.  I got my little kids today, some are brats, but what can you expect? I just don't know whether they'll be more or less brattish once we're done with them. Meh, and I forgot my trumpet lesson period 5 because i was so excited about english because its one of the only classes that I'm with Ashlea and Naomi, which is quite sad because I like playing trumpet and I don't like our english teacher. Who said rushing ment you were nervous? Not all stories have to have the climax at the end, and only one climax. And what are you really grading in writing anyway? the imagtivity? the grammar? the plot? the shape? I'm not complaining because i got a low mark, I got an A. But she just talks as if theres only one set way to do stuff and that annoys me. And she gives me the impression that she is performing more than teaching or living. Which is alittle like me, and that just scares me, especially coz I think she takes starsigns seriously and I think they are total astrom bullocks. The posistion of the stars and planets have no reign on me. You have no power over me. (from the laberinth, Bowies in tights!) Yeah well, and shes buying her stairway to heaven. This blog looks unhappy, or not good, but that wasn't how my day was. Thats only my impression now. I think I was actually smiling all day, wats new? On my outside, the thinkness of skin, cannot let you see, the breaking soul that is within. Ciao 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Got lions and tigers only in Kenya, forget Norway! Kenya! Oh Kenya! Where the giraffes are, and the zebras! Kenya! Kenya! Kenya! Kenya! Kenya, come to Kenya! Kenya beleive it!   Tats loopin' round and round inside my head.  Come on fhqwgads, I see you jocking me, trying to play like 'you know me?' Catchy webs they are. but i think i'm kinda stealing there pure brilliance by putting the words here, you just have to hear it. OH! Typing about pure brilliance, Brigie, your poem is awesome, wow. I love it. wow.  Now I have a blank of what else to say coz of the wowness... um... yeah. wow. um... so... everybody to the limit, frances is to the limit, come on now fhqwhgads! Alright, alright, alright. See ya buddys! Oh wait. Adios Agile Actor Amigos! 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      They call him, Flipper, Flipper, faster than lightning, no-one you see, is smarter than he, and we know Flipper, lives in a world full of wonder, flying there-under, under the sea!  I've had that tune stuck in my head all week and it wasn't until my good friend kate started singing along that I actually released what it was from. I would kinda go "Mumble, mumble, faster than lightning, not very frightning" Well I was wrong. Hurray for wrongness! I'm glad I can accept my being wrongness. Usually its like, "no i'm not wrong, you just misinterpretted me or I used the wrong wording, but I'm not wrong." Or something along those lines, stupid, stupid frances and her arrogant ways.  Meh, I am who I am, accept me for that, theres no word to me that means 'I can't', over the years I might change alittle, but it won't be a complete soul transplant.  You won't try to change me, unless you look for flaws, leave me living the way I am, living for my own, happy cause. So what are we up to on this beaming sunny saturday? I just got back from a sleep over at bens and I'm not sleeply... yet. It was good, we played alot of Nintendo Gamecube and watched freddie vs jason, and darkness falls. And I think we consumed about, 7-8 litres of coke, and 2 of solo.  Solo, meaning singular, and so-lo as how he felt. I read that out of a book my brother was reading, the ones that get left in the living room and you go, "wow, a book" and start reading, but it got abit boring, so I didn't finish it.  Hmm. And a million balloons and performing baboons, and give it to me, now! I want the world, I want the whole world, I want to lock it, all up in my pocket, its my bar of chocolate. Give it to me now! I want today, I want tomorrow, I want to wear them like braids in my hair, AND I DON'T WANT TO SHARE THEM!  You look outside through the window out into the dark garden and she a sad little girl. Or maybe its just a reflection from the light inside, the house that keeps you alive, but leaves you feeling empty. The sensation is gone again and you wonder who... what am I to only feel a slight heat when the world catches on fire. Wondering if something is missing in your eyes... Do what you have to, to get yourself across. So that people have the chance to try and understand, the chance to try and help. "Coz its me, and my life, its my life..." (Dido - My Life)
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      many people, many faces, many things, in many places. some people, some faces, some things, in some places. beautiful people, beautiful faces, beautiful things, in beautiful places. angry people, angry faces, angry things, in angry places. comfortable people, comfortable faces, comfortable things, in comfortable places. strange people, strange faces, strange things, in strange places. cold people, cold faces, cold things, in cold places. wonderful people, wonderful faces, wonderful things, in wonderful places. confronting people, confronting faces, confronting things, in confronting places. unforgiving people, unforgiving faces, unforgiving things, in unforgiving places...
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So you think you can stone me and spit in my eye, so you think you can love me and leave me to die! Oh baby! Can't do this to me baby! Just gotta get out! just gotta get right outta here! DA NANANA NA A LA AAAH! do do do do dooo, nothing really matters, Anyone can see, nothing really matters, nothing really matters tooo mmmmeeeeEE!! ahuh! Amy and I were singing that allllll day, 1 because it is the most awesomest awesome song and 2 because she had it the "We Will Rock You" CD. And the best thing is, everyone knows the words go you'll start the Galileo bit and you'll hear echos through-out the courtyard. Well thats how loud we were singing, in our very beautifull off tone, out of key voices. It was awesome, we should do it everyday, but different songs, that ppl know. Hmm. Anyway. AYE! 'Ow U doin'!? Noice.  Back in my day, we had to walk 30kms to school each day, and by the time we got home we had to go to school again, boy our feet hurt. And.. and our shoes were made of a block of wood strapped to our feet, oh boy, those were the days. You young people are so lucky. Where did that come from? OH! OH! Hyperventilating! I feel so loved, I'm home group leader. I get a shiny badge and get to say "I'm 10B leader!" and "CARN THE B!". Well I said the second one last year in our 9B posse, but meh. 10B is the best, you cannot beat the B.  GRR MSN NOT WORKING! Throw shoe at computer, but that would require going outside and getting my shoe. Anyway. Yeah. wow, form leader.  Well Adios Amature Archers Amigos! Love you!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OH NO I've run out of cantalope, or rock melon for those northern ppl. have to get some more!  mmmm beautiful cantalope. How are we all? I think I say that every blog and still no answer, u rude littl ppls! Well, if you want to know... I got chills, they're multiplyin', and I'm losin' control, cause the power you're supplyin', it's ELECTRIFYIN'! ahuh. it is. Yep I'm bored stiff, or as Catch Phrase would have it animated, a plank of wood with 'stiff' written on it. AAAH I'm out of cantaloope again, where does it go!?! I want to know! Just like I want to know who stole the cookie, from the cookie jar. and don't blame me, it was mine to start with. Wait, no, it wasn't me. ahhh! um, off that subject...  You better shape up, cause I need a man, and my heart is set on you, you better shape up, you better understand, to my heart I must be true. Who is the muffin man, everyone asks if you know the muffin man but seriously, I don't, and its unfair! I wanna know the muffin man! PLEASE HELP ME! Do you know the muffin man? Who is he?  Your the one that I want... sorry, its stuck in my head.  OH! And I got 'Minight Madness' stuck in my head from the bats musical in yr 8. Hello Everybody! It's twelve o'clock, its time for you to come alive, welcome to the party, we're really gonna rock, gonna boogie, gonna jive! Feel that groovn hipnotic beat, feel the beat, feel those disco rhythems in your feet, in your feet, we're gonna reach the top and we ain't never gonna stop! Midnight madness, midnight madness, feel the power of the witching hour, from the moment you hear the band start playing, your in a trace! Midnight madness midnight madness dance with me this disco fantasy, theres no use trying to resist the music GET UP AND DANCE!  Thats a bit scary I still remember that, I started making up a little and I don't think its "Feel that groovn hipnotic beat" but its along those lines.  Well anyway, HOW YOU DOIN"! Gotta scadadle now, Adios Abandoned Ape Amigos!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      do a little dance, make a little love, get down tonight, get down tonight, WOOT! Ahuh ahuh, ahuh-ahuh-ahuh, ooh yeah. yo hotstuff! How you doin'? I 've been meltin' in ma shoes coz you look so damn fine. Still Smilin' How are we all in the internet relm where reality is what we want it to be? I hope your happy, its always good to be happy, unless you're only happy when your beating the crap out of someone, ahhh! I hope your not that type of person, and sorry if I insulted you if you are. ahhhh.... Anyway! So I'm walking down this street, right? and this dog comes up to me and starts slobbering all over my leg. This doggy saliva wasn't your normal doggy saliva, it was yellow and has chunks of something, that I just hope was just some tanbark. And it was yuck and yeah, ewwwy. I ended up trying to get it off and wipe it on the over-friendly dog, then it lost intrest in me and walked off, well kinda galloped. Silly big dogs, I wonder whose it was. And that is my story. My team won tennis today, 43 - 33. HORRAY. My dad turned up just before my singles and sat on the otherside of the fence watching. and snapping bloody twigs! Does anyone know how annoying that is? If I he wasn't my dad who takes tennis resonably serious I would say he was doing it on purpose just to piss me off. and he kept butting in with the scores, like I'd ask my lovely opponent if it was 15-40 or 30 all and he'd just say 15-40. AND AHH! I love my dad but if he isn't playing he should remain quiet, please. yeah well, I lost my singles 3-6. MOOO!  Cows go moo, they really really do, moo moo moo, cows go moo. MOOO Pascal Moochews, which will you choose, pascal moochews, moochews. i wonder what happened to them? They like got taken off the market ages ago. hmm. Well thats al from me for now. But have no fear, Frances is here! Or maybe you should have fear because I'm here. aww whatever, love yas!  Arrivederci Amici, Adios Amigos, Auf Weidersehen Freunde, Au Revoir Amis, Adeus Amigos   P.S. How many languages say 'goodbye' starting with 'A'? thats pretty weird. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Do de do de do. I think I'm better now, all I needed was 2 solid hours of Christian Rock and I'm back in the game. HOOOO WA! gotcha nose. tehehe. No one is really talking to me on msn, but I really couldn't care, tehehe, they are funny people, people they are. i think. tehehe. yeah wow, the world is big, hello to those of you in china! wow, a hundred thousand or so k's from here. thats quite a way away. *wave* HELLOOOOOO! How are you on this lovely Friday Nite? What ever happened to saturday night, When you got dressed up and you felt all right, it don't seem the same since cosmic light. Then a little more verse and HOT PATOTEE BLESS MY SOUL! I REALLY LOVE THAT ROCK AND ROLL! Rocky Horror Picture Show, oh meatloaf, what has come of you? you better think twice janet wiese, your apple pie don't taste too nice. Yes well. tehehe, skip with me along, along, along, the yellow brick road. just follow the yellow brick road. I would sing with the sparrows and the boy who shoots the arrows if i only had a heart. I give you roses, I give you roses, I give you roses, to show my love for you. Adios Amazing Amigos
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      why do you hate me? why do you despise me so? why do you watch me bleed? do I really make you feel that low? I don't know what I did, to make you lothe my presence, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, Don't end you adolesence. Please stay, don't go, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, why don't you believe me? why don't you think I worry? I'm sorry, I'm sorry, please don't fall now, I'll make it up to you, some day, some how...
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      MSN not working, grrr, shut down. Repeating work we did in year 9. Sharing gym with 2 other forms, another year 10 and my sisters year 8 form. Annoying American Idol stealing my first half hour of Simpsons. I like my simpsons, how dare something so craptacular steal my simpsons on a day like this. I am not happy. Does anyone actually care about americas singing talent, or lack of it? arrrg!! Msn still not working. Not happy Jan. Cat meowing at me. Better go fed him.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Trying hard to understand it  Trying hard to make things real  Trying hard to understand it  But the real thing's just so sweet   Is there a meaning here?  Is there a meaning here?  Does it really mean a thing?   Come and see the real thing  Come and see the real thing  Come and see   I am the real - thing    
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Good morning, George. How are you? I hope you're feeling fine! I'd love to stay and talk but it's almost eight o' clock and I haven't got the time!!  Because we work real hard at the Chocolate factory, we start at eight and we don't get lunch 'till three. I've gotta drive a truck, to make a buck, so I can send it home to my family. =D Good Evening actually but my sis was singing it now it is here. I think I've onlt ever mentioned my sister when she's been singing. Hmm, what does that say? She talks alot, and usually loudly. AND HURRAY FOR CHIGGEN! I feel like chiggen tonight, like chiggen tonight. Hey! I actually had chiggen for dinner. wow. weird. But ahhhh! What about the bird flu?? AHHH! What if! AHH! What if someone did something. sorry just lost my train of thought. So I better go before I ruin the flow, ho ho ho, merry christmas and a happy new year. Adios AWOL Aztec Amigos 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      HURRAH! Hurray for dancing chickens with their funny hats and clever shoes! I love dancing chickens with funny hats and clever shoes. Aren't they just the coolest? Yeah, I know, they don't quite pass the margin of your coolness, but nothing can really do such a stunt. Disco, disco, disco, disco, its coloured gold baby! Or something like that. I was dancing when I was twelve. I was dancing when I was twelve! la la la la la alaaaa! Emma's shoes are cleverer but mine have magical soles that can say spaghetti. How cool is that? OH YOU MUST SEE MY SHOES BEFORE THEY DEPART! *sniffle* My very very favourite shoes in the whole wide world are nearly dead, after 3 years of loyal service. But they are so cool, I don't want to stop wearing them. WAHH! I want my shoey! the left one! Aww I have to find a picture of the make on the web so u can awe in its beauty. My poor flame airwalks, I shall miss you. Luckily you are not gone yet. HURRAY FOR SHOES! Wow, I never thought I'd say that line of shopping insaneness.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Zlusr ow zesl sla giha cio quc urn? Zapp E'q vis kievk si sapp cio yatc rstuekl jitzuth, evjugs, upp E'q kievk si ruc er: sla xoegn ftizv jib moqwr iyat sla pudc hik. Heh cio nviz slus? =D Ej cio guv xa xislatah slus er. cio pudc jiipr!   Iva huc E japp, uvh vi iva zur slata, ri E kis qcrapj ow, uvh jitkis liz si guta... 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Whats up with the code you may ask? Well I'm not going to tell you very straight forward, infact, all I'm going to say is: sla xoegn ftizv jib moqwr iyat sla pudc hik. Did you know that? =D If you can be bothered that is. cio pudc jiipr!  Iva huc E japp, uvh vi iva zur slata, ri E kis qcrapj ow, uvh jitkis liz si guta...
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lappi Upp! I mean, Hello all! How you doin'? I'm okay, hoping not to get a relaps of whatever I had yesterday. It was very bleh and crampy and gluggy. And not nice, like most sicknesses. Atleast its not diphtheria, because we got immunised for that and tetnus and whooping cough on wednesday. Woot! I would hate to die of any of those, the symptoms are gross. anyway. Grand final today, wow its only 7:45 and I'm already up, I don't have to go until later coz I'm not playing. Yeah well, hey, what about you? I want to know about you. Tell me how you are, share your story.  But Your life here has made it clear enough for me to see, that if I do not love, I am nothing... Adios amigos, hope youse have a happy day.  Lizta cio kievk si hea? Zlav cio kievk si jpc uzuc jtiq es upp?
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You are so beautiful, to me. Awww, I love you guys, and I'm really really sorry if I've ever offended you through this blog, especially when I went through that whole thing like "pfft who is gonna read this?" And odviously you do, you care, to some extent, other wise you wouldn't read. So I'd just like to say thank you. =D  I know the coolest guy, who died for me, spilled his blood so I could be free. And I want to thank Him also. Coz He is my Lord and Saviour and He deserves my praise.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Did you miss me? I haven't written in 5 days, ooooh. Sorry I was such a snob. But alot of people have been snobs of late which is no excuse and I apoligise for bringing up such a weak excuse. Bloody majority think they own the world. Just like americans and fish and leaves and those people who smoke in the toliets at shopping centres. And thats the end of my little people anger. Anyway. My brother turned 18 on Thursday, WOOT! And we had his party on Saturday, yeah, yeah, we did, we did, and he's my brother. Just ignore that last bit, so we had both sides of the family over and Ross's friends. Mmmhmm! And it was good and I'd have to say Red Bear is good. Not that I had any or anything.... umm... maybe. But I didn't wag the last period on Friday! We got permission to leave from a teacher, just not from my teacher, but it was only German, and no one else was there because they were all exhasted from basketball marathon and went home and I didn't want be alone in a room with.... Frau Moore *shivers* And now I shall leave you,  toots! toot toot train toot'n its way home
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      typing typing typing typing typing typing typing. Well that idea didn't work. I thought if I wrote that for a while something to type would come to me. But alas. Nothing. What have you little mushroom munchkins been up to? I've been doin' absolutly nothing! WOOT! Hmm, there should be a sign where you can show sarcasm. hmmm I got the hick-ups, thats pretty big news. No one is online because of basketball marathon, and if another person says that I should go or should've gone I'm not going to even bother replying. Why? you may ask? because its not my scene, and even if it was, I wouldn't feel comfortable. Like many days of late. Pppft stuff the past. Growin' old, growin' mould, bringin' in the dirt, chucking out the gold. adios all of youse
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sick cebu is rowing and sneezing achoo moo moo, achoo moo moo, moo moo.  I'm a Gnu, I'm a Gnu! The g-nicest work of g-nature in the zoo!  I'm a Gnu, how do you do? You really ought to k-now w-ho's w-ho's,  I'm a Gnu, spelt G-N-U, I'm g-not a Camel or a Kangaroo So let me introduce, I'm g-neither man or moose, Oh g-no g-no g-no I'm a Gnu! =) Daddy started out in San Fransico, tooting on his trumpet loud and mean. Suddenly a voice said go forth daddy, spead the picture on a wider screen. Yep, I thought I should return to some degree of unneeded nonesence. but then it might be needed by some.  Pass the pepper please! Thanks Catch a falling star and put it in your pocket, save it for a rainy day, catch a falling star and put it in your pocket never let it fade away. Bordem is mine! muhaha. Now everyone shall be bored for I am the Queen of the Borkingdem in Boretopia and I am here to take over... where am I? Wait I'm in Borkingdem, but I already rule Borkingdem. Oh never mind, I'll just sit here twiddling my thumbs. Or not because its really hard to type while twiddling thy thumbs.  She says, she says, she doesn't know where, she is, or where she was, or if she even lived, before you found her here. But where is that?  Never was really good at geography. Well I think my work here is done, now, your mission, if you choose to except it is... unknown to me, ask your parents. Toots 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      To soylent green bloggers... I read yours... do you read this?
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      MY SISTER HAS NO HAIR!!! Well she has a no. 1 but still! AHHH! Ca-RAZY! but its for 'The World's Greatest Shave For a Cure' so atleast it was worth it. She raised about $400, which is also good. SHE HAS NO HAIR! tehehe, skinhead, wow. No hair for her hair brush!  "Turn it off Neil" "No its really good this one... nnneee" *smash* Awww, the young ones, brilliance. I know you love it. "I can't beleive it, my parents, dead"-(p)Rick "thats bad"- Neil So what you do today? I hope you had fun. =)  Where was I before the day, that I first saw your lovely face? Now I see it everyday... And I know... that I am... I... am, I... am, the luckiest... Thanks for shopping, have a nice day!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tuesday night at church was awesome, I dunno what came over me, must of been the awesome atmospere, but I just started laughing during worship. It was hiralious. Wow, it was so good. You should of been there.   And today was pretty awesome too, especially for a wednesday. Double German wasn't as bad as I thought, which was good. And in sport we had gadorade ppl come and I kicked a goal, I feel soo spesh! We still lost, but carn the green! ELBOW!! WOOT! I.P. was good too. I got to continue my logo of "da chicken on wheels", its green. tehehe. Maths was abit of a bummer with our teacher keep on yelling at us telling us to listen and pens down and the next second asked if we had finished yet and why we hadn't finished yet. She probally had a bad day and needed to outlet somewhere.  WOOOOOOOOOT! Everybody, everybody! SAILING MISHAP! NEW TEEN GIRL SQUAD!!! OW! My hopes of reaching first base! This side has birds on it!! lol!! awww OOOH I'M TO NERVOUS!  Still laughing,  TEHEHE! MOHAHA, you know who I am. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello, my name is Penelope Richards, I live in Yorkshire and every Saturday I play polo with my daddy at his country club. Haw haw haw. Myes well, ther is my posh, snobby alter ego. My daddy has lots of money! Haw haw haw. Well that was out of young ones, but generally that type of thing.  one fish, two fish, red fish, blue fish. Fox in socks on box on Know in socks. Six sick chicks tick, six sick clocks tock. Dr Seuss you legend. Tweedle Beetle Paddle Battle. Of course on a noodle eating poodle. Where else? but Queensland. ummm, Melbourne, New York, London, Berlin. Just to name a few.   you've been so sad, it makes me worry, why not smile, you've been sad for a while, why not smile... I would do anything... to hear you speak of it...
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Amy's surprise party was a complete success. She came over to my house with a little of expectation of a surprise party but when she got here, no one was here except my beautiful family so that was good. Luckily she didn't see Kates rolled up sleeping bag in the middle of my room. So we set off to Blackburn Lake for "Kate's Cousin's Party". And when we got to the spot ppl were so well hidden I thought they'd buggered off. But then they jumped out and Amy was hopefully very surprised. I think she was surprised coz when Jo started bouncing  around shouting "open presents!" she still looked pretty shocked going "whaa?" GO TEAM! Yay. And the cake Kate made was sooo chocolatly and filling we didn't even bother buying the pizza. mmmm soo much chocolate...  Yeah so we all had a good time. mep. so many eccentric perspectives. well I got to vamoose, ciao!   be the salient one   
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      rolling down the same ol' hill, its fun while it lasts, the trouble is getting back up, the happiness now in the past. taking up the courage, to stumble back up the slope, I'll get back up there, get back to hanging onto my ledge of hope...  The colours of the rainbow so pretty in the sky, are also on the faces of people going by, I see friends shaking hands saying "how do you do?" they're really saying "I love you!" 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well hello there! DROP ELBOW! come on, yeah, we're in da house. WEll I'm in my house anyway, dunno where you are. If you every have the urge for a high five, do a drop elbow.  Oh I love to climb a mountain and to reach the highest peak, but it does thrill me half as much as dancing cheak to cheak.  So, how was your day? I just got back from playing to the little children that now filter through our school, also known as yr 7s. Then Loc, Brad, Jo'ash and I started busking and we got 50c!! WOOT! Bonza! But I chose not to take my share of our tresure as I have to be the responsible yr 10 and not make too much noise. tehehe, teachers say the funniest things. Oh come on dance with me, I want my arm about you, the charm about you, will carry me through. That is my new favourite song, as of this moment, it'll change by the end of the night to "Sweet Transvestite" out of Rocky Horror or "Why Not Smile" by REM. I've been making a man, with blonde hair and a tan, and he's good for relieving my... tension!  Well I better go Auf Weidersehen! Why don't you stay for the night, or maybe a bite...
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey ho hello there! How are we all? Hope you're happy. Fun, Laughs, Good time! Yeah! The schools doin' sweet charity for the musical this year and I'm just getting into some of the songs. Hit the floor and crawl to Daddy. Alot of people don't want the musical coz its taking to place of the Talent Quest, but the schools wack, if they get rid of the musical they're not gonna put the talent quest back on. Meh, too confusing. And the tingle in your feet. I want the talent quest too, but I'd rather 1 thing than none. All I can say is "wow!" we look at where I am! Yeah, its catchy. lol. And The Rhythm Of Life is a powerful beat, puts a tingle in your fingers and a tingle in your feet, rhythm in your bedroom, rhythm in the street, yes, the Rhythm Of Life is a powerful beat!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What's up in your life? I never really know, it just seems to pass and then it becomes nothing. Like when someone asks "What did you do today?" the reply is usually "not much" even if something good happened. Or something devisating or something new or something that really pissed you off. Has life lost it's charm, is it growing boring? I think life itself isn't getting boring, just the people are trying to be more extreme. Smalls things don't mean anything anymore, or maybe it does on the inside but people are too busy trying to project the "ness" they want to be, the person that is acceptable. Person that is accepted, but at the same time being different. Everyone craves to be different, but why? Why should we crave something we already have? I'm confused and puzzled and now I have asked you, hoping for a reply. I've never really written a blog like this, I don't know if its a good or a bad thing, but its something in my head that I thought I would share. I want to be different and accepted and have a reply to this blogging (wink wink nudge nudge), maybe not everyone does, but how am I meant to know that? It like asking someone next to you at the very back of a crowd if they can see anything up the front, it might seem stupid, but how do you know that they can't see anything either? I'm not trying to sound like the only one who thinks these things, I just wanted to write it down. So I'm gonna go now, leaving you with whatever thoughts are running 'round inside your head.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      G'days mate! howsit 'anging?  I'm the only hatcher child home! All my siblings, well all three of them, aren't here. And I won't have any guarenteed sibling company til Friday. You might think I should be happy to be rid of such family, but its terrible and now I am so glad I am not an only child. the bordem is terrifing! the land of bordem, is my kingdom. I rule with a mighty sword, here in the kingdom of the bored! well I have to go. cheers mateys! I'm working 6hrs on sunday! 6hrs!! Come visit me! I'll be the stunning... erhem... young lasse with the trainee badge that has trouble finding the right buttons on the cash register.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sorry about the amout of corny poetry recently, just got boreded. So bored that I now have alittle obsession with Act 4 of Shakespeares "As You Like It". And its just like I like it.   Rosalind: "Nay, an you be so tardy, come no more in my sight: I had as lief be wooed of a snail."  Orlando: "Of a snail?"  Rosalind: "Ay, of a snail; for though he comes slowly, he carries his house on his head; a better jointure, I think, than you make a woman: besides he brings his destiny with him."  Rosalind, you are so cool. Even if you have a little weird thing going on with Phebe. =S.  So what are you little people doing today, I'm working. Wait, have I told you that I got a job? At Bakers Delight? I might of mentioned it, but hey! I'm working class now. And already they have me working saturday and sunday. But I get to wear a funny hat, so that makes up for it. Oh! And that sexy checked apron.  "Come, woo me, woo me, for now I am in a holiday humour and like enough to consent. What would you say to me now, an I were your very very Rosalind?"  No me! Woo me! WOO! YEAH! WOOHOO!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In Reply: The faces of friends, the brightness they send, when your life is darkend... they'll help you cope New life begins, the new-born baby grins, the forgiveness of sins... there is still hope Sweet sented roses, cute puppies noses, grandpas snoring when he dozes... can't you just smile? Everyday's a new story,  no need to worry, sorry to be corny... but ain't that worth while? don't you know its alright, alright. Alright? It will be alright, alright. Alright? Why won't you hear me say, that there's still hope today...
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i feel like breaking something...
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      refugees, travel seas, to get to somewhere they can be free... and end up in prison. and war goes on, losing daughters and sons, coz it "must be won"... their blood's a dark crimson. we kill for meat, and eat and eat, prop up our feet... while others die of stavation no ones there and no one cares, except about celebrity affairs... what's happening to this nation? don't tell me its alright, alright. Alright? coz its not alright, alright. Alright? deep in inside you know, that you too feel like letting go. Maybe it'll be alright tomorrow...   
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Allo, hello, good day, aye, good morning, hey, g'day, yo, howsit, how you doing, greetings, howdy, salutations, hi, WOOP WOOP! they call me mellow yellow. Or caramello... koala, I go with the flow Actually, I don't think anyone calls me mellow yellow, but meh. Any old excuse will do. Questions running through my head, the same effect of a pulled loose thread, Where have all the dreamers gone? What are we all running from? All in all what have we done? So and so, and another someone? Who? What? Why? Are we afraid to dream? afraid to die?  Where have all the dreamers gone? Where are those who love, and those who care? Open you're eyes and see, that they haven't gone anywhere...
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I awake to find no piece of mind, I said how do you live as a fugitive? Down here? Where I cannot see so clear, I said what do I know? Show me the right way to go  Good day, hows your head? Is it happy and safe? hope so, unless thats not how you like it. =P "Thats what I'm talkin' 'BOUT!" tehehe funny people. Coz they're just spies... Well not really, I just got spies by coldplay stuck in my head and its seeping into this blog. Oh well, what you going to do about it eh? Nothing? Oh phew, I thought you might egg my house.  Cheerio! Daddy needs the computer    I awake to see that no one is free, well, we're all fugitives, look at the way we live down here I cannot sleep from fear, no I said which way do I turn? Oh I forget everything I learn  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      can I get a WOOP WOOP? awww, ok, don't worry 'bout it. Where are you? How are you? Who are you today? I hope you're happy where you are.  Jeans, jeans, homemade jeans, jeans, jeans, oh so cool, jeans, jeans, made by me, jeans, made, last year at school. Yes they are jeans, and I'm very proud of them, even though the waistbands abit screwy... Bones, sinking like stones, all that we have fought for, homes, places we've grown, all of us are done for... So... I'm into the "...'s" today... tehehe, there they are again. I thought I saw her smile. do do do do do dooooo.  you can't touch this, can't touch this, my, my, my, music hits me so hard makes me say oh my Lord, thank you for blessing me with a mind to rhyme and two hyped feet. It feels good when you know you're down, a superdope homeboy from the Oaktown and I'm known as such and this is a beat of the can't touch. tehehe, can't touch this. break it down! yeah, its good. Well I forgot the quote of the day stuff so I'm gonna just leave it. Or maybe I'll do it when I feel like it.  Quote: "and it's digestive system gets smashed hardcore and ends up being lodged in its brain" - guess who said that. =) His name starts with 'A'. lol, we weren't talking about dropping cats from the eiffel tower... umm... maybe we were... but he started it! I just sat there going "eww!", "save the kittens!" and "what if it hit one of the suports on the way down!! =(!"   Oh, all that I know, there's nothing here to run from, Cos yeah, everybody here, got somebody to lean on...  You are so beautiful to me... and I'll see YOU later! ;)
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Good morning George, how are you? I hope you're feeling fine, Allo, woo! morning blogging! woo and yay cried belle and bill.  I am thinking of an easter walk, like the Christmas one but with easter eggs and after easter. Would you like to be included? and get an easter egg? well then call 1800 65 31 22 within the next 10mins for your chance to win big! well, not actually, just e-mail me at gday2u88@hotmail.com In the mornin', in the mor-r-n-ing, it's great! to stay up late. Good morning, good morning to you. might be just as iffy if we was in Mississippi. tehehe iffy, i don't know if thats the right word, it could of been spiffy but i couldn't hear it properly. Well thats my excuse anyway. Well cheeri-o cuddly cats and dogs.   L A  U  GH DR E A M    T HINK  LIV E 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WOO! YEAH! WOOHOO!  tehehe Bill Boes, hahaha, production designer, hehehe, scooby doo 2. Yep, you guessed, or did you? I forgot what you did or didn't guess now so I'll just stop. A bit later. Tehehe BILL BOES!! awww, what a name, I love it.  And thats all I have to say on that topic. I'm lovin' it! goodbye gorgeous girls and boys! (tehehe, Bill Boes)
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yo people,  Bakers today was okay, there are too many buttons! and the slicing got alittle repedative, but hey, I'm not complaining. Hmmm, ooh yeah!This is one of my favourite poems, you might of heard it, maybe not. But I reckon its awesome! =)  One night I had a dream I dreamed I was walking along the beach with the Lord and across the sky flashed scenes from my life,  For each scene, I noticed two sets of footprints in the sand; one belonged to me, and the other to the Lord.  When the last scene of my life flashed before me,  I looked back at the footprints in the sand.   I noticed that many times along the path of my life, there was only one set of footprints.   I also noticed that it happened at the very lowest and saddest times in my life.  This really bothered me, and I questioned the Lord about it  "Lord, you said, that once I decided to follow you, you would walk with me all the way,  but I have noticed that during the most troublesome times in my life there is only one set of footprints. I don't understand why in times when I needed you most, you should leave me."  The Lord replied, "My precious, precious child, I love you and I would never, never leave you during your times of trial and suffering." "When you saw only one set of footprints, it was then that I carried you."  I don't know who it's by. Love'n'hugs from ME!! =D=D
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You people should slap me for being so ignorant to this poor dear blog that has been doing a awesome job. Really hard, with a maths book, encased in steal, covered in spikes. Well maybe not the spikes... Anyway! moving away from maths torture, damn maths test today, atleast its not like the japanese water torture where you are tied down and they make water drip on your forhead, continually for a looooong time. Erhem. Wow, its raining. Today, I gave people bubble wrap bracelets and you'd be in the middle of class and hear this "Snap!". I don't think the teachers like it. tehehe,   MUHAHAHA BUBBLE WRAP DOMINATION!       Yeah well my sister need the computer for educations purposes so I better go... OHH OOHH WAIT! WOOT! I need quotes of the day, it'll probally get really bad during the holidays but hey, whats a girl to do? Todays Quote: "I only use her for visual pleasure" - Alby (He was lying, lol)  Catch yas mateys!  Oh sing me a song a song of the sea, bird eye fish fingers....
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Something's up with Jack, something's up with Jack, don't know if we're ever going to get him back...  whats new? I finally got work experience, nowhere that I want to go my careering life, where ever that may be, but work experience all the same. First week at... nunawading library and second week at Spotlight in Box Hill. How boring are they?? Yawn, I can feel the tedium already, BUT BUT BUT!!!! Because I got them I can now go to STATE YOUTH GAMES!! WOO! YEAH!! STATE YOUTH GAMES!! yeah ok, and i'm nearly done... STATE YOUTH GAMES!! okay.  He's all alone up there, locked away inside, never says a word, hope he hasn't died...  Yeah I think our year level is having a little obsession with The Nightmare Before Christmas, mainly because it is awesome, but yeah. Top stuff. Well thats all from me, oh oh! wait! I feel so deprived! I finally worked out how much I get paid and its only $6.68 and hour. how cheap are they? Ashlea gets 8 something and she works at a Bakers Delight too and awwww, I feel so jibbed. Anyway, CHEERS! 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hello&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    DUDE! You have some serious thrill issues!&nbsp; urlLink     How cool? 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hahaha! hot "POWER GLOVE" on my hand. Its really hard to type with it on. It s like one of those old nintendo gloves that are oh so "futuristic" although it was made in 1989. Its only a year younger than me! wow, old technology, i don't even know where my brother got it from, we've never had a nintendo of any sort, wait are gameboys nintendo? well anyway. Howsit going? Hope ya good! ooooh! i got a new e-mail "purplesplat@hotmail.com", add me! unless you can't be bothered which is completely fair enough. Well I'm gonna go now. Happy happines hunting! cheers mates
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      How spesh is this new look? I don't know what I think of those dots but its still pretty hot. I probally could get rid of them. Woo! and you can put comments on them and stuff. and it got rid of my mutant babaa. I hope you got to see it. ! !!! I closed up last night!! And I took home HEAPS of bread and latice danishes and crosaunts and scrolls, and YUMMY! I got to clean the slicer and the wires. But I had to mop aswell, so I smelt like bread but my hands smelt like mop, and I wrote a song about it. I'll write it down for you.  I smell like bread, but my hands smell like mop, mopping mopping eating bread, can I please stop? I smell like Frances and my hands do too. And yes I still smell myself...  And that was the song, it sounded better last night.  Well I hope you people are mafficing. Because I sure am, well on the outside anyway. cheers big ears, same goes big nose!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow! Check out new look blogger! Its sweet!  Yeah went to parliament and magistrates court today with school, my feet hurt. But I got cool socks, so now my feet are happy. I also discovered that work has finally paid me, which is a pleasant surprise. and woo! yeah! woohoo!  Goin to smories tonight, gonna get sick too. I can feel it in my bones... well stomach. But it should still be good.  Whats yellow and a whiz at maths? A BANANA WITH A CALCULATOR!! HA HA love that sweet bad joke out of amy's joke book, ooh! ooh! another! Where do baby apes sleep? IN APRICOTS! HAHAHAHA! yeah, phew, I'm exhausted. I promise I'll blog more, maybe not as much as I used to but more than I have resently. And I'll see  YOU  tomorrow! wink-wink, nudge-nudge, hows ya father? Well I don't know if I will, but it'd be pretty special if I did.  cheers mates!  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Check out the hot mutant babaa at the bottom of the page! 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello hello hello. just got back from musical rehersal and thought i'd drop by and say "hello" three times "I'm looking for sex in the latter stages of marriage"  tehehe, yeah, I get to say that. Well i have to go and do... some stuff. adios Australian amigos! graciously they fall, but they hit the ground hard....
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yellow! blue, green, red, purple etc. running in cirlces, chasing our tails... hows youse ppl doin'? aight!  it looks as if we two will never be one... broken, window, pain. sposed to been pain not pane "I prithee, pretty youth, let me be better acquainted with thee." Is it better never to speak than to raise your voice and never be heard...? disjointed thoughts oh no, whats this? a spider web and I'm caught in the middle... where are you? what are you doing? "What have you done, you tit?" ha ha max I wonder where my watch is. Probally on my desk. Consider this, consider this, hint of the century... cheers mate Adios Another Anti-terroism Amigos
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      and I don't know what to write, all the words have gone from my head. sorry
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Pardon Sir?   "I know I'm laughing somewhere Not here I am for sure" pardon sir, but we have found that there is and will be no cure  After many years of figures and microscopes we gained knowledge, but had no success I finding why you can't experience the most joyful moments of happiness  we did try, but found no new day pardon me sir, but it is all bad news sorry for the inconvenience But we're all out of sun and only have dark blues
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Someone got in trouble with the manager today. Me :(. With out all useless words, and putting a few in, she basiclly said "Your doing a crap job at closes, do better and remember to fill in your avalibilities!" Yeah, well I was doing a crap job at closes but it doesn't mean Emily can dob me in, but I said sorry instead of saying all the stuff running through my head (e.g. "Why is it all critisim? Its getting to a point where its not very constructive."). Yeah well I really did have to apologise to Emily coz thats who I usually do do closes with, and it was a pretty rank job. oh well.  well most is okay with Frances, if anyones wondering, if anyones reading.  HI!! *wave* yeah... I'm still here...
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ahoy me hearties! I'll sing you a song a song of the sea! bird's eye fishfingers! Spidermang! Rock and roll ain't noise pollution. I want moon boots, the white ones with the blue neons that Alby owns, well that he says he owns. Moon boots, moon boots, magical, magnificent moon boots. And all these kinds of music keeps pouring out of me, cause somebody loves me, at last. Well all I'll tell, spells "ll". Loving you, is easy coz your beautiful, do-n-do-en-do-dooo YA! Everyday when you're walking down the street, everybody that you meet, has an original point of view, and I say , hey! hey, what a wonderful kind of day, we can learn to work and play, and get along with each other. What animal is the Brain meant to be in "Arthur"? A-a-r-d-v-a-r-k! And I don't want the worl dto see me, coz I don't think that they'll understand and when everythings made to be broken, I just want you to know who I am... I believe in a thing called love, just listen to the rhythm of my heart, there's a chance we could make it now, we'll be rocking 'til the sun goes down. Stripy toe socks, but they lack the purple. I stood on the end of the bridge and as he jumped into the water. He hit the water and was summerged for about 10 seconds, then exploded from the rippling water screaming. "AHHH! ITS SO COLD! YOU WON'T BELIEVE HOW...AHHH FREEZING!" He swam to the bank and clammered out and met me on the bridge, then we ran. black blue yellow green red pink purple orange white And I think thats the nonsense I've been waiting for. Thank you and good night.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm a brass band, I'm a harpsichord, I'm a clarinet. I'm the Philedelphia Orchestra, I'm the Modern Jazz Quartet. I'm the band in Macy's big parade, and wild count basie blast. I'm the bells of St Peter's in Rome, I'm tissue paper on a comb, and all these kinds of music keep pouring........ out of me coz...... someboday loves me! at LAST!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Destination unknown, as we pull in for some gas, freshly pasted poster reveals a smile from the past, elephants and acrobats, lions snakes monkey, Pele speaks "righteous", Sister Zina says "funky"  How bizarre, how bizarre, how bizarre!  I reckon its pretty bizarre. But what it has to do with dancing elephants with pink umbrellas, I don't know. Now where did those elephants go? I want their autographs.  I'm a brass band, I'm a harpsichord, I'm a clarinet! I'm the Philadelphia Orchestra I'm the modern jazz quartet!  Yeah, marching without marching is cool, and those batons! they were pretty sweet, a bit long, a bit skinny, but boy where they some nice peices of wood.   I don't have any reasons, I've left them all behind, I'm in a New York state of mind....  Yeah, Billy Joel, playing right now, I can hear it in lounge room, or kitchen, whichever its playing in. yeah. The suns not yellow, its chicken. Oh my dear Bob Dylan, where would we be without your tombstone blues? I guess I'll never know...
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I shot the sherif, but I did not shoot the deputy... WOOOOOOOOO! we lost tennis today. meh, potato, potato, tomato, tomato. Oh that so doesn't work when you write it. oh well. STATE YOUTH GAMES! OH SO GOOD SO GOOD! WOO! yeah so good, ULTIMATE FRISBEE! YUM! thats what our team name was YUM! (youth under mitcham) yummy yummy yummy I got love in my tummy and I feel like loving you. And we got cool t-shirts, they say yum on them. And we slept in tents and it was really uncomfortable, and then we sufferer from sleep depravation over the next 2-3 days. And I found out that I talk in my sleep. Supposedly I asked Jo if she wanted an apple... twice... and then said I couldn't be bothered, which was very rude of me. And did I meantion the yum t-shirts? oh yes... um... and and! the food! why we brought so much I don't know, but we did, and it was good. smelly cat, smelly cat, what are they feeding you. "Tell me Clarice, what did he say to you?"... I'm not gonna finish it coz I don't like the other half, but it was part of the ness of SYG.  OOOH! Working at 1 til close again. should go soon. have ta get changed. and then!! and then! and then! ALEX'S PARTY! WOOO! happy birthday mate!  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      STATE YOUTH GAMES! STATE YOUTH GAMES! STATE YOUTH GAMES! TOMORROW TOMORROW TOMORROW!!! ONE MORE SLEEP! WOOOOOOOO!! YEAH! Am I pumped! Its gonna be sweeeeeet! Yeah. wooh!  HA brother singing, but he's changing the lyrics, does anyone know this song?  My power, my pleasure, my pain, baby...to me you're like a growing addiction that I can't deny.. yeah. Won't you tell me is that healthy, baby? But did you know, that when it snows, my eyes become large and the light that you shine can be seen.  Well he's singing that but at the end he sings "My eyes are inlarged coz of all the carrots I ate and I can now seeee!!! IN THE DARK!" and its funny!  OOO! DINNER! PUMPKIN SOUP! WOO! 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      what's interesting about this?  and I'm also like to say , elephant juice!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      not a happy chappy, you'll get no smile out of me. Feeling quite crap at the moment, more than usual but it doesn't always some through my posts. who wants to read about someone complaining about something they don't understand? meh tomato tomarto how ever you like it, how's reading this anyway, I used to think I had an audience but I see I was wrong, so I guess theres no point of me writing here anymore.  so I'd officially like to say goodbye. I might be back, but if not, cheerio.   and did you know that when it snows my eyes become wide and the light that you shine can be seen    Light a candle, light a motive. step down, step down. watch a heel crush, crush. Uh oh, this means no, fear cavalier.     you dont need to be funnier for me, dont have to always be strong, you dont need to try to be beautiful, beauty was yours all along    You said I'm gonna buy a gun and start a war, if you can tell me something worth fighting for, oh and I'm gonna buy this place is what I said, blame it upon a rush of blood to the head    It's something sacred, something so beautiful, something quiet to ease the mind. when the pressure's taking me over and over.   ... yeah... I'm still here...  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I couldn't live&nbsp;if you would die,    don't ask me the reason why,    but I know that the world,    needs more people like you...    and its just funny how,    that no one looks at you now,    but I know that soon,    that they'll all want to be like&nbsp;you...     
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       do&nbsp;you want to show the world your scars,    that&nbsp;you got when&nbsp;you fell from the stars.   or just to tell them that it was    a mistake to come here because....   you&nbsp;miss&nbsp;your mothers,   your&nbsp;sons and daughters,   and the light that came from,    that place you called home.   but it'll be alright I guess,   I just miss you so, but all the best,   please come back soon,    coz its lonely here on the moon....    &nbsp;  yeah we all know it, come and show it, write it, in the shout box to your left. come on, write that its crap or crafty, or nice, or is red.... or something! man... I need a life.  how 'bout a banana? nah i'd rather my msn thanks... cheers to you and thanks from me, drink up my sweet the day draws near  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I don't care if the sun don't shine, I get my loving in the evening time, when I'm with my baby. Life no fun with the sun around, I get my loving when the sun goes down, when I'm with my baby. And first we... yeah I'm bored, I'm working today though, first   time in 2 months because I forgot to put in my avaliablities for the holidays. oops. meh, oh well. and i'm working tomorrow too. OHH! its orange, i made it orange, I made it orange, can you make your writing orange? or  blue?  or  pink?  or  green?    I CAN! tehehe I like this new blogger thingy.    Its soo cool right now, red it is, so hot. Kathy's party tonight, I only get to go to the last 2 hrs coz i'm working a close shift. Sweet Charity is next week too! AHHH! so close, thats scary, I have no idea whats going on. meh, she'll get over it.   well toodles from me  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was so bored today doing work expeirence that I thought I'd revamp the meaning for boredom.  original definition:  the state of being weary and restless through lack of interest    new definition to apply for today:  the state of being completely drained and "bored out of ones brain" at the thought of or the action of tedious and repedative actions (e.g. opening book, stamping book, closing book, repeat 100+ times) or through the lack of interest in these activities.  The staff were cool, and nice, but what I had to do. boy-o-boy. I might as well slept all of today. OH! but I get to help with storytime tomorrow! WOO! I hope its a Dr Suess or.. oh! I've forgotten the author of those books! oh ahh! they were so cool. oh bum. awww... losing my childhood. gotta go find it cheerio chaps!   words beyond words, of what wasn't said,  don't seem to stop, running 'round in my head.  years after years, pulling at the same loose thread,  around in circles, was the path that it lead. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      DEEPER DEEPER DEEPER!!! Oh-so awesome with its fantastic bible and exhilarating worship. Boy, it was so cool. Twas like drinking the spirit every morning, noon and night. sweet sweet that stuff is.  "Why am I so attractive?" lol yeah. the names fraces, coz people can't spell, frances. And then I'd go "Atlest put an 'n' in it please!" and they'd go "ok fracnes" and they'd laff and then I'd laff and we all laffed... with taffy. and I had 17 apples over those 5 days, and amanda had 20 coffees over those five days, but she didn't have one on friday morning coz we were all fasting for Tom to became a Christian. But he didn't know that, but he now is!! and thats awesome. yeaahh! Amanda and Tim became Christians on the camp to which is just so brilliant. 'tastic stuff mate. PUPPY DOG SLIPPERS ON MY FEET! they are soooo cute. =D OH! and I hav a penguin foam cup now, without a bottom. Well its drawn on upsidedown so really it doesn't have a top.  Well gotta go mateys! Eye-eye captian birds eye! God bless ya! 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The Raven  Cont.   But the Raven still beguiling my sad fancy into smiling,  Straight I wheeled a cushioned seat in front of bird and bust and door;  Then, upon the velvet sinking, I betook myself to linking  Fancy unto fancy, thinking what this ominous bird of yore-  What this grim, ungainly, ghastly, gaunt, and ominous bird of yore  Meant in croaking "Nevermore."   This I sat engaged in guessing, but no syllable expressing  To the fowl whose fiery eyes now burned into my bosom's core;  This and more I sat divining, with my head at ease reclining  On the cushion's velvet lining that the lamp-light gloating o'er,  But whose velvet-violet lining with the lamp-light gloating o'er,  She shall press, ah, nevermore!   Then, methought, the air grew denser, perfumed from an unseen censer  Swung by seraphim whose foot-falls tinkled on the tufted floor.  "Wretch," I cried, "thy God hath lent thee-by these angels he hath sent thee  Respite-respite and nepenthe from thy memories of Lenore;  Quaff, oh, quaff this kind nepenthe and forget this lost Lenore!"  Quoth the Raven, "Nevermore."  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yes I have run out of meaning ful things to say. Except for TOMORROW TOMORROW! DEEPER! TOMORROW! WHOOOP!!!   The Raven  Cont.   Open here I flung the shutter, when, with many a flirt and flutter, In there stepped a stately raven of the saintly days of yore. Not the least obeisance made he; not a minute stopped or stayed he; But, with mien of lord or lady, perched above my chamber door - Perched upon a bust of Pallas just above my chamber door - Perched, and sat, and nothing more.  Then this ebony bird beguiling my sad fancy into smiling, By the grave and stern decorum of the countenance it wore, `Though thy crest be shorn and shaven, thou,' I said, `art sure no craven. Ghastly grim and ancient raven wandering from the nightly shore - Tell me what thy lordly name is on the Night's Plutonian shore!' Quoth the raven, `Nevermore.'  Much I marvelled this ungainly fowl to hear discourse so plainly, Though its answer little meaning - little relevancy bore; For we cannot help agreeing that no living human being Ever yet was blessed with seeing bird above his chamber door - Bird or beast above the sculptured bust above his chamber door, With such name as `Nevermore.'  But the raven, sitting lonely on the placid bust, spoke only, That one word, as if his soul in that one word he did outpour. Nothing further then he uttered - not a feather then he fluttered - Till I scarcely more than muttered `Other friends have flown before - On the morrow will he leave me, as my hopes have flown before.' Then the bird said, `Nevermore.'  Startled at the stillness broken by reply so aptly spoken, `Doubtless,' said I, `what it utters is its only stock and store, Caught from some unhappy master whom unmerciful disaster Followed fast and followed faster till his songs one burden bore - Till the dirges of his hope that melancholy burden bore Of "Never-nevermore."' 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The Raven  Cont.   Presently my soul grew stronger; hesitating then no longer, `Sir,' said I, `or Madam, truly your forgiveness I implore; But the fact is I was napping, and so gently you came rapping, And so faintly you came tapping, tapping at my chamber door, That I scarce was sure I heard you' - here I opened wide the door; - Darkness there, and nothing more.  Deep into that darkness peering, long I stood there wondering, fearing, Doubting, dreaming dreams no mortal ever dared to dream before But the silence was unbroken, and the darkness gave no token, And the only word there spoken was the whispered word, `Lenore!' This I whispered, and an echo murmured back the word, `Lenore!' Merely this and nothing more.  Back into the chamber turning, all my soul within me burning, Soon again I heard a tapping somewhat louder than before. `Surely,' said I, `surely that is something at my window lattice; Let me see then, what thereat is, and this mystery explore - Let my heart be still a moment and this mystery explore; - 'Tis the wind and nothing more!' 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hello boys and girls,  nothing new today just thought I'd add a bit of Poe. (As in the awesome Edgar Allan Poe, and if you still don't know what I'm on about think "Nevermore!")    The Raven    Once upon a midnight dreary, while I pondered weak and weary,  Over many a quaint and curious volume of forgotten lore,  While I nodded, nearly napping, suddenly there came a tapping,  As of some one gently rapping, rapping at my chamber door.  `'Tis some visitor,' I muttered, `tapping at my chamber door -  Only this, and nothing more.'   Ah, distinctly I remember it was in the bleak December,  And each separate dying ember wrought its ghost upon the floor.  Eagerly I wished the morrow; - vainly I had sought to borrow  From my books surcease of sorrow - sorrow for the lost Lenore -  For the rare and radiant maiden whom the angels named Lenore -  Nameless here for evermore.   And the silken sad uncertain rustling of each purple curtain  Thrilled me - filled me with fantastic terrors never felt before;  So that now, to still the beating of my heart, I stood repeating  `'Tis some visitor entreating entrance at my chamber door -  Some late visitor entreating entrance at my chamber door; -  This it is, and nothing more,'    (rest will be in later posts)
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Into the sea, you and me, all these years and no one heard. I'll show you in spring, it's a treacherous thing, we missed, you hissed, the lovecats... ba-da da da da da da-da, daaa da da da da da da-da...  Heellloooooooooooooo! HyeS! HyeS! HeNO! Why do you talk like that? I had a sTROke! Woo! holidays, and guess where I've been going? TO SCHOOL! Yes it is the most awful thing to put people through while on holidays, but Ms Callow has decided that we need 6 days, 10am to 3pm, of rehersals. Its terrible, but the musical is coming along well... but thats not the point! Luckily I'm going on "deeper" next week which is gonna be so awesome! Its at Phillip Island and we're going to get all Godly and its going to be fantastic. and a bonus is that I can't get to 3 of the rehearsals. But Deeper!! Holidays aren't meant for school, teachers should understand that, why would they want to waste their holidays at school? Beats me.   We're so wonderfully, wonderfully, wonderfully, wonderfully pretty! Oh you know that I'd do anything for you.  Yeah so whats up with you people?!? I got a shout box and no ones used it except squashy and I, which is quite depressing really, thanks squashy! you're a gun. As for the rest of you who may or may not exsist, fair enough, I know I wouldn't waste my time on a crappy blogspot such as this.   Nothing could be the substitute, for the love I've found in you...
     

    
</post>


</Blog>