<Blog>


<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Fellow Logan Researchers,   This is some of the evidence that I have used to prove the children of James and Caroline Elizabeth (Hughes) Logan.  I also used the marriage records of some of the children for evidence of that relationship, but these articles, the marriage records and the pension application of James Logan are the best evidence I have found to date of the relationship of James and Caroline's children and his immigration into Kentucky.    There are some contradictions and omissions in these records and that is to be expected in genealogical research.     From History of Kentucky and Kentuckians: Biography of Daniel Boone Logan.    Daniel Boone Logan.  ----- Especially worthy of mention in a work of this character is Daniel Boone Logan, a gifted and well-known legist, now engaged in practice in Pineville, Bell county, Kentucky.  He is a native son, his birth having occurred April 23, 1858 in the country near Olive Hill, Carter county.  He comes from one of the old American families which in days gone by so securely laid the foundation of national independence.  The founder of the family on these shores was James Logan, great-grandfather of Daniel B.  He was the son of a Scotchman of the same name who emigrated from the old world about twenty years previous to the outbreak of the Revolutionary war, locating in the colony of Pennsylvania.  He found much to do in the new country besides winning a homestead from the wilderness in fighting the Indians for the Redskins at that time had not given up their claim to the state as their own hunting grounds.  He participated in the battle of Blue Licks, now in Nicholas county, Kentucky, and was severely wounded in the engagement.  Subsequently he located in that part of the state, in 1790, the section with which he was most familiar being now divided into Rowan, Fleming, Carter, Lewis and Boyd counties.  He took as his wife Caroline Elizabeth Hughes, a young woman of Keystone State stock.  They reared a family of fine sons and daughters, the sons being William, Moses, Abraham, Edward, and Tobias, the latter grandfather of Daniel Boone Logan; and the daughters were Julia, Susan, Sarah, and Elizabeth.  William Logan, the eldest son was among the early settlers on Triplett's Creek, as were called the waters of Licking River in that part of Fleming county out of which Rowan county was afterward formed.  There he resided all his life, being a well know citizen.  Moses, the second son, settled besides the head waters of  Kinnickonick Creek, a stream feeding the Ohio, in that part of Fleming county out of which Lewis county was afterward formed and there he continued to reside until his assassination by one Moses Burt about the year 1869.  He left a large family of sons and daughters, nearly all of whom are yet living within a few miles of their father's old home.  Abraham, the third son settled on what was then, and still is known as "Negro Hill," on the divide between Montgomery Creek and White Oak Creek, a tributary of Tygart's Creek in Lewis county, Kentucky, and there he lived until his death about the year 1900.  Edward, called "Ned" Logan, the fourth son, settled and lived all his life on Big White Oak Creek, near the home of his brother, "Abe" in what is now Greenup county, Kentucky.  He died about 1880.  Both left large families, who occupy the homesteads and adjacent farms.  Tobias, grandfather of the subject, was the fifth and youngest son of James Logan. He was born in 1796 at the mouth of Bull Fork  of Triplett's Creek, in what is now Rowan county and he married Polly A. Taber, daughter of Robert Taber, to their union having been born seven sons and two daughters.  They were as follows: James Fleming, father of the subject of this biographical record; Washington; Robert R.; Madison C.; Moses G.; Francis M.; Henry, Diana, who became the wife of Leander Markwell, and Elizabeth, who married Benjamin Hargett.  James Fleming Logan, father of the gentleman to who this review is dedicated, was born September 20, 1818, on Bull Fork of Triplett's Creek of Licking River, in what was then Fleming county and is now Rowan county.  He was a farmer and trader in live stock.  Like the majority of the young men of his day and generation he found it necessary to content himself with a limited education, his knowledge of teaching reading, writing and arithmetic to the "rule of 3" being gained behind a rule desk in the country school house.  In political conviction James Fleming Logan was a Whig in the earlier days and when the Civil War became a tragic reality, he enlisted as a volunteer soldier in the Union army, it being his from conviction that the integrity of the Union should be preserved at all costs.  He latterly was affiliated with the Democratic party and voted for McClellan for president in 1864 and for Seymour and Blair in 1868.  This good citizen was shot and wounded on March 17, 1869, by George (old George) and "Alf" Underwood, both horsetheives and criminals, and on Nov. 18, 1869, he died from the effect of his wounds at Rocky Ford, Tygart's Creek, in Greenup county, Kentucky.  On May 22, 1857, he married Nancy McGlone, daughter of William Owen McGlone and he and his bride located on a small farm on the Sugar Tree Fork, of Tygart's Creek, near his father home in Carter county, where Daniel B. Logan was born on the two hundred and ninety-fourth anniversary of the birth of Shakespeare.  The widow of James F. Logan, an admirable lady, now in her seventy-sixth year, resides near Morehead, in Rowan county, making her home with her son, Sebastian E. Logan.  Her grandfather, Owen McGlone, was a Scotchman, who settled in 1793 on Buffalo Fork of Tygart's Creek in what was then Fleming county and is now Carter county, Kentucky.  That pioneer citizen reared a large family of children, many of whose descendants reside on the McGlone fork of Buffalo Creek, which received its name from the founder of the McGlone family.  Daniel Boone Logan received his preliminary education in the common schools of Carter and Lewis counties, Kentucky, and later matriculated at Morehead high school in Rowan county and a Grayson Academy in Carter county.  At the latter institution he was under the tutorship of H. T. Littleton, principal.  His first adventures as a wage earner were in the capacity of a school teacher, this period extending from 1876 until 1886, and the fields of his pedagogical endeavors being Bath, Rowan and Fleming counties.  He became assistant to his former instructor in both Morehead and Grayson Academies, this service continuing from 1877 to 1880.  Subsequent to this he was principal of the Morehead high school for three years.  As has been so frequently the case, his career as an instructor was but preliminary to his career as a lawyer, for which his natural gifts and proclivities eminently fitted him.  He first prosecuted his studies under the direction of Judge Van B. Young of Mt. Sterling, Kentucky, and was admitted to the practice of the law at Morehead in August, 1886, forming a partnership in the law practice with his former patron, Mr. Young, which association continued to exist until Judge Young, was elected to the bench of the superior court of the state, an intermediate court of errors, then existing, which had been created by the legislature under the Kentucky constitution of 1849.  He removed to Bell county in 1890, and has ever since that time resided at Pinveille, where he is successfully engaged in the practice of the law.  Mr. Logan is a Democrat in his political convictions and has ever given most loyal service and support to the party, but he is not an office seeker and has never served in public capacity, with the exception of that of Master Commissioner of Rowan Circuit Court for two years.  He has various financial interest being concerned with the affairs of the Pineville Water Works, the Cumberland Heights Ice Company, the Bell National Bank or Pineville, the Elk Coal Company, the Pineville Investment Association, and the Straight Creek Mineral Company.  He is prominent in Masonry and exemplifies in his own living those ideals of moral and social  justice and brotherly love of which the order stands.  He is connected with Bell Lodge, F. A. M. No. 691; and Middleboro Chapter, No. 135, R. A. M.  He is also affiliated with Benevolent and Protective Order of Elks, No. 1041, of Middleboro, Kentucky, and with the Knights of the Maccabees of the World, Cumberland Tent No. 2, Pineville.             Mr. Logan assumed happy marital relations on January 29, 1884, when at Moorhead, Kentucky, Lizzie Evans, daughter of Benjamin and Zerilda Evans of Morehead became his bride.  Ben Evans was a Confederate Soldier and was killed in an engagement at West Liberty, Morgan county.  He was at first a captain in Humphrey Marshall's brigade, and for a time was attached to Morgan's celebrated raiders.  He was succeeded in command after his death by Thomas J. F. Hargis of Morehead, Kentucky, afterward a judge of the court of appeals.  Ben Evans, who was a son of Isaac Evans, of Cater county, Kentucky, was a millwright and trader from his boyhood until the beginning of the conflict between the states.  In 1856 he married Zerilda, daughter of Jackson Richards of Rowan county, and she survived him for many years, dying at Pineville, at the home of the subject in 1905.  At the time of her demise she was visiting her daughter, Mrs. Logan.  The union of Mr. and Mrs. Logan has been blessed by the birth of four children.  The eldest daughter, Gertrude Florence, was born April 28, 1885., at Morehead, Rowan county, Kentucky.  She was graduated in 1905, from Hamilton College, Lexington, Kentucky and in 1906 became the wife of John R. Boring, a lawyer of London, Laurel county, Kentucky.  The second daughter, Virginia May, born September 10, 1886, was graduated with her sister from Hamilton Female College, at Lexington, in June 1905, as president of the class and in the following December, married N. R. Patterson, attorney-at-law, at Owingsville, Bath county, Kentucky.  Mr. Patterson is at present residing at Pineville and is mayor of his adopted home city.  Benjamin F. Logan, born in Morehead, Kentucky, June 23, 1889, attended Lincoln Memorial University, at Cumberland Gap, Tennessee, for two years and was a student at Culver Military Academy, at Culver Indiana, during 1907 and 1908.  On June 23, 1911, he married Miss Clare Ewell, of London, Kentucky and they make their home at Pineville, Kentucky.  Daniel Boone Logan Jr. was born Oct. 6, 1896, and is the youngest of the four children.     From the Lawyers and Lawmakers of Kentucky - Published by The Lewis Publishing Company, Chicago, 1897.   	 Daniel Boone Logan, of Pineville, was born in Carter county, Kentucky, on the 23rd day of April, 1858.  By his life he has honored the name which he bears and which is so inseparably connected with the history of the state.  The family name, too, is closely interwoven with the annals of Kentucky, for the great-grandfather, James Logan, came to the wild and undeveloped region known as the "Dark and Bloody Ground" long before there was any attempt at government organization.  William Logan a native of Scotland and the first of the family to come to America settled in North Carolina, whence he removed to Kentucky, locating near Shelbyville.  James Logan was then a child.  He afterward participated in the Indian wars and was shot, scalped and left for dead at the battle of Blue Licks, but life was not extinct and many years afterward he told the tale of the cruelty and treachery of the savage.	   PS.  I have proven, with James Revolutionary War , urlLink pension application that James was from Washington Co., PA.  Also, I have never proven or disproved the ancestry of James Logan.  According to the pension application, James Logan came to Harrison Co., KY, not Shelbyville, KY.  The pension was disallowed by the Federal Government because his service was in 1792 and the Revolutionary War ended in 1782.  Henry Razor, below, was at witness to the pension application of James Logan.  See my web page for a complete viewing of the pension application. Henry Razor, b. 11 July 1771, d. 7 Feb. 1869, buried in Slaty Point Cemetery, Farmers, Rowan Co., KY.  Henry Razor's wife was Elizabeth Gantz.  He was born in Shepard's Town, PA.  

						
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Bruce E. Logan Jr.&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This is the place to begin a discussion on the research of the Logan family.  Please post your comments and suggestions to allow others to respond to them. 

						
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Daniel Boone Logan (1858 - 1919)&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>


</Blog>