<Blog>



<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Heh. Not funny, sorry. Well...yeah. Let's start figuring some of this crap out. First of all... what COULDN'T be a descendant?
     
    
</post>

<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Munthrek gixustrat wux"  It means : "Human Disembowel you." heh.... just a little laugh.....  But if you think of all this which ws mentioned before, most of which I said, actually makes sense. If you understand sciencey things. Me sleepy....  ~Trogdor~
     
    
</post>

<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      l Green Knight l: hey KooshBZP: yo l Green Knight l: whats up? KooshBZP: nuthin l Green Knight l: ah KooshBZP: got a new Magic deck l Green Knight l: which? KooshBZP: Bait and Destroy, sumthin' like that. Mirrodin Black/Blue. l Green Knight l: ah.... l Green Knight l: peh l Green Knight l: I got back from my friends house a few hours ago KooshBZP: either that or a Mirrodin White, an 8th Ed. White, or a 8th Ed. Blue KooshBZP: cool l Green Knight l: his neighbors have this ginormous tree in their field KooshBZP: I got back from a 4-day Band trip last night...at midnight KooshBZP: sweet l Green Knight l: cool KooshBZP: yeah l Green Knight l: yeah, its trunk is ....like 7 feet diameter KooshBZP: I was in Vancouver. And I saw more bums and sluts in 4 days than I have in my entire life. KooshBZP: shit l Green Knight l: yeah l Green Knight l: I climbed it KooshBZP: sweet l Green Knight l: because the tree branches hang to the groud because its so big KooshBZP: lol l Green Knight l: oh, and we were trespassing on his neighbors land, so whenever a car drove by, we had to duck in this really tall grass KooshBZP: lol l Green Knight l: but I couldn't be seen because the grass was up to my waist and I was wearing a green shirt KooshBZP: lol l Green Knight l: hang on a sec, comp is f***ing up KooshBZP: k l Green Knight l: gotta restart it KooshBZP: k l Green Knight l: k l Green Knight l: back KooshBZP: k l Green Knight l: you enter BBC 18? KooshBZP: not yet. Still working on it. KooshBZP: I just made a banner for it. The official banner. l Green Knight l: same l Green Knight l: I saw KooshBZP: likey? l Green Knight l: spiffy l Green Knight l: yes KooshBZP: thankee l Green Knight l: welcome KooshBZP: whatcha making? l Green Knight l: you play Warcraft 3? KooshBZP: played l Green Knight l: I'm making Arthas KooshBZP: cool KooshBZP: I'm making my version of Smaug. l Green Knight l: nice KooshBZP: yeah KooshBZP: he just needs back legs and a tail. l Green Knight l: I only have Arthas's leg built though KooshBZP: lol KooshBZP: when does entries end? l Green Knight l: yeah, a badass leg l Green Knight l: 15 KooshBZP: nice KooshBZP: k l Green Knight l: what are the prizes? you know yet? KooshBZP: nope l Green Knight l: ah KooshBZP: *checks the tropic for an update* KooshBZP: nothing yet KooshBZP: like my buddy icon? l Green Knight l: ooh, tropics.... l Green Knight l: yes, I do KooshBZP: Zeppelin. l Green Knight l: the Led kind,  KooshBZP: Of course. l Green Knight l: oh, need any help with dragon-ish designs? KooshBZP: I got the Stariway to Heaven poster in VAncouver. KooshBZP: Just feet. l Green Knight l: if you need help, I'm your Dragon-man KooshBZP: k l Green Knight l: I know so much about dragons KooshBZP: lol l Green Knight l: like, they have four eyelids KooshBZP: not getting THAT detailed... l Green Knight l: I figured KooshBZP: lol l Green Knight l: yeah, and I even know the NAME of the organ that allows them to breath fire, ice, acid, or whatever KooshBZP: . l Green Knight l: yeah l Green Knight l: I'm a nerd KooshBZP: yep. l Green Knight l: it's called th Draconis fundamentum KooshBZP: . l Green Knight l: I konw, I konw KooshBZP: ... l Green Knight l: I know, I know*** KooshBZP: lol l Green Knight l: plus, dragons can't really chew there food KooshBZP: ...they melt it, right? l Green Knight l: no, they grind it up in the back of their throat with little spikes KooshBZP: ... KooshBZP: why? l Green Knight l: plus, not all dragons breath fire KooshBZP: Komodo dragons. l Green Knight l: ... KooshBZP: monitor lizards. KooshBZP: really big ones. l Green Knight l: I know KooshBZP: no you don't. you just think you do. l Green Knight l: but some dragons breath ice, acid, or electricity KooshBZP: and air. l Green Knight l: shut up KooshBZP: lol KooshBZP: they DO. l Green Knight l: plus, dragons are endothermic and ectothermic KooshBZP: a dragon is a physical improbability. KooshBZP: well, flying fire-breathing ones to say the least. l Green Knight l: not entirely KooshBZP: yeah... it needs to carry whatever fluids, even in compressed liquid or even gas, and still be able to create fire and be light enough to not require wings many, MANY times bigger than itself l Green Knight l: actually, dragons are more like a bird/cat combonation l Green Knight l: their bones are light, much like a bird's, whereas its skeleton built like that of a huge, winged kitty cat KooshBZP: still, to carry the liquid fire, or even pure oxygen enough to create that damn much fire and still eb light enough to fly... l Green Knight l: well, birds can fly, cant they? l Green Knight l: and snakes can spew poison KooshBZP: yeah, but they don't carry liwuid fire in their guts, now do they? And snakes don't fly. l Green Knight l: and cats, well, they play with yarn KooshBZP: impressive. l Green Knight l: true, true, but birds and snakes once had a common ancestor, so....... KooshBZP: one that flew AND spat poison? l Green Knight l: yes. KooshBZP: which? KooshBZP: Pterodactyl? l Green Knight l: mebbe..... KooshBZP: or just all dinosaurs? l Green Knight l: all KooshBZP: yeha, I know, two different things. l Green Knight l: well, you neglect to remember that there are huge gaps still missing in the evolutionary chain KooshBZP: good point. KooshBZP: which evolutionary chain are we talking about, though?  l Green Knight l: all KooshBZP: how many could've had dragon? l Green Knight l: two or three KooshBZP: insects could eb possible... fish improbable, but still possible...lizards may have been...cats, like you mentioned...birds....crustaceans, mebbe? invertebrates? people, mebbe? l Green Knight l: well, the fish,...... some dragons are aquatic......I doubt people, but that would rock........... KooshBZP: or they could've been spread out...instead of just dragons, similar but totally different things... smaller, flying ones could've eveolved (or is it devolved?) into birds...aquatic ones, sea monsters and the like, could be fish... l Green Knight l: well, what you say makes sense, but fish were some of the first complex creatures around KooshBZP: hmmm...could have been related, then, instead of evolutianry predecessors. l Green Knight l: true.... KooshBZP: BTW, I'm gonna save a copy of this chat. Good stuff. l Green Knight l: yeah, how you save? KooshBZP: Copy and paste is the easiest way. l Green Knight l: k KooshBZP: heh...we should come up with a big evolutionary chart... not necessarily real, but plausible...and then write a story. That'd be sweet. l Green Knight l: yeah..... KooshBZP: I say we call it "Project Dragontown". l Green Knight l: yes KooshBZP: for now, of course. KooshBZP: We can't use that as a final... Dragontown's a newer Alice Cooper CD. l Green Knight l: oh, KooshBZP: but for now, tis good. l Green Knight l: yes l Green Knight l: oh, and a dragons muscles are just like a birds flight mucles....so... KooshBZP: Common ancestry? l Green Knight l: possibly KooshBZP: could link birds to most species in earth, by way of a small, subtle identicality. l Green Knight l: yes..... l Green Knight l: ooh, plus, because mammals are endothermic, and a reptile is ecto thermic, a dragon is kinda  a therapsid. KooshBZP: uh...therapsid? that's mammal/lizard, right? l Green Knight l: yeah, common ancestor of all mammals l Green Knight l: Man, Science class rocks! KooshBZP: k, just making sure. KooshBZP: heh...last thing I did in science class was talk about how the universe was made, and a bunch of intellectual stuff about that. KooshBZP: crazy. l Green Knight l: also, as with most horned animals, the horns of a dragon are part of its skeleton KooshBZP: of course. l Green Knight l: yeah KooshBZP: is it firmly attached to the skull, liek an extension of it, or another bone? l Green Knight l: but a dragon's spike are only attached by muscles to the body KooshBZP: ah, never mind. KooshBZP: oh, wait, that's spike, not horn... KooshBZP: meh., KooshBZP: you know what I mean. The question still stands... l Green Knight l: what., the horn or the spikes? KooshBZP: horn. l Green Knight l: its like part of the skull KooshBZP: like, is it an actual extension of the skull, or (minus skin, muscle, cartilage, etc.) removable, like a jaw? l Green Knight l: no, not removable, unless you TRY to cut it off l Green Knight l: which is almost impossible KooshBZP: ah. l Green Knight l: oh, and you know how Smaug died? KooshBZP: yeah, arrow through a chink in the armor. probably impossible, the skin'd be too thick for the arrow to continue through at fast enough speed... KooshBZP: it'd probably stop it after it got an inch in. KooshBZP: not skin, sorry, muscle too l Green Knight l: well, yes, but a dragons scales growback KooshBZP: they weren't scales, per se, in the book, they actually were diamond armor. Or some fancy words. KooshBZP: either or. l Green Knight l: yeah.... l Green Knight l: but dragons do have extremly thick skin KooshBZP: yeah l Green Knight l: ah, but their wings, thats another story KooshBZP: I eman, they're huge, the skin'd have to be thick.  KooshBZP: Wings are thin memberane, as always. KooshBZP: except birds, but I'm talking "flying lizards". KooshBZP: Pteranodons. l Green Knight l: yeah, but it still has scales on it l Green Knight l: yeah KooshBZP: yeah l Green Knight l: but looks at bats, the have the same wing structure KooshBZP: yeah, I remembered that a second ago. KooshBZP: another relative, that connects them to Mammalia even more. l Green Knight l: yeah l Green Knight l: I think I'll compile a book of this..... KooshBZP: or something. l Green Knight l: yeah... KooshBZP: we could use like a blog or a forum, then it'd all be in one central place, and we could share it and stuff. l Green Knight l: hmmm..... l Green Knight l: CoT? mebbe KooshBZP: I can throw either together in a few minutes. KooshBZP: CoT, no. I dun want dumb (and smart)-assn00bs going in and saying "drgaon s aernt rela!!!!!!11!!!" l Green Knight l: ok KooshBZP: Forum'd take a little while to setup...blog good? l Green Knight l: blog? KooshBZP: Weblog. l Green Knight l: oh.......uum...... l Green Knight l: i guess l Green Knight l: plus dragons have a very poor sense of touch KooshBZP: k l Green Knight l: thats why the can lay on treasure KooshBZP: yeah l Green Knight l:  to them, it feels like a nubby wool blanket KooshBZP: lol
     
    
</post>



</Blog>