<Blog>


<date>25,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So, I have gone and done it.  I seem to have truly entered the world of blogging, or at least I am pretending I have.  Maybe this will keep my thoughts somewhat straight or at least force me to track them.  Who knows?
     

    
</post>

<date>01,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So yeah, its the weekend.  I've done essentially nothing yet I'm still exhausted.  Hannah came over and we worked on our story book project, for 4 hours more or less steadily.  6 pages done woo hoo!! Anyways, before she left we got talking about all kinds of stuff, including ratemyteachers.com.  if you are ever really bored, or maybe just kind of bored check it out, there seems to be an entry on almost all of our teachers and its pretty amusing, especially when you try to match up people to comments.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Random Thought: we all waste so much time.  My cell phone bill came today and last month I spent 161 minutes on my cell phone.  That was almost 3 hours spent on conversations that lasted on average 1.2 minutes per call.  Wow, somehow the little things always add up and they shouldn't.  Little things should stay little, not grow and morph into a major deal.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Picture day today.  We all smiled pretty for the camera, to be ever immortalized in a yearbook.  It all seems so fake and unoriginal, everyone posed and proper (or improper depending on the person...), we all know that and yet it seems many go through the picture day morning ritual.  I know I did.  It seems so pointless yet still valid.  What I want to know is what I'm trying to prove by it all.  hmm....things to think about.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I have decided that I don't care about derivatives or Huck Finn or the reform groups of the 19th century.  I really don't care that there are 2 forms of the future tense in Spanish, it doesn't matter.  At some point I pretended that this nonsense was important and a good thing to spend my time on, but that has changed.  I don't know when it changed or how, but school is no longer about learning to me.  I used to relish in the academics of it all, but that disappeared.  When I say I enjoy a class I am no longer talking about the subject matter but the people and the dynamic that exists.  People have become so much more important to me as of late.  I mean, friends were important before but they were never my lifeline.  As the importance goes up, lines become fuzzy.  No one is simply a cut and dry friend it seems.  There are barriers that I see that I never saw before and that seems so odd.  Labels and determining where I stand has taken utmost importance, which makes me feel shaky about the whole thing.  Why can't things go back to the simple way they were before? Do I want them to?  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Random Thought: Balloons take up quite a bit of space and make me light headed.    Birthday pranks are so much fun, why haven't i done this before?  more explanation tomorrow, i promise!
     

    
</post>

<date>08,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Today is gonna be my day And nothing is gonna get in my way Certainly not this Certainly not this ... Now this smile has been in hiding For far, far too long You can't bottle it up I won't bottle it up ... Well I was just waiting for the sun to come up To shed a little light on the situation And why there's all this hesitation When it was so clear - The Weekend-  Victory 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I came home feeling downtrodden and slighted.  But somehow a few minutes of chatting reversed my mood and now I feel silly for being upset.  I can't explain why I got upset, it just happened.  I don't know what I was thinking going to the dance.  I don't belong there and I don't think I want to right now.  
     

    
</post>

<date>06,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I have decided that I must be wearing a sign that says "don't touch me" and is only readable by guys.  It sucks.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I sit here all dressed and ready to leave to go to the dance.  I'm not looking forward to it and am questioning my judgment.  Why do I do this time and time again, putting myself in situations I dread.  Even as I pose the question the answer forms in my head.  I do it because I care so damn much about what others think of me.  Not my close friends, the ones that matter, but all the other people out there.  I suppose I could say that it is silly and move past this but it isn't.  While I absolutely love having close friends seclusion scares me.  Last Friday I had flex day with about 35 people and I only knew one of them and a handful of names, a very small handful.  Yet I know that going tonight will not change that but some nagging voice in the back of my head is pushing me onward while the rest of me stays behind.  I guess I'll go and listen to that voice.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      " 'Rabbi,' complained a bachelor, 'I thought it is written that everyone has a basherte, a partner destined by heaven. why have i never found mine?'  "The Rabbi looked at him with his penetrating eyes and then replied, 'you did find her, but when you saw her you thought her nose too long and passed her up.' "  - from  The Commited Life  by Rebbetzin Esther Jungreis
     

    
</post>

<date>05,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      i totally just wasted lot of time but look what i learned:     My inner child is ten years old!    The adult world is pretty irrelevant to me. Whether I'm off on my bicycle (or pony) exploring, lost in a good book, or giggling with my best friend, I live in a world apart, one full of adventure and wonder and other stuff adults don't understand.    urlLink   How Old is Your Inner Child?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    I have also been informed that if i was to be in a movie it would be tarzan b/c "i am a very curious and well mannered person! Big things are always happening to mw.  i can adapt quickly to any situation and am very loyal to the ones i love"  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      You know...Normal people go to sleep when they are exhausted, but not me.  Instead I stay up and do silly things like look for lyrics to random Jewish folk songs about Russian oppression because the song is stuck in my head.  Its a gorgeous song filled with sadness and hope, set to a wonderful tune yet I can only remember 4 unrelated lines of the song and my mind is trying to play fill in the blank.  So I think I'll go to bed before I go any crazier. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Its rather depressing.  I'm a perfectionist with a short attention span.  I can spend hours on the first 95% of something and its perfect, but the last 5% I shove off and complete it haphazardly and it ruins the entire thing (sorry Hannah!).  So I had to finish that stupid apes project and it just wouldn't end.  First we had to add extra bubbles and glue everything down.  Then I had to hole punch the pages so that it could be bound. Then the pages didn't lay straight because of the foam, so I had to add foam spacers.  Then the spacers didn't look right.  Then a page was in backwards and so on.  So I threw the stupid thing in the corner and its done. This is the same scenario for everything I do.  I clean my room and everything is organized except for 15 miscellaneous items, which get thrown into a pile to deal with later, then they fall down etc. etc. I am done ranting...Sorry you had to read all that.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Why does the color of my coffee match your eyes? why do I see you when a stranger passes by? I swear I hear you in the whisper of the wind I feel you when the sun is dancing on my skin And when it's raining, you won't find me complaining because  When I think about rain, I think about singing When I think about singing it's a heavenly tune When I think about heaven, then I think about angels When I think about angels, I think about you Jamie O'neal-  When I Think About Rain 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So I officially love all of y'all, even if I haven't said it in a while.  No one else could keep me so amused while I procrastinate.  Talk of superior's and penny arcade is far superior to anything else I could have done last night.  And just to clarify if Stacy Orrico is a Christian singer the thing lacking in my life is not Jesus...At least I am 99.99% certain.  Even the rain can't bring me down.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So I did it again.  In an attempt to procrastinate I pulled up Penny Arcade's website.  Not the brightest idea because I have found myself hooked, yet again.  I can say however that I am officially caught up from August on, my great achievement of the afternoon. Some of the gaming references go over my head but I still find it quite amusing.  Now I am going to go and pretend to do some real work, though.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      My thoughts have come together and have become one tangled mess.  I stare at this post form as if I expect the words to flow from their tangled mess within my brain out onto this page... But they do not. Instead they wrap and twist upon themselves and I no longer know what is real and what is imagined.  Wishful thinking, I suspect, is slowly creeping in and taking over my brain, like kudzu on some poor unsuspecting tree. It colors every word, every action, every moment of silence and missed opportunity.  Soon, I suspect all vestiges of reality will be gone in a haze of rose.   There is no cause for this rosy tint that I can see; It came on its own provocation not on the action of another, or even an action of myself.  I suspect I'm falling and wonder how long I have until I reach the ground.  Because to put it simply I always hit the ground.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
           I've got it all, but I feel so deprived.      I go up, I come down, and I'm emptier inside.      Tell me what is this thing that I feel like I'm missing      and why can't I let it go?      Therre's gotta be more to life     than chasing down every temporary high     to satisfy me.     Cuz the more that I'm     trippin' up thinking there must be more to life.     Well it's life, but I'm sure.     There's gotta be more...     than wanting more.       I've got the time and I'm wasting it slowly      Here in this moment, I'm halfway out the door.      Onto the next thing, I'm searching      for something that's missing.      Therre's gotta be more to life     than chasing down every temporary high     to satisfy me.     Cuz the more that I'm     trippin' up thinking there must be more to life.     Well it's life, but I'm sure.       There's gotta be more...      I'm wanting more.      I'm always waiting on something other than this.      Why am I feelin' like there's something I missed? - Staccie Orrico-  More To Life    I don't really like the singer or the song but the lyrics are definitely hitting home right about now...
     

    
</post>

<date>15,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I attended a bat Mitzvah by myself.  It has been 4 years since I last did that and it felt odd.  The entire evening was one of deja vu (however you spell it).  I went through the same rituals I did when I was 12 and 13, shower hair make up etc.  I put on my favorite dress (also from when I was 13) and arranged my hair and did my makeup.  Same shoes, same purse, it was essentially the same as when I was 13. But when I went to walk out the door I caught a glimpse of my reflection in the clock and realized nothing was the same.  Where a portly girl once stood, now in her place was someone I barely recognized.  When did I grow up? It just happened.  Its funny thinking back to the days when I regularly went to Bar and Bat Mitzvahs.  I would primp for hours and when I was done would swear that it was the best I would ever look.  I thought I was gorgeous, yet when I look at the pictures now I can almost laugh at myself, gawky and done up.  I can;t help but wonder if when I look back on myself as I stand now if the same thing will happen.  I hope not because right now I'm just getting used to my reflection.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      My room is not only clean but organized, no minor feat.  I suspect that there is a link between the state of my room and the state of my mind.  When my room was destroyed I was not in control of my mind or my emotions, but now my room is organized and I feel calm and focused.  Its a shame that entropy exists, because I could get used to this.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      LOL...The  urlLink onion  did a story about a guy whose mother discovered his blog and the  urlLink blogger  came up with suggestions to avoid this.  Its quite amusing.  All I know is that I definitely do not want my parents reading this.  Its funny any stranger in the world can read my thoughts, yet if my mom or dad was to do it, I definitely would consider it invasion of privacy. Hmmm....
     

    
</post>

<date>11,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      As I drove home from class I could see the moon through my windshield, huge and almost round, quite distinctly a face.  It drew me back into the world of my childhood and car trips at night.  Ever since I was a toddler sitting still and quiet has been a problem, but for some reason watching the moon through a window has been a tranquilizer.  I remember asking my parents why the moon followed us and they just laughed it off and said that it was the curve of the earth or some logical thing like that.  Back then I didn't believe them and I still don't.  Sitting in my car with gorgeous music flowing from my speakers, I swear the moon was watching me.  Driving on the beltline at night always scares me, but I felt better with the moon watching.  It stayed positioned in the top left hand corner of my windshield as if glued to the spot the entire way. Every once and a while its nice to know that something, even if its only the man on the moon, is watching my back.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I think I prefer ignorance to knowledge.  I don't know for sure, but I think that being happy and not knowing there was more out there would be better than knowing what happiness other people have, but not having it myself.  On a similar vein as much as it kills me not to know how people (specifically one person) feel about me it is far superior than knowing that they carry a negative opinion of me.  Somehow knowledge seeks me out though, and I doubt that I will ever just be content, instead of reaching for more.  As I become closer, the desire to be even closer becomes stronger.  Instead we delude ourselves into believing we can keep something light, and become devastated when its gone.  Although I can say what I typed, I still reach for  it  and am willing to face the consequences later.  I am tired of being alone and wish for an interval of connectedness, even if it means that I have more knowledge later of what I'm missing. 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      "What is in your heart about your fellow man is most likely in his heart about you." -Sifre Deuteronomy, piska 24
     

    
</post>

<date>09,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      How did I miss the fact that so many of the bands that I listen to are Christian music? I've been misinterpreting lyrics right and left!
     

    
</post>

<date>09,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I spent my afternoon not doing the things I needed to do, but instead I spent them enjoying everything.  I settled out on the pond ledge with my boom box and my dog and literally just sat there for an hour.  The sun was glinting off the pond's surface and the fish frolicked below.  My dog too seemed entrenched in the moment.  Luck never sits still yet he lay at my feet, ears twitching in synch to the music.  It has been a long time since I have been so wrapped up in a moment of rest, and I didn't realize how I missed it so much.  We all need more beautiful days filled with nothing but beautiful thoughts.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I can't help but wonder; do all teenage minds live in the gutter, or does mine reside alone?
     

    
</post>

<date>09,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      And I can't recall myself How I went down Did I get shot  Or shoot myself  -Switchfoot   Don't Be There     I wish I had what I needed To be on my own 'Cause I feel so defeated And I'm feeling alone  And it all seems so helpless And I have no plans I'm a plane in the sunset With nowhere to land  And all I see It could never make me happy And all my sand castles Spend their time collapsing  .....  And I feel stuck Watching history repeating Yeah, who am I? Just a kid who knows [s]he's needy  Let me know that You hear me Let me know Your touch Let me know that You love me And let that be enough - Switchfoot   Let That Be Enough 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Why is it that I always want more?  Everyday it seems the bond grows stronger, yet it never seems strong enough.  On the other hand I think that I do not want things to change, that I am content, that I am happy with the ways things are.  What I really want is everything and I know I can't have that.  So I guess I need to decide which of the options I want more  than the other.  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So Kay and I spent part of the afternoon together and got along.  Well more than got along, we actually talked, it was kind of cool and really weird.  At one point in the conversation she said that she was really glad he could talk to me honestly about things.  I was taken aback for a minute, it did not occur to me that she hadn't shared anything with me in a long time, a really long time.  Although most of what she shared did not please me I, too, was glad she shared it. I guess we both grew up and grew together without even realizing it.  Hmm, I guess I have sister, again.   It's funny we have lived in the same home for the past 15 years and have clicked on and off for nearly as long, but in the last few months we seem to have been drifting closer.  I care for her input, and although I've been telling myself its because she is shallow and therefore could judge how I look in outfit x or how my hair looks, it runs deeper than that.  I care what she thinks of her big sister and in some ways look up to her for the things she does (gasp, I know).  Now the question is: what is to come?
     

    
</post>

<date>22,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Why does it seem like everyone holds onto feelings long after they should, yet I seem to let them go very easily, or at least tell myself I do? I guess I just haven't had incredibly strong feelings for anyone, because I can basically will them away when they seem to be outlandish or impossible. Something about that depresses me.     
     

    
</post>

<date>20,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So we are in starbucks this afternoon and Erica's mom comes in and sits down and talks to Frau Mensch (probably spelled wrong) and Frau Mensch says something like "how sophisticated" in relation to us.  It was rather amusing, particularly because i was sitting (sprawled actually) in a big brown chair with my feet up sipping what is essentially a glorified milkshake.  The things that amuse me when I'm tired...
     

    
</post>

<date>18,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      When we focus on abundance, our life feels abundant; when we focus on lack, our life feels lacking. It is purely a matter of focus.  --Susan Jeffers.  Today was an abundant day, full of fun and very little homework. It's really nice to be able to take time to go to starbucks with your friends and relax for an hour. The Flame got sorted and SLA stuff figured out. As previously mentioned we went to starbucks (we being Trevor, Hannah, Erica and I; Diana and Sam couldn't be bothered and Chris is STILL grounded). i came home and played High-Ho-CherryO with Torey and then avoided calc for a while. For the first time in a while my world didn't feel like it was lacking something, which was good, very good.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things you didn't do than by the ones you did. So throw off the bowlines. Sail away from the safe harbour. Catch the trade winds in your sails. Explore. Dream. - Mark Twain
     

    
</post>

<date>17,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I was talking to Hannah and how others view us came up.  at about the same time i found this thing so:  urlLink What do you really think of me? 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      "And you know, I always think that you would have been so much happier doing that play.  Even if it was just ok; even if it was great, just not the best ever.  And maybe, just maybe, it would have been the best ever.  You never know." -Judy Stein (Tovah Feldshuh) in  Kissing Jessica Stein  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Erica and I were talking on the way home about appearances, among many other topics.  It's funny, I analyze everyone, everyone that is except for those friends closest to me.  Whereas I tend to pick apart people who I do not know well, I naturally shy away from looking objectively at my friends.  So in an attempt to do something about this I began to think and what I discovered is that there is no way for me to be objective.  We have all become bound together and no way to determine where one begins and another ends (I just wish I could put this all into words better).  We seem to all have a really special group friendship, and while there are loops and circles within it we are all interwound.  It's amazing how lately even my mood seems bound to the group.  I think somehow I am afraid to analyze those around me, afraid for my perceptions of us to change, but that is a thought for another night.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I welcome feedback; even if I just tend to ignore it. - Mrs. Newmark
     

    
</post>

<date>16,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      This is really disturbing:  The group which claimed responsibility for the Turkish attacks, the Brigades of the Martyr Abu Hafz al-Masri, also claimed the attack on the United Nations headquarters in Baghdad in August, which killed 23 people.   "The remaining operations are coming, God willing, and by God, Jews around the world will regret that their ancestors even thought about occupying the land of Muslims," the statement from the Brigades group said.   "We tell the criminal Bush and his Arab and Western tails - especially Britain, Italy, Australia and Japan - that cars of death will not stop at Baghdad, Riyadh, Istanbul, Nasiriyah, Jakarta, etc, until you see them with your own eyes in the middle of the capital of this era's tyrant, America."    urlLink http://www.nzherald.co.nz/storydisplay.cfm?storyID=3534688&thesection=news&thesubsection=world 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      amusing..... F3nyx: Umm... no comment F3nyx: Except to say that Apex kicks the flaming hell out of Knightdale, but I don't want to start an argument here chitchat201: thats like saying, you are a loser, no offense chitchat201: but i'll let it slide with a glare chitchat201: that you can't see F3nyx: sounds like it should be a song quote chitchat201: lol chitchat201: it does, hmm F3nyx: write it, write it!  and then blog it!  mwahahaha 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Why does a perfectly wonderful day have to be ruined by homework?  I woke up this morning so exhausted and groggy that I could not keep my contacts in (something that has never happened to me since I got them in the 4th grade) and was certain that the day was going to be awful.  But luckily I was totally wrong, I went out to lunch with Erica and Elie, went for a walk, got a pedicure and even had dinner with my family (grandparents included).  Then it hit me I hadn't even started on my homework, so from 8:00 until now I have been working frantically trying to get it finished.  On gorgeous days homework should be excused and there is nothing you can say to sway my mind....
     

    
</post>

<date>16,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      What the hell is the matter with the world? Why do people do  urlLink this  to each other?  A little boy is being bar mitzvahed and during the service a car bomb goes off.  It should have been a time of passage into adulthood and rejoicing, not death and panic.  I hate people right now. 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I am in a perpetual state of semi consciousness.  I feel disconnected and incredibly antisocial, yet dying to do something, anything, with anyone.  It seems like no one is home when really only 2 people are gone.  If I had any energy I would be planning something for us to do, but instead I think I'll go take another nap.  I hate myself when I get like this.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      piece of wisdom stolen from an unlikely source Kisssmekay: sometimes all you wish for is someone to wish for you
     

    
</post>

<date>26,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Some things pass by without you ever noticing how strange they are until one day they hit you in the face and you wonder how you ever could have been so imperceptive.  My grandparents (the ones from NY) arrived yesterday and i saw them for the first time in 2 years, which is pretty cool, but i digress.  Tonight we invited my other set of grandparents to come to dinner so there we are, one set on one side of the table and the other across the way.   Seems perfectly normal in a family sort of way.  And it is until i begin to what my grandfathers are casually chatting about...Germane.  This too could pass as normal if you didn't know my family.  But here comes the weird part, 2 men, one conversation, totally different experiences.  My mom's dad is a catholic raised in Germany before and during WWII.  My dad's dad is a polish Jew who spent his late teens early twenties in a concentration camp in Germany.  Somehow it never occurred to me that it should be surprising that they can have a nice chat about the geography of Germany.  I look at the two of them hunched over their cups of coffee and it amazes me.  My Zayde (dad's dad) is this tiny, old, nearly deaf man huddled in his chair.  My Opa (mom's dad) is this huge booming robust guy.  It just seems so weird, and even odder that I never noticed it before.  For some reason I am incredibly protective of my Zayde, he's had such a life I guess I try to shield him, and yet he continually surprises me.  He very rarely talks about the war, which took all of his family, his childhood and most of his hearing.  When I was little he told me he doesn't speak German because its painful, yet in order to have something to talk about with my Opa he speaks of the little bits of the country he saw, and will read the German papers my Opa always brings so as not to offend him.  What was also weird is the difference between their lives now.  My mom's parents tour the world, Austria last year the Caribbean next or something like that, while the big outing for my dad's parents is going out to the grocery store not in their neighborhood.  My Bubbe and Zayde moved this week into a retirement community because they are getting to the point that they can no longer take care of themselves, yet my Opa and Grandma do meals on wheels to help the "old".  There is only a 3 year difference in age.  Yet they can come together and talk and talk for 3 hours straight.  Life is one of those oddities that seems incredibly hopeful, as seen by two people with so many reasons to be at odds having a nice little chat, and so unfair, as one having a happy active life and the other aging and living with immense guilt for having the opportunity to age.  Sometimes i wish it was more fair, but everything would be so different, I guess somwhere there is a master plan, but.... 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      The game was lots of fun, in spite of (or maybe because of) the distinct lack of close friends.  i ended out hanging with a bunch of seniors and we catcalled the other team.  Very amusing. Its times like that that i realize that we as a group are very sheltered. At lunch and after school there are 7 of us and its like the rest don't exist, except for the occasional hangers on.  Every once in a while i think i remember that they are there but its weird.  With that terribly strange thought i say good night....  Good Night
     

    
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Right now I hate someone, maybe I hate everyone, I don't know.  I came home in a wonderful mood, filled with me singing along (off key and on the top of my lungs, of course) to fun, fast paced music. I get the mail and theres this big packet for me.  Turns out one of our teachers reccomended me for the National Student Leadership Conference.  it essentially is a grouping of small workshops that you can attend.  some of them look really cool, but i digress.  it was really cool being reccomended for something.  typically it seems that i never get noticed, i do things and they slip under the radar.  so i'm all happy and i go find my dad to tell him about it.  He cuts me off midstream with a line like "why don't you do something usefulnow and maybe we can talk later?"  granted the house did need cleaning and my mom deserted but it really pissed me off.  why is it that my news is secondary to cleaning the house for my grandparents?  so right now i feel like i hate my parents as well as my grandparents.  if we could have had thanksgiving there i wouldn't have had to spend my week cleaning and my parents would not be quite so bitchy. this rant is done...sorry had to get it out of my system.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      It's amazing what you can learn from little kids.  My class was pure hell today, with good kids behaving badly.  There was tackling and, in a separate incident, somehow a kid accidentally got punched in his face while my back was turned.  As the kid put it "he was reaching for my kappa and his  fist  accidentally hit my eye", not his hand his fist.  It's shocking what we do to each other "accidentally" when we forget to pay attention.  Although its been a long time since I've physically hit anything except inanimate objects, I can't help but wonder how many people I've figuratively hit, just by not doing my share of something or ranting about them.   I guess I just need to watch myself more carefully, because that way even if I do screw up (which I will inevitably do) I can at least have some idea of what happened instead of having my back turned to the situation. 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So...I went shopping today.  I think we spent more this afternoon than I have spent in the past six months (which is quite a lot).  Mom and Kay convinced me to buy a gorgeous dress for a dance that is months away and I don't even know if I want to go.  The dress is on its hanger, sitting in my closet facing me.  I liked it better when dresses were loose and bright and flowery, and worn ragged.  Instead this is long and black and strapless and very very intimidating.  With every day that passes I want to be an adult less and less, yet every day i look more and more like one.  There was a time when I would have happily given up every one of my possessions to be an adult.  I would listen to my parents' music, borrow my mom's clothes, sit with the adults at parties and essentially do everything i could to be a mini adult.  Yet now that I'm old enough to sit with the grown ups all i want to do is sit at the kids table...Isn't life ironic?
     

    
</post>

<date>05,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Mrs. Nelson made us do a really stupid lab that required us traipsing through a graveyard recording how old people were when they died...I didn't do it.  Instead Hannah and I walked through looking at the stones wondering what stories had been buried there.  there were grave of children buried beside their parents, others of soldiers who came back from war in a box.  And all Mrs. Nelson wanted us to do was put a little hash mark in a box if their life coincided with a year.    Its really depressing to look upon these graves just abandoned with no one left to care for them.  The stone have outlast the legacy left in the people.  Stones covered in moss, buried in lichen.  And yet while i am upset that someone left them to slowly weather away I also know that when G-d forbid something happens to my Opa and my Grandma there will be nobody there to keep up their stones.  We are 12 hours away and you can't expect my grandmother's nieces or nephews to, they can't even keep their own lives straight.  Eventually we will all fall into decay, all be forgotten.  And although this is depressing there is a semi silver lining.  It means that with every story that is forgotten, every stupid thing you do will be erased too.  Realistically a stupid move made now won't matter in 20 years or probably even in 1 year.  As Mr. felder put it: if you don't look back on yourself a few years down the road and say "that was really stupid" you aren't taking enough risks.  Right now i can say with certainty I am not taking enough risks.  I think that'll be this year's resolution, take more risks!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Its hard to be happy for others when you pity yourself...
     

    
</post>

<date>03,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Aragorn: What do you fear, milady?  Eowyn: A cage. To stay behind bars until use and old age accept them and all chance of valor has gone beyond recall or desire.  -Lord of the Rings: Two Towers
     

    
</post>

<date>03,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Cold weather makes me wish for a warm body to share it with...  Ex-day with Mr. Felder brought out a lot, although about half of it followed along the lines of the above statement.  The other half though was about camp and middle school and how i let friendships fail by saying I'll call tomorrow, or we can talk later.  It's scary how easily let people drift away to the recesses of my mind.  It is especially scary when i fast forward to two years from now.  I'll be in college and what will be of my friends now?  Will there still be impromptu gatherings in starbucks like the one we had today? Almost definitely Not...Will i even know them as who they are and who they used to be? I hope so... But I always say that I'll keep in touch. I have all of the numbers of the CILTs from my session but have i used them, no.  I told myself I'd keep up with the Gan Izzy counselors but that didn't happen, i don't even know what country most of them are living in now.  So how can i guarantee that I'll keep up with friends now?  This is depressing me... I wish I had some way of comforting myself.  Another thing that surprised me was what I didn't write about.  The prompt was "I remember..." but in all my writings I did not write about huddling on top of Mr. Meyers's car, I didn't write about filling Diana's car with balloons, I didn't write about our freshmen year water fights in the parking lot or taking over that tiny table at Armadillo and getting 6 refills of chips.  Neither did I write about celebrating Christmas with my Opa or Hanukkah with my Zayde, I didn't write about almost not making it across the border back into the US from Canada because my Aunt was joking around when the border guard was questioning us, I didn't write about all of the vacations my parents took me on, nor the fights I've had with them parents, and I didn't write about visiting my relatives in the hospital or losing my Aunt.  Instead I wrote about battle of the books and not having friends in 5th grade because I put all my eggs in one basket. I wrote about being glued to the spot on the dock when I first tried drill, and about how I walked my midnight run without being scared. I wrote about playing in the snow with Torey and dancing in the rain when I was her age.  Its odd that the stuff I hold dearest to me now did not go onto the page, yet it was all I could think of after getting the rest written down on paper. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I hate it when people read too much into your words.  Particularly when it's prying parents.  just thought I'd share.  on another note, cars are happy inventions and even better hang out spots....
     

    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I have been informed that i can't not look guilty when I've done something, particularly something juvenile.  Hmm...is this a bad thing?  i can think of situations where looking guilty would be bad, but maybe the fact that i know i can't hide my guilt will hinder me from doing things that i don't want to be caught at.  I think thats why up until lately I've always been comfortable in the little box my parents worked to create for me.  i knew that I if I broke the rules I would get caught and didn't want to lead to my own demise.  Now part of me wants to get away with things, but I still know I won't.  My box seems to be shrinking rapidly and hte once comfortable boundaries are closing in on me.  Hmm...better start working on that face.  
     

    
</post>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Everyone in the world seemed talkative today, except myself.  I was in one of those odd little moods that appear and pull me back from the center.  I ignored this odd feeling most of the day, but found it cropping up this afternoon at work.  for once I was content to sit back and watch the game unfold, instead of trying to stop it.  The class was loud and everyone shouting, yet I was sitting there with a grin on my face, not doing anything.  After work I went and met this new family i'm babysitting for on saturday, they were cool and by then I was back to being myself.  I don't know what's up with these weird antisocial lazy moods, but they need to go away.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Warning: below is a rant...Proceed with caution  I HATE portraits.  They are incredibly fake and the worst part of the holidays.  Every year around this time my mom gets the idea that what she really needs is a portrait of "her two beautiful daughters".  The entire thing is a load of shit, especially since she doesn't want her daughters looking their normal beautiful, instead she wants us primped and curled and dressed up.  This year she was going to let us go casual, so I had on this brand new sweater that she convinced me to buy last week.  I come downstairs and she's like, you can't wear that you look so pretty in the Burgundy (never mind that Kayla is wearing pastel pink and we would look awful standing together).  So I change into another sweater that I like, but my dad determined that to be too casual and demanded we wear dresses.  Then after I had changed he rescinded his comment, but my mom was busy picking out something else, which happened to be a shirt that i hate, but haven't thrown out.  Then it was announced we weren't going and I was banished to my room.  I happily went, but Kay came to bother me and I slammed the door in her face. This pissed off my already pissed dad who has decided that grounding me for 3 weeks is a good idea...So guess what, I'm grounded through exam week.  So much for getting to see all my friends from camp on the 13th. Oh, and I still get to sit for pictures. 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm exhausted and about to crash any moment, but I wanted to say that, happily, my predictions from before turned out to be wrong.  I had fun at Kanata and now am really looking forward to the summer.  Its amazing all of the memories that the mind can store away and then retrieve when called upon.  The only thing that sucked was having to leave.  Its nice to have a happy ending to a really wierd day, that doesn't happen very often.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Eerily similar to a month ago, i sit in front of my computer worrying about the evening ahead of me.  I really should be leaving to go up to Kanata but instead I'm sitting here stressing about events that haven't happened.  I've changed so much since the start of the summer and i am sure they have too, yet we will all go tonight and pretend to be the people we once were or just stare blankly at each other thinking of all of our memories.    It all reminds me of a quote from Gatsby, "there must have been moments even that afternoon when Daisy tumbled short of his dreams--not through her own fault but because of the colossal vitality of his illusion.  It had gone beyond her, beyond everything.  He had thrown himself into it with a creative passion, adding to it all the time, decking it out with every bright feather that drifted his way.  No amount of freshness or fire can challenge what a man will store up in his ghostly heart."  I recently found an old roll of film from freshmen year that had not been developed.  i got back the pictures today and realized that while i recognize us we are totally different.  They are mainly pictures from English class, some project or another, and consist of Erica, Trevor, Chris, Diana, Kit and me.  Kit is in nearly every shot, but in newer rolls seems to have disappeared.  Suspiciously lacking are Sam and Hannah, but they didn't have English with us.  Time is slipping away from me...I'll reminisce later.  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Taking a study break (even though i only started 15 minutes ago) to say that my window is fixed and Rich is officially my favorite person of the day!
     

    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      As the moon rose higher the inessential houses began to melt away until gradually I became aware of the old island here that flowered once for Dutch sailors' eyes--a fresh, green breast of the new world.  Its vanished trees, the trees that had made way for Gatsby's house, had once pandered in whispers to the last and greatest of all human dreams; for a transitory enchanted moment man must have held his breath in the presence of this continent, compelled into an aesthetic contemplation he neither understood nor desired, face to face for the last time in history with something to commensurate to his capacity for wonder.  And as I sat there, brooding on the old unknown world, i thought of Gatsby's wonder when he first picked out the green light at the end of Daisy's dock.  He had come a long was to this blue lawn and his dream must have seemed so close he could hardly fail to grasp it.  He did not know that it was already behind him, somewhere back in that vast obscurity beyond the city, where the dark fields of the republic rolled on under the night.  Gatsby believed in the green light, the orgiastic future that year by year recedes before us.  It eluded us then, but that's no matter--tomorrow we will run faster, stretch out our arms further...And one fine morning----  So we beat on, boats against the current borne back ceaselessly into the past -  The Great Gatsby  F. Scott Fitzgerald  This is the last page of the most insightful books I have ever read and it ceaselessly draws my mind back to it.  Just because we will never reach what we are reaching for is no reason to give up.  I will never achieve the "American dream" I will never be satisfied, but I don't think I want to be.  I want to always have something that drives to run faster, to reach further forward.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      so they might be kind of sacreligious but these lyrics make me happy:  ...You take what you get and you get what you give I say don't run from yourself, man, that's no way to live I've got a record in my bag you should give it a spin Lift your hands in the air so that life can begin  If God Is a DJ... If God If God is a DJ (life is a dance floor) Get your ass on the dance floor  If God is a DJ Life is a dance floor Love is the rhythm You are the music If God is a DJ Life is a dance floor You get what you're given It's all how you use it - If G-d is a DJ  Pink
     

    
</post>

<date>08,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Got this in an email and it struck home...  "You might be best friends one year,  pretty good friends the next year,  don't talk that often the next year,  and don't want to talk at all the year after that.   So, I just wanted to say,  even if I never talk to you again in my life,  you are special to me and you have made a difference in my life,  I look up to you, respect you, and truly cherish you."  
     

    
</post>

<date>08,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm back under control, i'm offically caught back up and almost done with english.  It feels great to be once again in control of my life.  I was watching it fly away from beneath my feet and was just about to crash when today intervened.  I did my history, my apes labs, called exploris, typed 4 pages of my english...all thats left is that damn color chart.  I hate being out of control and it always simply spirals into further decay.  Entropy is the worst law that ever existed...why can't things be propelled into order, not disorder?      
     

    
</post>

<date>08,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Why is it that faced with a choice I make it incredibly complicated? I have two options one I know the probable outcome and the other I can guess it.  Most likely I would enjoy option A much much more than option B, but the unknown calls me.  I love the shelter of my box, but at times it seems to imprison me.  Why does it seem that I always must choose which side of the wall to be on? There should be some way for me to have both, yet I know that there isn't.  I think I'm making this bigger than it has to be.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I hate disposable cameras...they just don't take good shots.  First it was my Kanata pictures and now it's the pictures I took for yearbook.  I promised Jenny that I'd bring her pictures for the portrait pages and spent $10 getting two roles developed in one hour.  only 2 of the pictures are decent and the rest is essentially trash.  I can't wait for my b-day because I know I'm getting a digital camera.  In fact I can have it tonight if I want it, but that means nothing to be opened on my birthday.  Can I wait 3 weeks?  Oh and who ever took the pictures of our massive huddle did a crappy job of setting up the shots (which did develop properly).... 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Not much to report, really.  Took the SATs and saw all kinds of people that i knew at one point.  No one recognized me, in a way it was depressing, but it was also amusing.  I came upon Rachel and said hello and it took her a minute to process.  It's really sad that connections with the people who were my best friends in 8th grade have gotten to this point.  What was also funny is that out of the blue Betsy imed me today.  Maybe its the universe telling me that it is possible to reconnect those old ties.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Went and saw brother bear with Torey Sam and Roo.  It was really good in the whole disney-kids-movie-meant-for-adults way.  At one point the bear who used to be a human tells a bear cub that his brother was killed by a monster (when it was a bear, sort of) and then later in the movie the cub says that the monsters were really scary, especially when they carried sticks.  It was really sad.  Anyway it got me to thinking, and it all comes back to a quote...We do not see things as they are. We see things as we are. -- Anais Nin...What all have I missed?   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was a happy day...End of Exams, Return of the King and Hanukkah!   Its funny of all the things to get excited about, the best gift I received didn't even come to me.  Today my grandfather got new hearing aids and for the first time in my lifetime I didn't need to shout to be heard.  Its odd, it has become a habit to raise my voice when he is in the room, more often than not the only way he knows that a conversation at the table is occurring is by the fact that our lips move, but tonight he could listen to me and recognize that Lucky was barking in the garage. Sweaters and jewelry are nice, but they just don't really compare, especially in light of recent news/speculation...But I don't feel like downing my mood so I'll possibly go into that later.  Happy Holidays!  
     

    
</post>

<date>17,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Diseases suck, not normal illnesses but real diseases....why do they always prey on those you care about?
     

    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Remember when the days were long And rolled beneath a deep blue sky Didn't have a care in the world With mommy and daddy standing by When "happily ever after" fails And we've been poisoned by these fairy tales The lawyers dwell on small details Since daddy had to fly But I know a place where we can go That's still untouched by man We'll sit and watch the clouds roll by And the tall grass wave in the wind You can lay your head back on the ground And let your hair fall all around me Offer up your best defense But this is the end This is the end of the innocence O' beautiful, for spacious skies But now those skies are threatening They're beating plowshares into swords For this tired old man that we elected king Armchair warriors often fail And we've been poisoned by these fairy tales The lawyers clean up all details Since daddy had to lie But I know a place where we can go And wash away this sin We'll sit and watch the clouds roll by And the tall grass wave in the wind Just lay your head back on the ground And let your hair spill all around me Offer up your best defense But this is the end This is the end of the innocence Who knows how long this will last Now we've come so far, so fast But, somewhere back there in the dust That same small town in each of us I need to remember this So baby give me just one kiss And let me take a long last look Before we say good bye Just lay your head back on the ground And let your hair fall all around me Offer up your best defense But this is the end This is the end of the innocence - End of  the Innocence  Don Henley  At one point I was certain I understood this song.  I was probably about 13 and decided that I was grown up, I knew everything, understood everything and there was no wonder left in the world.  I had conquered it all and anybody who questioned was just wrong.  Somwhere along the way my perception changed and i now realize that I'm further than ever from knowing the end of innocence.  I'm no longer certain, no longer wonderless and I think I like that. 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Exams hit like a hammer to my vertebrae...Well maybe that's a bit extreme...I definitely feel as if I didn't prep enough at all.  But now that the hard ones are done I don't want to deal with the rest, so maybe I won't.  I definitely have put off studying tonight and its already 6:30.  Lunch was great, as we left Kay turns to me and asks "can your friends not go anywhere without attracting attention?"  What she doesn't realize is that its the attention that makes it fun, well not the attention but the acts that cause everyone to look.  Lunch was Sam, Diana, Hannah, Graham, Jeff, Erica, Trevor, Rini, Chris, Kayla and me (wow that list was longer than i anticipated, lots of hangers on) around two round tables squished together, each meant to hold no more than 4 a piece.   Wow... We are officially halfway through our 3rd year of school.  That really scares me, it seems just recently that most of us sat in English class as strangers.  First impressions were so odd between us and to an outsider i do imagine their impressions of our group would still be odd.  Now, though, things are just natural and that's awesome, I find that I've been checking my thoughts and actions less frequently.  Somehow over the past 2 1/2 years we all grew close, but lately while we are close we seem to be headed in different directions.  While I stop thinking about the way I act I do stupid things that I regret, which then makes me draw back.  Its an odd feeling, when you find yourself bound tighter and let loose all at once, and yet it seems to be popping up more and more frequently in my mind.  The cycle spins about me and makes me dizzy, a dizziness I love.   Reading over the above paragraph I realize that it ended up somewhere totally different than intended, but is still good.  Kind of like the group, hmm.... 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I accomplished nothing today but semi-organizing pictures.  I started creating flow charts of american history but only got throught 1789-1808 in and hour and a half.  Why is it that we spend all of this time locked indoors relearning what we already should know, instead of doing something useful...or if that is too much to ask... something enjoyable.  I do not know a single person who gains anything but an artificial number written on copy paper from cramming, except maybe a headache.  Instead of having a week of midterms we should have some sort of all encompassing project or activity that could somehow demonstrate our knowledge without forcing us to sit in a room and silently take a 2 hour test on 4 months of material.  But what do I know...I'm just the person who has to take the test, surely my opinion means nothing.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      How can we know how far The long way can be Looking from where we are It never seemed that long to me I've many miles behind me Maybe not so much ahead Seems I made good time With the directions I misread  I'm gonna spend my time Like it's going out of style I'm moving the bottom line Farther than a country mile I still have hills to climb Before I hit that wall No matter how much time I buy I can never spend it all  Funny thing that time We're always running out I'm always losing mine There's not enough of it about And though it's always here It will always come and go The days become the years That'll be gone before you know  So I'm gonna spend my time Like it's going out of style I'm moving the bottom line Better than a country mile I still have hills to climb Before I hit that wall  I won't go quietly into that dark night There'll be no more burning daylight I'll be living in Every moment that I'm in  I'm gonna spend my time Like it's going out of style I'll only use what's mine I've been saving for a while I still have hills to climb Before I hit that wall No matter how much time I buy I can never spend it all No matter how much time we buy We can never spend it all - Spend My Time  Clint Black  Somehow it seems that no matter how hard I try to out run reality it always manages to catch up to me.  Lately there have been so many reminders that life does not go on forever and I can no longer hide from them.  The recent death of Angela Stapelton and what should have been Dukie's 18th borthday have finally gotten into my thick skull where they are gathering and brooding.  In time both events along with countless other heart wrenching tales will be swept away and forgotten, just a single stone marker, somewhere, left behind.  Kanata is dedicating a building to Dukie, but over time it will be like the picture that hangs in the lodge, something to remember a kid that no one truly remembers.  We all do stupid things, why is it that only some of us die for them.  And what of the innocent, who did nothing, but still are gone?  I hate thinking of dark things, and instead choose to tell myself that there is some logic to all of this, but i cannot fathom what it might be.  Why is it that so many happy, good people are gone while the world is filled with bitter people filled with hate?  why is it that we can capture tyrants alive and unscathed, yet children die just because they rode the bus to school? I'm angry right now but i don't know what at.  Surely it cannot be G-d, because that is where my hope resides; so maybe its people, even though i believe that they are innately good.  I don't know who to blame and that bothers me greatly.  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So...I have a chatterbox now, don't know how long I'm going to keep it but...
     

    
</post>

<date>26,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      What to say, what not to say, that is the question.  I look at my sitemeter and see that 11 people have read my blog so far today and that that is the smallest number of people for the week (wow...11 people reading my blog in one day?) and I can probably guess who a few of them are but the rest....It makes it hard to say anything substantial.  But I will say this, people are really good at forcing me to be honest to myself.  I've been in denial over the meaning of this mood of mine for weeks and one short conversation forced me to face reality.  I know what this mood is, and I'm sure most people close to me could guess it.  not knowing what else to say without feeling pathetic I'll stop and of you are left wondering maybe (probably) at some point I'll enlighten you if you ask. 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I made a playlist of good sulky songs to go along with this evil mood and somehow this slips into the mix without my noticing...  Another day has almost come and gone Canat imagine what else could wrong Sometimes I'd like to hide away somewhere and lock the door A single battle lost but not the war (because)  Tomorrow is another day And I am thirsty anyway So bring on the rain  Itas almost like the hard times circle around A couple drops and they all start coming down Yeah, I might feel defeated, I might hang my head I might be barely breathing - but I am not dead  Tomorrow is another day And I am thirsty anyway So bring on the rain  I am not gonna let it get me down I am not gonna cry And I am not gonna lose any sleep tonight   Tomorrow is another day And I am thirsty anyway So bring on the rain - Bring on the Rain  Jo Dee Messina  Bring on the rain! 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      My frequent weird mood has once again decided to grace my mind with its presence.  I'm very close to grasping it, I can almost feel it. Yet still it eludes me to haunt my thoughts and actions, at least on this night.  The are no words to set it to, no way to express this sense of lost chances and emptiness.  It builds and builds and then suddenly seems to be banished from my thoughts.  It never goes far though, always waiting for a quiet calm moment to strike.  In an attempt to pretend it doesn't exist I move onto lighter subjects.  I have decided not to sleep tonight and instead to clean my room.  With exams and my natural tendency towards disorder it has turned to chaos and treachery.  I had nightmares last night of natural disasters and trying to escape through the piles of clutter.  They reached out from their clumps and latched onto me dragging me to the floor to succumb to whatever disaster was upon us.  Yet when I awoke this morning I chose to ignore the mess, as I have for the past 2 weeks, and it still exists.  Hence the need to clean...That and maybe I can work off this mood.  At the very least it's worth the work. 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Elena home all day, every day + big box of chocolate = uh oh!
     

    
</post>

<date>24,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Time has this magic way of slipping past you.  Monday I'll be 17 and it seems like there was so much I wanted to do during my 16th year.  It truly has been the best year of my life, mainly because of the freedom of a car and license.  I've been able to do so much more out and about with the car and for that I'm grateful.  This past year has also been one of great stresses and scares. Unfortunately some of my goals for the year didn't happen and I hope that they will soon.  So many thoughts and no way to express them.  When I was little I couldn't wait to be 16.  Sleeping beauty found true love, and i believe Cinderella too, at 16.  All of the cool kids on TV were 16 and they were all so happy.... Unfortunately the clock striking on my 16th birthday did not turn me into a maiden with long flowing blonde hair free to roam the woods and discovering I was a princess.  Neither did it bring along my prince charming.  What it did bring were new experiences and even better friends.  No matter how bleak I may seem at times I am grateful for such things and have loved this past year.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      so the image below is being evil but definitely worth seeing, go to the  urlLink Nov 10 strip 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       
     

    
</post>

<date>22,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Tonight was great, filled witha really bad movie and shallow conversation.  I honestly can't remember having that much fun or laughing that hard in quite some time.  One topic of much contention was well, umm...sex idols (yes you read that right!).  Unfortunately we girls couldn't pick one, even though Trevor picked his.  Sometimes you just need a night of shallowness and laughter.    
     

    
</post>

<date>22,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      My break just went down the tube...My parents took off most of the next two weeks and my cousins are flying in.  Don't get me wrong I love my family, but can I not have one fucking break to do my own thing.  Last break was thanksgiving and we all know what a blast that was.  So if anyone wants to rescue me to say, oh i don't know, go on a cross country road trip or something of the sort let me know.  My bags are already packed and by the door.  Sorry for swearing... 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I just realized that all of my parents' music isn't bad....scary  You belong among the wildflowers You belong in a boat out at sea Sail away, kill off the hours You belong somewhere you feel free  Run away, find you a lover Go away somewhere all bright and new I have seen no other Who compares with you  You belong among the wildflowers You belong in a boat out at sea You belong with your love on your arm You belong somewhere you feel free  Run away, go find a lover Run away, let your heart be your guide You deserve the deepest of cover You belong in that home by and by  You belong among the wildflowers You belong somewhere close to me Far away from your trouble and worry You belong somewhere you feel free You belong somewhere you feel free - Wildflowers  Tom Petty and the Heartbreakers    Well I won't back down, no I won't back down You could stand me up at the gates of hell But I won't back down  Gonna stand my ground, won't be turned around And I'll keep this world from draggin' me down Gonna stand my ground and I won't back down  Chorus Hey baby, there ain't no easy way out Hey I will stand my ground And I won't back down  Well I know what's right, I got just one life In a world that keeps on pushin' me around But I'll stand my ground and I won't back down  Hey baby there ain't no easy way out Hey I will stand my ground And I won't back down No, I won't back down  - Won't Back Down  Tom Petty  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow...late night blogging doesn't seem like a good plan, I tend to see things worse when I'm tired.  My dad has decided to mess with our network so now I can't be on after 11 during the week and 1 on the weekends...maybe that'll help. 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I realized that somewhere deep within the recesses of my mind there is a dam, holding in many things.  It seems as if somehow, very recently (tonight possibly) I cracked that dam and slowly but surely the crack is widening.  I certainly made myself miserable for no reason tonight, I was sitting laughing with my friends watching an entertaining movie and then...well i don't know what happened.  It would be nice to unravel this web, although I have no idea where it will lead, although most certainly into unchartered territory.    Riding home from Diana's the song Absolutely by 9 Days played over and over again in my head, coming from some dark recess of my brain that stores all of my middle school memories.  I look back in those days and see unhappiness, even though I know that there were days when my life seemed so happy.  I think I'll end this now and probably delete it in the morning...    This is the story of a girl Who cried a river and drowned the whole world And while she looks so sad in photographs I absolutely love her When she smiles  How many days in a year? She woke up with hope but she only found tears And I can be so insincere Making the promises never for real As long as she stands there waiting Wearin the holes in the soles of her shoes How many days disappear? You look in the mirror, so how do you choose?  Your clothes never wear as well the next day And your hair never falls in quite the same way You never seem to run out of things to say  This is the story of a girl Who cried a river and drowned the whole world And while she looks so sad in photographs I absolutely love her When she smiles  How many lovers would stay? Just to put up with this shit day after day How did we wind up this way? Watchin our mouths for the words that we say As long as we stand here waitin Wearin the clothes of the souls that we choose How do we get there today? When were walkin too far for the price of our shoes  Your clothes never wear as well the next day And your hair never falls in quite the same way You never seem to run out of things to say  This is the story of a girl Who cried a river and drowned the whole world And while she looks so sad in photographs I absolutely love her When she smiles  And your clothes never wear as well the next day And your hair never falls in quite the same way You never seem to run out of things to say  This is the story of a girl Who cried a river and drowned the whole world And while she looks so sad in photographs I absolutely love her  This is the story of a girl Whose pretty face she hid from the world And while she looks so sad and lonely there I absolutely love her When she smiles -  Absolutely , Nine Days
     

    
</post>

<date>03,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just wanted to boast to all of you poor Ms. Klein APUSHers my hmwk for the break is merely 14 pages of reading and 4 questions!
     

    
</post>

<date>30,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I took all of my frustration and sadness out on an essay that with time, and less raw emotion, might be worth submitting for a contest that peaked my interest. The Holocaust Remembrance Project Essay Contest asks for essays under 1200 words that address the holocaust and specifically why it is important to remember and what students can do.  It seemed worth trying to do.    Of course my essay is currently too emotional and begins with  "Six Million.  The number is impenetrable, I will never have six million of anything worthwhile in my possession, and nothing is as worthwhile as a human life.  Whenever the Holocaust is brought up that meaningless number is thrown out to try to evoke emotion and response, and instead shuts people down.  Looking at countless faces, countless stories just causes them to blend and fade into one tragedy, making them easy to shove aside and forget.    Forgetting the holocaust is something I will never have to deal with, because for me there are not countless faces, there is one.  That is the face of my grandfather, my zayde.  He is 76 and he is dying.  With him will die his story and his family, because out of his entire family he is the sole survivor"  and: "Only recently have I become to even slightly begun to perceive what life must have been like for him all those years ago.  Ironically the cancer that is killing him is slowly starving him, taking away all of his nourishment as it grows.  Every day he becomes more and more confined, trapped within the few rooms of the apartment he shares with my grandmother.  Eventually he will probably lose it all, all control, all support, all mental capability.  He is once again under the reign of terror of an awful dictator."  Now that I've written it though, i don't want to change it, don't want anyone to criticize it, don't want it to be read by my family.  I am more willing to let complete strangers know what I feel than my immediate family.  I get angry when my sister reads my blog, yet when I find out that some random person has looked at it, it doesn't bother me.  
     

    
</post>

<date>30,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      A Wreck.  That's how Erica described me the other night.  I just nodded and made a non-commital grunt, refusing to see myself as one.  I may be a mess, but I couldn't be a wreck.  If I am a wreck now, what will I be a week from now, a month, tomorrow.  What will I be when I have to say kaddish or yartzeit, what will I be then.  But in reality I think I have become a wreck.  I have spent the last few days looking for a fight, a fight within me just dying to be let out.  Bits of it escape from time to time, always aimed at the wrong person the wrong issue.  Eventually I will explode and I will no longer be a wreck, I will be nothing.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So because I won't be home tommorrow night I"ll make my new year's resolutions tonight: 1.  Spend more time with the ones I love 2.  Do more things for the sake of making me happy 3.  Actually start swimming regularly
     

    
</post>

<date>29,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Decided to pretend today was my birthday instead of yesterday, ie today was actually a good day.  Zayde got to go home today after a procedure that made him much better.  He will probably never be well, but at least he isn't struggling to breathe and move in some hospital bed.  I got to watch my dad yell at my uncle who was really, really pissing me off.  Then we went to dinner, my choice, but the cheescake factory line was ridiculous so we went out tonight and will again on Friday.  And... I get to drive the Mustang all day tomorrow.  Life looks a little bit better today.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      "There en't been nothing good more than about five minutes ahead.  Like I can see now, this bath's nice and there a nice warm towel there, about five minutes away.  And once I'm dry, maybe I'll think of summing nice to eat, but no further ahead than that.  And when I've eaten, maybe I'll look forward to a kip in a comfortable bed.  But after that, I dunno, Lyra.  There's been terrible things we seen, en't there? And more coming, more'n likely.  So I think I'd rather not know what's in the future." - The Golden Compass  Phillip Pullman  Can't sleep.  Tried to, but can't stop thinking.  I was given a precious gift and wasted it.  We got an extra year, a really good one, but that is all probably coming to an end.  And do you know what I spent that year doing? Nothing.  There was a time when I would sit at the table on Sundays for hours until they left.  I would sleep over at their apartment at least once a month.  Yet this past year I have neglected all of that.  Sunday nights were spent doing homework and the weekends were too busy.  I can't even claim I didn't know.  A year ago we thought we had six months, but then Glevic the wonder drug appeared and it was all sunshine and smiles and spending time was no longer a priority. Damn it.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was quite a day.  I learned alot but it all boils down to two things: (1) Life isn't fair and (2) tears can break through the toughest guard.  As one person put it: I have a perverse idea of what a fun 17th birthday is.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm 17!  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I hate sitting at home, not being able to do anything.  My grandmother called this morning because my grandfather was having chest pain and trouble breathing, but he refused to let her call EMS.  So my parents ran to his house and took him to wakemed.  I'm stuck at home not knowing what is going on and when I called to let them know that I was coming up, they told me not, at least until they knew something.  Fuck that.  I want to go now, but I won't, I'll sit here pulling out my hair but not going because it would just be more stress on my parents. 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      To all those who believed my new camera sucked....it doesn't, it is the photographer.  We accidentally had it in video mode so there are 6, 15 second, videos that took up the whole memory card.  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So its Saturday night at 8 oclock and I have a hot date...with my room.  It sucks, Kay is at Derick's, Mom and Dad went to a movie and I'm sitting at home, specifically in a room I'm sick of.  I want new everything.   It doesn't help that the Pottery Barn Teen catalog arrived today.  My dream room would cost... $2554 and thats not including anything on the wall or floors or curtain rods.   My furniture is beautiful but too formal large and dark for my small room. I really like sunny things and there is no way that cherry wood and brass can be sunny.  My room is also way way too cluttered and driving me insane.  Anyway, I'll stop complaining and start clearing stuff out, maybe if I cut out the amount of crap in here I can get some inspiration and start doing something to fix this thing.  ...maybe some spray paint will help....
     

    
</post>

<date>09,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My theory about being home with snow meant sleeping the day away was correct, well I wasn't actually sleeping that would have been productive.  Instead I laid on the couch under a really soft blanket and watched a marathon of Road Rules people battling it out with Real World people.  They did such crazy things as leap of of a 20 foot platform to catch a rope suspended from a holicopter and climb it (all done over water so they would have a chance of surviving the inevitable fall) and then fight over the fact that someone gave up and didn't try.  My day was officially wasted and all I feel like doing is lying down and sleeping away all memory of it.  Something about being home in the middle of a week day makes me sluggish, I hate it.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Its snowing and I'm sitting in APES wasting time in the computer lab.  I played in the snow during yearbook and I feel more accomplished than I would have if I had added captions to pages.  It sucks to be sitting in class and missing this snow.  Yet if school had been cancelled I probably would have slept the day away.  Hmm...
     

    
</post>

<date>08,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Also while lying in bed last night, I was reading  The Awakening  and a passage connected with me as I remember none doing before.  Described there on the pages of the book was my "mood", something that I have never been able to put into words.  So to be a plagiarist, this is me and my mood:  "On rainy or melancholy days Edna went out and sought the society of the friends she had made at the Grand Isle.  Or else she stayed indoors and nursed a mood with which she was becoming too familiar for her own comfort and peace of mind.  It was not despair; but it seemed to her as if life were passing by, leaving its promise broken and unfulfilled.  Yet there were other days when she listened, was led on and deceived by fresh promises which her youth held out to her."  and: "But as she sat there amid her guests, she felt the old ennui overtaking her; the hopelessness which so often assailed her, which came upon her like an obsession, like something extraneous, independent of volition.  It was something which announced itself; a chill breath that seemed to issue from some vast cavern wherein discords wailed.  There came over her the acute longing which always summoned into her spiritual vision the presence of the beloved one, overpowering her at once with a sense of the unattainable."  The second paragraph explains me exactly as I sat upon the futon at Diana's party, the difference, Edna knew the identity of the unattainable and I do not.  It is somewhat gratifying that here, within a (fairly) well known piece of Literature someone else feels as I feel.  It brings hope to realize that one is not alone, that others, too, have passed through such phases.  Such things are necessary to my sanity. 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lying in bed last night I wished for a pink bunny.    Ever since I was little I have made a wish whenever the clock's hours and minutes match (01:01, 11:11 or 12:12).  Generally its my time to be selfish and voice what I truly want.  Sometimes its for an event to occur or to change something about myself, and amazingly when looking back over these past wishes many of the ones I remember came true.   It never happens when I expect it or how I expect it.  When I was little I wished to grow up and guess what...It happened!! That's about the only one I am willing to share with the internet, but there were other one that came true that were more meaningful and more telling.  Having wishes makes me feel like someone out there is listening and working to help me achieve my goals.   Lately though I've been wishing for things that I know as soon as I say them that they will never come true, and its ruining my mind in some ways.  Knowing that my wishes cannot be granted makes me feel less like believing in anything.   (Its weird... What I call wishes are essentially prayer, but my mind rebels from calling them that.  I feel a distinct difference between my selfish whispers in the night and religion, yet I talk to the same thing.  And while wishes not coming true undermines my belief in the seemingly impossible, it does not seem to undermine my faith.)  But anyway, I saw the clock approaching 12:12 last night and began formulating my wishes in my head (they don't become the actual wish until said aloud) and had all kinds of plans for what I was to wish for, I wanted a specific event to occur or for me to find the courage to force it to occur, yet when the clock changed to 12:12 I blurt out: I wish for a pink rabbit, I don't care what kind as long as it is a pink rabbit.  Even as I said it I didn't know what I meant and I certainly don't now.  Part of me wanted to wake up and find one on the foot of my bed, just to prove to myself that wishes do come true, but in reality my wishes never work that way I wake up one morning and realized that it had come true and had come true a long time ago.  So who knows...   
     

    
</post>

<date>06,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My blog isn't meant to alarm anyone...Sorry if it does.  At this point I believe that I have subconsciously turned it into a rant board, because my mood seems to change the moment I begin writing.  Within moments of posting my mood reverses...I'm not really that depressed (at least I hope not!).  Anyway enough of this...  Amusing conversation about those stupid English semester plans (well that's where it started....) lisliasm: well i have to get English signed lisliasm: but chitchat201: i don't want to do that! chitchat201: i maintain an A simply because i read the books on time lisliasm: lol chitchat201: if i did the study guides and studied for vocab i might have a 96 instead of a 93 but whats the difference in the long run? lisliasm: NONE!! chitchat201: exactly chitchat201: its like my mom suggested i go to wake tech until i figure out what it is i want to do lisliasm: lol chitchat201: and its like why did i work my ass off for 3-4 years to go to some half assed community college lisliasm: exactly chitchat201: its not like high school does anything aside from getting you into collegre lisliasm: some people learn how to spell and type chitchat201: let me rephrase that working hard in high school does nothing lisliasm: ill second that lisliasm: and yet...look at us chitchat201: lol chitchat201: it for the good college lisliasm: ah but what does college get you lisliasm: ...just a job you'll hate anyway lisliasm: But im not pessimistic  chitchat201: exactly lets drop out now and move into a refrigerator box together lisliasm: OK! lisliasm: could we maybe each have our own lisliasm: it would be kinda tight chitchat201: hmm chitchat201: that might be too expensive lisliasm: maybe in the winter we could live in one...more body heat lisliasm: but you know in the summer... lisliasm: thats true lisliasm: you know those fridge boxes
     

    
</post>

<date>05,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got a haircut today....quite drastic  Nothing else has really happened, went out to dinner tonight with Sam, Diana and Trevor which was lots of fun (even though my parents didn't let me go to starbucks, grumble, grumble).  Been in a good, lazy mood the past two days so no real emotion in anything I wrote.  It seems that no one updates their blog anymore, at least not with a high frequency, is that because everyone is content-ish?  Break is over which majorly sucks...only 63 real school days, 6 ex days, 2 flex days and 4 exam days until summer!
     

    
</post>

<date>17,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I crashed...eating crap for a week straight and not sleeping at night finally caught up with me.  Canceled the evening's plans and decided to veg.  I need to start taking better care of myself...
     

    
</post>

<date>16,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       GO PHOENIX!  tonight's games were awesome....The girls slaughtered their opponent and the guys had a triumphant victory in the last 5 seconds of over time; Juniors also won the spirit Olympics.  In fact today was awesome, minus the classwork and 3 awkward conversations.  Enough said.  Night to all, sleep tight.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      From yesterday's discussion of cages: Ms. S.: ...and of course geeks have geeky fun Me: well we do, don't we?  also: Hannah: Losers have more fun Sam: I want that on a bumper sticker  right now I want to be having fun instead of doing homework.  After dropping Kay off at the synagogue and visiting my grandparents I drove home, right past North Raleigh Christian Academy and I really, really wanted to stop in and watch the meet, but no...I can't be a slacker all week, I have English.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tonight was a successful diversion.  Sam and I went to Armadillo and the game.  My mind is clear and I feel ready to do something, so I think I'll iron and put ribbon on my new curtains before I go to bed.  My face has color again and my eyes look less bloodshot and I have no voice.  I was in such a great mood on the way home that I lost it (my voice).  I rode home in a tank top with the windows down, sunroof open and the heat and stereo all the way up, with me singing along of course.  Since I wrote this entry in my head before I got home, I'm going to pretend that I didn't hear the conversation downstairs when my dad got home and instead go back to my sewing.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I decided to be selfish today.  I didn't do my homework last night and plan to do very little tonight.  Instead of going to visit Zayde as I should i decided that I would go to the basketball game at school and Armadillo (3rd time this week...I haven't really eaten anything else).  I know that I am being selfish, but I also doubt that my sanity can take much more sitting and watching someone waste away.  Since I can't do anything about it I decided to take a 24 hour break and not try.  The goal for tonight is to have fun and forget for a few hours the things that haunt me.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I stood on the patio looking up at the stars and decided I wanted to scream, so I did, or rather I tried to and all that came out were silent tears.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I quit work during the week today.  Decided I couldn't deal with listening to people stumble through their Hebrew while I had other things to deal with.  Not exactly other things so much as other thing.  It is taking over my entire mind, my entire thought pattern, my entire existence.  Well it really isn't it just feels that way.    Everything I do that is slightly cheerful somehow always ends in me feeling selfish for enjoying myself while my grandfather is sick and dying in some strange bed.  I'll just be going along working on homework and thinking of far off things and then bam it'll hit me and I feel like the lowest life form on earth.  This morning my alarm went off at 07:07 after hitting the snooze bar repeatedly, noticing the time I began to make a wish that went somewhere along the lines of my happy teenage-esque dream that I was having, then halfway through my wish the commercial on the radio ended and this song came on:   Hello God, it's me again. 2:00 a.m., Room 304.  Visiting hours are over, time for our bedside tug of war. This sleeping child between us may not make it through the night. I'm fighting back the tears as she fights for her life.  Well, it must be kind of crowded, On the streets of Heaven. So tell me: what do you need her for? Don't you know one day she'll be your little girl forever. But right now I need her so much more. She's much too young to be on her own: Barely just turned seven. So who will hold her hand when she crosses the streets of Heaven?  Tell me God, do you remember the wishes that she made, As she blew out the candles on her last birthday cake? She wants to ride a pony when she'd big enough. She wants to marry her Daddy when she's all grown up.  Well, it must be kind of crowded, On the streets of Heaven. So tell me: what do you need her for? Don't you know one day she'll be your little girl forever. But right now I need her so much more. She's much too young to be on her own: Barely just turned seven. So who will hold her hand when she crosses the streets of Heaven?  Lord, don't you know she's my angel You got plenty of your own And I know you hold a place for her But she's already got a home Well I don't know if you're listenin' But praying is all that's left to do So I ask you Lord have mercy, you lost a son once too  And it must be kind of crowded, On the streets of Heaven. So tell me: what do you need her for? Don't you know one day she'll be your little girl forever. But right now I need her so much more. Lord, I know once you've made up your mind, There's no use in beggin'. So if you take her with you today, will you make sure she looks both ways, And would you hold her hand when she crosses the streets of Heaven.  -Sherrie Austin  Streets of Heaven   As a slap in the face guess what is playing on the radio right this moment, streets of heaven.  It is as if the world wants me to feel guilty for thinking of myself.  Although my grandfather is not a child and I don't believe in Jesus as the song mentions the song still fits in my mind.  My grandfather is fiercely independent and in that sense like a child, he begged his doctor to find some excuse to admit him because he didn't want to be a burden.  When I reach out to hold his hand he resists, and sighs, but lets me hold it seeming as if he is doing me a favor, yet when he falls asleep he clutches my hand tightly and does not allow me to let go.  So yes he does need someone to hold his hand as he crosses the road before him, we all do.   I look like a wreck, I walk around moping and unmotivated, I feel burned out; yet if someone asks me I tell them I'm fine, what else can I really say?  People don't ask how you are doing out of concern, normally, but instead do so to reassure themselves.  Hell, I don't even know why I'm so bothered today...It certainly isn't as if anything has changed, good or bad.  Instead things stay the same.  I stopped by his apartment Sunday before he went back to the hospital and asked him as he was doing.  His answer: "the same as yesterday".  Laughing I asked him how he felt yesterday and he goes, "Lousy."  So that's where we are, in a perpetual yesterday.     
     

    
</post>

<date>12,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      To steal something directly from our English homework reading for the night: "He then for the first time began to be seriously worried about the man in the cage, for he knew that once resentment gets a firm start and becomes well rationalized and structuralized, it may become like a cancer.  When the person no longer knows whom he hates, he is much harder to help."  This quote brings up two totally different thought processes in my mind.  The first is of my grandfather, and how when he was first diagnosed I was truly angry and that anger could be channeled and funneled from me; now that anger has mellowed into resentment, something I cannot pinpoint and remove, so instead I carry it with me making it harder to deal with.  The other track my mind took was along the path of a conversation Erica and I had last night.  The gist of it was that when I am actually made aware of something it tends to be resolved.  My blog a week ago was filled with melancholy entries and I did not even notice that it had changed from its normal state until Erica mentioned it.  Then realizing that I had been melancholy my mind seemingly changed itself and that became reflected into my writing.  No, I did not begin to self edit my blog because of the conversation, my mind began to self edit and realize that my mood was negative and then I could work to truly change my mood.  Another example of this is my "mood," before I knew the cause it was like the resentment of the caged man, always present and non-specific, but as soon as I admitted to myself what it was I could identify it and move on past it.    Specific anger actually helps me yet the tendency seems to dilute things.  It always seems as if it is better to say that you resent something than that you hate a specific thing about it, but resentment just seems to build.  I think that people need to get over their fear of using strong words, as long as they use them for specific things and not for sweeping generalizations.   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hospice is an evil word....
     

    
</post>

<date>11,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Working on my homework with the radio on in the background this line sticks in my head "Getting paid by the hour, growing older by the minute".  I'm not even getting paid yet I'm wasting my day sitting at my computer doing stupid subjunctive excercises, in a language I plan to avoid using.  Oh well.  Only 54 real school days, 6 ex days, 2 flex days, 4 AP days (we get 1/2 the day off...yay) and 4 exam days til summer.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Erica and I went to Armadillo before RUACH and our accomplishment for the night was learning the Armadillo guy's name (which is John by the way).  After that we went to class which was pretty cool.  The first hour was spent watching Mr. Agasi cook with him throwing out Hebrew words while we all talked amongst ourselves about such things as "G-dness" and which people Elie knew.  Then we went on to Kabballah which was really cool.  The guy (whose name I can't remember) had us write down the ten things that make us and draw the connections between them.  I sat there and struggled to come up with 10, the first 3 blatantly obvious and the last 7 just seemed to be words that suited my mood at that moment and I have changed a dozen times in my head.  The three things that compile me: Energy, Order and Randomness.  Or maybe: Energy, Structure and spontaneity, but you get the idea.  I also see those things as linked but had trouble finding all of the connections.  My energy forces me to do things, but i cannot operate in chaos so I must be ordered, but my energy also creates chaos.  But order and structure give me energy and strength to do something more chaotic.  Or maybe its that i find chaos in order, and order in chaos, and it is the knowledge that nothing is absolute that gives me energy.  Whatever it is those are the 3 primary things i see in myself.  I am also demanding, observant, oblivious, amused, and myself (is that a copout?). Well at least thats 8...  Things to think about while I fall asleep.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just to let everyone know I'm ok...  Don't really know what I'm thinking at this point but I do know that things have gotten better.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      He died yesterday; the funeral is today.  
     

    
</post>

<date>19,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      No one knows what it's like To be the bad man To be the sad man Behind blue eyes And no one knows What it's like to be hated To be faded to telling only lies  But my dreams they aren't as empty As my conscious seems to be I have hours, only lonely My love is vengeance That's never free  No one knows what its like To feel these feelings Like i do, and i blame you! No one bites back as hard On their anger None of my pain woe Can show through  But my dreams they aren't as empty As my conscious seems to be I have hours, only lonely My love is vengeance That's never free  No one knows what its like To be mistreated, to be defeated Behind blue eyes No one knows how to say That they're sorry and don't worry I'm not telling lies  But my dreams they aren't as empty As my conscious seems to be I have hours, only lonely My love is vengeance That's never free  No one knows what its like To be the bad man to be the sad man Behind blue eyes. - Behind Blue Eyes   Don't know who wrote the song but its awesome.  I was driving home tonight, in the darkness of back roads and the silence of my tears when it came on the radio.  The sound filled my car, filled my mind and just won't let go.  Its so easy to fall into the trap of believing that you are alone, that no one has ever been through it.  Its a lie that I like to believe, that part of me has to believe.  Theres too much there for one person to handle, certainly too much for it too be a common occurance.  If it is, what does that say about this world and the realms beyond?
     

    
</post>

<date>18,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As time draws to a close the words to describe what I'm feeling become less and less useful.  No longer can I describe my thoughts or even my emotions they are just too jumbled.  I feel like G-d has failed me and that I have failed G-d.  It occurred to me that I really don't have any spirituality; I know the stories, I know some of the laws, but that does not comfort me...There needs to be something more.  I am thinking about going to Rabbi Herman for answers, and I know that some people think its brain washing, but I really don't care.  I need something, I just don't know what.  I sat tonight staring at two pictures in the same room of men I didn't know.  One was a framed photograph of Zayde from his twenties; the other, reality.  How does one come to terms with something when they don't recognize what is fact and what is fiction?
     

    
</post>

<date>18,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm sitting in traffic For the 5th year in a row Wasting my time Just to get Where I don't even wanna go I started jotting things down On a krispy kreme sack Everything I'd do If I could leave this place And never look back  I wanna do it all Visit paris in the fall Watch the yankees play ball I wanna take it all in Catch a few beads Down at Mardi Gras Start a tradition Lay down the law I wanna do it all  I want to drink tequila Down in Tijuana Say why not When somebody says Hey do you wanna I wanna get my heart broke Once or twice Settle down with the love of my life Rock little babies to sleep at night  I wanna do it all Visit paris in the fall Watch the yankee's play ball I wanna take it all in Catch a few beads Down at Mardi Gras Start a tradition Lay down the law I wanna do it all  I wanna stand today Every now and then Just doin what I want to do When I wanna do it Anytime I wanna do it  I wanna do it all Visit paris in the fall Watch the yankees play ball I wanna take it all in Catch a few beads Down at Mardi Gras Start a tradition Lay down the law  I wanna do it all See Niagara falls Fight city hall Feel good in my skin Beating the odds  With my back to the wall Trying to rob Peter Without paying Paul I wanna do it all I wanna do it all I wanna do it all    I wanna do it all  Terri Clark  
     

    
</post>

<date>30,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tired...Stressed...
     

    
</post>

<date>28,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I seem to frequently find myself in cages, and sadly I tend to just accept them, or at least pretend to accept them.  There is one cage however, that I cannot accept and have found myself constantly thrown against the bars of recently.  This cage is self built; something I didnt know existed until after the construction had been completed.  The cage I built for myself is made of independence, something stronger than any tangible metal.  Since I was a toddler I have been slowly building up my independence.  When I was three I resented the little child leash that my parents kept me on when we went shopping and decided to get rid of it.  I figured out how to work the Velcro and disconnected it from the harness I wore and connected it to a clothes rack and crawled off, much to the terror of my mother.  At age 5, I desperately wanted bunk beds so I could sleep up high, like my older neighbor.  After much pleading my parents bought me a set.  The first night I climbed up the ladder, into bed, and my parents kissed me goodnight; before they left the room, though, they removed the ladder to prevent me from falling.  It didnt take long for me to realize that I was trapped and needed them to get me in and out of bed.  Needless to say, the next night, and every night after that, I slept on the bottom bunk.  My independent tendency continued on throughout everything I did.  It became assumed that I did not need help on my homework, and if something I was struggling with something I would come and tell people when I was ready.  The problem is that I dont tell people when I am struggling and instead everyone realizes it after a lot of damage has been done.  I somewhere along the way decided that it was not good to be dependent on anybody for anything, and somehow never noticed that I made the decision.  Now that I have an issue before me to deal with I realize that I have no where to go.  I have become accustomed to making incredibly shallow friendships on my part and suddenly this is beginning to bother me.  No matter what is going on in my mind the standard answer to how are you doing, is fine.  Sometimes my lies are noticed, but people still assume that I will come to them if the issue grows large enough.  So now I am forced to look for support; an outlet to pour my emotions into and there is no where for them to go.  I go to approach someone and have a real discussion about how Im feeling and turn around, not knowing how to.  The most frustrating thing in dealing with this cage is knowing that I built it I welded the padlock shut, and I alone somewhere hold the key (hopefully).   
     

    
</post>

<date>28,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Note to self...And everyone else.  It is not a good idea to disregard explicit product warnings.  Particularly if the warning in its entirety is: Caution, do not use on cuts or freshly shaven skin.  Typically these warnings are in place for a reason....
     

    
</post>

<date>25,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's startling to read blog entries in which people acknowledge their self editing.  That is something I haven't fully thought about in quite a while.  Typically I just let my fingers do the typing and don't go back and change things.  Oftentimes I'll type things that I didn't know were residing in my mind, and they'll just spill out on to the screen.  I most of what I type seems removed and distant, or a least not personal, at least not at the time that I post.  Looking back though, there are things that I don't want the entire world to know here, on these pages.  That thought makes me nervous in some way, simply because I don't know exactly who reads this.  The knowledge wouldn't change what I write (I hope) but would be interesting to know.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I escaped for a few hours today to buy shoes for formal.  The formal I'm going to dateless...Not too thrilled about that.  If anything it taught me not to sit around waiting for things to magically happen.  I sit by idly waiting for things to happen entirely too frequently, and rarely does that work.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Have you ever been in a state of utter confusion?  Where thoughts would just refuse to formulate into something tangible, something that you could put into words.  It all refuses to come together, images, emotions swirling faster and faster within my mind, yet gone as soon as they come.  Its a dream world, when I surface i no longer can remember what pulled me under.  Instead I lose chunks of time, chunks of consciousness to nothing, to something. I sat down at my computer not knowing what to type but compelled to do something and my fingers are now flying.  Someone has IMed me but I am ignoring so as not to stop the flow of thoughts.  The snow has buried everything, the filth, the destruction, but also the beauty of bulbs just peaking out of the ground.  If I was to go to the cemetery, I would not know where Zayde is, buried under this thick blanket.  People have been so kind, so cautious, so welcoming.  Others have no idea that anything has happened.  Both drive me crazy.  Don't know why...  Don't know much, except that I still haven't caught up on calculus so its good i don't have school tomorrow.  Going stir crazy, sick of my house, sick of Bubby's apartment.  Lets go on a trip to somewhere, anywhere.  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Had a good day yesterday.  Did the whole Shabbos thing from 10:30 in the morning to 4:30 in the afternoon and then services at 6:15.  Friday night we went to services at 5:20 and then went to the Solkowitzs' for dinner and stayed until 11 ish.  Spent the rest of my time with my cousins playing pool, or with Erica and my cousins at Armadillo.  I realized that I may have found part of what I always felt was missing.  A truly relaxed day, with no appointments, no homework, no rushing (except to get to services at a reasonable tome).  To top it all off I awoke this morning to snow, which canceled work and class, so I get another day without deadlines.  Very nice indeed.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So here are the promised pictures of my gorgeous pups (I know you all have been sitting on the edges of your seats).  Lucky is the big one on the right and Pepper is on the left.         
     

    
</post>

<date>02,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well speaking of the meaningful I just got back my ex-day assignment from Felder and I thought I'd share:  "If I was to give everything up for something, it would be to have a purpose to my life.  I would give up what I have now if I knew...and I would really have to know...that I would gain a passion for something, a useful place working towards an actual goal, not the intangible ones I have now.  If someone could somehow guarantee that I would feel accomplished and closer to something tangible each night when I laid down to sleep, that I would have something worthy of cultivation and sacrifice, I would leap.  All too often do I feel like I'm treading water, never moving further, just continously straining to remain afloat in my fixed location."  Thats what has got me down as of late.  There are no longer signs of progress no end in sight.  As I accomplish one assignment another leaps out at me.  Right now most of my time is sucked up by school and homework so that I can get into a good college, so that I can get a good job.  But I don't know what I want to do, that I will be any more fulfilled or content tommorrow, or next year, or in five years, or ever.  I have spent the past 4 hours on homework and there is still mounds more and there will be tommorrow too.  There are so many things that I want to do that I want to see that I want to think about and yet there is never anytime.  I collapse into bed every night between 11 and midnight and have a few fleeting hours of fitful sleep.  I wake up repeatedly tangled and uncomfortable and yet somehow I can't escape it.  Suddenly all the purpose I had has dissipated, I feel disconected and hurried, not taking the time or care that things need.  Things like friendships, committments, myself.  Some element needs to change, but unfortunately I don't know what that element is.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We are keeping the gorgeous new dog.  Her name is Pepper and she is a sweetie.  Well to everyone but the groomer, who asked my dad when he went to pick up Pepper and Lucky if we were sure we wanted to take her home.  Apparently she does not know how to react to certain noises, whatever that means.  While Lucky is still being protective of us they play together now and follow each other around.  Pictures to come as soon as I figure out what went wrong with photobucket.  I realize that my blog has deteriorated into impersonal statements of daily matters.  I'm just physically and mentally exhausted and socially deprived.  Hopefully everything will be right after a good real weekend.  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Busy. Busy 1.5 day weekend...Formal, a second dog, and watched my first football game (hey, I may not have been there but I had the best seat in the house with the new 60 inch widescreen tv that FINALLY arrived)...also skipped out on work and forgot about Ruach.  I'll elaborate more tommorrow...after all what is APES for?
     

    
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Formal was fun...Well fun mixed with awkwardness...Anyway, I'll have pretty pictures soon for all to see.  
     

    
</post>

<date>14,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Will you be my valentine?   Fun question of the evening: Why are you here instead of out on some valentines date? Because I dont have a valentine 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Happy night that circled around one conversation topic for hours on end...that and random phone calls and van full of guys... Is valentines day really tomorrow?
     

    
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Minutes fly by so swiftly once school lets out.  Counting money seemed to take 10 minutes yet in reality took closer to a half an hour.  The mall sucked away over an hour and we spent 45 minutes going to walmart to get stuff for Kay's valentines day dinnner.  Now its 8:20 and I haven't done anything except spend oodles of money and agree to cook an elaborate (...well maybe not elaborate, just labor intensive) dinner for Kayla and her best friend to pass off as their own for their boyfriends on the table I decorated.  Hmm...maybe I need to channel this creative energy I pretend to have toward other things like english essays.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Buried deep as you can dig inside yourself,  and covered with a perfect shell,  such a charming beautiful exterior. Laced with brilliant smiles and shining eyes, perfect posture, but you're barely scraping by, but you're barely scraping by.  This is one time that you can't fake it hard enough to please everyone or anyone at all.  And the grave that you refuse to leave  the refuge that you've built to flee the places you have come to fear the most.   Buried deep as you can dig inside yourself,  and hidden in the public eye.  Such a stellar monument to loneliness.  Laced with brilliant smiles and shining eyes  and perfect makeup but you're barely scraping by  This is one time that you can't fake it hard enough to please everyone or anyone at all.  And the grave that you refuse to leave  the refuge that you've built to flee the places you have come to fear the most.   And you cant fake it hard enough to please everyone or anyone at all And the grave that you refuse to leave  the refuge that you've built to flee the places you have come to fear the most.  its the place that youve come to fear the most, its the place that youve come  to fear the most -Dashboard Confessional  The Places That You Have Come to Fear the Most   Maybe just sick vibes, maybe not 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've fallen into a sleep, drug and song induced trance.  I can't escape any of the three and its become a vicious cycle. I wake up, take some meds, log onto my computer and listen to the song and start feeling drifty and dozy.  Kind of a scary sick day,  I've accomplished nothing except shuffle from my bed to the kitchen and back.  I need to pull from it but fail everytime I try.  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Some part of my life has to be fiction.  There is no way all the contradictions are true.  To paraphrase Erica, when there are so many different things and they all disagree with each other none of them can be true.  Even as I write this I don't entirely believe it, but thats the entire problem.  On some gut level I sense things yet my mind then recognizes some of them and dissmisses others.  There is no way that I am everything I seem to be,  the person I am at school in class, the person I am in Shul, the person I am when we are out somewhere like armadillo.  It just doesn't work.  Nor can I eliminate the acting from the truth.  So many faces, so many choices, why do I pick the ones I do? 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Normally when in an odd mood I can find something somewhere that reflects it.  Sometimes its a song, sometimes a book, sometimes a random comment made. Tonight I can't find anything of the sort to plagerize so instead I'll sculpt a song.  A song filled with minor keys speaking of isolation and frustration, lyrics mournful and steady, of loss of normalcy, of over analyzing.  I can almost hear it in my head, can almost feel it within me, and yet at the same moment feels fake and cliche.      People who can causally dismiss things bother me, but people who come up with polar opposite opinions make me feel out of it.  Add the two together and you get isolation.  What we are plays a dramtic role in what we see.  No two realities are the same, things simply can't be.  Some would dismiss the multitudes of possibilities saying that such variability makes them all false, but I choose to see it differently.  Everyone is at a different angle, a different vantage.  This allows us to see many similar things but still have an individual part of the world that no one else can see.  without seeing things from another person's vantage makes it unfair to judge their actions yet we do it daily, hourly, constantly.  There is something vaguely depressing at this perpetual cycle of misjudgements, especially when you look at our nation's penal code, but that is not the subject of this entry.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Kit and I are co-speakers for SLA next year!!!! Very, very excited about this.  SLA was awesome today and then the after legislating partying at Mellow Mushroom was cool (even though there were only 6 of us).  Wish my evening was as cool....Have to babysit Kay and Derick as my parents met friends for dinner.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Eventful day....
     

    
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Its weird when you've considered yourself something your entire life and then someone informs you that you don't meet their particular group's standards.  Mom is pissed and said the hell with them, but I want to fix it and can't because I am living at home.  Grr don't know what to do except let it stew or forget entirely about it.  Have a feeling it'll stew though.  Not great at being vague but don't want people to judge others based off of my current issues.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Gorgeous out...Going to the lake tomorrow after school...wanna join me?  I've been telling my dreams to the scarecrow About the places that I'd like to see I say, "friend do you think I'll ever get there?" Oh, but he just stands there smilin' back at me So I confessed my sins to the preacher About the love I've been prayin' to find Is there a brown-eyed boy in my future, yeah And he says, "girl, you've got nothin' but time."  But how do you wait for heaven? And who has that much time? And how do you keep your feet on the ground When you know that you were born, You were born to fly  My daddy he is grounded like the oak tree My momma she is steady as the sun Oh, you know I love my folks But I keep starin' down the road Just lookin' for my one chance to run Hey, cause I will soar away like a blackbird I will blow in the wind like a seed I will plant my heart in the garden of my dreams And I will grow up where I wander wild and free  Oh, How do you wait for heaven? And who has that much time? And how do you keep your feet on the ground When you know, that you were born? You were born, yeah, you were born to fly  So how do you wait for heaven? And who has that much time? And how do you keep your feet on the ground When you know, that you were born You were born to fly, yeah  You were born to fly, fly, fly, fly, hey Oh, oh -Sara Evans   Born To Fly   Just for the record...Doesn't have to be a brown eyed boy in my future, I don't discriminate by eye color!
     

    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I drove a grand total of 6 miles today and slipped 7 times.  I entirely lost control twice, once making a U-turn at 5 miles an hour and the other by tapping my brakes going 20 mph on the highway.  If you've never slid across two lanes of traffic with no control over your direction, don't try it.  Its really scary, not being certain if you can make it back to your house without killing yourself or someone else.  Everyone else may have had no trouble on the roads, but at 8:30 in knightdale in a tiny civic they weren't manageable.  Wow...Guess I am mortal after all.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SLA and YLA are approaching and really the only thing I've done lately for either of them has been shopping for new clothes.  Its sad.  I've been to the mall 4 times in the past 5 days and have spent way too much of my parent's money, I myself have not spent a penny.  Nothing personal or insightful right now, brain shut off somewhere along the second mile of our 3 (or maybe 4) mile walk, along with the circulation in my hands which are still cool to the touch.  Walking at the lake is emotionally therapeutic if nothing else.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The sun is out from beneath the mountains of clouds.  Shimmering through my sheer curtains it dances on my floor playful and glorious.  There may be traces of snow on the ground from last night but that's fine because the sun says that spring is coming.  I'm tired of these threats of snow, of getting my hopes up for a day of snuggling under blankets sleeping because the snow has made it possible for me to cancel all plans and not have any deadlines, of being trapped for days on end in my house with my family, of always being cold.  Spring is in the air and nothing is going to stand in the way.  Anyone want to go to the lake?
     

    
</post>

<date>15,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I hate this weather but want it to last long enough to get us out of tomorrow's half day.  It was nasty enough that I came home, transferred all of my bedding from my bed to the floor of my parent's bedroom and snuggled up to a marathon to TV watching and napping.  Unfortunately woke up feeling crappy with an exceptionally large load of homework left (which I still haven't done).  In an attempt to wake up I just downed a coke float consisting of a full can of diet Pepsi and 1/2 cup of ice cream and an extra can of diet Pepsi.  Now just feel sick.    
     

    
</post>

<date>28,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tired, tired, tired.  Went to Kanata today for oreintation which was pretty cool, even though it was mainly rules.  Then went to lunch with my grandmother, then went back to Kanata to get Kay, took her to garner, picked up dinner for mom dad and myself on the way home, went to the fish store (which i have to go back to tomorrow) and then the mall.  All in all I think I drove 110 miles today and got a cool blazer and a pair of tanks out of it all.  Going off to collapse now...
     

    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow...So I'm officially an idiot.  Somehow I decided that the month of March didn't exist and April was starting on Monday, which in turn meant that YLA was next weekend... Now I realize I have 5 weeks until YLA and have all ready cancelled work and told my mom to get her vacation day back because we couldn't go college looking.  Also, it makes spring break really tight with YLA Friday through Sunday, Passover starting Monday, and my parent free college road trip the rest of the week.  Ack...Need a new brain!
     

    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sunshine and pink belts make me smile...
     

    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Fuck pity.  I don't deserve it.  I just recieved this narration that a woman recorded from my grandfather when he was sick.  He never once asked for pity or help and would have deserved it.  I don't and it's just that simple.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So how about some honesty?  Not the stuff that I tricked myself into believing was honesty (see below), but some real honesty.  It's easy to tell yourself that no one cares, and its your life to fuck up but in reality people do care and the whole "no one cares" routine is just an excuse to slack off.  I may be screwing up my life, but that's my fault and I'm choosing not to care about that too much right now.  Well I'm choosing to care about it and whine but not actually do anything proactive to fix the problem.  Its my life, my fault I didn't keep up with things and now all I want is pity I don't deserve.  Actually I want for the mess to go away but aside from that I'll settle for pity and my self respect back, because right now I look in the mirror and see nothing but this lazy self centered spoiled brat.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I see it around me I see it in everything I could be so much more than this  I said my goodbyes This is my sundown I'm going to be so much more than this  With one hand high You'll show them your progress You'll take your time But no one cares No one cares... No one cares...  I need you to show the way from crazy I want to be so much more than this  With one hand high You'll show them your progress You'll take your time But no one cares  With one hand high You'll show them your progress You'll take your time But no one cares No one cares... No one cares...  No one cares... I could be so much more than this No one cares... I want to be so much more than this  No one cares... I could be so much more than this No one cares... I want to be so much more than this  No one cares... I want to be so much more than this No one cares... I want to be so much more than this  Good good bye Lovely time Good good bye Tinsel shine  Good good bye I'll be fine Good good bye Good good night  - My Sundown  Jimmy Eat World  Ever sat at home in the dark with the music pulsating, so that you can  feel  it?  Not emotionally feel it, but literally feel the sound waves hitting you, almost creating images in the ripples they cause?  Its an amazing feeling, especially when the words resonate in your mind and you hear the truth ring from them.  No one cares, and this isn't me just feeling sorry for myself, its the truth.  In reality we all care too little.  My progress has little to no effect on you and so realistically I can't expect you to care, just as I would care very little for yours.  I will rejoice with you as you reach it, but once the moment has passed I will forget it for something else.  Don't look so shocked, in reality you do the same thing.  If you think you wouldn't you are either in denial or far better a person than me.  I'm tired, truly tired.  I spent half an hour staring at a wall, not asleep just unwilling to try to make myself think.  My eyes hardly stay open anymore, my motivation gone.  Knowing that no one is counting on me and not having my own motivation things are slipping. I am no longer  accomplishing  anything and in reality I haven't been for quite some time.  My life really has no purpose at this point no drive; each day just the repetition of the day before it, the dialogue changes but the scene does not.  I need to get out there and  do  something.  I need to lay my head down at night and be able to look proudly on my day, the day during which I made progress.  Right now I'm treading water, struggling to keep one stroke ahead of sinking but not actually getting any closer to the shore.  At camp I get a maximum of 7 hours of sleep a night and work from sun up to sunset and somehow have so much energy that I can't lie still enough to sleep, thoughts racing through my mind, little smiles dotting my dreams of the wonderful things that happened during the day.  Want to know the highlight of my day today? I got laughed at by a class of 4th graders.  We (Mark, Aaron and I) were singing the hatzi kaddish, each of us singing just one word, and I tripped up on my word.  The class laughed and I started laughing and couldn't stop.  In fact that moment got kind of scary, because I lost control.  I actually had to leave the room.  Something needs to change but I don't know what.  The entire month of March is booked and my grades need remediation, so I won't be able to do anything about this for at least a month.    Don't be worried...This is just a phase...I'm not actually this depressed and unbalanced (I don't think)...Maybe some sunshine would help, can anyone arrange that?
     

    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So what's new?... My hair shrunk again... I have become apathetic to nearly everything, sallowed by this spotty weather and laundry list of things to do or redo.  I am looking forward to this weekend (get to see al the Kanata peeps I'll be with this summer) but can barely see it in the haze of weekly trials.   Argh...Can't it all just be over?
     

    
</post>

<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Best away message I've seen in well...ever:  Legislative pick-up lines... 1) "You can bang my gavel." 2) "Wanna go up and caucus in my room?" 3) "You know, I'm on the Human Sexuality committee..."
     

    
</post>

<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Happy day, lots of incomplete thoughts and really bad limericks...  Open mic night...Wow, I can't really come up with much else convertible...Loud, shiny, red Auto flirt...hmm autoflirt...  so on to the portion of really bad limericks (I had hannah's assistance):   Limerick warning for photosynthetic organisms   While you're out having fun in the sun, Your cells are becoming well done-- UV-B is bad, And makes you mad-- And ruins your fun in the sun.  UV-B makes your cells fry, Which makes the consumers die-- UV-B is bad, And makes you mad-- So why don't you just say bye-bye?  The hole in the ozone is growing, People cause this without knowing UV-B is bad,  And makes you mad-- So, to your graves you're going. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      How many times can you think of where you just said "I love my life"?  I had one of those moments today, it just shocked me.  I know I've been in a really good mood lately but still...  Anyway I was speeding off down my street to meet Erica for dinner at Armadillo before we had RUACH and the windows were down the sunroof was open and the music was blaring some song that was really upbeat and awesome and I randomly said, out loud, "Man, I love my life"! Without thinking about it, without meaning to, it kind of shocked me.  Last week I felt alone and overwhelmed and this week I don't.  I've been in a good mood and more open, and I guess people can tell.  Random people start talking to me when I'm in a good mood, strangers in line and cashiers too, while it's kind of scary and really weird its also pretty nice.  And just a note for my future self, my life is pretty cool.  While things aren't how I pictured them to be when I was little, and yes, I'm still single, there are other things to make me happy.  This warm weather and light homework helps, so does getting starbucks on my way into school and going to dinner with a friend later in the day.  So yeah, life is good.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This morning I left the house 20 minutes earlier than normal.  I love spring because each morning starts in a haze of clouds and slowly the sun bursts through.  While waiting for the light to change, random rays of light radiated from this huge cloud. That has been me this week.  The light bursting from darkness, as the evil weather lifted so has my mood.  I really don't care about the homework I'm behind on and suddenly I have begun to make progress on the piles of it.  If I didn't have class tonight and Open Mic Night tomorrow, I would even begin cleaning my room.  I'm actually in the mood to open the windows wide, take down my curtains, blast music and then rip my room to parts, just to reorganize it
     

    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Argh....Hate this weather, why can't it just decide to be a beautiful warm day all day?  In case you can't tell I don't like dampness.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Things I learned this weekend: --Sleep and healthy food are neccesary for survival. --Staying up all night to write a paper when you already doubt you are going to school is a bad idea. --You can spend all day with a friend and still only approach serious conversation when you are 3 minutes away from dropping them off at home. --Don't visit colleges without a plan on a sunday morning, particularly duke. --Durham on a Sunday morning sucks. --My mom can see "flirting" from 20 feet away looking in a store window, and enjoys to bug me about it. --I am not allowed to go to New York and Company for a minimum of 6 months, unless I win the non-existant lottery. --On icy nights it's only ok to drive on the roads if you are picking up fast food for your family. 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I hate writing papers...
     

    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Prom dresses depress me.  I'm really tired of this whole single teenage girl thing.  I'm tired of watching my friends in their happy little couples.  I'm tired of being hit on by an assortment of older guys I don't know, and not ones my own age.  I'm tired of not knowing who to ask to prom, but most of all I'm tired of being alone, of not quite having a place anymore.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So the whole don't accept rides from strangers thing is good and all, but some kids are a bit extreme.    Driving into the neighborhood I saw Dusty, my neighbor's dog, lose and dangerously close to the highway.  The dog never comes when I call it so I kept driving.  When I pulled onto the street I saw Rich, my neighbor, in his truck waiting for Torey to get off the bus.  He went after Dusty and left me to pick up Torey.  So I'm sitting there and the bus pulls up and I get out of the car to get her.  One of the older elementary school boys who lives on my street, I think his name is AJ, sees me and falls to the back.  After all the kids except for Torey run to their parents, he grabs her and goes, "Torey, do you know her? If you don't come home with me, don't ride with strangers."  This from a kid who lives on my street!  I have baby sat him before.  His brother likes to run out and pet Lucky and Pepper, yet I'm a stranger.  I was shocked.  Do I look menacing? Wow...
     

    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What do you see? What is true? Do you understand me? Do I understand you?  Do you see me on this merry-go-round? Spinning, spinning up and down?  Do you see me grinning? Smiling and joking with friends? Do you watch me spinning? Hoping the day never ends?  Do you see me on this merry-go-round? Spinning, spinning up and down?  Do you see a girl looking towards the future? As she was taught to do? That every move forward is torture? Knowing that shell never do?  Do you see me on this merry-go-round? Spinning, spinning up and down?  Do you see her run away? Wanting to stop chasing tomorrow? Just to start living today? Her eyes filled with sorrow?  Do you see me on this merry-go-round? Spinning, spinning up and down?  Do you really understand? That some days are wonderful and good? And others cant keep up with demand? Do you think that you could?  Do you see me on this merry-go-round? Spinning, spinning up and down?  Do you see my moments in the sun? Times when Im alive? How I feel when something is done? Catching the reason that I strive?  Do you see me on this merry-go-round? Spinning, spinning up and down?  Do you see me as a child? Doing what I love? Being able to let go and run wild? Dreams flying away like a dove?  Do you see me on this merry-go-round? Spinning, spinning up and down?  Do you see the shell Ive made? Trying to reach my ideal? Stuck inside this painted cave? Is it even real?  Do you see me on this merry-go-round? Spinning, spinning up and down?  Do you look in my eyes? And see the fires burning? Looking to the skies? Filled with a sense of yearning?  Do you see me on this merry-go-round? Spinning, spinning up and down?  Do you see the top? The highlights of my life? Or is it just the drop? When I succumb to strife?  Do you see me on this merry-go-round? Spinning, spinning up and down?  Do you see my tears? Or watch for the smiles? See me face my fears? Or run from trials?  Do you see me trapped on this merry-go-round? Spinning, spinning up and down?  Do you see honesty? My struggle to be true? Do you see me? Or just a reflection of you? 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Damn, admitting all that royally sucks. But, it's the truth and I can't pretend it isn't, no matter how much I want to.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Fragmented.  That's what we've become.  No longer close, no longer one big group, but instead lots of little overlapping groups with new alliances pulling at the framework.  When did this happen?  How did this happen?  We've floated along for so long, hanging out, bound by the past, but in reality when have we actually done something as a group.  Pairs, triples, sometimes even four of us do things but seven of us?  Was there ever just seven.  It seems as if all of our linkages have been dying and while we are all individually friends, there is no group.  Is this even a bad thing, or just different?  I don't know.  All I know is that somewhere along the line things changed. Why?  Oddly enough, I don't know how I feel about this.  A nostalgia for the past, a sadness that that chapter seems to have somehow ended and yet can't help but wonder what the future holds.  Will I become closer to each person, as I have these past few weeks, or will I drift off to some other place?  Should I even be writing this?  So many questions, so few answers.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why are some decisions hard to make, while others truly aren't?  If you think about it, some of your most trivial decisions are the ones that could change your life, while ones you agonize over could really have no affect.   Take for example choosing a route to get somewhere.  If you make a wrong turn or a careless lane change your life could be over in an instant, or it could continue on with nothing more than an angry beep of a horn. Other choices, like who to select as co-chairs have really very little lasting impact.  Yes I'll have to deal with the consequences if I make the wrong choice, but they are really quite insignificant in the scope of things.  There are other choices that I have to make in the coming weeks that I would rather pretend aren't there, simply because I'm afraid to make them.  Afraid of a response I wouldn't like, or worse pity.  I can sit at my computer knowing that the outcome will really have no effect on my life in the grand scheme of things, yet be immobilized by fear.  My dad always talks about how right now I should live for the future.  I have tried that, and I don't like it.  But I also know that I'm afraid to live in the present, afraid to take active steps of change, and so I continue on, living for the day when things will be different, when I will be different.  Will that day come? And if it does, will I recognize it, or continue to reach forward?  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We had to take the world as it was given:  The nursemaid sitting passive in the park  Was rarely by a changeling prince accosted,  The mornings happened similar and stark  In rooms of selfhood where we woke and lay  Watching today unfold like yesterday.  -Adrienne Rich  Ideal Landscapes   I can only find the first verse of the poem that ruined my day.  Its an amazing poem and one that hit home.  It goes on to talk about human nature being flawed, that we are not unearthly and that in the face of thunder we hide in the cupboard.  It also asserts that time moves on and we cannot go back.  Even if we could,  the past would not be perfect, we still would not be happy.  This poem made me uncomfortable, how is it that my dreams, my ideals don't exist?  That because of cowardice I will never move forward, changing my tomorrow so that it doesn't look like today.  Honestly I am a coward, I just hate to admit it.  I hate that part of me the part that is so intensely scared of being shut down, of being cast off.  I am sure that it is the reason that I feel so alone, that I'm so lost.  It is in this moment that I realize why I liked  The Awakening   and  The Great Gatsby  so much.  Edna and Gatsby looked out at the world and wanted something that didn't exist.  Every time I glance out my window onto the world I realize more and more that what I want doesn't exist.  If by some chance it does exist, then I will never reach it, because I am too scared to venture from my doorstep.  From a distance I can see what I want, what my ideal landscape is, yet as I approach it I realize its merely a veneer, reality gilded.  The things I am searching for don't seem to truly exist, at least not in the form that I yearn for.  The acceptance of that was enough to make me break down on my rounds as chauffeur,  As I played music and ignored the couple in the back seat, silent tears began to fall.  Losing your ideal images is heartrending and painful.  On a side note, my entire day was not bad.  I went out to dinner and a movie and Ben and Jerry's and Starbucks with Hannah, and those hours were a very nice reprieve from my thoughts of lost ideals.    
     

    
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Being a co-chair is hard. First we had to interview all these people and now we have to pick who stays and who goes.  I don't want to have to make these decisions, and yet I do.  I enjoy having this responsibility a lot until I take a look across the table and see a friend, or see a person I used to be friends with, or a friend's sibling.  Then *poof* it sucks.  Well I'm off to bed to forget about all this for a little bit.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      spring break + plans + beach = happiness  So maybe things didn't turn out as expected, my dream trip fell through.  But new things came about and these look good and happy so its ok.  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm in a hurry to get things done Oh I rush and rush until life's no fun All I really gotta do is live and die But I'm in a hurry and don't know why  Don't know why I have to drive so fast My car has nothing to prove It's not new But it'll do zero to sixty in five point two  I'm in a hurry to get things done Oh I rush and rush until life's no fun All I really gotta do is live and die But I'm in a hurry and don't know why  Can't be late, I leave in plenty of time Shakin' hands with the clock I can't stop I'm on a roll and I'm ready to rock  I'm in a hurry to get things done Oh I rush and rush until life's no fun All I really gotta do is live and die But I'm in a hurry and don't know why  Oh, I hear a voice That says I'm running behind Better pick up my pace It's a race and there ain't no room for someone in second place  I'm in a hurry to get things done Oh I rush and rush until life's no fun All I really gotta do is live and die But I'm in a hurry and don't know why  -   In a Hurry  Alabama
     

    
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Argh.  It never ends!
     

    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The e-book works (after only two hours of sweat and tears) and is very cool.  If only libraries could lend copies of ebooks, they are definitely handier than normal books, but a bit pricey.  So this is the last update until Sunday night and its pretty pathetic, but anyway, hasta el domingo, adios.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I would like to say first of all that I do not speak today only on behalf of the Israeli government but also on the behalf of all those who cannot speak of all the victims of Sheikh Yassin, of the hundreds and hundreds of Israelis who have been killed by the direct orders of this so called spiritual leader of an organization which is bent on the destruction of Israel.  Sheikh Yassin was a most dangerous terrorist chief. his elimination today Im sure in the long run, will ensure the stability of this region. Because with a weakened Hamas, I believe, I believe it will be easier to restore stability to our region.  Obviously Hamas is not dead and continues to exist as a very dangerous terrorist organization, but Hamas has been weakened and will be weakened without its leader.  We cannot forget that Sheikh Yassin was the founder of Hamas and of its terrorist ideology.  He is personally responsible for ordering the most dreadful terrorist attacks in Israel, like in the 2 yrs ago, which killed 30 people, like in Caf Moment in Jerusalem which killed 25 people.  Here we have with his disappearance now, I believe, an opportunity to weaken an extremely dangerous organization, which has proven over the last few years, that its only aim is the destruction of the state of Israel and of its inhabitants.  As you remember, Hamas declared, a few months ago, a ceasefire, which was immediately broken on the order of Sheikh Yassin.  Sheikh Yassin was a dangerous, an extreme of Islamic ideologies.  I believe that he was a threat, not only to Israel, but to the entire region.  I believe that in the least, without Sheikh Yassin, that in the long run, it will be a better place to live.  There might be some difficulties, momentarily we see, of course, whats going on in Gaza, but we are convinced that by eliminating this threat to peace we will improve conditions in the Middle East for the future.    Avi Pazner, Israeli Government Spokesman
     

    
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I freak out because wake county never bought Kissinger's new book, the one written about his role in the Yom Kippur war, the one relevant to my project, and call all the local book sellers.  It appears that neither Barnes and noble nor borders has a copy anywhere between here and chapel hill.  Giving up on the idea of getting an actual copy in time to *gasp* read it I order an ebook version of it online from Amazon.  $14 to view the book from my computer screen, pleasant, eh?  Anyway I pay for it and everything and wait for the email with the link to download it.  After an hour of waiting I get a confirmation number and go to download the book, but guess what their is a 24-hour wait time to download.  Argh, the whole damn world doesn't want me to write this paper.  Its driving me up a wall.  So tomorrow I'm going to go buy a power converter for the car so that I can take my dad's laptop with me to Charleston to write my paper and read my book along the way.    On a side note I managed to book the rooms.  It came to $31 a person so I need the money ASAP, my dad isn't thrilled that I had to pay to reserve.  We are staying at the Courtyard Carolina Beach in non-smoking rooms and with a request for two cots.  Oh and guys, I did not reserve your room, the ball is in your court and at the moment I don't care if you reserve a room or not.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm going to take a few minutes to freak out and probably burst into tears again, I'm feeling just slightly overwhelmed.  Ok, so the much dreaded Charleston trip is this week.  Mom and I leave Wednesday after school to begin the college segment of the trip.  Then she leaves and I stay in Charleston with my religious school director, Abby, and the twins.  While nothing particularly vile is happening and I don't actively hate everyone going I'm not having nice feelings about the trip.  I come home Sunday night and have to go to school on Monday.  So then comes all the stuff due Monday and Tuesday.  Next week is the end of the grading period and that means that everything is due next week.  So while I'm in Charleston I will miss a calc test and an APUSH test.  Due Monday is the take home test for English and some poster presentation in science.  My massive history paper is due Tuesday and I just spent the past four hours working on it and made absolutely no progress whatsoever.  I have work tomorrow afterschool, an SLA meeting next Tuesday, an overdue Spanish journal entry, another one due when I get back because I'm missing the Spanish flex activity.  I have my their eyes were watching G-d study guide due tomorrow as well as two nights worth of calculus and the dogs won't stop crying, not to mention my mother keeps calling up the stairs asking me when I plan to do the dishes.  My room is so disgusting that I couldn't sleep last night and I somehow managed to make it worse when cleaning it, I have no clean laundry, or if I do I can't find it in the wreckage.  Kayla stayed home today watching movies and ransacking the house, all signs of illness mysteriously disappearing after all family members left.  Also, my phone is missing and dead somewhere in the house.  I could go on but I'm making myself feel worse instead of better.  Now I have to try and track down a copy of Kissinger's new book and somehow read it and incorporate it into my paper by Tuesday morning.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is to be a religion based blog entry, if that bothers you skip it.  I went to a choir concert tonight.  Sha'rei's girls have had this little choir all year and finally performed.  Because of religious restrictions the audience was entirely female, and it didn't seem to bother anyone at all.  I heard two of the most beautiful, comforting songs I have heard in a long time.  They weren't beautiful because of the singers, because some of the girls weren't great, but because of something deeper.  When I was just a small girl I heard the legend of the dove Like all the other animals  Hashem created it with love  But the dove was special For it was so pure and white Hashem sent it to the forest To turn the darkness into light  But all the animals were jealous And their hatred grew so strong They plotted ways to rid themselves Of the dove and its sweet songs  First the Tiger, then the Jaguar Then the Bear, Then the Snake When they'd attack, the dove would run And the dove barely escaped  So the dove turned to Hashem Tears streaming down his face I feel that I am alone With no one close to me  But then from under Hashem's throne Where He stores his precious things He gave the dove a special gift He gave the Dove his wings  And He said higher and higher Higher than the sky Higher and higher Its as high as you can fly You'll fly up to the heavens Even higher than you dream Higher and higher You'll fly close to me  The dove went to the forest With confidence and pride He'd never have to run again And he's never have to hide  He would always be protected And now that he had wings He would sit in a treetop And the world would hear him sing  But all the animals were furious When they saw the dove's new wings It was as if Hashem was telling them That the dove would be their king  So they pounced upon the dove And he could barely fly They left him torn and wounded They left him there to die  So the dove turned to Hashem And he cried it isn't fair These precious wings you gave to me That I always have to wear  They are so very heavy Much more than I can bear Please take me from the forest I cannot take it here  And Hashem turned to the dove My child please understand Now I have given you these wings Your destiny is in your hands  If you use your wings for flying They'll never weigh you down And you'll fly much higher Than those who live upon the ground  And you'll go higher and higher Higher than the sky Higher and higher Its as high as you can fly You'll fly up to the heavens Even higher than you dream Higher and higher You'll fly close to me  The dove returned back to the forest And now the others lay in wait They'd attack in unison And this time death would be his fate  But the dove was so determined And he began to fly And like Hashem had promised him He soared up to the sky  And he went higher and higher Higher than the sky Higher and higher Its as high as you can fly You'll fly up to the heavens Even higher than you dream Higher and higher You'll fly close to me  Our story has concluded But friends there's one more thing The little dove that's you and me And the Torah is our wings  You'll fly up to the heavens Even higher than you dream Higher and higher  You'll fly close to me - Higher and Higher      Mother please tell me Help me understand Who made what surrounds us The sky and the land  The water we drink The air that we breathe Mother please tell me  What should I believe?  Listen my child Put your trust in me There is a creator that man cannot see And we owe our existence To no one but him Beraishis Barah Elokim ( G-d created the world )  Its not just a story A tale that's been told A fable, a myth, or a legend of old  It's not someone's fantasy, theory or whim It's what I believe Ani Maamin  Mother please tell me I'm asking of you Why am I different What makes me a Jew  How am I to know The right life to lead Mother please tell me What am I to believe  Listen My child  I was long, long ago When we stood by a mountain One nation one soul And what we received Is our very life's blood Naaseh V'nishmah Amru K'echad (  We will do and we will hear, they said as one )  Its not just a story A tale that's been told A fable, a myth, or a legend of old  It's not someone's fantasy, theory, or whim It's what I believe Ani Maamin  Mother please tell me  What does G-d intend Will this long bitter exile soon come to an end Or must we continue to grieve Mother please tell me What I believe?  Listen my child  The future will bring A day when the world knows who's King of all kings Today or tomorrow I don't need to know Achakeh Lo B'chol Yom Sheyavo ( I await his coming every day ) - Mother Please Tell Me   The concert was absolutely beautiful.  It was at someone's home and the acoustics weren't great, but none of that mattered.  Every single one of the girls got a solo and if one stumbled the others, or the audience, would help her along.  They knew all the songs by heart and stood proud and tall at the microphone.  Their shyness and insecurities, which I know they have, dropped away before the women of their community, they were just part of the whole.  It was amazing to be a part of that.  Leah, Helana, Leiba, Kaila and Chaya sang a few songs together.  The first two are the Rabbis Herman's wives, the middle is Rabbi Pinney's daughter and the last two are teachers at hillel.  I sat there watching these five beautiful women sing their hearts out in front of everyone and was jealous.  I have never felt jealousy so strongly before.  The women standing before me were talented and loved, they had a place securely in the community and are totally confident in themselves.  Their belief is so strong that they can face the world, different from the rest.  While they were singing I forgot who they were, what they were.  They weren't five orthodox women, some fanatics or pious saints, but simply people.  Leiba wasn't Rabbi's oldest about to leave for seminary.  Helana and Leah weren't rebetzins.  Watching them share their gifts with the community to which they belonged did make me jealous.  I was more jealous than I have ever been before,  I wanted that more than I've wanted anything before.  It shocked me to realize it, that I wanted to be one of those girls singing in the choir, that I wanted to go back and have that memory in my past, to know that I could stand before a group of people without fear and sing, even though I might fail.  To know that if I failed, someone would be there to help me move on.  Now that I have this knowledge of what I want, I don't know what to do. My life would be so different, if I followed that path.  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm really gone this time...I'll return on Sunday.  If you can't live without my wit and charm for 3 days call me on my cell and I might take time out of my schedule to talk.  Have a good weekend y'all.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So RUACH turned into a one on one learning session with me and Rabbi Herman, but it was still pretty cool.  He talked about why during Passover we read this whole long discussion between Rabbis on whether or not we should read the third paragraph of the shema, the most important daily prayer, at night.  The paragraph talks of remembering the exodus from Egypt.  He asked me what Egypt represented and I said slavery, and he asked what slavery was and I said restriction.  So then working with that definition the whole thing takes on new meanings, and when we say the shema , it is to remind ourselves to work our way out of restrictions, whether they are self imposed, physical or societal, to improve ourselves.  But I'll stop boring you with this stuff, but its pretty cool and I can't really do it justice.    I'll be gone until Sunday afternoon, so no new posts, sorry.
     

    
</post>

<date>31,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      From the renowned astrologist Josh Sokol, who also happens to be a freshman in my pubs class (imagine that!) comes my wonderful horoscope...  Capricorn (December 22  January 19) All the good things that happened for Sagittarius leave you lonely and penniless. Since God has abandoned you, you turn to Satan worship. You find friendship in your worse enemy, who promptly stabs you in the back.  check out yours on the  urlLink flame web site ...I spent the past week creating and testing links, someone had better look at it!  Horoscopes are in the "you call this a life" category and under the title "what does the future hold" and are definitely worth the time it takes to find them
     

    
</post>

<date>31,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This summer a counselor at Kanata died in a car accident, involving a cop who ran a flashing red light in the middle of the night.  Matt (Dukie) West was 17 when he died and from the little I knew him an awesome person.  The cop received his  urlLink sentence  today, a $100 fine and a citation.  He admitted to running the light, and that he was not answering a call.  $100 and a slap on the wrist, it drives me absolutely crazy.  But when I told my dad about it his response was "what would you have wanted the penalty to have been if you had killed someone in your accident?  You essentially did the same thing, would you want to go to jail?"  I really don't know the answer to that and that bothers me.  Is it ok to be hypocritical?  Dukie is gone and the penalty on the cop really won't change that, yet it still bothers me.  Teenagers aren't supposed to die, especially ones that you know and like.  Damn it...Why can't there be no heartache, no trouble?
     

    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      By the way...the really really long post should probably be four smaller posts but got jammed together, sorry for those of y'all whose eyes rolled back into your heads when you saw it.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It is done.  It being the evil two headed monster of a paper on the effect of Nuclear Politics in US intervention of the Yom Kippur War.  After completing 12 pages with footnotes and toting the laptop around charleston on the first half of my trip I can't say I'm sad to see it go.  I think I'm going to avoid Israel in future papers, this is the second major one I've written and I need a new topic.  But off to bed with me, still tired from my trip.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What makes me happy? Do I even know?  There are days when I just am and others when I'm not.  Why was I so giddy on the swing last night?  Was it an act or me? Hmm... I had an awesome weekend: sun, pretty college, boat, and a new friend.  Is it as easy as that? We'll just have to see.   Charleston made me happy with its pretty buildings and weather.  The trip was fun, who would have thought?  Cheer and smiles, services on the beach.  Our mini service was amazing.  Picture yourself standing on the edge of the water, waves almost lapping your toes as the sun sets behind you and the wind rustles through your hair.  Now add to that the comforting and welcoming melodies of Kabbalat Shabbat and you have a rough idea of it.  The wind seemed to carry our prayer, and our cares away, up to heaven.  It was truly a divinely inspired moment.  Time stooped, everyone disappeared and the moment overtook me.  Then suddenly it was over and we went home as if nothing happened. But back to happiness.  What is it?  Is it in the past, moments that flutter by and never return?  Or is it a constant, merely interrupted by bursts of unhappiness?  Is that why we rarely notice ourselves happy, that we only notice its absence?  Why do I complain so much?  I'm always whining, always seem to be looking for sympathy, do me a favor smack me the next time I whine.  My life is full of happy moments, but they are so easy to forget.  Next time I'm sad will I remember swinging on the dock?  Remember how I nearly lost my Rainbows over the edge?  Remember praying in the sand?  Remember the boat ride to Fort Sumter breaking every rule in sight and pretending to be King (technically queen) of the world on the bow of the ferry boat?  Or, will all I remember be the sunburn and being tongue tied on the tour of the college? I hope I remember the happy and for get the rest.  As Hurston wrote: "Women forget all those things they don't want to remember, and remember everything they don't want to forget."  I don't like having a selective mood based memory. When we were downtown last night some guys had their stereo blasting and were jamming at a stoplight.  In the middle of this crowded street and stoplight everything just kind of stopped.  People started bobbing to the music and one girl was in the midst of the crosswalk and started to dance around.  People heckled and cheered, the music played and the world stopped turning while it was caught in the moment.  Then as suddenly as it began the light changed and everything started up again.  Is that life?  Just a glimpse and as soon as you get in the groove its gone?  Or does it continue on in your mind and the minds of those around you becoming immortalized?    Driving home I'm watching the clouds, constantly shifting, constantly changing.  Nobody notices when a cloud  changes shape, changes texture, falls apart or gathers together.  A cloud is allowed to be free, allowed to change.  Why can't I suddenly change? Why must people be surprised when I do things, when I change my life, my clothes, or G-d forbid, my mind?  Why do I have a box, a peg on the wall?  Everyone thinks they know me, and I really don't even know myself.  I want to be a cloud, allowed to change, allowed to drift and then return.  I want to float away and be recreated over and over again.  But that can't happen.  I can't go back and don't want to rush forward.  I lived this weekend in the moment, forgot who I was supposed to be, what I was supposed to be doing and just lived.  I wasn't Elena: GPA of 3.5 unwieghted, 4.6 weighted, SAT score 1410, Co-president of SLA and Sunday school teacher.  Instead I was Elena: 17 year old girl at the beach.  Big difference.  No one cared whether or not I'm going to prom, whether or not I did my homework, what music I listened to.  The only future planning I did was in my imagination and the only writing was the exchange of contact info.  Because I was with people I didn't know super well I was able to release.  Did you know I could walk into the ocean fully dressed without thinking about it?  Did you know I could jump onto a moving porch swing?  I certainly didn't.  It was the most fun I've had in a long, long time.  I don't need a box anymore, I can build a new one.  But even as I write this I get closer to home and I feel my box coming back together.  Back to the mindset of school work and papers and deadline.  The clouds are going away, and with them goes the freedom and lightness that I felt.  One day they will return, giant and wispy, and maybe next time I will leave with them.  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Standing in Barnes and Noble I remembered why I have never had an established journal.  I have commitment issues.  I can't find something good enough for me to want to keep onto for a long long time.  Those that I would want to hold onto are too expensive and not nearly resilient enough for a life with me.  So instead I write in transient little notebooks that I then lose.  In a lot of ways my relationships with journals are very similar to my life.  I don't make lasting ties and commitments get forgotten.  Wow, that's pretty depressing.  I'm going to go drown my thoughts in a quart of watermelon.  
     

    
</post>

<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      And the binging continues...  "I remembered something my father'd once said, that anything too stupid to be spoken is sung" - Fell  M.E. Kerr  I reread over my blog and realized a lot.  I lie frequently, well in reality lying isn't the right word, I downplay the validity of what I feel.  I either mask it with song lyrics or a quote or post a something a few hours later along the lines of "late night blogging makes me melodramatic".  It is really scary and really clarifying to be able to read back over what I have written in the past five months.  It has only been five and a half months since I began and I don't recognize that person anymore.  There were parts of my blog that made me cry, to remember things that I have somehow managed to hide away and pretend to forget. There were others that made me smile.  But the ones that stuck the most were the ones in which I bared my soul and managed somehow to hide it, almost to the point that I personally can't tell the deception from the truth.  How did things change so drastically?  How did my blog become meaningful instead of some hobby to keep me occupied when lounging in my room?  Are other people's blogs more meaningful than they appear?  Why are some magically forgotten?  All wonderful topics to be attacked at another time.  Out of curiosity what are your views on going back and editing or adding entries to months ago?  Should they be changed or stay the same?  I honestly don't know. 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm blog binging tonight...  Time is a cruel thief to rob us of our former selves. We lose as much to life as we do to death. -Elizabeth Forsythe Hailey, 'A Woman of Independent Means'  Nothing is as far away as one minute ago. -Jim Bishop   My goal for tomorrow: Find the perfect book.  I don't want a book with words on the pages, but pages and pages of nothingness.  I have never owned something bound and substantial for the express purpose of writing.  I have jotted in spiral notebooks, typed on this blog, even stood in a boathouse and written on the walls in paint, yet none of that is permanent.  Those things are meant to fade overtime.  I want a place to store profound thoughts, some that might even be my own, mainly borrowed wisdom.  I change every moment that I breathe and what I value changes too.  I want something that reflects that, that mirrors my progression.  So tomorrow I will take the first step in that and try to find a book that I am willing to commit to keeping.  It will most likely be simple, something that I hope to become.  I doubt I will find it but we shall see.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I got an email from Hawaii Pacific University...Sunshine, Beaches, Rainbows and Waterfalls, sounds perfect, but wait...would I really be willing to sit in class all day everyday?  I think not! So much for that plan.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Swan, a new television show, has shown just how low society has sunk.  Every week the producers of the show take average looking women and do massive surgery and life restructuring to turn them into possible beauty queens.  A woman who was maybe a little over average weight was given liposuction in 5 different areas, had her face restructured in plastic surgery, given false veneers over her existing teeth and 3 months with a personal trainer to make her look beautiful.  Instead of looking at someone and seeing the beauty they carry with them this show teaches us to look at people and see what they could be with some help from some very skilled surgeons.  This show is not real life, yet raises the bar for the rest of the world pushing expectations and possibilities.  I don't look at these girls and say wow, isn't that amazing, I look at these girls and say wow that's atrocious.  There are people in this world who deal with serious cosmetic flaws, they do not look average, and I'm not saying that cosmetic surgery is evil.  But to totally remake someone who does not look bad, just because its possible to make them look better is sickening.  What hope does it give to everyone else when they see someone who looks similar to themselves go through millions of dollars worth of surgery for no better reason than that they were picked by a TV show.  These women claim to have no self esteem because of the way they look, but what will they have in 5 years when the surgery begins to sag and decay?  Maybe instead of focusing on our exteriors we should move within ourselves and begin working there.  Lack of self esteem is an awful thing, but fleeting beauty is not the way to solve it.  
     

    
</post>

<date>07,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So the beach was absolutely awesome.  Spring break is flying by so fast tomorrow is already thursday.  Because it feels like summer and I love the song(yes Diana and Sam have corrupted me):  Well, I'm a'gonna raise a fuss, An' I'm a'gonna raise a holler I've been working all summer Just to try and earn a dollar Well I went to the boss Said I had a date The boss said "No dice, son, you gotta work late" Sometimes I wonder what I'm a'gonna do There ain't no cure for the summertime blues  Well my mom and poppa told me "Son you gotta earn some money, If you want to use the car To go out next Sunday."  Well I didn't go to work I told the boss I was sick He said "You can't use the car 'cause you didn't work a lick." Sometimes I wonder what I'm a'gonna do Cause there ain't no cure for the summertime blues.  Gonna take two weeks Gonna have a fine vacation Gonna take my problems To the United Nations Well I went to my congressman He said, quote: "I'd like to help you son, But you're too young to vote." Sometimes I wonder what I'm a'gonna do Cause there ain't no cure for the summertime blues.  - Summertime Blues , The Who  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm home, I'm exhausted and I'm in a bad mood.  I had an awesome weekend.  It was just as cool, but in a different way, as the Charleston trip.  Most of the people I met were pretty sketchy but it was still awesome.  The bad mood is induced by a lot of things:  The first thing said to me as I walk through the door after getting a grand total of 10 hours of sleep is "Elena I need you to mow the lawn," my dad is lying on the couch watching some show on the discovery and he needs me to mow the lawn, then the psychotic sibling came home, the psychotic sibling who is currently crying and cursing at me because I shot down her plans for her and her friend to tag along on MY beach trip.  In addition to this G-d awful, totally stupid unauthorized plan my mother told her that Derick can spend the night Monday night and we will drop him off at home somehow on the way to the beach! How the hell is Garner anywhere near the beach and how the hell do we plan to make this whole thing work.  My mom totally doesn't get the group thing and it's pissing me off.  Finally the last thing that ruined my day is our summer vacation.  She fucking planned it to start the Sunday after school gets out! I had called that week to spend with all of y'all before I go away to camp for who knows how long.  So instead of seeing my friends I'll get to spend time with psycho and the parents.  We'll get home sometime mid Saturday and I will leave for Kanata Sunday morning at 8.  Sounds as much fun as a barrel of monkeys...I HATE MY FAMILY right now
     

    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My belief in my religion has been reaffirmed by a  urlLink website , aren't you excited?  I came out 100% reform jew and 96% orthodox jew.  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am currently so insanely pissed off that I do not know what to do.  Why does doing a nice thing always seem to become some big stressful ordeal?
     

    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So Blogger tries to match up advertisements to your blog that seem fitting.  On the top of Kit's blog today was this  urlLink link .  It amuses me greatly.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The rain is seeping in making me sleepy and unproductive...
     

    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This song amuses me greatly (maybe its because I'm a good little girl)  She's a momma's baby  She's her daddy's pride and joy  They've kept her under eyes  She aint been hangin out with any ugly actin boy  Hardly ever been kissed  Twenty years of inocence   And just what I'm lookin for  I wanna be the man who's a  Holdin her hand when she can't hold it back nomore   Good little girls make some mighty wild women  Been saving it up since the very beginning  When They fall in love they wanna take it to the limit Good little girls make some mighty wild women   Well, she's never been to Vegas  Or danced in a honky tonk  No trail of broken hearts  Although she looks the part  That aint the kind of life she wants  Shes waiting for a gold ring  Before she tries her wings   Thats what I'm waiting for  I wanna be the man whos a  Holding her hand when she cant hold it back no more   Good little girls make some mighty wild women  Been saving it up since the very beginning  When They fall in love they wanna take it to the limit Good little girls make some mighty wild women   Good little girls make some mighty wild women  Been saving it up since the very beginning  When They fall in love they wanna take it to the limit  Good little girls make some mighty wild women  Been saving it up since the very beginning  When They fall in love they wanna take it to the limit  Good little girls make some mighty wild women   Good little girls make some mighty wild women   - Good little girls  Blue County 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      How can break fly by so fast?  There was so much I wanted to accomplish, but never got to.  Sleep was one of those things... I also packed more in than I can ever remember doing before.  In the past 10 days I: went to YLA, helped prepare a Seder, went to my first Seder at someone else's house, first overnight at the beach with friends, got sunburned, played Frisbee and volley ball, jumped in to the ultra cold ocean, got hollered at while on a balcony, joy rode the island with friends in the mustang, washed the inside and outside of my car, played with my neighbors, got a massage and facial, wore way way too much makeup at the mall, went out to lunch and a movie, ran across 5 lanes of traffic.  Its no wonder that I had to get up at the crack of dawn to finish up homework before school.  Why must we return to school?  But alas we must and luckily there are only 7 weeks remaining!  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Good bye beloved break...I will miss you, but look back and smile with fond memories of interesting incidents...
     

    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Thought I'd join the club and share some  urlLink googlisms  with y'all: elena is a very special 'package' elena is reverent elena is busy elena is cool elena is seventeen years old elena is in mourning for her brother federigo d'austria who has been executed as a traitor elena is without a doubt the best thing i have ever done in my life elena is a werewolf who has left her pack elena is a composite drawn from several real people elena is pretty impossible at this point elena is no longer disoriented  elena is a world elena is also very humble elena is always available elena is a very beautiful young woman with brown eyes and hair elena is a fair tempered humanoid elena is not a licensed private investigator and she is afraid to break her self elena is reputably cold and unemotional
     

    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So what's the deal with beeping?  Why do random guys feel compelled to beep their horns as they drive by? Sorry, sorry but its bugging me.  It doesn't piss me off so much as catch me off balance. Realistically, what's the point of it?  At least heckling might have some possible outcome, but beeping as you go speeding by at 30 mph?  What's with that?  I'm going to stop now because this isn't helpful. It's been slowly driving me crazy for a while now.  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Shopping is really good therapy when you are stressed, especially when kohls is having massive sales and your mommy gives you her charge card and an $80 limit to find some spring stuff.  I got: 2 new skirts, 5 tank tops, a halter top and one pair of tinkerbell pajama pants.  I really don't want to lose this post shopping high by doing homework but can't afford to skip another night.  Why can't all of this school work stuff just end?
     

    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "I'm old, Gandalf. I don't look it, but I feel it in my bones. I feel stretched, like butter spread over too much bread. I need a holiday, a very long holiday, and I don't expect I shall return. In fact, I mean not to." -Bilbo Baggins  Why is it that blogs are neglected when life is good and overly typed in when life isn't so good?  Is my blog my rainy weather friend?  Only when I'm stressed do I feel a strong urge to blog.  Hmm...
     

    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Do you think life goes on forever?  That behind every chance comes another one and another one and another?  It's the worst kind of extravagance, the way you spend your chances."  What an amazing movie with Sandra Bullock, Harry Connick Jr. and Gena Rowlands as headliners.  I finally saw it for the first time all the way through.  Its about a woman whose husband leaves her and her daughter, forcing her to move back to her small home town to live with her mother and start anew.  Watch it if you haven't, it's definitely worth it.   "The American Dream. You find something that you love and then you twist it and torture it trying to find a way to make money at it.  You can spend a lifetime doing that and at the end you can't find a trace of what you started out loving." - Hope Floats 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I accomplished a lot of studying tonight....Not  Between watching the One Tree Hill I taped (gotta get those guys!) and 2 trips to Armadillo Grill, Fletcher Park, and Starbucks with Sam and Diana did you really expect otherwise? 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I did it.  I finished the essay for the contest and am proud of it.  It needs to be edited tomorrow and then can be mailed away.  Wow.  It feels good to get it on paper, to get it all down.  I feel clean and honest.  Emotion did seep through and I think it made it stronger, made it more real.  It has been a long long time since I've allowed myself to just write.  Everything seems to have become false.  Papers and journal entries at school have dulled my writing, have cornered it in a box and taken away the freedom and power I feel when I am writing something I care about, something I am proud of.  I can never become a writer, it would kill me to have to write to a specific thing, to have commitments to others twist my words.  I worked through this essay, worked through some of my baggage, and worked through the chaos that this essay made me feel and because of all that working I can lie back in exhausted bliss.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm so tired and so stressed yet I seem to endlessly waste time.  Why is it that amongst all of things on my to do list I still find time to waste in front of the computer or TV?  I don't know but its getting ridiculous.  What is even sadder is that I've seemed to have disappeared.  Friday night was awesome, but did I post about it? Did I write about my time at UNC? No.  I forget what I do each day, moving forward in a daze, looking to the end, but not knowing what I'm looking forward to.  I'm stuck in this cloud of fog and can't see out.  Instead I see swirls, hints of things that used to be bright and clear and a slight foreshadow of the future. When did my present become a way station to bigger and better things?  When did I begin to accept tomorrow as an appropriate time to do everything?
     

    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Do you ever feel as if life is slipping by?  Right now I feel as if I'm flying.  It used to be a good feeling, to be free and unfettered, but now it just feels pathetic.  Instead of feeling wonderfully content and spontaneous, because I never have plans, I feel lost and alone.  It has gotten to the point where my errands are the highlight of my week.  When did this happen when did I fall off of the face of the planet? Why did this happen?  I've taken to sitting in seclusion and watching shows like Sex and the City.  Wow... Any way summer is approaching and instead of feeling good about that I'm scared.  What if everyone has forgotten about me when I come home, or worse, I forget about everyone.  I don't want to stay at camp all summer because I want time with friends, but will we really ever do something? Or, will it be like last summer where I was home but they weren't or I was home but working, or I was just too lazy to pick up the phone.  A better question to have started this entry with would have been, when did I become so insecure?  Instead of feeling better for writing this I feel worse, so I think I'll stop while I still have a shred of self respect. Do I really mean that?  Argh, my world seems to be such a mess right now.  Flying really isn't fun when you don't know how to land, but realize you are running out of gas.  What I really need is a genie to straighten it all up again.  *sigh*
     

    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Where have the days gone?  I've been counting down days until summer for a while now and forgot one tiny detail.  Well, its not tiny at all, it is humongus.  In less than 4 weeks classes will be over and in 3 weeks work will be finished.  Yay right? Well the think I forgot in all of my looking to the future was all of my casual friendships.  People I'm not close enough to  pick up the phone and make plans to see a movie with them.  I love the guys at work, we have a blast joking around and goofing off in class, yet we have no real common ground for a friendship.  Unfortunately the more I think about this year ending the more I realize I've forgotten.  I've forgotten that we are all individual variables, not constants.  I've forgotten that every year, every month, every day, every moment I change.  My thoughts, my actions, my values they all are constantly changing and so are everybody else's.  With the end of school comes summer at time where we all grow distant and lead individual lives.  I will leave camp a different person than I was when I arrived.  I will return to a world that has changed without me, friends who have also done so.  With summer uncertainty returns, what will be here when I return? Will we still be able to be close?  To reform the bonds that tighten every year?  Or, will my entire world no longer keep me content, will I be searching for that feeling that can only come with change? When counting down the days it is easy to forget so many things, to push aside all fears of the future just to escape the present.  Now that I can see the light it is too late to turn around and run in the opposite direction, but it is the only thing I want to do now.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Go into your 25th post. Copy the 5th line. Paste it here along with the directions.   It has been a long time since I have been so wrapped up in a moment of rest, and I didn't realize how I missed it so much.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I can't sleep.  I tried and all I accomplished was a lot of tossing and turning.  I'm all churned up from the dance and can't seem to detox.  So instead I figured I would babble here.  I was reading this romance novel  Face the Fire  for purely entertainment because I've simply been too tired to read something that would make me think, but guess what it did.  Well, actually one quote did.  "Some people expect things to fall into their lap. Oh, they might work a bit for it.  I'll just shake this tree, and if I shake it long enough that pretty red apple will plop right into my hand.  Never occurs to them that they might have to climb the damn tree, fall out a couple of times, get some scrapes and bruises before they get to that apple.  Because if the apple's worth wanting, it's worth risking a broken neck."  I realize sitting here that I've never climbed a tree, never been able to risk harm.  I've always been sedate and cautious, hiding behind such things as books and fabricated images.  When I say I've never climbed a tree I mean that literally as well as symbolically.  I have begun to many times but have always stopped as soon as I realize that my feet can no longer touch the ground.  I have always maintained control, maintained my buffer and because of that have never tasted the sweet fruit of beating the odds.  Have I ever wanted something enough to say that I was willing to risk a broken neck?  Yes.  Have I ever gone out on a limb, truly with no backup plan, no harness to catch me if things don't work out exactly as planned?  No.  I am a chronic over analyzer, I pick apart everything I do or say and find flaws, supposedly to help myself.  Instead all that happens is that I lose confidence, lose the strength and blinding excitement that could carry me into the high branches of that apple tree.  I continuously stand on the ground colliding over and over again with the trunk, waiting for the apple to fall, but it is not until the apple is old and rotten that I am able to obtain it.  How does one go about learning to climb trees?  Is there a secret out there somewhere, a book that contains the instructions? Or is it one of those touchy feely, 'every person's journey is different' type of experiences?    My goals for the summer and the future in general: climb a tree, risk it all keep in touch with my current world find some answers learn to enjoy every moment as much as I can  I know they seem cliche and somewhat kitschy but at the moment that is how my mind is operating and playing the game.  
     

    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So tonight was awesome.  For once I did not feel like an outsider at a school function.  Apathy has a lot to do with it.  Since there are only two weeks left I don't feel the need to fight so hard to fit into my little spot.  Instead I was able to let loose and dance, albeit poorly.  My life is changing.  For once I can feel it.  In a way its kind of like special relativity, even though I'm always moving forward I don't feel it unless the process accelerates or decelerates.  Right now I'm accelerating. In a way my life feels a lot like driving home tonight.  The windows were down, it was dark and the music was blaring.  But with all of those distractions I still felt one with the car, one with the road.  There is no greater feeling than driving fast on dark windy roads.   It makes me feel simultaneously in control and out of control.  And that's what life feels like right now, a dark windy road.  Yet while I'm ready to press down the accelerator and see where this road leads I can't help but look in the rear-view mirror wistfully at what I'm leaving behind.  So, I'm off to bed to dream happy dreams and do some serious thinking about which road to take at the next intersection that comes my way.   One more thing...Assertiveness is a good thing.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm out of things to say.  Ideas of what to write seem to have left me and I am filled with a sense of loss.  I used to be creative, I used to be a free(ish) thinker.  I used to be able to compose entire entries in my mind.  I can no longer do that, I don't know what to expect when I sit down at the keyboard anymore.  My fingers do the typing almost before my mind knows what it is thinking.  It's odd but I learned to live with it.  I got used to the soothing flow of clicking keys and being able to watch my thoughts progress in front of me.  But even that is gone.  My days have become lazy, trivial at school and systematic at home.  I come home change my clothes and lie out in the sun reading for an hour, then I come in and shower and either go next door or settle down in front of the TV.  I eat dinner and then waste time pretending to do homework or talking online.  Nothing new has really happened, at least not worth recording.  I need something to inspire me.  I need some sort of muse.  hmmm, where can I find a muse?
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm out of things to say.  Ideas of what to write seem to have left me and I am filled with a sense of loss.  I used to be creative, I used to be a free(ish) thinker.  I used to be able to compose entire entries in my mind.  I can no longer do that, I don't know what to expect when I sit down at the keyboard anymore.  My fingers do the typing almost before my mind knows what it is thinking.  It's odd but I learned to live with it.  I got used to the soothing flow of clicking keys and being able to watch my thoughts progress in front of me.  But even that is gone.  My days have become lazy, trivial at school and systematic at home.  I come home change my clothes and lie out in the sun reading for an hour, then I come in and shower and either go next door or settle down in front of the TV.  I eat dinner and then waste time pretending to do homework or talking online.  Nothing new has really happened, at least not worth recording.  I need something to inspire me.  I need some sort of muse.  hmmm, where can I find a muse?
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm so tired but AP exams are done.  I can now relax and have fun.  It's a relatively new feeling, this having fun thing.  Conversations are so much more interesting and enjoyable now that I'm relaxed and open to silliness and games.  Thats enough for now, too chill to keep going with this thought.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have written approximately 30,000 words to date in this blog.  I'm telling the truth, blogger claims that I've written 29,700 and some words.  In all of that blabber have I once said something profound or useful to anyone out there but my self?  I can't believe I have written that much.  The number is staggering.  30,000...Wow.  Anyway the blog got a face lift.  My life is jealous.  It seems as if everything in the world moves on except me.  I'm stuck in the same place, like a little child, waiting for someone to take my hand and help me cross the street safely.  I don't like changing.  I like changes to occur, and need one to occur soon, but I don't like making them happen.  I am not a catalyst, at least not in my own life. I can demand things of the people around me, I can motivate them to change, yet here I am stuck in a rut and not confident enough to leave it.  Why is it that we (I'm assuming I'm not truly all alone here) lack the ability to change our own world, yet expect others to change theirs?  Why is it that when someone takes a drastic step we are shocked?  Having a good group of people is like having a crutch.  You become content and lazy and timid.  Slowly but surely you work yourself into a rut.  But now a new season is coming upon the world.  With this season I want to embrace new people, new routines, and a new me.  Then maybe I will be ready to embrace a new you.       
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The storm is coming in.  I can feel it.  I went outside to get my work bag so that I could begin report cards and was surprised to realize how close it was.  Before I even stepped of the porch I could hear the soft rumble of thunder and see the sky come alive with bolts of electricity.  Once enveloped in the darkness I could hear the wind and feel it across my skin.  Combined with the electricity of the air I began to tingle all over, and for the first time in a long time the sense of loneliness faded.  I have no idea how long I stood there, eyes shut, just feeling the weather, feeling alive and connected.  I could hear the thunder, the wind, the frogs in the pond and the low hum of traffic.  I could feel the cool air brushing by, the vibrancy and current pulsing through it, the power it contained.  And with every bolt of lightning I could see the edges of the things around me, the trees, the houses, the clouds.  It was like a spark pulsed through me and took over for a moment. Just thinking about it brings back the feeling and returns those magic moments to my mind.  The storm brings me hope, it lets me know that there will be turbulence, will be a show of power, will be consequences, but it will pass through and be replaced by a clean new day, waiting to be explored. 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If you think of life as a winding trail I seem to have just gone around a bend.  I can't tell if I'm just a little ahead of everyone or a little behind.  It's like driving on a winding road at night, there are lights in front of you and behind you, leading you forward into the darkness and revealing where you've been.  But every so often the road curves and for just a moment you lose sight of both.  For that short time you are both awed and scared.  Awed because what is around you is so beautiful, so seemingly calm and peaceful, but scared because you are alone and can't tell what's ahead.  For those few moments you have nothing but the thoughts in your head and the music in your CD player to keep you company.  The thoughts in my head lately have echoed the road.  I'm alone.  I can be surrounded by people, surrounded by noise and light, but I still feel like I'm on that road, watching, waiting, but distinctly alone.  But more than simply being alone, I feel it, a yearning, a sense of my loneliness.  I don't know why, particularly since lately I've been more social, more friendly, more flirtatious, but I am, I am lonely.  Can it be the apathy, my acceptance that the year is ending, that we will all be moving into separate lives?  Or is it more, is it deeper than that?  I am choosing to look at this feeling as temporary, that pretty soon the road will line up again and I will catch sight of someone else, but what if I'm wrong?  What if the road is perfectly straight and simply deserted?  What if I'm lost? 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm in a new place, with the same face  And nothing is familiar to me,  But theres a storm rush, then the wind starts And its bringing out the woman in me I know that you're out there somewhere  Waiting on a deeper connection Now I'm lookin to my left, searching on my right 'Cause we could be the greatest adventure, I'm  Ready Come and find me, I'm not gonna hide I got the sun on my side, it's Heavy 'cause I'm finally open for the one and  I'm ready, ready   I'm moving out there,  So baby beware, because now its just a matter of time  (now it's just a matter of time)  Before our paths cross, and the sky falls,  The very moment that I tell you you're mine  I know that you're out there somewhere  Moving in another direction So just hurry up and come, as fast as you can run,  I've been waiting far too long, and I'm  Ready Come and find me, I'm not gonna hide I got the sun on my side, it's Heavy 'cause I'm finally open for the one and  I'm ready, ready  Oh you, You gotta be close,  Because I breathe you in and out, wherever I go,  Ohh  I'm ready  Come and find me, I'm not gunna hide,  I got the sun on my side, it's  Heavy, 'cause I'm finally, open for the one,  I'm ready  I'm ready for love, I'm ready - I'm Ready  Cherie 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yearbooks arrived!!!! They are beautiful and done, and I'm in it.  All of this makes me happy, but what makes me happiest are the things people have written.  While I have been sad when looking back at last year's yearbook, I also have been forced to admit a few things to myself.  I have moved on, I am a different person and the new relationships in my life reflect that.  I am no longer serious and quiet, seemingly shy and terribly forgetable.  I hope that people now know who I am and that yes, I am in their ______ class.  The people who signed my yearbook now are the people who i wanted to sign it.  there really are none of those random impersonal notes that consumed my yearbooks of the past.  Its just different.  I can really see a change in myself a change in the people who matter to me and I feel as if instead of moving on, I've become rooted.  Rooted not in agroup, but in a location in a dynamic, in something I will always want to be part of.  I don't feel nearly as secluded, nearly as trapped as I used to, and although I am not terribly comfortable far from my group I feel myslef branching out, creating new roots all around me.  I must admit that as scared as I am of the future I am glad to be moving forward.  i am going to miss so much this summer, so many people I've taken for granted, but new opportunities lie ahead of me and contrary to what seems to be popular belief, no I am not a senior just yet and I will have another year to build and grow before I will have to leave.    By the way in case you didn't know, the yearbook kicks ass and I am proud to say that I helped create it.  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've been on a yearbook kick all week, waiting for my new one to arrive and more importantly, to read what people write in it.  Why do we do it to ourselves year after year?  Why do we record our feelings for one another on its pages, just to look back later and see that things aren't the same.  I pulled out my yearbook from last year to look through it.  The cover is scarred from Rini bashing Tom over the head with it.  The inside cover is filled with convoluted writing, stretching across and around both of the pages and the one that follows.  Three pages essentially filled up by one person.  And what hurts most of all is to know that at the time she meant everything she said about our friendship.  Now though we are strangers, two people who pass in the hall and occasionally wave.  "one thing that I want you to know--if you don't know anything else, it's that when I'm sitting alone in my room and thinking about my friends-the real ones- your face is one of the first to come into my mind."  That is no longer true, we no longer know each other.  Friendships fade long before the ink does, long before the memories do.  Will I be looking back next year at what you write and think the same thing?  Does Chris's comment that "the group is finally solidifying" still true?  Or have we simply become stuck, mentally drifting apart and only close by proximity?  When was the last time we piled onto a swing?  The last time we went to a movie? The last time we had a real conversation?  Its been too long, we've grown up and we seem to be moving apart.  Our minds seem to have rewired, this one to that one, this one to new friends.  The wires may still tangle between us, but the strength that once was there seems to be gone.  We sit outside on the hill quietly.  Maybe the night and seeing the end is getting to me.  Maybe these feelings are all in my head, or maybe I'm just trying to comfort myself because everyone else seems to have moved on and I alone am left behind.  I loved our group, loved eating Thai in the tree house, loved huge water fights, loved late night conversations about superheroes and person Y.  But when was the last time all that existed?  When was the last time we were all that close?  It was last year.  My best memories come from the gathering at Erica's the day before I went to camp.  The goodbye cupcakes I had to buy cocoa for, the really weird movie (Donnie Darko),  the hammock mess that turned into a water fight and killed my cell.  But when I came home it was different.  We had gotten used to not seeing each other everyday, to only talking to one person at a time.  And now that's where we are, little pockets of what used to be something much bigger.  And at this stage I'm leaving.  I'm leaving with things in the air, with no answers.  I'm leaving not a group, but individual friends.  What will I come home to?  What will be left for me to pick up and carry on?    In many ways I have moved on and that scares me even more.  Instead of having a group behind me I have tenuous ties to many people all over the place.  That makes it harder to gather, harder to fell secure, yet at the same time comforting and hopeful.  Right now all the lines are tangled.  I hope to have them untangled soon, because if I don't the knot will just get worse while I'm gone.  Here's to hope.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why is it that taking a step into unknown territory is so hard?  It seems to get harder as I get older, each day we become more cautious, or at least I do.  When I was little I would refuse to test the water at the pool because I knew that I would chicken out at the last moment because it would be colder than what I was comfortable with.  Instead, I would get in line for the diving board and dive in head first so that by the time I knew the temperature it was too late to turn back.  But as I get older I'm no longer able to just dive in.  Instead I must test the waters and more often than not I find myself turning around because the initial shock is not to my liking.  So I sit here now, poised on the edge looking down into the pool beneath me.  How should I approach it?  Should I put my toe in slowly and possibly let time slip past and lose my opportunity or nerve?  Or should I dive in and make a huge splash and possibly bellyflop?  Which hurts more, rejection or never knowing?  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sometimes there is such a thing as being too assertive... Just for the record its not a good idea to ever, ever sit down at a table you are waiting on, find out the girls you are talking to are at least four years younger than you, and then give your number to one of them while informing them that you are off the next day.  Under no circumstances is that acceptable. Don't get me wrong, I don't have a problem with getting attention and if he had been someone else, maybe someone younger who I had met more than once, I would have been flattered and would have considered calling (lets face it, probably would have called)--but no, its not ok to try to pick up minors whom you have never met when you are graduating college in the next year.  Sorry, had to get that out of my system.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Reading my blog, looking back over this past week Ive come to realize that my emotions are like a roller coaster, all over the place, up and down.  It all a part of one big cycle.  There are nights when I feel a part of a unit, just a piece of the whole.  Then there are the nights when I feel contently isolated.,  But the nights I hate the most are nights like tonight, nights when I feel as if Ive been yanked from my roots and left to wither in the ever approaching sun.  Knowing that Ill only be gone a month should make it easier, deluding myself into believing that I can come back to today and pick up back at Ericas surrounded by everyone.  Even though it should make it easier, it doesnt, not when I think back to standing in Ericas kitchen looking at my friends, not knowing what to say to express my gratitude for the past year, for its ups and downs, for their unwavering support and their willingness to put me in my place when I needed it.  So instead I said nothing, and merely looked at them, giving quick hugs on my way out the door.  Will my departures always be like this, leaving without saying what I intended, without knowing what I wanted to say until I am alone and driving away from everyone in a dark empty car?  I didnt return a phone call tonight, I promised I would, but I just cant, cant deal with anymore goodbyes right now.  I feel bad for this, even selfish, but I just cant bring myself to pick up the phone and face another person.  I am glad that my family was asleep by the time I came in the door; glad I got by my neighbor with a mere grunt.  But at the same time Im lonely and wish I had a person to look in the face and deal with everything brewing inside me right now.  The contradictions are back, the cycle has started once again, and once again I feel lost, spinning round and round, deeper and deeper into my own world.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's over, the year has finally come to a close.  Of course this didn't occur to me until we were standing in Erica's dark driveway saying goodbye.  I am standing there, trying desperately to make plans to see everyone in my few days home for the next few weeks and trying desperately to disguise my tears.  I'm really going away.  Not for too long but, still, long enough.  Long enough to miss all of my friends, long enough to be left out of the loop, long enough to miss Erica all together before she leaves for New York, long enough to know that you can never return to find things the way they are today.  Today things were perfect, well almost perfect.  Even getting a C in calculus for the year won't damper this day in my memory. I don't want to go.  I didn't know that before tonight, but at this moment I would rather stay home more than anything else.  I didn't know that I would be hit so hard with emotions, hard enough to make me cry on the way home, hard enough to make my body wrack.  I never knew how happy I am beneath all of my griping, how much I feel I need the dynamic around me even though I complain. What will I do without you?  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So in case you were wondering how to get motivated to clean your room, lose your credit card.  It certainly is a big motivator to pull out that shovel and find the floor again.  I have just spent the past 5 hours cleaning and looking and now you can see my floor as well as the card.  And the best advice in the world is officially "I will leave you with parting words of wisdom (and you must know they come from the wisest source there is--the other two voices in my head) look on your dresser and in a three foot radius around said dresser."  I also discovered that I have way too many clothes, even after I bagged up 2 complete trash bags of stuff for goodwill.  Its rather depressing when I think of all that I have.  My life is entirely consumerist. Losing my credit card is the scariest thing I've had to deal with in a long long time.  My drawers and closet are still bursting, after bagging up 4 dresses, 6 pairs of pants, 12 pairs of shorts, and countless tops.  I have 6 pairs of shoes to get rid of as well.  When did this happen?  I didn't used to be so clothes obsessive, did I?   Apparently i have an addiction...  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This weather is oppressive.  It comes in and bears down, making me sluggish and temperamental.  There is nothing that can be done in 92 degree weather except whine and burn.  So instead I am relegated to this house, to this room.  I look out the window and it looks beautiful-sunny and still lush- but the second you step through the door it hits you, draining everything from your body.  How can we be expected to do well on exams in weather like this?  How can we be expected to be motivated and to complete late calculus assignments?  What happened to the cool weather?
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      while it is true that I haven't written in a week, it's not just laziness, i have an excuse, I was out of town.  Unfortunately I lack summary ability so if you want the details you will have to talk to me at some point.  Also, I'm leaving again tomorrow.  Hopefully I will be better about writing stuff down and typing it when I get home, but don't expect any posts in the next 3 weeks.  However, I love mail (and might have to sing for it if you send me enough) so write me often.  'Lena (CIT) Camp Kanata 13524 Camp Kanata Rd Wake Forest, NC 27587
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I havent written anything of merit in nearly a month and I fear that I will not be able to do so tonight either.  So much has happened in these past 3 weeks, so many stories, so many new friends, so much unchartered territory.  As I sit here tonight I dont know where to begin.  My mind seems clouded and every time I try to find a place to start everything that settled out reemerges and becomes part of the picture once again.  Maybe Im still too close, too entrenched, too tired to even attempt to sort through what has happened.  As I sit here I think back to last nights devotion and the particularly insightful point that we cannot go back and change the past, nor can we control the future.  All we have is the present.  The problem is that I do not know what I want to do with my present, where and how I want to spend it.  There are so many options before mw, yet the second I step forward I know that the rest will be lost.  Each one entices me, each one draws me to it, yet I know that I must pick only one.  To try anything else would not only turn into a failure, it would hurt me and negatively affect those around me as well.  It is so much easier to sit passively and let time and other slowly take away option after option, taking away the decision, tomorrow I return to Kanata, not as a trainee but as a staff member.  Already that simple decision seems to be guiding my path; closing doors that I never even knew existed.  Yet at the same time I hope that it will allow new doors to open, leaving me with precious memories and new paths to take when it is over.  Tomorrow will take me one step further into the woods, and while I may be apprehensive I look forward to tomorrow.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The world keeps turning, even when you sleep.  My fears are slowly coming true.  The world is changing.  More specifically my world is changing, and for the most part, without me.  Every year there seems to be a realignment and I never noticed.  It normally happens in December, but its coming early, I can feel it.  This feeling scares me and makes me sick to my stomach.  I had an awesome night, but it was shattered suddenly, in a series of infinitesimal moments, each individual, each representing a different facet of change.  I'm at the point where I no longer care about the group, but I'm also at the point where I feel the least connected to those I've come to rely on over the past few years.  I need to sit down and talk, really talk, to each of them individual, to reconnect in a sense.  So many things have happened in the past few weeks, not all of them bad, the majority of them positive in some way, but added up they build what appears to be a nearly insurmountable wall of change.  I guess its just something I have to accept, but I don't want to.  In the end change is what you make it, so I have to strive to make my life work out the way I want it.  Damn it, change is hard to accept. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>