<Blog>

<date>28,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Style... Your style of writing will always be with you and your writing will always be great when you tap into it.  Try not to write like you're someone else.  This is great advice but it's hard to follow.  How do you find your style?  How do you stick to it?  How can you be flexible with it?  Your style is the type of writing you create when you're not looking to show it to anyone but yourself.     It's not easy, specially for those people taking classes or being apart of writing groups.  You know everyone is going to be reading, absorbing, and (hopefully) constructional critiquing your work.  Try writing about something you really enjoy, where the words just flow from your finger tips.  For me it was star wars...  Being a big fan but knowing it would never be published (and I would feel weird showing it to people) I knew I would be writing it just for me.  It took me a few years but I finally finished the novel.  Over that time I realized I had a particular style with positive and negative tendencies.  I knew I was quick to describe something but always described everything.  I could dive deeply into the emotions of a character and never come up for air.  Also, I found I enjoy writing heart felt tragedies and had a bad habit of using "backwards" sentences.  I'm going to work on those things but enjoy my style of writing.  Hopefully I will have some of that style up here in the form of a story soon. 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Characters...  Got to love juicy characters.  Those ones that have many facets or just one that goes so deep you get lost in it.  My Favorites...  Kira... My all purpose dark jedi trying to break free from it's hold.  She's strong and has thief qualities.  She can't stand someone getting one up on her.  She won't kill you if she can destroy your ego.  She wouldn't want to free herself but the dark side never gave her what she wanted.  She couldn't protect herself - from being a pawn and she couldn't control life and death.  At first she was trapped in it but she frees her soul when she saves a life through giving up her own.  Ashley... Another tragic character.  Finding a gift for bending time in her hands she finds herself being called Ashes.  Not only can she bend time but she feels the change in time line.  She has the power to change everything and nothing at the same time.  For one change leads to another and sometimes it leads to a greater tragedy.  Sometimes she must not stop ashes from becoming ashes.  Orion... A bounty hunter hunted by too many deaths.  He sinks further into his shell forsaking humanity.  Soon he becomes as cold as the criminals he brings in.  Petyr Snow... Powerful, cruel and lustful.  A typical bad guy except for the fact that he will take his time with the object of his desire, enduring all the pain that could come from it.  Nothing seems to be able to keep him from smiling, and he's just a little too fast to wipe that smile off his face for all time.  He's that bad guy you could hit with a knock-out punch but hope he's back in the next scene so you can resume your love of hating him.  I love building a story with characters everyone can enjoy and want to see again... even the villains.  I adore my villains.  Sinister, sneaky bastards!  Sometimes they will have to perform a seriously shocking evil deed but I'll have you enamored with them the very next moment!  My belief is that if you make them so horrible people will turn away.  It's happen to me.  I was reading a divinely written piece of work that seemed to be similar to the Lion, the Witch, and the Wardrobe but suddenly the book just kept darkening so much that I had to turn away.  I found myself not wanting to pick up the book anymore because it was always going from bad to worse with evil incarnate as the villain.  One of the lesser villains intrigued me but I don't know if I can bring myself to find out about him.  I wonder if anyone else has that problem?  Do you read to what agrees with you or can you pick up anything and enjoy it (so long as the author knows how to write)? 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Today the rain fell on a much shorter day.    And as I sat there trying to perform my little operations assistant job I found myself wondering back to this blog.  What was I going to say next.  Would anyone ever be reading it.  First of all, I would like to tell any potential bloggers that this thing rocks.  Not only can I play with some html as I like (since I don't know that much but enjoy learning) but I can just sit here and type out anything I wish onto a stable website that I can control.  Just rocks.  I highly suggest a blogspot for anyone who has time on the internet and enjoys writing.  Me... I love to write and this is my chance to publish my work onto the web.  For all of you looking for that paper to hand into English class.  LOOK IN YOUR HEAD.  My work is not up for plagiarism.  But for all of you who enjoy reading someone else's take on writing: I'm here for your enjoyment.   I'm thinking of starting off with a short story of some sorts.  I'm not sure what I want to write but I have a tendency for the sci-fi and indulge in a few star wars stories on occasion.  I hope you stick around to see my work.      
    
    
</post>

<date>26,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Why WhitePearl?  White Pearls came to me as a gift from someone I deeply felt but hardly knew.  They were a very unexpected gift that has touched deeply even more so since she has departed this earth.  They became my link to her and I felt compelled to know more about them in some attempt to know her more; especially since they supposedly belonged to her first.  I learned that pearls are timeless, as was she.  They have been worn for century upon century and their value has been greater than gold.  They are the Queen's Gem since they have always been associated with the feminine sea and moon.  They have come in dozens of shapes and sizes from all corners of the earth.    To be given pearls is a great gift of love and helps for the receiver to see the love and kindness of the giver.  It sure has in my case.  They say pearls don't just give you a glimpse of the love of another but also let you see yourself.  These pearls don't rest on my neck anymore.  They rest on my heart and reflect every feeling back to me.  They have showed me that even though I do have flaws of my own and sometimes falter I also have a beautiful truthful heart that someone else was able to see.  It's not totally hidden or misinterpreted as I always thought it was.  The necklace she gave me is old and mysterious. Was this strand really her's first?  Are they old and very real?  Were they a gift from her mother?  Was giving these pearls some kind of a tradition for her?  I fear I'll never know.  It reminds me that I didn't know her as well as I liked.  There was still so much more about her to know and cherish.  At least I can know her more threw her family, which I am very lovingly attached to.  I hope I have the courage to ask about her some day.    Where ever she is in that wide and wonderful beyond, I want her to know the immense gratitude in my heart.  I want her to know that this shy and insecure girl had grown to hold a special love for her despite all the distance both geographical and linguistically.  Thank you Nermin.  I only wish I had a chance to call you "Mom".  In my heart I always did.     
    
    
</post>

<date>17,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Hi World,  I'd just like to send the following out to my Dad.     My Dad is a busy harley riding grease monkey,  Who surprisingly is an Anne McCaffrey junkie.  He's always on his toes,  Whether replacing a break pad or patching a hose.  It's just the curve life threw his way,  I don't blame him even if he's booked all day. Just wish things were easier for him  So a chance at visiting didn't look so grim.  Today's his birthday so he's all mine  No matter the day or the time. We're going out to dinner  And tonight he's not going to be the bread-winner.  I want to see him smile and laugh to forget his working woes. Because he's my loving Dad and tonight is his night to glow!  So put on your comfortable best because after tonight you'll have a lot to digest!  Why do all this?  Why care so much?  Because depsite it all he's my wonderful Dad, and I love him so much.  I love you Dad.  Happy Birthday!    
    
    
</post>

<date>30,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       My First short story.  Writer’s Note: It’s not about the facts, it’s about issue.  This is an issue that has always been a problem for me.  I technically believe in freedom of choice but life is the most precious thing in my mind.  The conflict of feelings is always inside me.  I’m bringing it out for all of you.    A Great Hollow   It was the cold busy days right before the holidays and two police officers stood at the mouth of the north corridor standing vigil over the travelers, shoppers, and holiday tourists.  They were natives of Manhattan.  Both were used to the charge in crowds around the festive season.  From this position in the grand main hall of the terminal they had helped to stop purse thieves, shop lifters, and too often gave directions to a weary passer-byer.  It was a welcome beat out of the cold of winter.  Both stood relaxed as they gazed over the cavernous marble room filled with couples, families, and chatty groups.  Everyone was bustling about to their own rhythm in the grand hall, each oblivious most of the others.  It was like watching bugs in the summer.  Each had their own little route, plan, and goal to accomplish as they went in and out and back in again.  The two cops were quite adept to watching the human bugs buzz around.  They always took notice of anything unordinary among the disorganization.  It was a trait every officer had to develop.  At this time of the year they both noted the lack of single travelers other than the occasional businessman.  However, it just so happened that the two officers happened to see a young man walk into the grand hall, crossed his legs, and sit down on the polished marble floor with his back to a great pillar.  Both officers looked to one another as they took notice of this abnormality.  With the fall collegial year over this boy stood out.  The 20-some year old boy looked up at the train schedule and then over to the storefronts before settling his gaze on a book he had in his hands.  He was a rebellious looking young man; with his pants big, black, and baggy.  His hair was cut at uneven lengths and many of his visible body parts were pierced or encrusted with silver.  It wasn’t long before he took up a pen and began glancing about the large hall as he wrote through his dangling bangs of deep brown hair.  The officers stopped their regular hall gazing to take a good look at him.  Each considered himself a good judge of character but when they turned to each other the words did not come out the same. “Look at this one, probably didn’t finish his community service at the college.  He must have had to stay an extra two weeks because he was up late drinking one night and got caught.” The older one said as he crossed his arms across his broad chest.  He was Officer John McKarney, a loyal husband, and father of two boys.  He considered himself an expert on college age behavior since having his oldest son graduating soon and his younger just starting his freshmen year.  He was already forming the boy’s family life in his mind. “He probably got a full scholarship because of his writing but is blowing it all by spending too much time hanging with his ‘peeps’ in moody coffee cafes rather than studying.  He’s most likely going home to face a busy father and an overly social or drugged up mother.  For now the only thing he has to comfort him is that ratty journal.” He finished allowing his horse voice to really show through, as if he were leaning back in his chair watching a movie to which he already knew the end.  Officer Mike Lawrence took in the idea openly but had his own take on the young but individualized youth.  Being only in his early 30’s he took a look back at his younger self and then though on the boy. “He’s probably a good kid.  Maybe he was working at the café you mentioned and he couldn’t get out of work early enough.  If he has both his parents they are just open minded towards his approach to life.  You can’t be so negative on the boy, John.” He said sympathetically.  The older cop made a noise somewhere between a grunt and a sigh.  As much as they were able to get along during the long hours on the beat, both officers didn’t like to back down about their opinions on a person.  Usually, a disagreement meant a change in subject.  Both tried to look beyond the boy and get back to their surveillance of the main hall.  But both noticed as the boy checked out the train schedules again, then picked up his pack, and headed right past between them for his train.  Both the policemen noted that he didn’t have much of an expression on his face.  He wasn’t worried or happy or sad.  Each made some more mental notes on his heavy pack and ragged notebook before turning back to the main room.  				******  Earlier that evening the library closed and Ms. Loraine stretched and sighed as she got up from her chair at the information desk.  It was another quiet day only filled with infectious whispering.  When the last person left the library she turned on her small radio and began gathering up the books left out or misplaced.    She had always wondered about the people who left the books out on the table.  She usually found a variety of subjects all out next to one chair.  She imagined there must be some real bookworms in New York.  Either that or someone’s Internet connection was down.  She giggled to herself slightly as she picked up oddly stacked self-help books and a dieting book that was along side a book on chocolate.  There were children’s books mixed with romance novels… obviously a mother and child.  There were the occasional how-to books where she would also find pens and the rare greasy handprint.  This one kitten book was out again… she knew the cute blond girl with a sunny smile to match her hair.  She must still b trying to convince her mother to let her have a cat.  She softly whispered to the book “you keep on trying little one… she’ll give in soon.”  She seemed to know everyone in the city though she didn’t know their names.  Rarely were there new books left out and if so they always seemed to be on the front table.  However, as she made her way to the back she noticed a very odd assortment of books laid out across a dark table.  It was an obscure table in the back non-fiction and reference section.  She almost never found books here.  Perhaps a map or two come summer time but during the winter no one would sit back here on this cold and ill lit corner of the library.  She approached normally to scoop up the books but she found herself still as she looked over them.  Out there on that table were half a dozen books that didn’t make much sense.  There was the King James Version of the Holy Bible; there was a book on landmines and bombs, and a bunch of medical journals.  She took a closer look at the medical journals.  They seemed primarily concerned with pregnancy.  A cold shiver shuddered her body as if a door had just been slammed.  She looked around in a frantic attempt to find the reader but she remembered that it was only she now and the janitor Bob.  She felt an urgent need to tell someone, but what could she say?  She’s just conjecturing now… but oh God… what if?    				******  It was late at night by the time the officers Lawrence and McKarney returned to headquarters to end their shift.  As they walked past some of the small window lined offices they noticed the same boy was sitting with one of the top detectives.  It was a bit of a shock.  The boy they had so closely examined earlier didn’t seem to be the criminal type.  John muttered something like running a ticket booth but both primarily thought he was a witness of some kind.  They had to know and so slinked to the captain’s office. “Sir, what’s the story with the kid over there in Carson’s office?” Officer Lawrence asked quietly.  Captain Bingham didn’t have time for their strange inquiry and answered them bluntly. “The kid’s a born-again and tried to blow up an abortion clinic downtown.” He said shortly in his heavy jersey accent.   Both cops were stunned.  Neither of them had expected it from such a simple looking rebel-without-a-cause.  They had seen dozens of them before.  This one stood out and now they know why.  Neither of them spoke as they went to prepare to go home. Before leaving Officer Lawrence saw that Detective Carson was alone and reading the notebook the kid had with him. “Do you mind, Jim?” he said reaching a hand out for the book.  Jim looked up at him quizzically and then back down to the page he was on. “You wouldn’t be the younger and optimistic looking cop, now would you?” he asked strangely.  Mike Lawrence didn’t understand at first but as soon as he started reading the book he had found that the young boy had definitely noticed his and his partner’s glances.  These two cops at the north corridor might be aware of my mission.  I wouldn’t know what to say to them if they caught me.  I’m just doing what I know is right in my heart.  I feel the young optimistic-looking one might sympathize with me, but I think scowling older one will be the first to walk over and investigate me.  Isn’t their motto ‘to protect and serve’?  What about protecting the freedom of every child brought into existence? Life and death is God’s alone and we should protect his right to have control over it.  We shouldn’t pretend we’re like God.  Maybe if they officers could just understand that they would help me do the right thing instead of sitting there and judging me.  Knowing what’s happening out there in the world… there is this great hollow of a feeling in me the longer I do nothing.  The hollow is greater than the entire grand central terminal.  I need to do what I feel is right and true.  Let God be the only one to judge me.  Mike looked in mourning as he shut his eyes from the writing and handed the old notebook back to Jim.  At first he mind was reeling with all those words.  How a boy could take something like this into his hands was unbelievable. “Hard to believe, huh?” he said to Mike trying ease whatever he’s feeling. “Yeah.” He was able to squeeze out from between his teeth. “It’s just one of those issues that get taken too far.  Frankly, I feel if you have a belief you shouldn’t force it on people.” He said matter-of-factly.  Mike thought about his words for a moment there, but the words of the boy were much more powerful.  He wasn’t a religious man but he knew his Scriptures.  The passion for right was almost admirable but the horrible feeling of wrongness was shuddering.  He thought about when he saw the boy and again he was so young.  Was there anyway he could have talked to him?  Was there anyway of reaching someone like that who thinks he is out there fighting a war to save everyone? “Mike,” Jims voice brought him out of his wonderings. “Yeah Jim?” Mike finally looked him in the eyes. “Go home.  You can’t think so deeply on these things.  You’ll wind up having a great hollow inside that you can’t fill.” He said.  With that Mike finally turned and left the office convinced to let the whole matter go.  Detective Carson was right, the kid was wrong.  The end.      
    
    
</post>

<date>29,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       The following is information on the elements of a short story for all of you new to the experience. This comes from webpage: http://www.english.uga.edu/~msmith/1102_elements_short_story.htm   Elements of the Short Story  Definition:  A short story is a relatively brief fictional narrative in prose.  It may range in length from the short-short story of 500 words up to the "long short story" of 12,000 to 15,000 words.  It may be distinguished from the sketch and the tale in that it has a definite formal development, a firmness in construction.  It finds its unity in many things other than plot---although it often finds it there---in effect, theme, character, tone, mood, and style.  It may be distinguished from the novel in that it tends to reveal character through actions, the purpose of the story being accomplished when the reader comes to know what the true nature of a character is.  The novel tends, on the other hand, to show character developing as a result of actions.  However natural and formless the short story may sometimes give the impression of being, a distinguishing characteristic of the genre is that it is consciously made and reveals itself to be the result of conscious, skilled work.  Furthermore, however slight the short story may appear, it consists of more than a mere record of an incident or an anecdote.  It has a beginning, a middle, and an end; it possesses at least the rudiments of plot.   A very brief history of the short story:   In France in the second half of the 18th century, Denis Diderot made important contributions to the development of the short story.  In the 19th century came Scott, Irving, Hawthorne, Poe, Merimee and Balzac, Gautier and Musset, Maupassant, Chekhov, and E. T. A. Hoffman.  With these writers the short story as a distinct genre came into being.  Some of these writers consciously formulated the short story as an art form.  This development flowered with such speed and force in America that the modern short story is often called an American art form, with only minor exaggeration.   In the middle 19th century, under the impulse of Poe's persuasive statement in his 1842 review of Hawthorne's Twice-Told Tales, critics postulated a definite structure and technique for the short story.  To this was added, around the end of the century, the tight "surprise-ending story" of O. Henry, and the short story came to be thought of as corresponding to a formula, a pattern that was much repeated in the popular short story.  After the turn of the century, however, the impact of Realism and Naturalism joined with the example of Chekhov's slice of life stories to force open the formula, and such masters of the form as Somerset Maugham and Katherine Mansfield in England and Sherwood Anderson, F. Scott Fitzgerald, Ernest Hemingway, and most recently, Raymond Carver in America developed the short story to a dominant form of literary expression in the 20th century.   
    
    
</post>

<date>26,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Speaking of Literature...  There is something to be said for the short story.  I know we all want to write that great novel someday but what about the short story?  Does anyone try to write those anymore?  I don't see many new collections floating around the bookstore.  Taking a small love in them I have decided to try my hand at them.  One of my favs is one done by Hemmingway.  I decided to use his as a template but I hope it evolves into something very original.  I also thought about starting a collection of my own.  But of course, first I must discover the heart of my short stories.  Will it be to show off a culture, to express a moral, to investiage emotions, or will it be something on a humanitarian level?  I'm sure to figure it out sooner or later.  In the meantime I am getting ideas from writers like Hemmingway and Faulkner.  Frankly, I get a lot of ideas just reading the great introduction to these authors.  Why the wrote it, what was their inspiration, and what they thought of their own work are all wonderful insights.  Again, I advise to check out the great writers.  You may be surprised. 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       As you will all notice, there is another link on this blog labeled: English Lit on the Web.  Not only do I love to write but I also love to read.  I always enjoy the great works of famous literature writers and I love diving deep into them.  Sometimes it gives me insight on how I can make my own works deep and thought provoking.  This is a great sight put up by a very nice person in japan.  I encourage all of you interested in writing to take a look at some of the authors listed there and find inspiration in their work.  
    
    
</post>

<date>26,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Recently I have come across another problem writers have to contend with... originality.  Everyone has that one great idea.  They begin working with it dilligently but sooner or later they're in the local bookstore or watching a movie and realize that their idea isn't original at all.  It can be a hard blow.  Sometimes writers deny the fact and keep on writing because they have become obsessed with finishing their vision.  I've been there myself... I'm there right now actually.  I have an idea for a sci-fi novel but it's already been done.  Good examples are Titan A.E. and Final Fanatsy The Spirits Within.  It's the idea of the war riddled future or a future where earth is no more.  The main theme would be the survival of the human race.  Frankly, I think people should read those types of stories more often.  We don't realize all that we have until everything is destroyed and LIFE is all we're really hanging onto.  It's really the most important thing.  Some people still do't realize that when they start wars.  Soldiers' lives are lives wasted when we could just band together as humans.  Instead we call each other aliens and fight for meaningless borders with what seems to be meaningless lives.  Well... before I start rambling some more I'll just leave you with this...  It's getting even harder to come up with an original idea so don't beat yourself up for repeating a little.  Before you know it you'll find that idea thats just original enough to catch the eye of the public.   
    
    
</post>

<date>24,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       As you can see I made some changes to the blog.    I've decided to really get into it now and to do that it can't be a simple little thing I play with once a month.  Instead it needs to be a sight dedicated to me and my thoughts.  It's not just going to be writing advice... nope, in fact the original idea of creating a blog was to publish my works.    Actually, I have just two things left to do.  One, I need to come to grips with putting my weird work out there so people can see it.  Two, I need to figure out how to change the settings so you, the public, can post on my blog.  Because I do want to hear what you have to say.  So let me work on those things and soon enough you'll see some original Jill Work with room for comments - both cheers and jeers.  Thanks. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       As you can see I made some changes to the blog.    I've decided to really get into posting now and to do that this can't be a simple little thing I play with once a month.  Instead it needs to be a blog dedicated to me and my thoughts.  It's not just going to be writing advice... nope, in fact the original idea of creating a blog was to publish my works.    Actually, I have just two things left to do.  One, I need to come to grips with putting my weird work out there so people can see it.  Two, I need to figure out how to change the settings so you, the public, can post on my blog.  Because I do want to hear what you have to say.  So let me work on those things and soon enough you'll see some original Jill Work with room for comments - both cheers and jeers.  Thanks. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       As you can see I made some changes to the blog.    I've decided to really get into posting now and to do that this can't be a simple little thing I play with once a month.  Instead it needs to be a blog dedicated to me and my thoughts.  It's not just going to be writing advice... nope, in fact the original idea of creating a blog was to publish my works.    Actually, I have just two things left to do.  One, I need to come to grips with putting my weird work out there so people can see it.  Two, I need to figure out how to change the settings so you, the public, can post on my blog.  Because I do want to hear what you have to say.  So let me work on those things and soon enough you'll see some original Jill Work with room for comments - both cheers and jeers.  By the way - HAPPY HOLIDAYS EVERYONE!!!  Thanks for reading. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I've heard it said that once a writer starts writing in a particular theme... fiction, science fiction, mystery, romance, and etc that they can't move to another.  Take a science fiction writer trying to take on a romance... he could try to focus on these two people and their feelings but before you know it they get sucked into a worm hole or one turns out to be from another dimension.  I think a good piece of advice for young writers out there is to try and vary your work.  Write what you want but try to make sure you touch on every theme at least once.  Specialization can be good.  Being the best mystery writer would give you an edge but if the only job open is short story sci-fi then you'll have to adapt and quick if you want to keep the job.  I'm a sci-fi person myself but I have tried many times to take stories out of a completely imaginative world and bring them into a world closer to the one we're all living in now.  I think my first good try will be posted here.  I'm sure to have it up before the end of the year. 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       A poem, which was an inspiration from a class assignment.    Pearls from a Pearl    Pearls… is there anything more precious? Pearls… was there ever a more heart felt gift?  Pearls… were my special gift a New Years before the last.     Between us it was a rough night at first. I was left alone until I heard my phone ring.  A sisterly voice told me to come along.  Upon arriving things were stiff and quiet, Though comforting whispers kept me there. Things became better when gifts were exchanged.  I wished his Mom would know...  That things were just rough… That I didn’t mean to hurt him… That I truly loved him so much...  Then…  A few Turkish words came out and bag came to me. A bag that was small but strangely heavy.  Oh Thank you!  …even before looking… just because of the smile. The surprising smile that lifted the weight on my heart.  Upon opening the bag, my mouth fell open as the necklace came out, A necklace of pure pearls.  Some pearls can be deceiving.  They can be too light and false. They can be too colored and false. They can be too perfect and false.  Instead they were imperfect and true… and most beautiful Just like her heart.  May Allah bless and keep her.   A pearl among a sea of pebbles.  (Dedicated to a special Mom who shared so much love with so few words.) 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       An original idea has finally struct my brain.  Not only is it an original idea but it hasn't been touched upon by anyone else fictionally.  Someone once wrote that the "great idea" is like falling in love (I believe it was in a writers market book... maybe the one for short stories).  The rest of what he wrote was also true... you just go after the idea and work at it.  Give is a full try even after you fall out of that flowery initial love.  You never know when you actually have a gem of a story that only needs some tweeking before it shines.  One thing I have noticed is all the research this idea is going to need.  It's a controversial subject so I need to find the main consenses.  I need to also pick up some opinions from people who have heard about it and/or believe it.  It's a religious theme too, so I have to be careful how the religion is represented.    I was thinking about puting this story in an exotic local.  I once visited Turkey with my Fiance (who is Turkish) and I feel I want to put the story in Istanbul.  I also feel this location would help character development and increase intrigue in the book.  I'll just have to be sure to have my Fiance look over it and make sure it sounds correct.  Last thing I need is to accidenly lie about life in that gorgeous city.  It's going to be a daunting task but I feel that in the end I will have a original and unique story that I could actually sell to a publishing company.  If this idea grows into at least 10 pages then I'll be sure to elaborate on it in a post. 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Paper or Disk Space?  The art of writing has definitely undergone an evolution from the page to the magnetically written disk.  Typewriters have become a novelty and the personal computer a must for any serious composer of written work.  The method of research has changed as well.  The internet has taken the place of the library because it could be updated more easily and the method of 'searching' has been simplified.  So what does this mean to writers of the future?  It means adaptation is key.  Never have there been so many changes in the writing world.  For the longest time pen and paper was the latest technology.  As electronic technology has improved the writing world has been forced to keep up or drop out.  More drastic changes are bound to take place, but for the time, writers are still a necessary part of life.  Writers create advertisements, manuals, teaching text, poems, entertainment books, movie scripts, business proposals, and is still a major medium for the news.  Since the evolution to the internet, more writers have been hired to word online business introduction websites, intranets, public/emailed newsletters, and informative websites.  However, one reason website designer positions have decreased is because more companies and non-profit organizations are looking for a writer/web designer to cut costs.  Not only do you need to be able to use writing programs but having knowledge on html, CSS, JavaScript, and other web design languages is a great plus.  It shows that the writer is slowly being integrated into the technology department.  No longer is a writer someone who simply writes in a secluded corner of society periodically emerging to hand in work.  The writers of the future need to see this coming so they can prepare.  It's not just about 'metaphors' vs. 'similes' anymore.  It's also about "what font shall I make this description?".  Since writers are expected to do so much more in groups they are also expected to participate more.  Those people will be expected to have great teamwork skills and good verbal communication.  Some writers are even expected to have indepth knowledge on the business prior to hiring.    Who knows what will be beyond this stage.  Writing might actually evolve out of our lives as telepathy or a collective conciseness is created through technology.  However, if you grasp any part of this post, please let it be that adaptability and awareness is key.  Adaptability will save you from being passed over but you must be aware of what you need to adapt to in order to truly survive this new information world.  One personal suggestion... enjoy working with a blog like this one.  It is teaching me much about the future world of writing and how to adapt in this one.   
    
    
</post>

<date>22,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       As you may have noticed, I added some new links, played with fonts, added more information on myself, and redefined my blog in the subject.  I guess as much as I like to term myself as a "Techie Writer" the term is confusing and vague when taking in my blog, so I changed it to Every Writer.  This is because I want any and all writers to read my work and essays on the writing world.  I might be a sci-fi buff but that doesn't mean that I can't write about something relevent to the romance writer.  On the topic of creative work, I am taking a Creative Writing class this semester and I believe I will be publishing my assignments, which prove to be interesting.  My instructor is a Mrs. Barbara Daniels.  She is an accomplished poet.  She is very understanding and interesting.  I feel this is going to be a good class.  One of the first essays I want to publish is on the wide range of jobs available to writers these days and in the future.  Its very interesting and positive since a increase in available jobs are predicted.  Being hopeful of finding a job myself I suspect this should be a good start to my collection of essays.  Thanks for dealing with all my tweeking! 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Like the new colors?  Feels a lot better to me.  Also, I will hopefully add a Hit Meter so I actually know whether or not anyone is actually reading these posts. 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       As I mentioned earlier... I've notice a lack of innovative writing on my part.  No matter my drive to creatively write I also want to write in a more professional manner and I think that could be attained by essays.  But what to write an essay on?  I don't just want to write about Classic Literature or the advantages of having a laptop.  Anyone who would be interested in writing would already know about those things for the most part.  So... being the techie writer that I am... I searched the internet and came up with some ideas to improve my spiffy little blog.  I am not going to change the title or location again but the subject matter is definately going to change.  I am going to behave as a professional columnist would but ocassionally I will post a work of fiction for all you creative writers out there.  However, that doesn't mean you should only read my blog at those times... no... what I plan to be columnizing about is writing itself.  No more grammar or tidbits about hemingway... no I am going to be talking about such subjects as the impact of blogging on the writing world.  I am going to be talking about the future of writing in response to many news articles on the writing, publishers, and the media in general.  For instance...  Did you know that many, many newspapers that are distributed at your local convienance stores are also posted on the web.  With more and more people zipping to the web for weather, news briefs, and ebooks will the written word soon only exist as a magnetically written disk space in a server?  Questions like these I hope to discuss.    They are much more meater and there is room enough for creative expression.    I should have a schedule up in my subject space, which will give details on articles and creative projects.  Also, I will be changing links around so I hope everyone who liked them have bookmarked them. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Looking back on my last post... that novel idea kind of sounds like Ghost (the movie) except that the coupling is different.  Man, an original idea is very hard to come by.  Also, I noticed that my vocab could use an update.  Besides the last post I have been once again pondering about the future of this blog.  As I have noticed here and there... most of the blogs have at least their pinky finger in current events constantly, whether the current events be news, technology, improvements, new ideas, or what have you.  I would hope that my little blog has the same time of intrigue as those but I fear I'm just typing this all for myself and no one sees it.    I don't want to depart from writing... it's the origin reason I started this blog.  Maybe I just need to look at things a little differently and I'll find out what I really want to do or change about this blog.  Be on the look out for changes!!! 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Jill's Paginates  
    
    
</post>

<date>13,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It was a horrible dream, but thankfully parts of it were already fading as Julie tried to focus her eyes on the dim electronic clock.  6:29AM.  But the thought of work didn't motivate her.  Something from her dream planted a question in her mind. "Damian?" she said softly.  He was always there. "Yeah?" he replied just as quiet. "What happens when we die?  Do you think our soul or spirit ever go somewhere?" She asked feeling just a tad silly for oputting it to him. "I sure hope something happens.  I don't want to keep existing like this." he said with a sigh.  Julie sighed as well and turned around in bed.  She looked over at the other side. "Are you there?" she asked.  It wouldn't be the first time he stayed in the same bed as her.  It no longer shocked her that he could be anywhere. "No, I'm by the window.  Any form of rest has been getting harder." he said in a depressed voice.  Worry instantly came to Julie's mind.  As much as Damian was a shock at first he had now become a close comfort and she knew the stress meant something.  As she laid there slowly waking to the sounds of distant birds she was reminded of the day she discovered Damian and her talent for hearing him.  It was a gorgeous summer day at the local community college where she had been attending part time.  She was just on her way to pick up text books when she heard an angry voice cursing about the empty court yard.  Birds had stopped chirpping and the wind suddenly blew cold as more outragous curses bounced off the brick walls of classroom halls.   "Hello?" she asked wanting to make sure she wasn't dreaming but also afraid of the anger. "Huh?" the voice suddenly responded to her. "Are you Ok?" she asked trying to be helpful.  Suddenly the cold breeze got a little stronger as it blew through her knitted sweater.   "You can hear me?" a whisper said right next to her ear.  She nearly jumped and spun to find no one near her. "Yes," she said more frightened then before.  Then the voice suddenly began laughing like a maniac and she ran.  It wasn't long before the voice caught up with her and explained the strange circumstance.  Damian Westen was killed 6 months earlier from that day and what remained of him was left wandering about on the brink of insanity.  All he wanted was to understand what was happening but then when he gave up on his future he turned to revenge and has been seeking his murders.  Since Julie came he has had more control over himself.  He has not left her for fear of that raw insanity of existing but not existing.   Julie finally threw off the covers and got ready for the day paying no mind to Damian.  He had never left her, not for a second since their meeting, and she had to get use to having a what was left of a 28 year old man constantly around her.  At least he never seemed to care about such hormonal things anymore.  He only wanted to find comfort and rest.  She was soon dressed and called to Damian. "Time to go.  Don't be such of a hardass to Dr. Abdul today, alright.  Just because you won't leave doesn't mean that I have to suffer minimum wage.  OK?" she said.  Dr. Abdul was the curious scientist who first noticed the strange phenomenon around Julie and since then as acquired her and Damian as projects in which she is paid a comfortable salary.  Suspicious Damian agreed only because "at least it's not the military".  Damian was a realist but Julie could easily tell he was one of those troubled people.  The ones that never got good grades but still had enough commonsense to make it in life.  He was a smoker and constantly complains but the lack of cigerettes but Julie thinks he misses much more than just cancer sticks.  She can't seem him but she can hear the longing in his voice.  The longing for all this teasing to end.  Whats the good of existing like this, he once yelled in anger.  Indeed, Julie thought, why does he stay like this?  She always hoped Dr. Abdul would someday figure this out.  --------------------------------------------------- to be continued.......  This is The Pair.  My sci-fi coupling of a ghost and the one who knows he still exists.  It's a question that has always "haunted me".  There have been these "haunted houses" and I wondered... do these ghosts ever leave?  Do they ever join the rest, where ever they may be?  Are they just seeking comfort by staying in those houses?  Julie is a dependant young girl that has been sheltered and Damian is the complete oppsite but no matter the difference they are forced to deal with one another because of Julie's gift and Damian's need for companionship.      
    
    
</post>

<date>13,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I've been doing a lot of driving lately and all this driving has taken me through my hometown quite a few times and as I drive by I have been noticing new things and remembering the old.  It struck me that this old hometown of mine that once looked dull and boring actually has a real character and story appeal.    I noticed how somethings have never changed, including the ever changing corner store... I noticed how the west side is always improving while the east side is always falling apart... I noticed that you can still sit at the Phily Diner all day drinking coffee and pastries.  Stories have just started popping up in my head like mad...  So I'm going to write... :)   
    
    
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       With the help of my significant other, I got a new pda by Sony with palm software.  It's affordable and splendid.  If you want to check it out for yourself it's TJ25.  As you've noticed I have added a new list of literature links with a new link called The Gutenberg project.  This is a great idea.  It's a slowly increasing collect of ebooks that (so far) consist of classics and historical accounts & documents.  They are still building the collection but they already have a large quantity of Dickens and Mark Twain.  Poetry is also available.  Some of the notable names I saw were Emily Dickenson and Lord Alfred Tennyson.  It's free to all so check it out!   
    
    
</post>

<date>03,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I've been debating lately as to what are the best things for a writer to have.  There are so many books and gagets out there and I don't mean to be too materialistic, but some of these things look really useful.    For instance, I have a laptop that allows me to take my writing anywhere but I find that it only moves inside my home... from the living room, to the bedroom, to the... bathroom.  I do use it for taking notes at college, but as for writing... I don't take it to inspirational areas.  I wish I would but it just doesn't happen whether it be time or convenience.  I also have a old PDA I got on recommendation from a friend.  Now that... on the other hand... was a great idea.  It's easy to carry and I can just jot down ideas when they happen.  If I get a really great idea and want to expand on it then I can sit down and write it in there.  I even had a keyboard for that one and it was great for bookstores and plane trips.  But you don't need a keyboard if you can get cushy with the method of writing on the PDA.  I highly recommend one for any writer.  I don't use it for dates or expenses at all so it doesn't bother me to get rid of those programs and download story building programs from nifty websites.  When it comes to reference books I'm afraid the jury is still out.  I have looked at dozens of reference books and besides the grammar book I got from college, I haven't seen a need to collect anything else.  I do enjoy articles by other writers on inspiration but you can get that from the occasional magazine.  You can read these magazines in a good bookstore and not have to leave with it.  Just keep a note pad or PDA with you to jot down the ideas the writers discuss.  Journals are great... whether they are paper, computer document, or online.  I have all three!  I actually have many paper journals laying around here and there.  I just see something in a blank book and when I find one I like I have to collect it.  I always end up using them for one thing or another.  I also have this blog as a sort of journal!  It's just a little more formal and solely on the subject of writing.  Basically, in the end you just have to use what you feel helps you the most.  It's not really about logic as much as it is about feeling.  Do you feel you are supporting you need to write?    Recently, my PDA has been having difficulties... partly because it's old and beat-up and for some reason the keyboard doesn't want to talk to it.  Though I love the little thing I think it's just had it's day and needs to be put out to pasture so I can move on and get something else to serve me.  Yes, I could keep with my little PDA and save the money... that idea is strong.  But I think someday this year I will move onto a new model.  Just because I know I will feel denied by the old PDA wearing out and frustration will get to me.  But that's just me.  Remember... listening to someone talk about what they think of as good or bad is an intelligent thing to do but in the end you have to make the final choices for yourself based on how you feel or think. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I finally received my copy of the Complete Short Stories of Ernest Hemingway.  I must say that this guy really knew how to write.  I have already read a A Clean, Well-Lighted Place, but just randomly I decided to read The Butterfly and the Tank.  It's amazing how this man can tell a story.  Both are very different but very vivid with just the right amount of description.  A Clean, Well-Lighted Place is written in third ominpresent, but The Butterfly and the Tank was written in first person... supposedly Mr. Hemingway had seen this whole story unfold and wrote the story as the bartender had asked him to do.  The more I read the more I realized that description and the amount used is key to writing a good short story.  It can't be too much or the story becomes too long or boring.  If it's too little then you can hardly picture it.  For instance... when you read about the old man sitting at the cafe in A Clean, Well-Lighted Place you get a sense of him without Hemingway having to describe exactly how he looks.  Same for the forceful woman in the bar in The Butterfly and the Tank.  She is easily pictured without him having to tell you how she has her hair or how she's dressed underneath her leather rain coat.  I think I am going to have to work on that... getting the description down tight... not diving in too deeping... just going in enough so that the reader can make a vision.  Also, I love the way he writes in The Butterfly and the Tank.  It must be how he talks naturally and it's just great.  Sounds like the real voice of a great story teller and those people are just magnificent.  I hightly recommend picking up a copy of this book, even if you're not a big reader.  The stories are short enough that you can easily read them in one night and this author writes gems that are not to be overlooked.  I hope to soon pick up one of his novels.   
    
    
</post>

<date>29,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Revised poem.  "Pearls"  By Jill Wakefield  (Dedicated to Nermin Bal for her unconditional love for a future daughter-in-law.)  These curvy strung jewels must have come from some curvy street shop deep in the depths of the Covered Bazaar.  They came to me in a soft little bag accompanied by a few Turkish words, and a smile that meant more to me than any language could explain. My mouth fell open when they tumbled out into my hand and immediately began capturing all the light in the room, which they all held in their depths and reflected back warmly.  Words escaped me.  What do you say to a gift like this? I could barely utter the "Thank you!" echoing in my mind.  Translating it was beyond me. I suddenly knew the true depths of her heart.  The heart of this Mother , who I might have called my own as her son stands by my side.  Who loved me like a daughter though barely a word between us was understood.  While wishing I could be able to express more in those foreign words I soon learned that I would be wishing to see her warm smile again.  Now only a pearlescent memory of her shines in all the hearts of her children. But like the pearls around my neck, my memory for her will never lose it's loving glow.  May Allah bless and keep her. A pearl among a sea of pebbles.    
    
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       A poem.  "Canim" (A Turkish Word)  One little word, which means two. Pronounced wit a "J" it means "My Life."  My partner is Canim. Every beat of his heart, Grants me Canim.  I am his Canim. Every rise of my chest, Grants him Canim.  One little word, which means two, is meant for two. Binding the couple with one name.  In a land where Dervishes whirl, You will hear this name, Exchanged between only two, As they go through life As one.  
    
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I feel something needs to be said about the "recycling" of literary devices.  First of all... what is a literary device?  Personally, I believe this term applies to methods of story telling whether that be how the story is viewed by the narrator, how the plot twists, not necesarily the whole story in detail but how it moves or works.  Edgar Alan Poe used a tremedously different device in many of his books, which was the insane narrator.  This is a device anyone can use in their story, which hopefully does not exactly resemble "The Black Cat" or "The Tell-Tale Heart".  Another example of a literary device could be a particular type of character.  There are such things as arctypical characters and examples of these would be the victorious hero, the tragic hero, the wise man, the fated lovers, and the ill-fated lovers.  More types of characters have developed with time, such as Sherlock Holms - who never resembled any character when he was created but is now an arctypical mystery solver.  One thing that needs to be defined is "Borrowing Literary Devices" vs. "Plagurisim".  Borrowing ideas and taking them to your own work is acceptable and frankly necesary considering it's very hard to have an original idea nowadays.  However, the stealing of every story detail except character names would not be acceptable.  In my personal opinion your story should be at least 85% all your own creative product.  The other 15% could be ideas from other books, certain plot twists you would like to apply to your characters and so on.  The only acception is Fanfiction, which should never be published anyway unless you have the written permission from the original author.  Oh, and one more thing... Should you use a literary device, it would be considerate to mention the author you took it from in your forward or "Thanks" section.  Because, if that device makes the story work, which allows it to get published, then you do owe this person some thanks.  
    
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       A poem I created from my experience of learning stick-shift.  "Sticking to it"  Shaking with stomach fluttering, My hands are now on the wheel.  Sighs blow, the engine goes Now my forehead is on the wheel.  One little process of toothy gears, That grinds my nerves as I learn it.  Will I ever have it flowing As smooth as silk on a polished table?  Halt then vault and back to start.  So damn sensitive! Worse than my teacher beside me!  One more time?  Doing Fine?  I feel like a martini! Shaken - not stirred.  Back to neutral and out with the keys. We'll stick-it to the stick tomorrow, I say And we switch views yet Again.  
    
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       My creative writing instructor brought up an interesting concept not too long ago, which stirred controversy in the class.  She said that we need to "write for this century", that we cannot write like the poets of old because their writing is of a certain past time.  However, who's to say that her style is that of this time?  With bellbottom pants and other such styles coming back into popularity, why can't literary styles come back into popularity?  It's true that certain literary devices get "recycled" throughout time... why not styles as well?  This discussion was primarily directed towards old style rhyming poems.  Most of these poems that we recongize were created by ground-breakers of the time.  These author's only defined their time after they had died and their poems anaylsed by the next generation and seen for their greatness.  When they were writing these poems they could have been severely critized for being odd, old-styled, or beyond understanding.  The fact is, we will not know what the writing style for this century will be until it passes.  This is something only hind-sight can show.  Not you, me, or any of my class mates should feel they have to write a certain way.  Write the way you feel like writing and let the critics of the future decide whether or not you define the time.  Now is the time to be you.  Thank you.    
    
    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yes, I know it's almost been a month since I last posted.  However, between the class work, the reading, - learning stick (long story), and handling the regular biz... I have been a little overworked lately.  I want to post more poems, if for the only reason that I'm proud of myself for doing so well with them.  The creative writing class will head into fictional stories by mid March.  So there will be a change in content around that time.  I want to make some more adjustments to the blog itself again.  Perhaps even the subject will change.  Again, I'm just trying to make it interesting and true to itself.  Thanks for reading me. 
    
    
</post>

<date>31,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       War Torn Love – By Jill Wakefield  Katherine stared into the white face of the old pocket watch, ten 'til nine it read.  She then looked up to the north corridor entrance across the grand hall of the station.  She sighed as she watched holiday shoppers bustling about with soon-to-be gifts in their hands.  Murmurs and the occasional cry of a child filled the tile and marble hall.  Amidst the constant echoes she felt strangely alone at the café.  Katherine's weariness was beginning to gnaw at her anxiousness and excitement as she waited.  She adjusted her stiff and fatigued body in the small wooden chair as she thought to herself: 'He’s three hours late now'.  Katherine pulled her shawl closer to her as she sat waiting.  She would wait there all night for him if necessary.    	She began to dread that this delay might not be that he simply missed his train but that his letter of decommission came too soon.  What if he was never able to escape eastern France?  What if he died from the injuries he had mentioned in earlier letters?  She had counted the long months and cherished every letter from her husband since he was sent off to war in Europe.  For once she had developed an intimate relationship with their regular mailman, always hoping he would bring some good news.  When the letter finally came that he was being honorably discharged due to injury her happiness overran any thoughts about his condition.  What if he died as he was being transported to the states? Honestly, Katherine had always felt that he was unsuited for this trial and feared it would take his life.  He was a gentle man, always tender even to strangers.  He was not timid nor a coward but the horrors of this war seemed more than any sensitive soul could handle.  Katherine had more than once wrapped herself in her own arms as she read the news about Hitler's ravaging army in occupied east Europe and France.  In her dreams she had seen her fair Benjamin fall to his knees in horror as he stood upon the blood soaked ground.  The fact that her mind could conjure up such images was frightening.   	A touch on her shoulder brought her back to the cold Grand Central Station.  It was the elderly waiter.  He informed her that the café would be closing shortly.  He welcomed her to sit at the small table as long as she liked but urged her to order anything else now.  She smiled faintly and checked her small purse.  She had hoped to treat her husband to a warm meal with her newly hard earned money but now she saw fit to have one more cup of coffee in an effort to help her stay awake.  The kindly old man nodded her request to a young serving boy and then walked over to another gentleman who was waiting at a far table.  Katherine noticed how the bearded man also ordered a coffee with what coins he had in his pocket.  	Katherine had noticed him when she first sat down.  She couldn't imagine whom he was waiting for in such a disheveled state.  He wore a hat down tight on his head, complimented with a tattered long coat and extra large scarf.  She had no choice to arrive in her office clothes and her hair was falling down out of the bun she had made this morning, but she still thought of herself as presentable.  Katherine soon realized her own arrogant thoughts and scolded herself.  Times were hard nowadays.  Many people didn't have much and were too often starving.  ‘This man was probably spending what he has on food at the cost of his appearance’, she thought to herself.  She smiled faintly to apologize for her rude thoughts.  The man reacted strange to her awareness of him.  As her cup of coffee arrived Katherine turned her gaze back to the grand hall and the far north corridor.   	Another half an hour went by and the crowds had begun to decrease.  Not many were traveling at night.  Most of the travelers earlier had been women.  Though many American housewives had taken up a job in the past two years most still clung to their old ideas and values.  One of them was to be home before too late. Katherine had believed in these womanly rules too.  Working for a local department store had helped her manage the household affairs but she had to get use to coming home to an empty house in the evening.  It was disturbing for her those first months.  She found herself praying every night not only for Benjamin's safety but also for strength to carry on with his normal duties.  Just then she noticed a chair being pulled over to her table. It was the shaggy gentlemen.  	"May I sit down with you Madam?  If we could find company with one another we would not have to wait alone.  If you don't find me too gruesome, of course." he said in a shy and soft voice.  At this moment Katherine was able to see him much clearly as she looked up into his face.  She saw that he wore a tattered military coat and hat, but what startled her was his face.  Beneath his hairy features was much scarring, especially on the left side of his face.  The left eye seemed pale like rotten milk, most likely blinded.  His hand in which he grasped the chair was missing the last two fingers and knuckles of others.  It too was scarred but functioning at best as it held the back of the chair.  She recognized that he must be another decommissioned soldier.  His torn features did send a shiver down her back but her kind heart went out to him.  	"I... I would enjoy the company, Sir.  Please pardon my reaction. You simply startled me,” she said politely and inviting.  He, of course, already knew what had happened but was desperately thankful for her tender entreaty.   	He had been watching her for sometime now, ever since she arrived and began waiting.  He had watched as she took out the golden pocket watch, how she caged it in her slender pale fingers.  He had counted each chestnut brown strand of her hair as it fell loose from her bun and began to frame her face.  ‘It was such a beautiful face’, he had thought.  With hearing her kind words in his good ear he almost wept.  Her fidelity in waiting up to this late hour finally stirred enough strength in his heart to approach her.  	"Who is it that you're waiting for Miss?" he asked.  	"Mrs., Mrs. Hansen.  I'm waiting for my husband who is home from the war in Europe. Were you there, Sir?" she asked timidly, not wanting to upset him.  The man took a deep breath into his lungs before answering.  He seemed to be quelling something.  	"Yes, Mrs. Hansen, I have seen that land and it has seen me," he said in a sad tone.  Katherine nodded not wishing to ask him more and have him recall any pain.  Silence took over the table again as the two sipped their coffee.  A desperate question had been pushing at the man ever since he saw her sit down and soon he felt that question boiling up to his lips.  He was scared of her answer.  So much seemed to be resting on it.   	"Mrs. Hansen, may I beg of you to answer a sensitive and possibly disturbing question?" he asked very softly as he covered his bad left hand with his normal right hand.  Katherine was taken aback by the sudden change in conversation.  She felt trapped by her feelings to be kind to the man so nervously she agreed to the strange request.  "You don't need to pretend Madam. I know my appearance is more than startling. What I have been waiting for here in this café is to learn whether or not I can come home looking as I do.  I want to know if I can be accepted and loved like any other man - like the man I was before.  You're a tender and kind young woman, who I'm sure, is loving and sweet.  Could you see a woman not unlike yourself loving a man who looks as I do?" he asked almost shaking with those last words.  Katherine looked into his eyes deeply and swallowed.  She struggled with an answer for such a question.  She looked back to the north corridor and thought of her own Benjamin.  ‘What if those injuries he spoke of were similar to this man's’ she thought. Of course she would continue to love him in her heart but to feel comfortable... it would be very hard to find comfort in the visage of a battle torn man.  She had always loved Benjamin’s handsome looks.  She couldn’t imagine them gone, but she did know that what she loved most of all about him was his wit and kindness.  It was his tender carefree nature that had always stirred her passion.  She instantly recalled a time when they were walking in Central Park and happened upon a large muddy road. He had attempted to carry her over it but slipped and both fell into the sludge. At first she was upset and glowing like a boiling kettle, but then Benjamin began laughing and it was infectious.  She was soon giggling as they threw mud at each other.  They looked like a pair of dirty bums as they walked home but the joy was there nonetheless.  Though mud cannot compare to carnage, she felt love would overcome the aftermath of war.  Finally, she replied to the soldier.  	"Sir, I will not lie to you.  Your looks are more than startling.  In fact they hamper my response.  But thinking of my own dear Benjamin.  I realized he too could return looking much like yourself.  So much in fact that I might not recognize him, fore I can’t imagine him in such a state.  Although, the sight of him would at first be frightening, and sadness would grip us both, I'm sure our love will spark during that first awkward embrace.  No matter what the war has done to him, he will always be my Benjamin inside.  I know I would be able to look on him and see his love shining through, making him more dear to me than ever." she said as she started to glow for the first time that night.  Her words brought tears to eyes of the soldier. With his good hand he wiped them away.   	At that moment the man reached into his pocket and pulled out a folded up handkerchief and offered it to her.  Katherine wasn't sure what to make of it until she unfolded it.  Inside was a locket.  This was the same locket she exchanged for her dear Benjamin's pocket watch.  They had agreed to exchange these items while he was away during this war.  	"What does this mean?" she cried shaking with fear, tears of having lost her beloved husband were already forming in her eyes.  	"It means, my sweet Katherine, that your dear Benjamin has come home." he said as he choked on more of his own tears.  Before her gaping eyes he removed the tight hat and scarf.  Katherine stared and slowly she saw her Benjamin under the thin, pale, scruffy, and scarred soldier before her.  She began to cry as she reached out for him with shaking hands.  Her lips trembled as she brought his good hand close them.  Her touch was like an angel's.  Benjamin wanted to embrace her with all his might, but he was still afraid her reaction.  He couldn’t bear to see her shocked gaze.  Katherine felt shattered by love and grief as she looked upon her husband.  The tears wouldn’t stop but the love in her swelled and shaking as much as him, she stood holding both his good and bad hands gently urging him to stand with her.  As they both stood crying in sadness and joy she reached her arms around his neck and hugged him as she kissed his scarred cheek.  Feeling his own love for his dear sweet Katherine over powered him.  Benjamin scooped her up into his arms and spun around on both good and bad legs. Oh how he had wanted to hold her high, to show her that he still could.  They simply stood holding one another as the last station officer peered at them from a distant doorway.  The old man shed a tear himself as he left them to their war torn love - still thriving.  
    
    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I can officially declared success today.    Yesterday, during my creative writing class I received my "Poetry Folder" back from grading and many happy comment plus a big "A" accompanied my work.  As I flipped through pages I began to feel even better as I saw my professor's comments all over other poems.  Just about all the comments were praise.  It lifted my spirit.  I was already happy with my work but to know that she thought so much of it made me feel even better.  I will be posting my poems soon.  Frankly, I would like to offer them as a little email book for those who request it but no only do I think no one will request it but I think thats a little conceded of me.  However, it got me thinking... why pay for any book of poetry or fiction?  Especially from an unknown writer?  Does that person think they are being conceded if they sell their first book?  Oh well, maybe I'll talk about those ethics another time.  
    
    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       There are two things on my posting list today.  1. On the topic of New's Stories: I'd like to promote national public radio and WHYY.  These publically funded broadcasts are just marvelous.  Not only do you get the news and some very interesting news stories but you get them from different public networks that are not tainted by big corporate ownership.  The only big news organization on the radio is BBC news from London, which I have always regarded highly since they are so internationally orientated.  Obviously I have been listening to these broadcasts more often and I actually find myself wanting to comment on them so you might see my opinions on current events more often.  2. I have finally found a suitable beginning for my new novel idea.  I have just been going with the flow slowly and summarizing where things get fuzzy.  I want to let everyone know that it's OK to summarize sometimes when you are starting a new novel.  You will get inspiration for those fuzzy parts and can go back to fill them in.  The summaries help you to remember the story line and that expansion is needed.  Hopefully I will post that new beginning soon.  
    
    
</post>

<date>19,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       As you can tell I tried to place this new novel idea in a new location other than down the street or in the next universe.  I always wanted to use a foreign atmosphere but I never had enough experience to write about another place other than my home or a completely made-up world.  To keep myself from messing up too much I decided to make my main characters on the outside of the local social environment.  This way I won't need to go deep into the social behavior of another culture and just enjoy the exotic setting.    If this story ever develops into a gem and I still have it in the foreign setting I will be sure to pass it under the nose of a native born Turk (either my Fiance', his family or friends) before I send it off to a publisher.  Just to be sure I kept everything true to the culture and land.  Actually, even though it appears that I named the entity... I really haven't picked out names yet.  With me, that comes after the personality of the character is down tight.  Anyone who knows me will know where the name "Davrem" came from...*smirk*  I couldn't help it, without a name the draft would sound funny.  I want it to roll as best as possible right now.  However, this draft doesn't seem to be flowing much at all.  I'm going to try and post a new first page of the novel; this one will not be done in first person.  I need to do some more experimenting so I explore all the beginning angles.  Usually, I start with a person and a destiny and just fill in the gaps as the character's personality runs.  This time I have a special character with a gift but I don't know yet what I want her to accomplish.  It has to be big... maybe not big in the physical sense.  But I surely want this to be a moving and emotion piece.  I want it to embody my deep humanitarian feelings.  I want it to be a struggle for life in some way.  The life of everyone.  It could be a secret battle, sacrifice, or something of that nature.  I'm still fleshing it out.    I've realized that this is going to take me a lot longer than my first fanfiction novel.  I have to create a whole world and a brand new array of characters.  Whereas before I only had to create my new character to perform a destiny in a predesigned setting filled with wellknown characters.    Sometimes I feel like destroying it thinking it's a bad idea... like it's already been done... so why do it again?  But when I think about it seriously I can't recall a book like this.  I'm not sure if anyone is gonna want to read it but thats not really my goal.  I want to write, period.  If I think it's great and I have exceeded my expectations then I will declare it a success.  If someone wants to publish it thats just fine with me.       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Thanks to the wonderful people at blogger.com I have learned that my archives for this blog will never be lost no matter how long I blog.  I plan on backing up a lot of my writing on the BLOG.  Please be warned: a lot of that stuff is weird and choppy because they are either buds of ideas or deep personal feelings.  I will state if a work is simply a back-upped draft or a finished product of my creativity.  Thank you. 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       An Attempt to start my new Novel idea...  bear with me... my beginning are always bad.  1st Attempt... testing 1st person point of view.  People have explained to me that living in the world is difficult.  They have yet to feel the tumult of having one foot in an entirely different world at all times.  I grew up that way.  With two parents assisting though only one contributed to my birth.  The other... his hands have never touched me in the way everyone else knows 'touch'.  He saw me when I was two; partly because I saw him first.  I could see them all, those strange glowing entities that live half-way into our material world.  He saw how my special gift made me unable to function normally.  Gifts have always come at a price.  My price was the painful fact that I will never see my mother's face clearly.  The doctors branded me as legally blind when I was born.  Nothing maybe visually clear to me but from what I  can  see, most things I know are completely alien to the rest of my kind.  Let me explain...  It was a hot day again.  After my real father died, we had moved to quiet outskirts of Bodrum in southwest Turkey.  My father was a native of this country but my mother and I had always stood out as strangers with our foreign milkish skin and blue eyes.  She felt more comfortable close to the popular resort, which was a favorite of English speaking tourists.  Ocassionally she would invite a wellknown doctor from London to come and examen me while enjoying the highlights of the seaside city.  Today, we were to visit with a Dr. Fairfield who would be relaxing at the popular Deniz Gul hotel, one my Mother recommended often.  The breeze and the blue of the sea was all I looked forward to as we swung around the mountain road.  It was probably a gorgeous view from the road but I hardly knew where the sky met the land or if there were expanses of olive green and sand brown.  My near sight vision was no better.  I could hardly make out the fruit in the backseat with me.  The city was yet another blurr of vague color and the smell of cars and food.  We arrived at the hotel around noon though it felt like nine.    I walked in with Mom unassisted.  She never believed it was him who guided me but she did finally acknowledge that she no longer had to hold my hand.  Davrem, as I called him, was there with me as always.  He whispered to me about the people in the room.  His whisper is not like anyone else's.  Only I can hear it and it's not always clear.  Instead of words, like those on this page, he spoke to me in ideas, or meanings.  It took me my childhood to learn it and respond accordingly.  He never liked to reveal too much.  He could easily do more than just observe people but he prefered to never do those things.  Thats what separated him from the others.  He did not indulge in the power he was given, he didn't use it to deceive either.  He believed in love and truth, the same as most of us.  When he saw me for the first time he thought it was his duty to look after me.  to be continued...            
    
    
</post>

<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'd like to take a small break from my normal publishing to say something about current events.  After all, posting opinions about the news is what these blogs were created to do.  If you'll notice I am a recent convert to Islam.  I did not convert for any reason less that faith.  A revelation came to me and I will say nothing more about that.  However, since that revelation I have been forced to deal with a religion that is widely misunderstood, misrepresented, and incorrectly practiced.  I want to say so much about it that I could probably start a whole new blog just on that topic alone.  However, speaking from this point of view about the current events in the Middle East I would just like to say this to the world:  Life is God's great gift to everything and anything and that gift should be honored and "lived".  If everyone could just see Death as their enemy and not some other man then we would find peace.   Yes, men make mistakes... to err is human.  If that error causes Death, then it needs to be corrected, but more death is not the answer.  Death begets Death.  If you stop one death you will stop the subsequent death.  Soon all death from human hands will stop and once we all are just living as God intended - then we can achieve anything.  Another life is not the enemy.  Only death is the enemy.  Thank you. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today I am finishing the poetry half of my creative writing class.  The below poems that I have posted earlier are my best works, which I will be submitting for quality.  Frankly, I'm very proud of them and my tackling of poetry in general.  In fact there is one poem, which I wanted to create but didn't finish.  Even though it is no longer required for class I think I'll continue to work on it anyway.  I have to admit that poetry is quite theraputic.  I just found myself spilling my emotions and deep rooted thoughts all over the page.  I couldn't help it.  Those were the feelings that got the most descriptive detail.  I couldn't stop myself from crying periodically because of people or memories I wrote about.  Frankly, when I stopped to see what I actually wrote and how it made me feel it was refreshing.  This hidden emotions we're ugly and didn't need to be covered up anymore.  They became beautiful songs.  I highly recommend poetry and the book we used as a text book: In the Palm of your Hand - A poet's portable workshop, by Mr. Steve Kowit.   
    
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I still don't have any new members in my icq group for workshopping creative writing works.  If I don't see anybody by the end of this week I am going to consider shutting down the group.  No point in taking up bandwidth if no one is utilizing the group. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ICQ Group Update...  I have been having some difficulty posting stories onto the message boards.  Perhaps there is a character limit that is not mentioned.  There are ways around this.    Once a group of people have been established I will add the members to my ICQ.  If someone has a story they would like others to read, then that person can send it to me and I will transfer it to others (perhaps I'll use the file sharing thing once I investigate it).  This way there is less chance of passing anything unwanted, whether it be virus encrusted or just curse filled.  An example would be if a story is rated R then I would be sure to pass it to adult members only.  Of course this only works with an HONEST GROUP.  Frankly, I don't even have a group at all but I hope that I will and that everyone will be honest so we can enjoy this workshop.  Thank you.   
    
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       You'll easily notice all the new ICQ things I added.  There is a link to my icq group, a icq status thingie under "Contact Me" and at the very bottom is a fun ICQ panel, which has buttons that allow you to page me and such.    Feel free to do so!  I am dying to know if anyone reads this blog of mine!  Enjoy!  
    
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Recently, I created a ICQ group called Writer's Workshop.    I made this group to model the workshop process I am undergoing in my Creative Writing class.  During this workshopping everyone in the class gets to read your work, mention all the things they like, and add how the draft could be improved.  It's absolutly marvelous to see how an audiance reacts to your work.  I find it instrumental in the revision process.  The link for this group will be added to my links.  Please join if you're free! 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The below long story doesn't move as I would like it to and it doesn't have an ending.  I am not going to be bringing it to class.  Instead I have chosen a story, which I wrote with inspiration from classic essay/book "The Prince".  I am currently reading the book for World Literature class and it inspired me to write about a man who holds to Macaivelli's idea of the perfect ruler.  Unfortunately, I couldn't achieve an ending, especially since the story had to be double spaced.  I couldn't even make the target 6 pages.  Instead I have 8 and it cost me nearly 14 dollars to have all the copies printed!  The story is called "Maid For A Man" and it's not only about an Prince ruling a small portion of Italy during the reniassance but also about his chosen Man... or Maid... the head servant that accompanies him always.   He chose a young orphan woman who offered her services.  He named her Temperance after the attribute he so admires in her.  He has gone as far to say that "She possesses many attributes any father would desire in a son.", which is rare praise for a woman in those times.  These are two very interesting people, but I'm already sure this story will end in heartache because the Prince's occupation doesn't allow room for love, let alone to someone like Temperance.  She too is bound by thoughts of his occupation and how she would be a weakness or a danger.  Though many devious actions take place in the end the two realize that it's all for the people that they do what they do.  After sacrificing much I believe they will either find themselves as peasants or the Prince will sit alone on his throne without Temperance.   I want to let the Maciavellian rules of conduct and warfare twist the story as the book itself twists most of my classmates. 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Story for Long Story Workshop - Creative Writing Class  The Pounding By Jill Wakefield (Not historically accurate, nor based on a true story)   The pounding of his bare feet matched the rapid beat of his heart.  Pillars of black smoke rose from all around the open desert plain.  The dead, half buried by sand blowing in an unnatural wind had their arms thrown out wide as if embracing death.  He never stopped, even as he stared.  Tears streamed down his cheek for no reason he could understand.  Everyone was dead now.  No one was in danger except him.  He had to conserve his strength.  He had to make it to the city.    Only few hours ago it was a just another hot afternoon when his family had heard the planes overhead.  They thought that the city would be the target and planned to stay out in their tents for the entire year.  His family had descended from desert nomads.  The tents were always the best shelter from any storm, natural or political.   He was helping his sister with her weaving when the tanks and infantry arrived.  They were on their way to the city.  The army found time to stop and steal him family’s possessions and kill them all.  He could still hear his father telling them to run as he wiped out his rifle and began taking down Iraqis.  Everyone was cut down by the automatic rifles except for him.  He managed to sneak into an outcrop of rock and the infantry had no pleasure in trying to flush him out.  After they passed he crept out to found his home burning.  He couldn’t stay there.       As he continued to run another's heavy breath came to his ears and he looked around.  Just behind him to his left was a girl running the same as him.  Her long thick dark hair was waving in the air.  He saw that her skirt was torn off at the knee and that her loose shirt was tied to her thin waist by a ragged sash. "Hey!" he called out, forgetting his own worries for a moment. "You can't run like that!" he said matter-of-factly.  She glared at him with tears in her eyes. "I run for safety.  What’s more important?  Clothes or life?" she yelled back in anger.  Both ran on in silence.  She didn’t know where she was going but she saw this man had a determined glare and decided to follow him.  When much of the death was out of sight the girl spoke to him. "Are you running to your family or away from them?" she asked breathless. "My family is dead." he replied. "Mine too." she said sadly.  The boy turned over his shoulder again to look at her.  Another explosion shook the ground and air.  Both stooped and slowed down but their feet could not stop.  It was like a desperate madness.    The young man was beginning to think differently of his companion.  He never imagined having company on his flight.  He had never been married but he knew that women don't survive alone.  They need a man to protect them, to provide for them.  These were the basic truths he had been brought up to know.  The young man realized that he was being presented with a possible obligation.  "Who will take care of you?" he asked her.  She took a moment before responding. "I don't know.  Maybe the Iraq's will have mercy." she said as a few tears squeezed out.  The young man didn't understand the Iraqis but he knew they would not have mercy on her if they had no mercy on his family.  Tight lipped he reached out his hand.  He knew this action would start him on a different life, no matter how short. "I will take care of you.  Trust me?" he said to her.  With only a slight hesitation she took his hand.  It was unusual to say the least.  Most single women never had relations with unmarried men but it was a desperate time and she would behave as if this bond was permanent.  They ran together hand in hand now across the pebbly desert.   	After a couple hours hey saw the oil pumps rising and falling before them.  They heard the sweep of metal on metal, the creaking, and pinging as oil was brought up from below their homeland.  They were at the outskirts of Kuwait City.  Smoke and men ran around many of the pumps.  They kept on running despite the fact that they were leaving a trail of blood from their cut and sore feet.  Only one thing made them stop.  It was a tiny white sign standing in the ground that stopped them.  It read "Beware: Minefield".  Then they notice the pain in their feet and dropped to the dirt to relief it.  Their chests were still rising and dropping rapidly as they watched convoys of trucks in the distance.  Occasionally there was a woman's scream or an explosion carried on the unnatural wind.  Other than that the pumps made the only sound.     	He took care of her feet first.  He wrapped them with part of his pant leg.  Then he tended to his own.  He regretted not having enough fabric to cover her properly but he resolved that she wasn't horribly improper concerning the circumstances. "What's your name?" he asked. "Aisha," she replied. "I'm Ahmad," he said.  Slowly more questions bubbled up and each learned about the other. They were both members of oil worker families.  Both families had lived around the rich land of Kuwait and were the first to be attacked by the invading Iraqis.  Each was running for the safety of the city.  Though Iraqi forces were there also, the city offered better chances at survival. "Do you know anyone in the city?" Aisha asked hoping they would not be running through alleyways. "My mother and sisters use to make baskets and other wares to sell in the city.  A friendly merchant named Abdul would help us sell them.  If he is still alive he should take us in." Ahmad said to reassure himself as well. "Some people say that the Americans are going to come." she said with down cast eyes.  She had never liked the westerners but with her family dead she wanted her home to be rescued by anyone. "I don't know." Ahmad said softly.  He knew about the rumors as well, but for all he knew they were only rumors.  Suddenly there was a large explosion at the pumps and a convoy of tanks and soldiers were coming in their direction.  Ahmed helped Aisha to her feet. "We need to cross the minefield.  Watch where I step." he said to her as he directed her behind him.  Sorely they stepped forward into the field avoiding any mounds in the sand.  Luckily, the mines were meant for tanks.  They were too large to bury sufficiently.  Many large metal plate-looking devices were seen under a sprinkling of sand as the couple walked around them.  The mines would have been buried better if they were meant for people.  They were well into the minefield when Aisha turned to see the tanks advancing on the field. "Ahmad we need to run!" she screamed as she grabbed his shoulder and hand tightly.  Ahmad turned to see it.  There were no troops with these tanks and the convoy would surely miss that tiny sign.  "Aisha, run right behind me and step where I step!" he said letting go of her hand.  They ran fast despite their bandages coming loose from their feet.  Ahead was another small white sign facing away from them.  It was the end of the minefield.  The ground shook them to their knees as the first tank reached the minefield and exploded.  Ahmad barely kept himself from falling shoulder first into a mine.  When they got up they only looked back once and then kept on running as more explosions followed.  Fear kept them running towards the distant city.   	The pain in their legs and feet overwhelmed their fear a mile from the city.  Dirt had caked onto open wounds and was grinding against tender flesh as they walked.  Aisha sat down first, crying a little from the pain.  Ahmad knew they couldn't stop out in the open but her tender feet were in bad shape. "Come, I'll carry you." he said. "Your feet are hurt too.  Just leave me,” she said refusing as she swooned in the heat.   "You took my hand.  Now do this.  We can't stay here." he said slightly angry with her waning spirit.  She looked up to him sadly and then took his hand.  He pulled her up onto his back and continued to walk with labored breaths.  Though his legs shook he continued to carry her until they reached the shade of the first tall building.  There they both collapsed exhausted from the trek.  After catching his breath Ahmad took notice of the rumbling silent city.  He had been there before when delivering handmade goods with his father.  Though sounds of battle echoed from all around the city, where they were was eerily deserted and silent.  Some windows and doors were boarded up completely while in other places wares were thrown about the street with the owner's door swaying in the breeze.  Quietly he crept over to the wares and scooped up some shoes and fabric.  Gently he removed most of the caked blood and sand from Aisha's feet and dressed it with fabric before handing her some sandals.  He did the same for his own torn feet.  Looking at them he knew he needed stitches but he didn't know if a doctor could still be found.  Ahmad told Aisha to take what was left of the fabric to cover her head and legs.  She did so thankfully.   Aisha had always thought about what it would be like to be with a husband.  She had few happy examples in her family.  Too often she would dread the thought of marriage.  However, as she looked upon Ahmad she saw a young tried man who knew his duties and possessed a good heart.  She only wished her family was still alive.  The random thought brought tears to her eyes. "Don't cry Aisha.  There is no time for it now.  We need to find Mr. Abdul before we can rest." he said helping her to her feet.  She wobbled a bit and wrapped the makeshift long skirt around her waist once more.    It felt hotter in the city.  Both had dry cracked lips and were nearing dehydration.  Ahmad wondered about trying to get his bearings.  Some buildings were crumbled and burning.  The debris kept him from going down the streets he could recall from memory.  It took him longer than he thought but he soon found the shop.  The tables were bare but the door was not boarded up.  Ahmad stepped up and after peering down both ends of the street he pounded on the door.  A window opened a crack above and a hushed voice demanded to know who they were. "It's me, Ahmad, son of Hamdi.  You helped him sell handmade wares." Ahmed called back hoping the thought of his associate's son would stir his heart. "Ahmad! Where is your father?" the voice asked. "Dead, my whole family is dead.  In the name of Allah, please shelter us!" he begged.  After a few tense moments the window shut and the door creaked open. "Come on! Come on!" whispered the man.  He was a gray-bearded man with a traditional white headdress.  Swiftly he shut the door behind them and began locking it up from top to bottom.  Finally he turned to the youths. "My boy, you made it all the way here?  And who is this you have with you?" Abdul began asking. "Sir, it has been long since we last drank." Ahmad said wearily.  Abdul then called up the stairs that were before them.  "Sertab, have water ready." he said.  He then helped the two up the narrow wooden stairs to his living apartment.  Inside were his young wife and two young sons.  Sertab had glasses of water for them and the two boys, both no more than 12 yrs old, sat close to a window watching the guests enter.  Aisha almost collapsed as she sat down on the floor to drink the water. "Not so fast, my Dear." Sertab warned.  "You may overwhelm your system,” she said as she handed the other glass to Ahmad.  He sat down as well to drink.  Abdul sat down with his wife and children before continuing with his questions.  Ahmad answered them sadly, explaining all that had happened to him and Aisha.  Abdul feared for his family and had been listening to the radio news.  So far the Iraqis were taking control of all the major buildings that weren't already destroyed by the aerial bombardment.    Abdul was a common businessman with adequate living space for his family.  The comfortable living room was wrapped in soft blankets and rugs.  Some rice and dates were brought to the large squat coffee table.  Abdul offered plush rugs and pillows for the two travelers. "Please feel free to stay here and be comfortable.  If any one comes I will say that you are my son and this is your wife." he said gesturing to Aisha. "You're too kind, Sir.  I hardly know you and now I don't know how to repay you,” she said with her eyes low. "No, you are a guest now and you must allow yourself to feel like family because we may be shut in for a long time." he said shaking his head.  Ahmad agreed and told her she could remove the headscarf.  Beneath the scarf were a pair of weary but sparkling eyes and a healing smile.  Aisha and Ahmad made themselves comfortable as Abdul suggested.  First came the matter of their feet.  Sertab was the first to notice. “Allah be merciful!  What happened to your feet?” she said whisking over to examine Ahmad’s gashes.  “These will need stitches!” she said with worry on her face. “Madam, I can stitch if you have the thread and needle.” Aisha said timidly.  Sertab walked quickly over to her sewing. “Sertab, be sure to pass a flame over that needle.” Abdul warned her as he kept his boys off to the side.  She found a needle and an old Zippo lighter.  She passed it a few times before handing it to Aisha.  Wet cloths soon appeared to clean the wounds. “Ahmad, this is going to hurt.” Aisha warned him.  She shook her head at such a silly thing to say but she did know why she said it.  She was afraid to bring him pain after all that he did for her.  With Sertab looking on she made a few knots on the larger lacerations and wrapped up the rest.  The bandages would have to be changed everyday until the wounds heal.  Her own feet needed attention but luckily the wounds looked like they would close on their own. “From now on I want both of you to stay off your feet.” Abdul said as he helped Ahmad into a comfortable position.    Rest came easily to the two wonderers.  When they awoke from sad sandy dreams they found Abdul’s family listening to the radio.  They were listening to the BBC and other news broadcasts.  The situation in Kuwait sounded grim.  The Iraqis had killed many and were taking control of major buildings.  Abdul cursed his feelings for his shop.  If he had cared less about the damn building he would have left for nearby Saudi Arabia.  Ahmad reminded him that if he had left then Aisha and him would be roaming the city in desperation.  It was enough to calm his host.   To be continued…  
    
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Handel sat down on the sidewalk with his popsicle dripping over his fingers.  He didn’t really care for the cold orange flavored ice but he was always given one.  It was a sign that he would never be an adult in their eyes.  A pat on the head from his mother only confirmed this.  Handel fumed under his narrowing gaze.  Just because he couldn’t speak his thoughts didn’t mean that he didn’t have any.  But he couldn’t speak that thought either.  He simply brought the sicle to his lips and slurped up the juice as he turned back to the 4th of July parade. 	It was a quaint suburban parade full of boy scouts, girl scouts, local bands, a few mummers, and a small assortment of civil war re-enactors.  They were all tossing candy, flags, and plastic hats.  It was loud but melodious and made for a nice sight in the humid heat.  Of course, all the spectators that were crowded along the street made the heat worse.  No breeze could reach Handel and his mother as they sat closed in by bodies that were reaching for goodies.   One red, white, and blue hat landed near Handel and he slowly reached forward to scoop it up.  Luck would have it that a boy ran down and snatched it right before his fingers could touch it. 	“Cool!” he said as he tried to walk away with it. 	“Now wait a minute, Handel was reaching for that.  Hand it over!” Handel’s Mom said in that high-pitched irritating tone that meant business.  The boy’s smile dropped and as did Handel’s.  He fumed again at the thought of being a man who can’t even say “Hey!” when his proverbial toes were being stepped on.  He just scowled at the boy with his blue eyes as he walked back over. 	“Sorry Mrs. Bateman,” the boy replied as he handed the hat to Handel with a sigh.  Handel’s ill functioning fingers clasped the brim and slowly he placed it on his head.  He tried to forget the incident as he looked across the street.  The parade was already dwindling and he could see all those standing on the other side.  There was that nice blonde girl named Sarah.  She always smiled at him when others just tried to look the other way.  She looked the same age as him but she was just like the rest of them, normal.  He always tried to forget her smile.  He knew it didn’t mean anything other than that she was brought up to be polite. 	“All right Handel Honey, time to go home and cool off,” his mom said as she took his arm.  She slowly helped him up to his feet that wobbled but soon stood on their own.  Mrs. Bateman thanked the Lord and cursed this “John” fellow as she walked with him back to their little cape cod house on 3rd Ave.  Handel never did understand who this “John” was but she was always mad at him and what he did.   	      	Once they reached the house Handel declined to come in.  He always did so.  The dammed window mounted air conditioner never really worked.  It only dripped water inside adding to the humidity.  Besides, he wouldn’t deal with his mother anymore today.  Instead he sat down on the porch swing and put his chin in his hand.  He noticed his beard was growing again.  He knew he was a bit shaggy looking but he didn’t really care.  Everyone always tried to look away from him anyway.  He was an eyesore in the community.  While on these angry depressing thoughts he happened to see more kids running by with hats, candy, and flags.  Briefly they took him back to a better day when he was more human.  	Handel could still remember the smell of the soccer field.  It was there that spent most of him time back then.  He had two dozen goals that year.  He was practicing when his father drove up on his motorcycle.  It was a loud bike that could easily speed down a street and set all the car alarms off.  Handel would ride with his father everytime he brought it out of the garage.  His mother always complained that they should be wearing helmets.  The day she didn’t remind them was the day it all happened. 	Handel hopped on with the soccer ball under one arm while the other held his hand.  They raced down the streets towards home with suddenly a small child ran out into the street.  Another was chasing her and there was no room to turn.  Handel’s dad threw the bike into a parked car and it sent Handel flying.  The last thing he could remember was loosing the ball from his hands.   	Weeks passed by before he woke up in a hospital bed with only his mother by his side.  He could never remember seeing his father and after the accident it was like his father never existed.  His mother was the only one there to take him through physical and mental therapy for years and years.  She was the one who home schooled him through that time as well.  She received donations from the community.  Everyone was hoping Handel would recover fully.  When he hit twenty they all knew that the active engaging Handel would never be coming back.  They all shunned the slightly twisted homely man boy who took his place.  	Thinking of this Handel went back to hating life and the people around him.  He decided to get up and walk.  He knew his mother would call the cops if she couldn’t find him but he didn’t care about any of them anymore, not even his mom.  ‘What kind of a life was this?’ he would ask himself with each step on the uneven but steady sidewalk.       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       In these controversial times I think every writer needs to know where they stand on the issue of censoring, government enforced or otherwise.  I am in the process of writing my own essay on issue.  If others have essays or have been meaning to write one, please let me know.  I would love to send a bundle of them to writer's digest magazine as a collection of views.  I hope that all who submit to this bundle idea include their full name and state of residence.  This just so I can give you proper recognition.  Thanks for considering.  
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It was someone's comment that I use an adult who is treated like a child for the main character in my hometown inspiration.  I've been doing my brainstorming and I have come up with a man in his late twenties who had an accident when he was a child.  He still has intelligence but his brain was damaged in such a way that thoughts can't automatically be put into words.  He has to focus to express simple thoughts like Yes, No, Thank You, and Please.  He also has some mobility problems too but is no wheelchair bound.  This way his mother is always looking after him, he barely goes anywhere, he is always in town, and the whole town thinks he's still a child.  Everyone knows him so he can go out by himself as the dismay of his protective mother.  He is always thinking and we will always be seeing his thoughts.  The reader will find a frustrated trapped man who has little hope but a lot of anger and just wants to be left alone or understood.  I will add a love interest.  Some girl who has always smiled at him.  Though I don't know if this will be a good thing for him.  I might make her just sweet but uninterested in him.  I will be posting the beginning of this piece this weekend.  I still don't have a title for it.  How does it sound?  
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Continuing...  I just saw a few replies to a post I made on Fiction Addition (.net) and I'm surprised that people think of blogging as a journal that takes up too much time.  Mine is my publisher!  I publish my work on here and ask for comments.  I talk about writing when I want to.  I also add a writing exercise (rather daily) as a "thank you" towards my readers who I assume are writers and do practice with inspiring promps.  I don't have to juggle the blog and my work... they are one in the same.  There are drafts I keep that aren't published yet.  Some are HUGE because they are novels in progress.  This blog is instrumental in getting feedback and logging my writing progress.  Granted, not many famous writers use their blogs as such but I do and there is no reason why other writers can't.  Always, thanks for reading and commenting.  
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I have tried numerous times to hook up a network of writers' blogs.  Unfortunately, writers either don't have a blog or they just don't have the time, but I think it would be a great way to workshop.  Workshopping is a very important writing tool.  With a group of people reviewing your work you easily see how a general audiance will receive your story, possible revisions are pointed out, simple observations are given.  When I workshopped I even got possible endings for my stories!  Lots of great ideas from caring people.  to continue...  
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       One Page  Describe body language during conversation without adding any dialogue.  Have a party of three at a table, two men and a woman.  One man is in love with the woman, the woman is in love with the other man, and he's in love with himself.  Describe their posture, inclinations of the bodies, hand motions and so on.  Show the bodies talking.  Please let me know if this exercise works for you and why.  
    
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This is a first for me.  I have a setting I want to use that has limitless possibilities but I don't have a character to experience it all.  Below I have chosen a boy of 7 years but I fear that he is just two young to get around to everywhere and be in on all issues happening in the town.  It would be interesting to see it all from the innocent view of a child.  However, I feel that I can't keep the story too close to a child and keep it stimulating for adults.  I need to find someone who can focus on the town, but I want it to be an unusual character that will catch people's attention.  I still like the name Handel, which I realized I was spelling wrong :P  So, I think I would still like it to be a male character.  I think I may have to write main character a letter and just not tailor it to any particular age.  After I'm done I should just read it and see what age he sounds like and then build on that.  Maybe he could be in my position... grew up there, moved away, now back and realizing how it's a little paradise no matter what anyone could be complaining about.  
    
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Testing 1, 2, 3...  
    
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Writing Exercise 005-04  2 to 3 pages  Create a character ithout relying on anyboby you have known or seen.  You might consult an astrological chart (which normally speaks about the personalities of certain birthdays).  Place this person in a social context, lets say, a cocktail party, and have him exchange lines with the hostess.  Frankly, when trying to come up with an original character I like to take several parts from people or characters I have already known.  Other times I just have this vision of a person after I think up a name.  Let me know if this helps you. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This is an idea I am currently running with for the home town inspiration.  I thought it would be best to describe everything as a child being the main character but I'm not sure how this is going to work beacause a kid can only get to so many places.  Where there are no sidewalks...  Handle sat down on the curb to slurp his popcicle, which was melting in the summer heat.  As he sat with some of his friends he noticed how a very large old tree was lifting the sidewalk with it's roots.  He could actually see under the slab of concrete as he leaned over dripping popcicle juice for the ants.  He began to wonder if there were places where the sidewalks ends.  He wondered if they were end at deserts or jungles.  Suddenly he heard his mother calling.  It was late and dinner was ready.  Handle put the question in the back of mind with other such adolescent inquries like how long to spitballs stay attached to the bathroom ceiling.  While quickly swallowing the sloppy ice he said bye to his friends and ran down the block.  He took his time a bit as he came to some tall bushes, just so he would have a moment to wipe most of the orange popcicle juice on the under side of his shirt.  It didn't do much good. "Handle Robert Bateman WHAT have you been eating?!" yelled his mother as he stepped up onto the front porch. "Danny's Mom let us have a popcicle, thats all.  I'll still eat dinner, promise!" he stampered. "Doesn't Danny's Mother know you have dinner at 6pm?" she said in that irritated tone as she tugged Handle inside.  "At least go change that filthy shirt before dinner and don't forget to wash your hands." she said as her tone began to ease.  It ended with a motherly sigh as she walked into the kitchen.  Little Jessica was even more a mess as always with spagetti everywhere but her mouth.  She almost wished that babies came with washer instructions.  Instead she just grabbed a paper towel and began wipping.  Handle was lucky enough to find a clean shirt somewhere in his room, which of late was a mud laboratory.  He almost forgot to wash his hands again as he made his way to the dinning table.  Again it was him, his mom, and little Jess in her sleep swing.  His mom served him the meatloaf and spagetti and the talking began. "Mom, can I have a be-be gun?" Handle asked as if complaining that he should have been given one by now. "No, of course not.  You're too young for that." she said with a quick glare. "But I'm the man of the house.  Danny has one!" he said.  His mom sighed. "Handle, you are not the man of the house, your father will be home, and I don't want to hear about what Danny has!  Eat your dinner." she said in that had Handle's fork go right into his mouth.  The spongy meatloaf didn't satisfy anything, but he didn't start again.  He knew she was getting upset and would soon start taking TV time away from him.  Handle never lost his TV time; not even the next Saturday morning.  He was there in his spot on the floor right in front of the TV when his mom woke up.  Handle noted how she never looked good in the morning anymore.  Her normally fair and lovely face always looked sad or grumpy.  Her hair wasn't put up anymore and it took her an hour or so to say "Ok, breakfast time."  After breakfast Handle was turned out so that his mother could clean the house.  He met up with Danny and Chris in front of Danny's house to talk about what to do. "I think we should go walk down the pike and look for money.  Anything we find we can take to the Henry's for penny candy." Chris said.  He was a candy addict and never known to share, even when he has the most. "I think we should go to the park to play basketball." Danny responded.  He was always the best at it since he had a hoop all his own hanging on the garage.  Losing always became boring.   Handle really wanted to explore that thought he had earlier about the sidewalk ending.  He knew it was kind of childish to think the sidewalk could just end.  Obviously, the sidewalk is everywhere and if he did follow it he would just end up walking forever.  But there was something that sounded adventurous about looking for the end of the sidewalk.  In the end he just kept it to himself and suggested exploring the back trails of the park. "Sure!" both friends were up to exploring.  Chris knew he could bring candy and Danny had the same adventurous spirit as Handle.  The park was actually a mile long jogging track in a small patch of woods but there were numerous kid-made trails that ran off in all directions into the dense bush.  The trails felt like tunnels on a thick summer day.  They were cool from shading canopy and offered many large roots to sit on when you got tired.  Supposedly, all these trails were circular and led you back to the jogging track but there was a rumor that one trail led all the way down into the dense pine barrens.  Many kids didn't look for it because of all the tales of the Jersey Devil, but those brave enough always hoped to find it and win the fame.  Handle was one of those boys. He was a deep thinking boy for the tender age of eight.  He walked with a certain confidense you didn't always see, which never led you on.  The boy was clever.  He knew posion ivy from regular creepers.  He knew when a storm was coming.  He also knew how to avoid the older kids who would use him for some kind of target practice.  It's rumored that he once beat up Frank Fallom but he never admitted, he said Frank did it to himself.  "So which trail shall we try this time?" Chris asked as they reached the jogging track. "How about the trail that runs along the swap.  Last year we gave up on it because of all the flies.  Maybe thats the one that goes to the pines." Danny said.  He had always been interested in finding that trail too. "You know, I think the trail we should try is that one to the south of the park." Handle said seriously. "But all those older kids hang out there." Chris whined. "I think thats cause they know something about that trail.  It's still early.  They shouldn't be around til later." Handle said.  He soon convinced Chris and Danny was already willing.  They first walked their way around the jogging track to the south.  The trail soon came into view.  Thought it was heavily traveled the beginning of it was still hardly visable.       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I was speaking with one of my professors lately and he too said write about the world as it is now.  This is something my creative writing professor was telling me and I wonder why this is. Why am I being encouraged to write about the now?  Frankly, with so many sensitive issues in the news and stress running rampid through our lives I don't know if I can write about the now and keep it from being depressing.  I do have one avenue of inspiration open to me... small town NJ has openned it's wonder to my eyes and I think I will be basing a store in a town not unlike the one I grew up in.  I think it makes a great exercise to base a story (novel or short) in your home town.  I will be posting anything good that comes from this. 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Writing Exercise 004-04  2 to 3 Pages  Write a story that starts off like this... The first time  I or Name  heard the song  title  by  author  (I, he, she) was...  This is an activity that I did in my creative writing class and it was really helpful once you could think of a song.  As soon as the song hit my mind I thought about where I was, what I was doing, I thought about another character hearing it.  It was very inspirational.  What do you think?  Also, I would like to make everyone aware of a need for freelance writing.  Below is the link.  I believe they are looking for articles under the topics highlighted on their page.  Their page is about the path to America.     urlLink Freelance Writers WANTED    
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yes, I know I have been neglecting my blog.  The obstacles of life will rear their ugly heads and keep you from the things you love... like writing.    I'm currently stuck at work right now, but I do vow to catch up with a new writing activity when I get home today.  I have approx. 7 hours to go.  Please bear with me.  It's hard to keep myself from writing for so long.  Thanks for your patience. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       My new great idea for a short story came from the grade school music concert I attended yesterday.  There were many kids running around the auditorium despite parents' effort to keep them in their seats.  It reminded me of times when everything was still and quiet except for one kid making a problem.  I thought of a professional band at a carnival or an orchestra captivating an audiance and suddenly everyone notices this young toddler running around and making a scene.  Perhaps a pair of women start discussing the child.  First the reader would be critical of them because they never had kids of their own.  However, at the end everyone leaves and the child is still there.  No one has come to claim him.  The two women are saddened and regret their words regarding the child.  They sit and wait for the mother.  I don't know if I will have the mother show up or not.  If she doesn't that would be the end.  If she does there will have to be a conversation.  What do you think?  Comment if you would. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Writing Exercise 003-04  One Page  Describe somebody's character by the shape, posture and gait of his or her body.  Don't describe the head of the person and don't tell if that character is lazy or happy.  Show these traits through body language.  This exercise helps the writer look at evidence of character in the whole body, not just the face.   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Due to an unexpected outting I wasn't able to finish the letter or the daily assignment.  I apologize for not posting the assignment for today.  I will post it in just a few hours when I get home for lunch.  I hope to complete the letter today, complete the assignments, post my submitted short story, and work on my new idea of a short story.  Also, I have received a message from an online magazine offering free exposure to writers who would like to submit an article.  The website is: http://www.useless-knowledge.com .  Please check it out if you would be interested in writing an articule. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Lately, I have been getting inspiration from the past.  I feel this is a deeply personal thing.  With what comes in the news and all the worries I have about my own life I guess I can't write about the present because I feel it's just too complicated.  I feel that if I tried to create a character in this time I would have to give that person opinions on many issues that are happening and have MANY outside forces direct the character's future.    It would probably make a good challenge though.  So, besides the daily exercise I am going to write a letter from a main character (thats how I get a feel for the character, I write a letter as if I'm the character writing to someone else).  I'm going to see how well I can mix in issues and worries that are all common place in this time.  I will be posting that later on either today or tomorrow.  Try it yourself or comment on how you already write present day characters.  I would love to hear it.   
    
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Exercise 002-04  2 or 3 pages Write down your first three memories.  Can you make a stry out of them?  Try.  Even if you aren't sure what you remember exactly, keep going.  Imagine that you remember more than you do.  Expand rewrite in the third person and forget it's you.  This could be precious material for you.  Again, remember not to give up so easily.  If those memories are just too fuzzy and fleeting then pick some others but obviously memories from the early part of your life. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Writing Exercise 001-04 By Jill Wakefield  	 It seemed that at least three hundred people woke up this morning and used their crusty morning voices to call out sick from work.  At least that’s how many people were out enjoying the sun and fair sky in the park.  Some were picnicking on this Wednesday morning.  Others were walking dogs, jogging, or writing under a tree with vibrating earphones on.  “And this is a white oak,” announced a tall and thin man with graying hair.  In a denser part of the park a grade school teacher was showing his 3rd graders different types of North Eastern trees.  Gingerly they each picked leaves to add to the manila envelopes they were carrying, probably for some later project.  When the teacher would turn to the next tree you could see the troublemakers teasing bugs or giggling between one another.  All wore a faint relaxed smile as they enjoyed their classroom in the park.  “Doggies!” a cute blond girl shrieked.  A couple walking their dogs made their way past the bunch and the class took a break so everyone could pet the smiling golden retrievers.  They couple defiantly looked like they should be at work.  Each was well dressed for a jog in department store fashion.  The dogs themselves were groomed, collared, and equipped with the latest leash technology.  The couple smiled and laughed with the teacher before walking on.  “Heads up!” yelled a middle aged, middleweight man in an unofficial baseball uniform as a baseball came flying past the dogs.  Both pulled at their leashes in an effort to chase the ball.  It was a younger outfielder that had to retrieve the ball from a dense sticker bush.  Overall it was a great looking day at the park.  
    
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Writing Exercise 001-04  A one page exercise.   Write a scene of a story from a glimpse you have had of a group of people - in a cafe, zoo, train or anywhere.  Outline characters in this scene and have them interact.  Try to visualize the scene.  The objective is to make as much as you can out of little.  And remember DON'T GIVE UP TOO EASILY.  I like to use Grand Central Station or maybe a crowded city park myself.  I'll give this one a try and post it later today. 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Lately, I have been trying to schedule in writing time, but when I do sit down to write I find myself without inspiration to run on.  So, to counter this problem I have been hunting up exercises to assign myself.  I've realized that you have to be serious like this if you want to make writing your career.  Many I know shy away from this saying that they have to be genuinely inspired to write anything good but through my creative writing class I found that when pushed I pop into a story that actually has potential and it gives me greater confidense in my abilities.  I will try to find an exercise everyday and post it here so we all can try them out together. 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'd like to make everyone aware of a writing contest that is very big with many winners.  It's the Writer's Digest 73rd Annual Creative Writing Contest. It's for poetry, short stories, memoirs, and inspirational writing. Entries are due this saturday, May 15th but you can send and entry over the internet at their website. There is an entry fee but it's worth it since they have 1,001 winners.  This means you have a good chance at winning.  You can send in as many entries as you want. You get to hear back about them in August.  I will be submitting the revised version of my "War Torn Love." I have to say that I did a good job revising it with a completely different ending.  Of course I will be renaming it to maybe "To Wait" or "December Rain".  I will be posting it after I submit it (cause that means I will be done revising it.) 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, I got on the band wagon and updated the blog to one of the new templates.  All the same links are available.  All credits are mentioned.  Even the cool ICQ panel is down at the bottom with my warning about reproduction of my posts.  Now anyone will be able to comment on my posts by clicking on the highlighted date and time.  I also plan to add a ticker soon so I can actually tell if I'm talking to anyone out there in cyberspace. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today I have destroyed the workshop group on ICQ because of lack of members.  Obivously, it wasn't popular enough to get off the ground - even with me advertising it to my creative writing class.  I will remove the link shortly.  However, I am trying to be on ICQ more often because the lack of discussion in my life is a stressful sometimes.  I'll definately need the interesting mind of another to make it through the long summer.  Soon I will post my entry for the Writer's Digest 73rd Annual Writing Contest.  I would love to hear what anyone thinks of it.  Thanks 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Like I mentioned before, I was visiting a local writer's group to continue workshopping my stories.  Though all the members of the group had great ideas and had the best intentions in mind - the group made me realize something about GROUPS.  You either  A.  Bend to the ideas (build up or tear down) of the group. B.  Flex to the ideas taking those that enhance but disregarding those that you feel take away from your original vision. C.  Crack under the pressure of critiquing.  There isn't always a choice.  Some people lack confidence in their style, so they take up any idea impressed on them.  Some people lack a LOT of confidence in their ability to write so they crack because if there are so many ideas for improving their story then the story must be bad (which leads to "I must be a bad writer").  Only those who have confidence in themselves as a writer and a confidence in their art can flex with the ideas of a serious group.  And there's another thing... A serious group.  Are you a serious writer?  Are you a weekend writer?  Do you have a dream of being published?  Or do you expect your next work to take you into professional writing?  If you want to workshop your stories with a group you need to make sure you have found the group for you.  If they don't understand your goals then they will at best guess and at worst impose their goal on you and they might be more serious or hobbyish than you.  I say all this because I joined the group for two sessions and even though I enjoyed the great ideas they sometimes came too hot and heavy.  There wasn't enough positive feedback about the parts that didn't look like they needed to be improved.  That positive stuff is important.  I think it's important even for the established writer.  But am I asking too much here?  After all I did join this group for help in improving my writing.... Yes.... Thinking about it right now... Helping me out with my writing is not just giving ideas on how to improve my story but is also helping me write more, write better and to do that I also need confidence.  I do think the group was helpful but I think I was in a little bit over my head.  They were a little too serious for me.  I'm not ready for publishing.  I am still finding my voice in writing since all my previous writing was fanfiction.  Just the end of last year did I take my writing to the next level with the nurturing of a great teacher.  (You know I mean you, Barbara)  I think I still need the nurturing until I can stand up for my writing.  This means that I need to stick it out on my own or bunk with people at my own level.  I do have one friend on the same level so it looks like we will be bouncing things off one another for a while.  I hope this has been informative for you all.  Thanks for reading.  
    
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       2 to 3 Pages  Research an obsure holiday and then write about a family or a person celebrating that holiday.  The research is minimal but is good practice.  The holiday could be a local township holiday or an international celebration.  Hopefully, you'll already be getting ideas for storie as you browse lists that could easily be found on the internet.  Write about the entire day and try to pick one character to be close to.  If anyone tries this, let me know how it works out.  I think this could easily help someone create a short story. 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Below is a summary of creative tips to help your creativity from the wonderful people at Writer's Digest.  By the way... this magazine is available at your local bookstore but I will do my best to share the info with you here.  Feeling like your writing is a chore?  Here are a few suggestions to get the juices flowing and having you once again looking forward to sitting down and writing. 1. Change your location... sometimes you just need to be somewhere else to have new ideas coming to you.  Frankly, if I'm having trouble with my characters I love to take a notebook or my jornada (pda) and go to a cafe or diner and watch people as I sit with a hot cocoa and cheese fries.  You could just need a little fresh air.  I always find that being outside with just the wind and trees can help me focus on my writing - Less distractions, interactions, and no tv. 2. Turn on some music... I LOVE music while writing.  Not only does it create a wall between me and everything else but the beat keeps me move and the right song just puts me in the mood to write a scene.  I'm sure everyone knows what I'm talking about. 3. Switch gears... If you're a novel writer try a short story as a constructive break from your novel.  The nuance of trying something different can produce new interest and creativity.  I thought I would hate trying to write poems for a class but when I finally got the hang of it I got such great ideas for my stories along with it.   4. Retrace your writing... this is the most unusual but intriguing suggestion yet... rewrite your last paragraphe word for word.  It's like retracing the inspiration you had yesterday!  Amazing, I will be trying this one out myself!  It's always good to know WHY you write... It's like finding your roots so to help explain your own style.  Why do I write?    I write because I always have.  Even when I was too young to know what I should write I wanted to write something down.  I use to keep one of those cute little girl diaries and there was just something wonderful about all the empty pages.  Even if each page read the same thing over and over again (because to most kids every day's the same) it was still wonderful to look back at the entries and think "This is my book."  My writing took a back seat after 3rd grade but popped up again in 8th and from there on I was always writing fanfiction.  I have one Star Wars novel and dozens of short stories.  I wonder if Mr. Lucas will ever want to see them?  :)  Now I write more because I am becoming more and more aware to the subtlities of life.  Just feel like I have to log it all down and show the world to people... show characters to people.  I want them all to read and enjoy a sliver of fiction based on truth.  Thats why I first leaned into historical fiction.  Now I am trying my first real time, right now story.  I can't wait to see how it and I evolve.  I plan to post more so stay tuned :)  I hope you have enjoyed this and will comment on why YOU write.  
    
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I've been thinking more and more on my novel idea lately.  I feel myself becoming more and more interested in it.  Frustrated me that I am still telling too much and not describing enough.  SO I took to the internet for some help.  (Writers!  There are so many articles on the internet about writing that you don't have to buy a book on tips!) I found a article by a sci fi writer who showed me that showing a fact about a character or setting can take up quite a bit of space.  He had a simple sentence stating the fact as an example of telling and then he had a small paragraph as an example of showing!  However, when it's your first draft and you are just starting he said it was common and normal to end up telling the story.  This the stage where you are learning connections and themes for your characters.  When you are first trying to familerize youself with the setting and everyone and the goal the "showing" starts coming to you.  An example would be, when I decided that I definately wanted to have a musical theme (maybe even make it the salvation of the main character) I knew I should focus on the playing of music and from where he received his knowledge.  Though I might not continue to use his Mother's piano skills in the openning scene I will include it in the first chapter.  I want to show more about Handel but I am still fleshing him out in my mind.  I haven't even decided on what type of an accident he was in!  So all you other writers out there, chill!  You can explain it all at first but then go back in and think about how you would know this if you could only WATCH the character.  Thats one of MY favorite tips.  Pretend to be watching him or her like a scientist studying an animal.  What could the character do to convey his emotion, thoughts, history?  Hope this helps! 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       1 Page  Close your eyes and recall your last job or most memorable job.  Put youself back there for a few minutes.  Recall the sights, sounds, smells, touch, occurances of people and their actions.  See how much you can pull out of that one memory of sitting or standing at this job.  Then start recalling how you would feel while working.  The idea is to create a lot from one simple memory.  See how textured of an environment you can create from this memory.  It also helps you remember that there are many elements to a simple location or scene.  The more you can create the more the location will come alive to the reader.  You can apply this exercise to any memory.  It's good for helping you remember things too. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Starting this week I will be again posting writing exercises.  I won't be posting them everyday though... maybe more like once or twice a week at most.  There will be one tomorrow.  I WILL be posting stories.  I have been meaning to do that for a while.  Just give me a day or two to add some revisions to them. (I have so much on my mind).  I'm really bad with titles though.  So if any of you get a chance to read these feel free to throw out a title you think would sound good. :)  Talk to you again soon.   
    
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yeah, yeah...I know I'm behind in my blogging.  Good News... I found a local writers' group that is open, supportive, and has great ideas. Bad News... This monday is the last meeting til september.  More Bad News... I never did post that story I submitted to the group. More Good News... They thought it was interesting and gave me lots to think about. Even More Good News... I will be making some revisions and posting HOPEFULLY this weekend.  Question... I'd really like someone maybe more than one to comment on this question. -Earlier I was posting writing exercises.  I thought it would be great to stir up my writing and my readers' writing.  Since I never got any comments back about those exercises I stopped posting them. Does anyone want them back?  Was anyone enjoying them?  Were they a waste, lame, or uninteresting?  Thanks very much for your feedback.  I really enjoying making this blog interesting and fun for any and all visitors. 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I will be meeting with a local writers' group on Monday.  They discuss short story fiction and I plan on whiping up a story for them to workshop.  The goal is to have something interesting and dramatic but under 6 pages (double spaced of course).    I have this one story which I am tweeking currently, which I have plainly titled The Larson Sisters.  (I have a habit of cataloging stories by character names)  It's about two spinter sisters who try to enjoy a nice play but an out of control toddler is bugging everyone and ends up ruining the play.  The sisters, who are ready to give him the spanking of his life, suddenly have a change of heart when no one comes for the little boy.  I plan on posting it sometime this weekend and I hope a few of you readers give it a once over before Monday evening.   
    
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       As I ponder on this character of mine I have already begun reshaping his world.  One obvious reshaping in the below start is his family life.  The father is still missing but now there is a better bond between him and his mother.  Choosing the name "Handel" I realized there should be musical reasons for it.  The beginning jumps right into the music as you find Handel's mother playing the piano.  Frankly, with writing this new beginning I have realized how much I am explaining.  I really should be showing the reader more.  For some reason I just feel I need to explain the situation right away... so they know he can't speak and have been physically crippled.  How many clues can you place before the explanation and still keep the reader interested?  I'm working on it :)  I hope I end up putting much more between the beginning and the explanation of Handel's state.  In anycase, this beginning sounds a lot better in my opinion.  ...  	 Handel listened intently to his mother’s hands as they floated over the ivory keys.  She had the grace and passion of a professional pianist.  She did all this by memory, not having read sheet music since she was eighteen.  Her voice soon rose gracefully over the notes to serenade him with a soulful German song.  She was as well tuned as the piano she played.  It was really her joy to perform like this.  She was lost to the world for the duration of each tune.  She wouldn’t tend to a boiling soup or a simple wayward strand of brown hair.  She just sat down at the keys anytime she felt life coming apart at the seams.  The music always seemed to stabilize her.   Music was one of the few subjects the two of them bonded over and Handel had always used to join her in chorus, up until the accident happened.  He looked down at his twisted fingers and tried to stretch them out in despair.  Though he could never join his mother in voice his hopes were high that more therapy would give him enough locomotion in his fingers to play with her.  The song ended and Handel’s mother released a deep breath before turning back to her son with a gentle smile.  That smile always seemed to say to Handel: “It’s all going to be OK”.  He twisted his face into a smile that looked more like a shy smirk in reply.  She then closed the cover over the keys and began straightening out things.  First, she pulled her shoulder length chestnut hair back into a better ponytail and retied her cotton blouse at the waist.  Then everything from the keys to the kitchen doorway got straightened out, put away, or folded up.  Handel watch her swift grace applied to all the cleaning and felt the usual desire for it in his own form.  Anything she did was a ballet in his eyes.  He desired it madly but he was thankful that she possessed it.  Handel found himself limping out onto the front porch to take in the afternoon. Outside he breathed in the small town summer air.  Past the porch, grass, bushes, and sidewalk was a busy little street.  Kids and cars were always passing by not without starring at him as he sat down on the small bench swing.  One such kid in a cartoon encrusted t-shirt was gawking while riding his bike.  He didn’t see the corner fast approaching.  A car was coming up that adjacent street.   Handel would have yelled but all he could do was nod his head violently.  It only engrossed the kid.  Luckily the car saw the boy and stopped to let him ride past.  Handel sighed inside himself and shuddered as he received flashes of what happened to him when he was that age. One bad blow to the head left him a mind without a voice.  Somehow the function of thought to word was disconnected in him.  He never did remember any pain but the fear was painful enough.  Seeing the car, the little kids, the soccer ball flying from his hands.  The next thing he knew he was in the hospital with his mom.  For all the anger that he felt a sense of thankfulness came with it.  Therapy had helped him out of the wheelchair he use to have and all of his senses were intact.  (add more here)     ‘What more can you think about when you can’t speak to anyone?’ Handel would think to himself in defense of his self-obsession.  He was 28 years old and everyone but his mother treated him like he was five.  One thing Handel liked better than thinking on himself was walking.  It was the best thing he had going for him even though his ambling lacked much to be desired.  Thought he hated how giggling kids on the street probably refer to him as Igor, it didn’t stop him from walking all over Glendale.  His mother had always fretted about it until the therapist said it would be great exercise.  He would go for one of these walks right after dinner.  “Handel Honey?” his mother called through the screen door.  Handel leaned over to see a glimmer of her through the metal mesh.  “It’s dinner time, come on in.” she said opening the door for him.   (Add more here)     Handel’s after dinner walk always started with the school around the block from his house.  It was a grade school complete with a wooden jungle gym.  He had once attended the school.  He limped right through the asphalt lot and the grass baseball field.  Across the street were well little well kept houses.  He noticed how owners who were out talking saddening walking into their backyards as he approached.  Handel began comparing himself to the vagrants on the city streets that no one wants to see.  Although, he never news coverage on holidays.  No one came to offer him help in the form of a blanket, a meal, or just to talk.       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       In the beginning, this idea about placing a story in a setting much like my hometown was just so I can show off a old style suburban small town and the people who live there.  I thought the town would be the real interesting part.  However, as I created a main character to view the town I started turning the main character into the real story.  I became more interested in him, his family situation, and so on.  I'm sure I'll take him out into the community and make the town a major part but I'm surprised at how I got so interested in this needed character.  The character... A cripple with a speech problem.  He has to lean on everyone even though he wishes it were different.  I really am interested in his spirit, which is ripe with anger and hope.  He will become more focused on his indenpendance as the story continues.  I may even have him try to defend someone's honor as he constantly tries to be the man his is inside that no one hears.  What do you think?  
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey Everyone,  It's that time of the summer.&nbsp; Starting July 30th I will be on a vacation to visit sights and family in Tucson, AZ.&nbsp; Besides taking my Fiance there for the first time I am also under obligation to bring home a small fortune in Turquois Jewelry.  Right before we leave though we will be hosting his sister and family as they change gears between vacation and their new home.&nbsp; So things are hectic as we clean up, put food in the fridge, do laundry and pack our own suit cases.  I probably won't be posting again until the 8th of August.  While I'm out I hope you all have a good time whether you're on vacation too or still doing the same'ol.&nbsp; Whatever you do, keep writing :)&nbsp; I certainly will be taking advantage of the long plane ride.  Talk to you all later then.&nbsp; Thanks for your patience.  
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey everyone!  I saw this one on Writer's Digest.com and I had to bring it to everyone's attention.&nbsp; It really sounds fun.  "Imagine three strangers stuck in an elevator: a born-again Baptist preacher, an atheist and a satanic high priest. Write the dialogue."  Enjoy!  
    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Just recently I realized the little success of someone reading your story and enjoying it.&nbsp;   I only have maybe 7 pages (doubled spaced) so far, but the fact that people are enjoying it and wanting more makes me feel great.&nbsp; I feel I don't have to truly publish it anymore.&nbsp; If I can just make the writing available for someone to read and enjoy thats plenty of success for me.  Emma (who is recently enjoying poetry on the blog: Infra-Red) and Glenn (who is networking writing groups on and off the net - net one being Yahoo Group: Writer Circle) are both very different.&nbsp; One is a serious writer who is well opinionated&nbsp;and movtivating&nbsp;and&nbsp;the other&nbsp;is just learning the joy stringing together words to produce raw emotion or a luscious vision.&nbsp; Both taking such a keen interest in my book is just an unimaginable high.&nbsp; It's worth it if just these two people read it and enjoy it.  Even though I am writing a lot of this story with my portable mini-laptop pda I will be keeping a mostly finished and consolidated version on my computer.&nbsp; Anyone who wants to see the story all together (so far)&nbsp;in a nice format is welcome to email me and I'll send it as an attachment.&nbsp; Of course I will be posting more if it here.  I just want to send out a big thank you to all my readers.&nbsp; Without you, I wouldn't be doing all this.  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hi Everyone,   Below I have continued with the story I have been working on for&nbsp;a Novel: A Handle on Life.   For any new-comers the beginning is a few posts back.   I hope you all enjoy.&nbsp; Please let me know what you think of it if you have the time to comment.  (Forgive the poor spacing - been having trouble with that and indenting)  Thanks.&nbsp;   ...&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Dinner was always finger food,&nbsp;it was another&nbsp;reminder&nbsp;to Handel but he&nbsp;agreed that&nbsp;food&nbsp;did taste good when you grab it was both hands.&nbsp; His plate was made up of corn on the cob, carrots, and chicken strips.&nbsp; Oddly enough utensils were always there for him but using them&nbsp;still seemed fruitless.&nbsp; However, instead of vaguely glancing at them Handel attempted to pick up his fork.&nbsp; His mother stopped to watch him try to place the smooth flower stem-like metal handle in his scrunched always-clenching fingers.&nbsp; He did his best to relax and open them and was able to thread the fork through two knuckles.&nbsp; Handel was just about to try his shaking hand at skewering the tender white chicken meat when a stiff hand rapped on the front screen door. &nbsp;The main door was have closed so neither of them could see the badly timed visitor.&nbsp;   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Mrs. Kearny was at the door.&nbsp; Her thin lips were stiff and cold like her flat gaze.&nbsp; She was a frumpy woman of Irish decent who had a habit of speaking loudly.&nbsp; Just loud enough for neighbors to hear.&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; "Kathy dear, I'm sorry to interrupt but I want to speak to you about your son." Mrs. Kearny said, she wasn't sorry.&nbsp; She was huffing slightly, which meant that she had already spent the time complaining to her husband, loudly, and then trotting over to the house.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  She never did understand the idea of "timing".   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; "Sure Agnes, let me just come out onto the porch." Kathy said as she unlatched the screen and stepped out.&nbsp; Handel abandoned the fork and came over to sit down on the chair behind the door to listen.  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; "Kathy, you really need to keep that boy of yours indoors.&nbsp; He's been scaring the poor children so they start running around the neighborhood trying to avoid him.&nbsp; He doesn't seem to know about them or care about his presence in the community,” she would have continued but she could see the unflinching gaze Kathy held as she held her temper.  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; "Agnes, he is not a boy.&nbsp; He has succeeded in walking on his own.&nbsp; Who am I to keep this man in this house as an even bigger outsider to this community." Kathy said as evenly as she could.&nbsp; Handel heard it and recalled the tiny incident.&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; The walk always started with the school around the block from his house.&nbsp; It was a grade school complete with a wooden jungle gym.&nbsp; Handel had once attended the school.&nbsp; He limped right through the asphalt lot and the grass baseball field.&nbsp; Across the street were little well kept houses.&nbsp; He noticed how owners who were out talking suddenly walk into their backyards as he approached.&nbsp; Handel began comparing himself to the vagrants on the city streets that no one wants to see.&nbsp;   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; It’s a shame I can't get news coverage on holidays.&nbsp; No blanket, or a meal, not even just a talk.&nbsp; After all, what kind of conversation can a mute boy have? &nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; It was then that Handel found himself hobbling towards some kids who instantly crossed the street when he got within range.&nbsp; Mrs. Kearny saw it and instantly spoke up as she stopped watering her roses.  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; "Boy!&nbsp; Go Home!&nbsp; You're scarring the children,” she said not expecting him to understand.&nbsp; She held a scowling face and pointed in the direction of his house.&nbsp; Handel did his best to scowl back.&nbsp; It only made her ears glow red as she steamed.  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; "If it weren't for your mother I'd turn this hose on you and hope it makes you sick!&nbsp; At least you wouldn't be scarring those little children,” she said.&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Harsh words for someone who use to baby-sit me when I was young and offer to help my mom out when I was first injured.&nbsp; I never liked those kids anyway.&nbsp; They would only ride around like idiots on their bikes calling me "Igor".&nbsp; I'm just a stupid dare for spin the bottle. &nbsp;   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; One young boy was dared to walk over and steal his scarf one February afternoon.&nbsp; All so he could enter in some "secret" club.&nbsp; Since then Handel had tried to steer clear of them.&nbsp; Mrs. Kearny need not threaten him but how could she know.&nbsp; She was just as ignorant as the kids.&nbsp; She just had a bigger mouth.&nbsp;   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; The size of pothole .&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; The pothole continued, "Isn't there a place where he can walk with ... his own kind?" Mrs. Kearny stampered.&nbsp; Handel's mother was gentle but her boiling point was approaching fast.&nbsp;&nbsp;It was&nbsp;the next-door neighbors peering over their fence or through their blinds helped her keep her emotions in check.&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; "Agnes, do you want him to be as whole and functional as possible or isolated further producing abnormal behaviors and an inability to rejoin society?&nbsp; I for one think he is an admirable display of perseverance and courage.&nbsp; We both know how little children are, I think they should understand people like Handel.&nbsp; They will only find more as they grow up." Kathy said in a clear voice that almost seemed to echo.&nbsp; Agnes shook her head like Kathy couldn't be made to understand the truth but the truth was only that Agnes wasn't getting her way.&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;"My dear, I'm happy he's made so much improvement but what do you really expect from him?&nbsp; What could he possibly do in society today mute and dum-"&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; "He is not dumb Agnes!" Kathy spouted out loud as she glared into the Agnes.&nbsp; Agnes bit her wrinkled lower lip a bit with her dentures as she dealt with Kathy's sudden anger.&nbsp; Kathy let out a quick breath and continued before Agnes could recover.&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; "Thank you but no thank you for your advice.&nbsp; Obviously you don't know anything about Handel.&nbsp; Possibly because you rather shun him.&nbsp; Now kindly allow me to return to the dinner you so rudely interrupted." she said in a clear loud voice.&nbsp; Mrs. Kearny said nothing more but just left.&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Kathy walked inside and found Handel sitting next to the door.&nbsp; A few tears broke out as she looked down at him.&nbsp; She sat down slowly on the padded arm of the easy chair and leaned over to hug him.&nbsp; She brushed his sandy brown hair out of his face.&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; "Don't let those people get to you Sweetie.&nbsp; I know it’s hard,” she whispered.&nbsp; They both sat there for a little while longer before going back to a cold dinner.&nbsp; Handel didn't try the fork again that night.      
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       (Yes I know I need to post more of my story.  If tonight is quiet, I will.)  In the meantime, something dawned on me.  For all you novel writers out there, keeping a quota of how many words you type a day is a very useful tool.  Whether it's 350 or 1000 words, it will keep you moving.  You'll feel good knowing you accomplished that little goal and looking back on a month's work will make you feel even better.  It's great disipline.  I've read that many people like to do this first thing in the morning before even getting a shower.  That their morning will not start until they complete that little quota.  It also makes a nice metaphor that way... that life can't go on without writing.  It sounds like a religion but in truth many people dedicate themselves like this to their individual careers.  My Fiance' for example, has dedicated himself to networking and network protection (computers) and it's hard to get him off his little laptop because he is studying, investigating, testing at all hours of the day and night.  I think I have a quota of 600 words.  How about you? 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I just want to thank everyone for writing comments.  What you said was very encouraging and I'm very glad you enjoyed the piece.  You know, I think thats why I write sometimes... I like to see people enjoying something I came up with :)  I think I am definately going to keep this as my beginning.  I may refine it just a little more but won't be taking anything away... only adding.  From here I'm going to move into pieces I have already written but didn't know quite where to put them.  I'm hoping for a nice upward flow in building Handel's character, his bad relationship with the sleepy suburban town, and his drive to somehow be on his own.  Characters that I plan to introduce are: Jessica - a soon to be friend and fiend in Handel's life, Michael Hans - the one who dared Handel into the act that caused his injuries, Mrs. Kearny - A backwards old woman who thinks Handel should be sent to an institution, and some flash backs to Handel's father who I am still uncertain about.  If you have any cool ideas I am always open.  I'll try to take a break today to go visit all your sites in hopes of giving my own helpful opinions and encouragements to you.    Thanks everyone!  P.s. I will be postin another writing exercise and more promps from that creative Writer's Dijest magazine I mentioned earlier. 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yes, I am actually posting my new start to my Hometown novel.  You'll notice that I stuck a more striking image as the first line.  I also show you some of my better movements into Handel's thoughts.  This is turning out to be a tough piece.  I feel myself being dragged into sci fi ideas but I don't want to start something new.  I want to continue with this idea.  I promised myself that if I am desperate to write something different I won't do more than a page a week.  I don't want this project to become one of my many "unfinished".  Please let me know what you think if you have the time :)  A Handle On Life (working title) By Jill Wakefield	   I would slam my fingers in a doorway a dozen times if that would hammer them out straight , Handel thought to himself as he stared down at them.  He then looked longingly at the piano keys.  His mouth watered as if he were starving for their sound.  Handel rested his twisted hand on the center octave and heard the vibrating clear tone of the strings.  They were clean and straight sounding, it was just perfect.  He wished he could be just as easily tuned.  "Don't worry Honey, I'm sure you and Dr. Greyson will work those hands out straight sooner or later." His mother reassured him as she walked into the room.  She was smiling sweetly as always.  She began to kick off her heels as she looked for a nice place to drop the tests she brought home for grading.  On top of the stack was a lavender colored box, which she openned and broughto Handel's nose.  "Do you like?" she asked curiously.  Inside was a lavender colored candle that smelled of lilac blossoms.  Handel always enjoyed the smell and nodded.  "Henry Bauer gave it to me.  I think he was hoping that it would help him pass his final." she explained.  Handel shook his head low but smiled as best as he could creating a shy smirk.  It fitted the situation.  "Yes, I told him so.  I just hope he did his best anyway." she said as she took off her blazer and scarf.  Just as she was settling in Handel bended down and picked up his shoes with both unable hands and placed them on the piano seat with him as he looked to his mother.  "Are you sure you want to go for a walk now?  I'll have dinner ready soon." she said to him.  Handel looked over to the window and tapped on the pane with his knuckles.  "Yes, it is a nice day out.  Please be sure to come back in time, ok?" she said as she began to put his shoes on.  Handel tapped his coiled finger tips on his watch and smiled that shy smile again.  His mother smiled back with her sweet perfect smile as she helped him to his feet.  She then openned the door and Handel slowly stepped out.    He could see the worry spread across her face as he took that first step out the door.  She still needed to get use to the fact that he was walking on his own now.  He knew that she was happy for him.  It was just motherly of her to worry for his safety.  Afterall, things were never easy for him and no one seemed to understand that.  Once he came back without his scarf, and at least twice the police had brought him home because someone called him in as a disturbance.  But as Handel turned back to look at her from the bottom of the porch steps he smiled again and nodded his head.  It was how he liked to say "I love you." before he went walking or before she went off to teach in the morning.  His mother waved back fondly and saw him walk down the block before turning to the kitchen.   What surprises me the most is how everyone forgot the boy I use to be but continue to treat me like him.  It's a strange concept.  For everyone to think you're this big dumb idiot but forget that you were once the pride of their flock who fell victim to peer pressure.    If I hadn't taken that stupid dare I probably would have been ostrosized just the same, at least until college.  Then the completely new crowd would have accepted me for my talents and bring me to a faternity... just to face another stupid dare probably.  	  I might have lost a lot but I can still take some back by getting the hell out of here.  At least then I could escape this history thats eating me alive.   Just then he was walking along the main pike and saw Jessica.  The porcelain faced blond that had haunted his childhood dreams when he still daydreamed about soccer championships.  She was older now, back from college, and probably walking with new friends but she was just as lovely and as nice.  She was just stepping out the doorway of Old Joe's Gift Shop.  She had a hallmark bag in her hand as she was turning to either side and gabbing with her friends.  Her grace of walk reminded him of his mom as she walked closer.  Jessica seemed to recongize him right away and dawned her kind smile.  It wasn't shy like his, or flirty like the one she use to give Mikey Hans, it was just kind and heart warming.  It warmed Handel's pounding heart as he stopped to let her walk by.  He watched her walk down the street and fell sleezy about it as he released his breath.   When people don't expect you to feel any emotions, should you?  She's gorgeous, why not look at her with what chances I get.  Why do I need to feel like it's wrong when so many wronged me.  Maybe's it's because at least she smiles at me.   Handel arrived home with a familer sigh.  The sigh that said,  why am I coming home to this place still?     We're going nowhere.   Still he walked up the steps and came inside just as the smell of dinner entered his nostrils.  It lifted his spirits but not by much.    
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am experiencing technical difficulties in getting my work on here... or actually OFF my jornada.  I may just have to go buy this damn device if I can't use the one I have been borrowing.  I'm still working on it and haven't forgotten. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I would just like to share a new idea I came up with for the novel I am working with.    As many of you know, I am writing this novel very close to the main character Handel who has an inabilty to speak.  As I was writing him time and time again I realized some scenes would sound better in first person but I don't want to have the whole story that way.  So I have decided to keep it 3rd person except for when Handel goes walking around the community.  When he does he is thinking to himself in first person format indicated by italics.  There will be breaks that go back the 3rd person if anything happens on his walks.  I will be showing you this idea as soon as I can get the story off my jornada... need a device to help move it. Hopefully I will get that done later today since I don't have any plans.  Stay Tuned. 
    
    
</post>


</Blog>