<Blog>

<date>07,May,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Why is this blog diary so interesting to me? I've never thought of myself as a good writer, and I don't generally wish for people to have access to my thoughts like this. Which, should obviously lead to the censoring of certain things that go on. So nothing really juicy will be recorded, right? No words on the topics of illegal activities, things I do whilst intoxicated, or boys. Really - I never thought that it would be necessary, but lately I've been running into people who gossip like they're in high school. Can't I just live my life?  I think it's fair to say that I feel really good about where my life is right now. Inside, I've been very energetic and generally stoked on what's happening with me. Except for the parking ticket I got this morning. That sucked! Since when does the city of Seattle consider five feet away from the corner "blocking the curb?" Yeah.  Ok that's it. Depending on when I get my dsl hooked back up, I'll make another entry before July..... ..
     
    
</post>

<date>23,January,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Man, what a trip. I've been cleaning my room lately - too much accumulation. There's this box I've had since middle school with random things in in. Old school pictures, notes and things I cut out of books that were little secret jokes between me and girlfriends. Anyway, I came across all these letters from an exboyfriend I dated my junior year in high school. Some of them are funny, he'd draw all these random things and weird people, he talked with jargon I didn't use and I still think it's weird. When we were dating I thought it was because he came from California, but now I think it was just a mixture of him and the fact that he did acid. Well, I found these letters and decided to read them. There are three that I want to keep just because they still make me laugh. Then there are others that make me feel so strange, because my memory is so faded and selective.   He's writing me to say that he loves me. Telling me he's in class, thinking about ditching school to come and hang out with me (even though I'm in class, too?). He's writing me to say he's sorry he had to work so much all week because he had to work or whatever. Even though my memory doesn't recall everything, I don't think I've ever been the kind of person to be all upset about someone not being around, or having a life. Then he's telling me he's sorry he pissed me off, he wants to know if I still love him and that he still loves me. I don't remember a hard breakup. I don't think he even broke my heart. What I remember is that he was doing drugs so much, I got tired of hanging out with his loser friends so we stopped hanging out. From his letters it sounds so serious. I guess that's how high school was. Everything had so much Meaning.  Is this about my memory? Have I created a false memory of my life?  OH WELL.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,January,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Surprise me and grind me Who's turning round?  I hate thinking about what I went through with him. It always reminds me about how I always have to have someone but I Hate that about me. In my dreams I fly alone, in my thoughts I am strong and don't let people persuade me. But come back down - where am I now? This moment should be cherished, I should be lavishing about and smiling at who I am becoming.   I don't want to be social. I want to float up and lose my mind, be able to let go and have my art carry itself, build and grow and become something that I would be in awe of. So many things I have built into this wall that I think is there. It's not. Begonia is sitting on my skateboard looking all stoic. She has been in this really poised attitude lately. As if there is always someone adoring her from nearby. I need to take a picture of this - my 6lb. dainty kitty, who has perfected the "who, me?" look - looking 'cute' on my skateboard. I know that griptape has to be irritating her delicate pads and fur on her paws...
     
    
</post>

<date>13,January,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Was it before - or after - that I felt beautiful? Before I had to break it down for myself because he couldn't speak on his own. I hate feeling this feeling that I have refined for myself. I don't want to be welcoming it, feeling like this is okay because I've put myself through it so many times. Fear that I might forget how to love hits me sometimes. Does that mean I'm losing it? Losing touch with reality, or what I have built for myself...  There was something there because we both could feel it. It was hard to keep away, and some part of it was addicting because we didn't tire of being around each other. The thing that I get hung up on is what is it about me that makes him feel weird? Really, most of the time I don't accuse myself of doing something wrong, but something about him got me all hung up. It's been a long time since someone had that effect on me. I should be scared. I should run to somewhere besides here and think about other things, because this one is not going to magically go somewhere wonderful. 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,January,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Today my mind is refreshed. I don't feel like doing anything, so I'm not. Part of me is wondering what's going to happen next; am I going to stop this gray feeling soon? I want to - and yet there is that numbing comfort in not venturing out. Underground. Stay in, make sure they don't see you because that way you won't have to give out any information. The dreaded information packets. There should be some kind of (anti)social party that is all about Not showing up, Not having to say what you've been up to because there is nothing to report. Not that I don't do things, I do plenty. But I do think it's the depression that keeps me home. There hasn't been enough goings-on to make me tired enough to stay home. I think lately I get tired because I never really woke up.   I can wait a million days.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,January,2002</date>
<post>

     
      What a break. I'm supposed to be looking for a job, sending out resumes and building myself up to look like I'm the best candidate for some job that I would never be looking for except that we are experiencing technical difficulties. I feel out of sync, I want that motivation to come back where I feel like painting, listening to music really loud, and not caring about the fact that I don't have a boyfriend. That isn't actually what I'm lacking; a boyfriend, I mean. It's just hard for me right now because I lack a job. I lack a feeling of normalcy, so I don't want to be sharing my self with many people. Selective about everything I do - from talking on the phone, going out, or even if I come out of my room to face my roommates.  It's not that I'm depressed, I just lack that feeling of love that I usually have inside. I feel it in there, I know I will get past this point in my life. Everyone says (and they're right) that I'm young and I have much to look forward to. Getting past this no-job, no-life, basic blah period of my life isn't the worst. At least I keep plodding forth. At least I'm not married with kids, or have some bad disease. There are so many positives, but it's hard when my negatives add up to this big weight that I don't like feeling every day. I feel angry inside, like some grrrl band is constantly playing hate songs: the kind we used to joke about in high school, when it was funny to listen to bikini kill and not take them seriously. But now there are girls screaming inside my head and I am constantly scared of lashing out on someone and killing all friendships, just because I'm mad at the world that my situation won't change.   The internet is great because It doesn't care. Everyone or no one could be listening, and maybe it will just implode into space - we'll all be left wondering what to do with ourselves.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,February,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Delerium. Love. Thhhbbtth.  Back from surfing, or what there was to be had. What a quick trip, am I really back? I love leaving. I love seeing how other people live, meeting people who live in different cultures, and just letting go of the rules that this country imposes on you. Each time I go away, I want to not go home more. No, wait. Each time I come home from a trip I want to go somewhere new. Being in the same place... Makes me want adventures. I feel tied to where I live because of comfort. Because of friends, the mountains which I love so much, the weather is great for what I like to do...  But it isn't permanent. Where do I go next? Can I stay away longer?  Or can I just eat sushi and float off into a tasty dragon roll? Mmmm. 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2002</date>
<post>

     
      This white sausage is FAST.  I just wanted to say that watching the olympics is fun and I love what the announcers say. XOXO announcers!  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,February,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Something in me is speaking but I cannot verbalize it. Why do I keep hanging out with him? It's not like I feel like things are changing. I hope to god I'm not deceiving my self but I probably am. Honesty is good. Feeling happy is good. Acknowledging that right now, I am doing what I want to be doing, is good. But I still feel unfulfilled, which is making me feel dislodged. Disgruntled. Discouraged. Disembodied? Disdisdisdis.  It was a slight surprise to have him call me when he was coming home. What really goes on in a man's head? Why is it that I care so much? Because I will never know, and there are some things that are hard to accept, such as not knowing things that I could possibly find out if I was persistent & bitchy. But I really don't want to be bitchy. Too much is going on for me to do That. Some part of me is satified running on the fact that it's nice he calls me & wants to see me. At the same time I feel like I know I'm cheating myself out of something that could be better because I'm letting him be like that to me. Not actively doing something about it, I'm just giving up. I'm putting my dreams on a shelf and focusing on the other parts of my story.  I hope Casey calls me back because I need to talk to someone tonight. My emotions have been pretty even and I feel upward about where I'm going, which is encouraging especially since I feel like I've been fed a dirty dish sometimes lately. Casey helps me at least feel normal. It's so easy to wonder why I'm so weird and then I talk to him and am reminded that everyone's life is weird and hard and fun and a challenge all at once. That's why you have to live it, make your decisions and learn to accept what happens. Loving yourself and having no regrets has to be some of the best words to live by for me. Learning is so much more valuable than dwelling on the things that have turned you upside down in your past and allowing them to grow into huge road blocks.
     
    
</post>

<date>31,March,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Happy Easter! I just wanted to mark this day as being the first that I have eaten chocolate in almost 40 days. Yes, I gave up chocolate for lent this year (who didn't know that?). My girlfriend Jackie got me to do it. I mean, she's Jewish and gave up cheese... I was at least raised Catholic so I couldn't just NOT give up something, right? It took a few weeks but the cravings slowed down and I wasn't freaking out as much to eat it today as I expected. I mean, it is the bomb and I'm sure glad I'm not allergic to it & all. Yay la chocolat.  Mmmm, chocolate. How I love you. How I am going to be incredibly sick and ill from over-indulgence of chocolate after tonight...  I gotta go get some wine for dinner. I'm still on a semi-hiatus from drinking (haven't gotten buzzed in about 2 weeks), but wine is always fine. Next time you see me, I'll be hangin' with the winos on 2nd and Pine.   The Olympia skatepark has scary roll-ins. I haven't felt so wussy about skating in a very long time. Wah.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,March,2002</date>
<post>

     
      It's official. I am not drinking anymore. There must be a direct correlation between my drinking and the lack of finding a job. For how long have I been looking for a job and I still find nothing? I really don't want to have to cave in and get a poo-job. Hire me! I'm smart, I'm funny, and I have the ability to learn anything. Puh-leeese. At the very least, can I get an email response that isn't generric?  Last night and this morning will not be on my blog. Censored. If you were around me, I'm sorry. I didn't know I could be like that. It's 6:47pm and I'm just starting to generate new brain cells. Ug. Today was meant to be snowboarding. Since I've been riding Stevens since like February, I really wanted to go back to Alpy. This year is the first in like 5 years that I didn't go to the pass almost every day. I miss it! I've probably ridden Whistler more than Alpental, that's how bad it's been. But I've gotten some really good powder days in, and my major plus this season: Girls. Maybe it's something to do with Stevens, I dunno - but this year I have ridden almost solidly with girls. Yay, us!   I gotta stop this thinking. Can't handle it. Tired of resisting chocolate. Are you happy, Jesus? 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,March,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Man, what a hangover. I don't drink (much.often?) and well, that party i don't know what happened. Okay I do. All day we worked on raising money - over $4000 - and I was running around, hanging out with the public, and doing demo boards all day. Didn't eat. Nobody did, really. Then we had to take everything apart & run down to the bar to get setup for the afterparty. It was 6pm, and I remember having a plate of pasta, some veggies and beer. BEER: $1 PBR's all night! Woo hoo! Let's all get raging drunk by eight-o-clock so we don't even know what's going on! It was so much fun, that group of girls was Fun to hang out with. I've met the nicest people through Jackie. Anywhey, ummm... where was I? No, I mean last night. I was all over the place. For awhile I was playing pool, and I got good again for a minute. Then I spilled a gallon of beer on my shirt. Ten times. And then, and then, and then!  I can't remember last night. So many people, and most of them I just met so it was a lot of talking. This morning (even right now), there is about twelve pounds of rocks in my head. Breakfast this morning, we went to the Index cafe which is famous for getting shut down every month from the health board. We went in and sat down but when they saw how many people there were, we got called a fire hazard and got moved to the corner. Thank god for breakfast. The food was way shitty - the ketchup was sour (??) and even the OJ tasted funny, but I needed it so bad.   And now I'm home. And, I need a job. The crackhead I was supposed to start working for (tomorrow!) decided that he didn't like that I didn't want to work after 6pm. Even left me a nice (sarcasm), long message on my phone saying how I have the completely wrong attitude and if I don't change how I am my whole life is going to be a disaster. Man, that guy was weird. I'm not even getting into it.  So the hunt continues.   Anyone wanna hire me?
     
    
</post>

<date>04,March,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I love to take a bath. I love bubbles by lush, they make it all movie-starrish, and I don't want to get out even though my fingers turn all raisins.   So soon, I start working (hypothetically). Today I spent hours skating. Burien, Lakewood, Gig Harbor. I really like skateboarding because it's hard. When I can finally do something (like, if I ever can do a backside turn!) it's a great feeling. The kind that makes me want to keep trying and not go in for beers. The kind that pushes me although my legs say "no more!" It's just something that I can't do every once & awhile. Ok, I can but then I stay on this plateau. Since I snowboard so much I don't think I notice the plateaus and even if I do, it's easier to get a step up because I spend longer trying things, I go up more often. Until last summer, I spent more time surfing in the summers than skating. Why does everything have a give & take? Well, at least I can - it's just a matter of if I want to get better at one thing over another.   I should be doing so many Things, instead of this blog right now. Forever am I hating the list I create of my to-dos. So much time, always things to do. Today I vote to not prioritize until I go to bed. Maybe I'll add to my website. It's still shabby...  poems, sinking like stones, all that we fall for homes, places we've grown, all of us are done for and we live in a beautiful world, yes we do 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Aww, yeah! Skateboard! After yesterday I could barely wait for it to dry up today. Even got up at 8am without help of alarm clock to head out. But Of Course, god was testing my patience. Wet pavement? Crikey, it wasn't raining when I came home at 2 in the morning! Did that stop us? Noooo. Us dumbasses drove out to Renton & Burien, back up to seaskate only to find that we had to come home by 10am. Then I waited. Checked my email, got some pancakes. It cleared up and we headed out to Redmond which seemed to have over 100 kids there. Not kidding. Bag that, back down to Redmond. Too good to be true, with 3 bikes and like 4 other kids - why did we get over it in 15 minutes? The bikes were all about the bowl and were completely oblivious to anyone else. I almost died. Cussed at a little kid which I hate to do but he prolly didn't hear me anyway.  Don't ask why we always do the mini-tour of parks. I'm starting to get really stoked on Burien. Went out tonight for like an hour.5, it was super fun especially cuz there were 2 other girls there. Yay! And a bunch of guys who were ripping up the bowl. This summer is going to be Rad.   Kinda bummed I'm going surfing tomorrow. Not because I'm surfing. That will be fun, for sure. This time it sounds like I'm actually going to hit it at the right time. Bummed because I could just skate most of tomorrow. If we get back early enough I'm taking the 5 back down to Burien.  Need a website layout. Tired of the photo-display approach. Need colors, need better/mas creative navigation and stuffs. Going to bed soon. Yawn. I'm such a pooper, don't wanna do nuthin' on a Saturday night. Want to rent Blue Velvet but too lazy to go to movie place. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2002</date>
<post>

     
      So, um where have I been again? Gone most of the month, apparently. This month has made me completely Over Whistler. I need to make at least 2 solid trips to Hood and ride pipe there before heading north again. This isn't the first year that I get "over" riding before the season is over. Once the powder's gone all I think about is pipe anyway. Can only handle speedy groomers for so long. Most all I've been wanting to do lately is skate and surf. Since surfing hasn't completely sold me yet (needs to get warmer but still having fun) I've been skating. It was cool going out to Burien yesterday. Put hopes on today but obviously god is favoring someone else because it started raining just as soon as I got done w/work today. I knew I should have gone surfing... Sunday will come. It will be good. (repeat) I also get stoked because I can go faster and higher in the snake runs now. Such a slow progression but such a Rewarding Feeling!  Anything else new? It's been almost a month. My stupid car needs a Third tranny overhaul. How dumb is that? I have 3 interviews next week so everyone get ready for drinks, I'm gonna want 'em. Need to post like 3 different categories of pics to my site. Where have I been that all these things aren't getting done? Looking for a job, trying to find strategic places to stash my car so I can report it stolen and just get a new one...  Besides skating this summer has some rad concerts coming. I better get a job so I can better support my extracurricular activities. No drugs, silly. Between mini road trips and shows I'm gonna be a busy girl.  There was a point where I wanted to mark festical and the trips up to Whistler with Jackson but now they're past and I guess I'm going to haf to rely on myself to get those pics up to tell the stories. Drank a bunch of vodka before skating yesterday and now all I want is sunny days and so-Oregon skateparks. Ship me outta here, I want better, smoother, bigger parks! You hear me? Grrrr....
     
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2002</date>
<post>

     
       Today was my go-nowhere day. It was nice, having a Monday all for ME. I stayed at Rich's last night and got to sleep in. Nice. Smelling his hair. Flannel sheets and daylight slowly creeping through windows. Whispers of butterflies and laughter... I should have gotten up when he left and headed out surfing.    It was so sunny and nice out today! Perfect for surfing. Since I got that new leash, maybe this time I won't get stranded out past the breakers. That was Lame. But it didn't kill my wanting. It's back, the get out & go; the don'twannaride the rest of the season feeling. What's with that? Snowboarding consumes me, it gets in the way of me doing so much. The past few years though, once the powder is over and it's not quite to the slushy park/pipe days full of blishful sun, I'm over it. Don't wanna trek up and ride. Want to surf though. Want to go!   So, not today. No ocean. What did I do, then? Laundry! Weee! Got out all of my artsy papers and had a rad thing I was going to glue together, but then I got a nap attack and slept for 2 hours. Next thing I know, I wake up to the sun blaring over my neighbor's roof into my room and all I can think about is running around Greenlake with the rest of the Seattle. So that's what I did. Ahh!
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2002</date>
<post>

     
      First day feeling better (yesterday) and I'm already back to beer? Ug. I can't say for sure, but I think I had 6+ beers last night. And I drove home from the E-side. I kept asking Gin if she'd want to drive, because I would never actually admit that I can't drive. She didn't want to. I made it, we got home. I passed out and woke up this morning, regaining my senses out at breakfast over some coffee. That stuff is evil.  Now I'm dealing with a really great headache, but other than that I feel pretty great. It's sunny out today! Whooee. Soon we'll get out and skate, gotta take advantage of all the kids being in school right now. You know, I really don't want to deal with moving. Too bad I don't have a nice income so I can just pay people to pack & move my shit while I'm out having fun. At least we have volunteers, that's nice. I can't write this blog right now, who am I kidding.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2002</date>
<post>

     
      note: Redhook has a brewery in Woodinville. Where is it? What else is hidden in Woodinville? I swear the only thing it's been good for is that rad Molbak's and sometimes I stop there to get food, either at a drive-thru or the top foods. Mostly because it's kinda on the way to Stevens.    WHEEEEE!
     
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Today: - take drug test on vashon. boo on paying ferry fee, but at least i'll have a job. - take car to get transmission fluid checked. doing this will help validate (?) my warranty on a third rebuild. no car should have to go through what mine has. - skate. must do this as much as possible in order to ensure sanity when starting new job in 10.5 days. any time it is dry, i will skate. i will go to nearest convenience store and buy PBR or like beer. Jerry said he found 24oz'rs of PBR - must look into this. - go to Redhook brewery for meeting. must confess my consumation of mega beer at Baker's TapRoom during festical. unless Patrick is on my side, which he might be since he's such a nice guy. hoping for kickdowns of beer and maybe munchies. at least beer.  Nothing else planned. Hoping it stays dry, maybe I'll "pack" some more, since we Are moving tomorrow. Is it tomorrow? Everything goes away? New place? Wheeeeee!! I should get cable hooked up earlier than the 2nd, and call to get a phone maybe like Tuesday. Add that to list of things to do... maybe I'll call en route to pee test.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2002</date>
<post>

     
      What am I going to do this summer? I can't imagine starting work now. It's just getting sunny out! WAh. No more running around, drinking at noon. No more wondering what I'll be doing today. No more forgetting what day it is.   Don't get me wrong - I DO want to work again. Having a reasonable income would be grand, working my brain a little bit would be nice too. It's kinda funny, when I first got laid off I thought I'd be consumed by art. I got all these canvases & loaded up on extra oil paints, I have a bunch of rad drawing pens... You know what I was really up to? I learned to skate, I took mega snowboard trips, went to Mexico (2x!), I started a liquor collection and have friends to hang out with almost anytime I'm lookin' for em.  I have had an awesome vacation from work. Must go find skate now. Interview went well, semi-freaked on starting a real job again. 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Soundandthefury Saturday:  Waking up to a phone call 20 minutes before my alarm was going to scream, pounding headache from stiff drinks at I-Spy the night before, wondering if I have any clean clothes to wear today, and I'm out of all food except frozen burritos. Not that frozen burritos aren't the Bomb, but I wish I could have showed up to the comp about 3 hours later than I did. It went ok, I saw a bunch of people in a scene that doesn't happen all the time so that was cool. Didn't get to see much of the comp, which was fine because it hurt to concentrate on things. Am I making sense? Somehow it's 8:20 at night, and I don't know where my day went. Left the hangar to skate west Kent bowl which was Dead, which was Cool because I didn't want to deal with little kids. Then went to the pool (little mexico) because even though my legs (and ankles, shoulders and knees) were stiff and sore, I had to keep skating. Those guys are doing sick moves in there and I really want to get better. I know I won't make it up to the tile but it would be sweet to be able to do a kick-turn higher up and on the wall. It's just that those trannies are So Tight, the corners are gnarr but i keep going. I hope the pool is still a go in the summer because it's chill there. Nice. Legs about to give out, still drinking beer (bad habit, must stop drinking beer while skating) - (especially when it's sunny. that's the worst!), and I can't stop until my body is giving out, it no longer obeys what my mind commands. That is when I leave and have decided that tonight I will stay home and watch a moovey. Or just go to bed.   Must be more awake tomorrow - the finals! Wheee!
     
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I just realized that what I just posted sounds whiney and I'm sorry. Beat me with a fork if it makes you feel better. Then feed me some chocolate and I'll forgive you.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Late, late, ohhh it's late. I should be going to bed soon but I wanted to mark this as: I had such a fun day! Going to new parks is always fun and even though it's a bad habit, drinking biers while skating is also fun.   Too bad it was $15 for the buffalo daughter show. Why don't places have discounts for the unemployed? Surely it's because they want to motivate us to get jobs so we can pay for ourselves and whatever, but come ON! Wahh. Yeah, so I hung out upstairs which was equally if not more entertaining. Today, three things happened repeatedly. One is, I met new people. New names to learn and things to find out. (fun). Two, I got asked if I have a car. Yes I do and why is that a main question? (vroom). Three is people would ask if I have a boyfriend and although I'd like one (why? dontask) -- I don't. That's fine, but how come I haven't been asked that in awhile? Is it the faabulous haircut Jackie Chan gave me, with her funky kung-fu stizzle? Or is it that after awhile, the unemployed seek out each other and I'll be making out with some guy who's averaging about what I am from the government every week? Answer me! It's okay... I don't need to deal with guys anyways. They suck.  Having said that, I am going to bed so I don't have to think anymore. snarf.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I promise, just this one post and THEN I'll add to my site. Or get those god damn mamapics up. Something.  Ok, so WHY did we go out drinking, again? Was it to make up for the fact that the weekend was pretty beige? Gray? Narrow pinstripes that are so close together they make your eyes hurt? Most everyone I talked to was like, "Whee! Cinco de Mayo! Oh, yeah, I drank allll weekend lonnng... still recovering, thanks for asking!" Whereas mine was like, umm can I sit around for awhile, go see a skatemovie while drinking a minimal amount of nasty vodka then roll out to Burien? Ah, lovely Burien skatepark. Nothing like a 12vr of Busch (don't ask. out of PBR) and a skatemovie to get you stoked on fast snakebowl runs. I think I was in bed by like 10pm on Sunday. yay the fifth of May, y'all!  With that intro, I don't know how to come to last night, today. It was fuzzy but quickly dissolving into a bunch of "huh?" I really actually had my mind set for Rival Schools and I was kind of OK with the other bands which I'm sure were fun and I hope Jakson wasn't bummed I wanted to go somewhere else. I felt like one of those signs where the arrows go around in circles and point off into 3 different directions but eventually the circle comes back to where you're standing. Linda's is good for chillin'. I didn't want to go home yet I lacked the energy it takes to think of what to DO. That somehow lead us to Nation. Monday nights ROCK there! I totally forgot! Too bad it didn't start earlier. Another too bad was Marcy staying past 2am to keep dancing and drinking because I Hate having beer in my belly in the morning. I should have gotten a ticket for driving this morning, swear to god. I feel like I should be able to breakdance, it's in me but there is no way in hell you're going to see me out there rubbing my head against a well polished floor. Maybe if I had my own apartment with wood floors and mirrors all over the living room... Right now I think I hafe enough going on and don't really need to add a new activity.  Man I had such great aspirations for today. Wonderful things were going to happen, I tell you! So far the coolest thing I've done is get a hashbrown at mcd's. Mmmm, tasty hashbrown I love you. If the guy I marry can make hashbrowns like that, I'll be the luckiest girl.  Sweet potatoey inside. My cat is being a nerd today and doesn't want any attention. I really wanted her to sit on me to keep from reeling off the bed this afternoon, before I was able to walk straight. But noooo. Kitty rules. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2002</date>
<post>

     
      This online journal is great, isn't it? Don't you just love how much fun I'm having? Me too! Now, if only I had a job bringing in what I used to...  Yesterday, it was so hot out I couldn't get over it! Met Caro for lunch at the ohsotasty Honey Hole, where the guy behind the counter gets a dollar tip from me for getting a lime for my beer. Mmmm, sanwich! Then we skated (Burien. what'd you think?), headed over to Rain City for about 3 minutes then to get yummy icecream at the Mix. Oooh, there's another place I love. Where else do you get to tell someone to put reeses, caramel and boysenberries in your dish? Nowhere I know! Then there were killer reject pigeons attacking us for food, so we left to get a 12vr of PBR from ye ol' Hop-In market. Longboarding down fresh pavement with a beer in your hand with the sun blaring down while you're wearing a tank top and sunglasses is so rad. Then today comes and it's overcast. Why do I wonder? It's like, I grew up here and just from hearing all the imports talk about the schitty weather - makes me get stupid and wonder, too?   Then Jackson picked me up and I had another beer, but I was tired and couldn't drink very well anymore. Now it's today and I kinda just want to drink again. Need a job, searching MS-jobs online and need to call my cousin to see if she knows any of the people who are hiring.  I gotta do some stuffs now. Bye!
     
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2002</date>
<post>

     
      CANCER (June 21-July 22): Lunar aspect emphasizes communication, dealings with people from foreign lands. Pressure is on due to added responsibility; you will be up to it. Capricorn plays key role.   1 - I don't like Capricorns. Yes, I know some and yes we get along; but for the most part I keep my distance but am friendly upon impact.  2 - What's this talk of responsibility? I really don't need any more than I already have and am not up to even that much. Can't someone else do it? At least for a little while?  3 - Hmmm. This seems vaguely suspicious. Familiar? Does it mean that a certain someone who is ignoring me, I will have to (get to) deal with them? Doubt it. Nothing that the moon can help me with now, but thanks mr.horoscope guy.  I am so sick of this weekend. Sicker of thinking about going back to werk. I'm back to feeling like shit in numerous categories so just don't even get me started. I drank this weekend but to no avail (waste of money, barely got buzzed). I bailed at skateboarding and in one swift movement I bruised my palm, elbow, hip, and hipbone. Owch. I was happy to be there with only like 4 other guys so I could cower on the ground for a few minutes before getting up and being fully pissed at my fall.  Good things: woke up early sat & sun to skate, spent like 3 hours at burien today and that was fun. Yesterday I learned how to roll in which was rad considering I've only done it at Kent before... So, yay me. And I only spent $15 all weekend which is good because I am Broke. So broke I don't even want to get into it. I'm going now, too sad to write any more about my stupid life. Maybe overnight I'll get happy and be a gem tomorrow. Byeeee.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Damit, I just burned myself putting in And taking out the pizza. Putting it in, because I was talking on the phone and thinking I was superhuman and could take a pan out of the 400degree oven with one hand and that didn't work, but now it's done and I'm so hungry and impatient that I want to Eat It Now but it won't cut because of the cheese still being too fucking hot and melty. So maybe I'll write a blog and my pizza will cool down.  So, today at the skatepark I yelled at a little kid on a bmx. I hate those fuckers. Some of them are cool, they stay out of your way and will apologize if they got in your way. They are not allowed at the park and what can we do? Nothing. Anyway, this little fuck dropped in in front of me when I was turning blind and I fell off. Could have broken something! So I told him to watch where other people were going. I don't know what this kid's problem was, but he totally started shit with me and usually I blow it off but he was within arms reach. I was so pissed, I yelled at him and then I called the cops. Fuck those kids on bikes. The cop came and of course the kids were just sitting there and the cop didn't do shit. I think it sucks that bmx's are not allowed and the cop's just like "well, have a nice day. don't hurt yourself." Like, Hell-o! I won't hurt myself if those little assholes stay out of my way. Lame.  Big wah: pizza is burnt.   I've been so good this week, I'd like an award for it. Since Tuesday I haven't gone anywhere. Let me rephrase that. I haven't gone out drinking anywhere. I have stayed at home to drink in effort to save money. This job I got, it doesn't pay enough. For a normal person, I'm sure it's enough. I am in debt and this time next year I'll have some loans paid off and will be richer. Until then, I'm to be grounded from going out, and I have to get another job. I'm not happy about this. If I find one, I'll work somewhere else. Reality is that I'm most likely going to end up at a restaurant being a cashier part-time while I keep the k2 one. Which is fine. Aaron said I might be able to do some web design for his clients but that might not happen until August and I need money nOW!  Man, I am just one big spew of wah. I'll be back later.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I don't really feel like writing, but I'm still living so what's up?  It's raining and feels good. How come I always get these surges of want to be productive and do things after 10pm? That is frustrating because simultaneously, I get tired. So it's like, I can stay up and do things that are fulfilling - or I can sleep and get none of it done. I could pay my bills, that would be great! Or, I can work on my website and wouldn't that feel good too? Yeah...  It sucks being broke. All week, I've spent only $30 at the bar. That is an Accomplishment. Can't say the last time that happened. I'm so proud of myself! Work is really sucking right now, I have Zero Things to do. Literally. Especially because I'd rather be on my home pooter, I don't want to "play" on the internet or email. Since I'm "not supposed" to have pirated software, I can't do much of anything there. I can talk on the phone but then it's really apparent that I don't have any work. I mean, my boss knows I have Nothing To Do but she hasn't given me any work! Ugh. Oh well... I should just shut my mouth and stop complaining about things that aren't that big of a deal. I mean, I'm not dying, I have a house to live in. I'm almost out of beer but that's barely an acceptable wah. I guess I'll go to bed. Fuck that shit I said about being productive. I like sleep, it's good. bye.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2002</date>
<post>

     
      My cat is the biggest stuck up spoiled bitch in the world.  She insists on hanging out in my roommates room - thus, shedding her long, thick fur all over and especially where she sleeps. Yet when my roommate tries to be friends (play, pet her, feed her) my cat turns up her nose and gives her the stinkface. My cat knows she has annoyingly long fur and will hide when she sees me coming with the brush. I'm not abusive, rough, or mean when I brush her. And when I'm done, to rub in the fact that I Am So Abusive, she hides behind the stereo and gives my friends (and me) pity-me looks. In the morning I wake up with just enough time to get ready and get to work on time. Sleep is good. Sometimes, I have a five minutes extra and so I play mouse with her. When I explain that I have to work so that she can eat premium food and shit in a box, she gives more pity-me looks. Friends come over and she acts scared, like she can only hang out with me. Somewhere along the lines of her upbringing, she got the notion that she is royalty. That she deserves constant attention and love...  What have I done to create such a selfish little bitch-cat? Is there anything I can do to curb this behavior? I'm just glad she's not related to me or I'd actually feel responsible for this type of behavior.  In other (yet slightly related) news, I'm going to Whistler this weekend and Gin's going to KY, and that can only mean one thing: The Cat Will Suffer. She will be alone for over 24 hours and hopefully will think we deserted her, so when I return she isn't such a little cunt.   Did I mention I hate ASP? Well I do.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I just faxed my ID to volt! Wheee!!  Now I just need to: pick up my prescription scan and put up mamafest pics. (note: can't scan until my driver gets fixed. i will be very upset if i have to get rid of scanner) food shop get a new license & get my old mail that is piling up at the old house. (finally found my moneycard so i changed my address today online)  Ahhhh.... Now I just have to decide what I'm doing this weekend. Beerfest? Skatefest? Free dinner at dad's on Sunday for dads-day.   My eyes are burning from staring at this gd screen for too long. Even walking around the office doesn't really help much. Leaving early today, must escape. 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I feel SO MUCH BETTER! Aside from brainless, menial werk, today I:  renewed my prescription (still haf to p/u)  did laundry (clean sheets!)  got kitty litter - ahhhh...  cleaned up 80% of the krap that was bugging me about my house  watched tv (the dvd is missing a cable. hmmm) (??)  played with my kitty, who is still a spoiled princess  emailed some folks    But still haven't found my moneycard. It was Great for me to get all this done tonight! I was so dead, the ferry was late but it was nice hanging out on the deck with the sun out. Didn't get to skate today but since I kicked ass tonight I'm gonna take my car to werk & go out tomorrow. Or at least drinking. (think small drinking, casual). I get my first paycheck -- wheeeoo!    Tomorrow my only goal is to fax in my goddamn passport. No skateing or drunking until I do! grrrr.....
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Sometimes, this makes sense to me:  CANCER (June 21-July 22) Overcome tendency to brood. Transform moods into action. Define terms, find ways of speeding production. You will be regarded as a "mystery figure." Pisces plays dramatic role.  Tendency to brood? ME??  Whatever. Whoever wrote that can fuck off. And I don't need any drama in my life! If you are pisces, I will avoid you. bye.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Right now I hate myself. Why am I such a complete slacker? To keep up with my last few posts, I STILL haven't faxed in my passport to get that $200 from Salomon. I've been drinking too much, in every way that a person can. I haven't been calling friends back, emailing, cleaning up after myself, or doing anything I usually do and now my TODO list is out of control. I even went food shopping tonight, got to the checkout stand, and didn't have my card in my wallet. So I am still foodless. Where the fuck is my money-card? It seems like the only thing I have been doing right lately is getting to work on time. That's an accomplishment, taking into account the fact that in the last 4 years, I haven't had a job with a definite start time. Pretty much crawl in when you want to, which would be about 9am but since I have to take the mo-fo ferry I am slave to the schedule. If I'm late, it's going to be at least an hour.   Somebody please shoot me. I am lower than low and I don't even want to poke fun at it anymore. Even went skating tonight and although I was there almost an hour, I just wasn't feeling it.   So I'm eating canned chili and beer for dinner. At eleven o' clock at night. This is just ridiculous. I feel like crying but that would take too much energy. I want to draw my frustrations out but would proably start crying. I'd make a drink but probably keep drinking and not wake up tomorrow. Can I just crawl in a hole and die? Don't take this the wrong way - I am happy with my life right now. Everything IS under control, just not me. Somewhere in the past month, with me getting a Job and moving, I lost track of everything. Lost my mind, forgot what to do to Live. Right now I'm spewing words from my brain in case you can't tell.  Tomorrow I will: go food shopping buy kitty litter do laundry laugh clean up that pile of krap in my living room and take a deep breath, tomorrow is a new day.  To spare the world from hearing what's inside me I'm going to close out and take this to my book. It's proabaly my low blood sugar but I feel really wah, upset, and sad right now and want to just shutup. Want to have tomorrow come. Oh, and I need to renew my prescription. My brain is out of control. Gimme some drugs.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Still haven't faxed that lady. Why am I such a slacker on Everything? Capitol letters l,a,z, and y. The number I need to fax my passport to is still packed away in that bigass box in my closet... It would probably be good to collect my damage deposit so I could have some mon-ay as well.  What's new, people? I am slowly adjusting to life at work - training was so easy and we've been super slow waiting for another promotion to come along. yay. I've been wanting to skate lately but when I get out there, I kinda feel like I'm on this dumb plateau where I need to be doing something different but aren't ready to push myself. Not lazy, just underconfident. And now I'm Sooper Excited because I get to be stuck indoors as the temperatures rise. It's sunny, the kids are still in school, and I get to be here. (wah)  Actually, I'm pretty content right now. Things are starting to slide back into place. I'm a cog again but that's OK because I've got my fun when I need it. Maybe sometime soon I'll get my creative juices back. Inside my head there are creatures, they won't shut up but they don't want to show their faces. It's like having a cave or a tunnel like in the labyrinth where the walls talk. Only sometimes scary, sometimes not. And the creatures are little devils with horns and swollen bellies and grimey little faces. They tell me to ignore this life and just crawl in my head. Then I remember to talk and be normal. I can do it. Illusions. Anyway, for awhile I've wanted to put these guys in a book or something to free them. Free myself, in a way. I haven't talked to Frank in a long time but we were going to do a book together but I wasn't focused enough to follow through. And it was probably just me, but I didn't like his writing style. It would have been like if someone didn't like my drawings.  Someone close to where I'm sitting just doused herself in perfume that is making my eyes sting. I gotta go.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I need to remember to fax in that thing to that lady down in PDX so I can get paaid, yo! Where is my mind?   Deleri-ism sinking in fast. Spaghetti-O's clogging system. Can't write complete sentences...  yaaawn.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Oh man I haf to wake up and work. In 5.5 hrs.  God, why are there people like Frank?  I really like pabst but water will do just fine.  Sometimes, it's easier to leave the thinking to other people. I hate having to make decisions when I really don't know what's going on. Should I brush my teeth now; or is it OK to wait until the morning? Should I eat someting now or will it make me feel fat & bloated when I wake up?  Like I said... someone else will know. But I don't think anyone else will know what's going on in my head. I don't tell very many people what I'm up to or who I'm meeting, what's going on in my life. Can you guess? There is some super-secret-covert operation going on, involving a certain individual. I won't say names but if that person reads my blog I'm down. Should already be down, according to how retarded I am already.  What am I saying?  I'm going to bed. Goodnight, world. Pray that my toothpaste has the powers to erase all bad stinks from my breath right now.  xoxox -- marcy, melissa MCD.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Oh my god, I'm out of my drunken stupor. Ate some dinner last night to try and generate some brain cells. Woke up this morning so fucking early but that's been how it goes lately because the sun reflects off of the buildings across from me. I've been in the best mood lately, although I feel slightly off-balance, it's just due to moving. I'm almost ready to be social again and answer my phone. It's just been nice, hanging out with some great company and having adventures. I think I had the perfect last couple of weeks before starting work. Sitting and staring at a computer all day will take some getting used to. I'm going to see if I can take 45-min. lunch breaks with Gin to skate the park because not seeing the outside world is going to bum me out. Hopefully I can transfer positions and work 4 ten's A.S.A.P.  I love my new place! It is a great location, almost perfect proximity to the bars. Great walking distance to beer, downtown, and the freeway. One of the best things is having only one roommate, and especially one that I can't complain about. No more ass-cat, no more driving me insane with arguments. Aaahhh.... Just us and the cable discrambler. And pretty sunset views.  I REally wanted to skate ALL last week. Somehow, the occurence of me sliding on my face at the pool prevented me from wanting to get out and skate. Instead, I got to spend time nannying, moving, and alcohol consuming. Hopefully I have drank enough that this week I won't miss stumbling around and bar hopping. Wait - did I just say I won't drink all week? Noooo. I just mean I'll be sober at noon. And at three-o-clock. I'll be one of those people who rolls out to drink around the time the sun sets. Right now I'm enjoying my 3rd black label (butt licker) so maybe I'll stay in tonight. Get some stuff done, be productive... look at my to-do list. (where IS that thing??)  What the hell am I talking about? I nEEd to stay home tonight! Saving money is good, rehabilitation is good, just chillin' to some cable tv is good. It's all good. Oh yeah, what's not good is we got kicked out of the dog bowl on Saturday. (friday?) Something about the king county housing authorities buying the lot and even though the cops were cool, it sounds like pretty soon we won't be able to hang there. I wonder how long it will be until the no trespassing signs are up. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Day 2: I'm doing great! Went to bed at 11 last night, which was fabulous. All day I did so much and didn't need to take five smoke breaks...  Tonight I hope to change the layout of my website. Think I'll order a pizza. Think that will help get me going? Or maybe just make me broke. Man I love living so close to food that I can walk to stores. I haven't done anything besides work and I'm NOT talking about Work on this thing. Not worth it. Imma go eatin' now.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Dear whoeverreads myblog: I have a drinking problem. This whole month, I have only been notdrunk six times. I have tried not drinking that much, pacing myself, bringing only cash/not buying - and I end up getting drunk, drunker, and before I know it I'm massively hungover and not feeling good about my Self. I am making this post to start my non-drinking binge. Going to be making an effort to post regularly and keep track of how much fun I'm having Not Drinking. Today I'm going to hang out with my cat and watch PPV TV. Go to the store and buy some decent food, for once. Enough of living off of Hot Mama's $1.50 pizza slices and Linda's fries. It's getting gross that I wake up smelling like a stinky bar and beer seeping out of my pores every morning. It's lame that I start coming around at 12noon every day, after I've had a coffee, maybe a coke, and trying to sop up the beer in my stomach with potato chips.  So, there marks the beginning. My parents have been warning me not to drink, because I went through a really low depression - and how I dealt with it was to drink. And I haven't quite come out of it yet, so I might slip back down when I'm not drinking. But I do have a great network of friends that support my not-drinking. That want to hang out and not get utterly wasted, rendered useless.  Okaye! So that's done. Now, am I supposed to work? UG on work.  I went skating last night, the first time in 3 weeks. It was fun, but I was really out of it because I haven't done anything active for so long. My whole body was shaking, I had to stretch out. But I got back into it. I hope we get to hit Newburg this week...
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I just made a blog and tried to post it and the darn thing froze. Fuck this shit. If you know me, you know what I was going to say anyway.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I am dying. NO work to do. Zero, ziltch, nada, non. I have been doing online tests and surveys, emailing, reading the world's news, sleeping under my desk and ROTTING AWAY since 9 am. My boss knows it too. Said it's OK because I'm "covering the phone". Which never rings. I even checked to make sure it didn't come unplugged. So I asked if I could leave early and got granted 30 minutes. Wheee! The best part is, since it's Friday and touristy season I get to leave 40 minutes before the ferry comes and sit and rot in my car.   Am I bitchy enough? Sometimes when I sit in my work chair too long it feels like the fat is being pulled by gravity into my butt. Sorry, I had to share that. I'm gonna go wander outta here now. I've had it with work. 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2002</date>
<post>

     
      CANCER (June 21-July 22) You will be handsomely rewarded for creative endeavors. You have added responsibility; some depend on you for their emotional and financial security.   I was going to do a post anyway, reading my horoscope just reminded me to do it. Really, the next post will Not include my horrorscope. Though I must say, I'm bummed I forgot to read it on my birthday. Those are always more insightful. This one sounds pretty promising, though. Creative endeavors? I'm all over it! See, I knew it was a good thing I decided to stay home (most of) this weekend. Maybe I'll spend it writing a book that will become famous (see previous blog) or do some oil painting that will be noticed and I'll get sponsored to quit my job and just paint (yeah, right). But what's this about people depending on me for their financial security? I thought I was the one depending on others. Maybe it's all that imported food, wine and clothes that I buy that are imported from around the world. That's the only thing I can think of. Unless they're referring to my frequenting a certain bar by my house, and how that's helping others. Who knows. The part about what sign is prominent or whatever, I omitted that cus I Don't Care.  So, catchup. Uhh... Everything I was going to say just totally slipped out. A few minutes ago, I hit a crisis. Tired of my cds at work, I ran around trying to borrow others' but to no avail. So I'm streaming kcmu and hoping I'm not tying up the network. John in the Morning is so rad! YAAYYY! You know what's funny though, is that I'm listening to an archive of his and he's talking about how it's 54 out and we're expecting rain. Reality is, it's 80 out and we're expecting a drought. California is already at a stage 2 or something which means that they're down to less than 5% of their water supply. Wheee, folks. So rolling blackouts might be expected, people are being asked to turn off major appliances in the afternoon. I hope we don't have to get into water trouble.. I think we're fine because Hood and Stevens still have mass snow right now. Yeah, the pnw is the bomb. Ha.  Currently, I'm trying to work off this lingering drunkenness. Talked to Jessica last night and ended up meeting her at Linda's at like 11:30 for some pool. I was So Close to winning! It was rad, I haven't really played more than like 5 games all year and I'm actually doing good. We had a pitcher there, and then mosey'd over to the ca-ca to meet some others, had another beer and a whiskey. Needless to say, I got home late, took a shower at like 2:15a because I really didn't want to wake up earlier than I did this morning. My guess is that around 2pm today I'm going to involuntarily pass out on my keyboard. The coffee was a good jumpstart, but now I'm feeling kinda ill (not licensed to) and not even my munch em's are helping at this point.  Well I guess I should work again. I'm so unmotivated right now. Kinda surprised I even got out of bed. Sometimes I feel like I should be rewarded for being on time every day and working a full eight hours every day, by getting a free day off. Stupid, lousy real-world rules. Sick days, vacation days, number of hours worked, blah blah blah.  YAAAAYYYYYYY!
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Ok, I'm keeping with the latest trend... CANCER (June 21-July 22) Look beyond the immediate. Big things await; fame and fortune are beckoning. Answer the call and let it be known you are alive and kicking. Aries plays dominant role.  I'm ignoring the "dominant role" of X sign, because who cares anyway? Maybe the guy who takes my ferry tickets every day is an Aries and that was the Big Dominant Role. Fuck that shit.  Fame and fortune, though? Now this sounds promising. What am I going to be famous for? And will it be fame that leads to fortune, or am I going to stumble across a hundred dollar bill (yo) and that, in itself, will give me a break from my current dispair? And I'm not answering my phone today, I don't want to talk to anyone for awhile. So whoever's wondering if I'm dead, I'm not. Just read this and believe that I am indeed alive and kicking. Maybe I should start a rock band where all I do is scream on stage about how alive I am and just start kicking things for the hell of it. One thing is certain, I do have to look beyond what is immediately happening in my life, or I would totally not be alive. I'd be kicking everything including my own ass.  Back to work. Oh, sweet work. How I dispise thee even though it gives me a paycheck, I'm still trying to reason with myself on WHY this is a Good Thing. Hmm.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I just read that blog and I wanted to note that it's almost my birthday, and about a month before my birthday, ever since I was 17 or whatever, I get super manic. And depressed. It sends me reeling in all different directions but for some reason, even as I acknowledge that this happens, every instance feels as if I've been feeling it for a Very Long Time.   Right now, I feel like I have been Pissed Off for about a month, and it gets me upset that I can't be happier inside. But you know what? I know that I Was happy this weekend because I went skating twice both days and hung out at Linda's (sure fix) and was productive. And I played with my cat. Aww, I love her.  Still, right NOW I am afraid that if someone calls me before I go to bed they are going to be frightened of me. Like, oh shit what happened to Marcy? Is she on drugs? No, not that I know of, why? Well, she's just going off about all sorts of shit and not making sense but she wants to hang out but I don't want to hang out with her because all she does is wah about her life.  I know people have said this about me because I've said it about them. That which bothers you about other people, you have it in you too.   Ew, I almost just added something like "don't judge, lest ye be judged." I'm logging out now.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2002</date>
<post>

     
      CANCER (June 21-July 22): You need a little more time; don't be cajoled into making snap decision. Perfect techniques, streamline procedures. You have yet to hear ``complete story.'' Pisces involved.   Ok, first off - who really uses "cajoled" in everyday jargon? And I DON't need more time. I'm tired of being patient, it hasn't gotten me what I want now so far. And what do I need more time for? Finding a job, yes. More time to sit and be pissed? No. Second thing, I don't have techniques and what kind of procedure are you talking about? Sorry to turn this into "Marcy's Horoscope" but really, folks. "Complete story?" I don't want to hear it. Won't believe it, so don't waste your breath.   God, I feel bitchy tonight. How 'bout you? Maybe I need a beer...  Well, I'm gonna leave that half-drank MGD in there to fuzzle a little longer while I drink my Last Pabst. Oh, sweet cold PBR, how I love thee... See? I feel better already! Back to my horoscope. I love Pisces. My sister, roommate, and 2 reallyreally good friends are Pisces. We always get along because we are Water (gurgle). But wait! What's the Pisces involved in?? With the "complete story?" Ug. Nevermind, fuck those fishes. I don't need anyone! I stand alone in my pain, glory, angst and bitchiness. But if you're heading to Linda's, invite me along because that's like my second home.   Monnndayyy, like the corner of my mind... You know what? I have completely forgotten what it feels like to be unemployed. Part of me really wants to get laid off so I can hop back on the happy wagon. Actually, it's more like the "happy, yet subtly distressed by not being a cog in society" wagon. I have a job, and it's great that I get to meet rad people and "feel" like a "normal" person again, but sheesh. Financially I suck right now! I don't have the $7 to get another 12 pack o' Pabst, and it's almost 10 so I'm too tired to walk up there. Too tired?! Hell, a month ago I was stayin' up late reeking havok all over the place with so much alcohol in my system I almost qualified as the next human-keg.   Yeah, I'm exxagerating. But I did wake up most of the time too drunk to feel like a safe, reliable driver. On the up-side I have to admit it's nice waking up and not feeling like I'm gonna hurl when I put the toothbrush in my mouth to clean my teeth. What Am I Blogging About? I can't wait to get some insurance. The first thing I'm gonna do is get me a shrink so I can maybe curb this anxiety/depression/o-c behavior that is taking over me. Damnit, I want to be normal and be able to make more productive decisions in my life than "well, should I go get more beer, or should I just sit on my bed and stare at the walls." Which, by the way, are still bare. The artist in me is scared to come out lately, I think due to my manic behaviour. Like, when I finally wake up out of this stage I'm gonna be scared.   Maybe that's where my friends have gone.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,August,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Goddamnit work is killing me right now. I fucking had to leave a conference call meeting thing today so that I could go puke. I am SO over puking. I can't wait to get the fuck out of Dodge this weekend and let my mind have a break. Why was I cursed with such a shitty hangover? I didn't drink that much, I went to bed okay...Damit.  I want candy and I can't find any and I am Big Wah who wants to go home. I think I will.... 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,August,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Right now I am floating through life. Not much aim, little fuel left to push me along. Easily swayed by emotion and tired of thinking every little thought that enters my mind.   It's too hard to wonder how I went from ten years ago to now - and how the pieces fit together but yet I still hate myself sometimes and I still feel like I have so much potential sometimes, too. I don't like hating myself. Waking up and seeing someone I'm tired of looking at, living in the same place with the same brain talking me through my every move. It could be poetry, it could be beautiful but right now it's all cobwebs that are stuck to each other. I can't clean them off, I can't chase away the hauntings of thoughts that pollute my blue skies. It would be easy to slip away and not exist somehow; but even when I think about that I think about what it would be like when I come back and what the hell would I tell people? That I moved to Europe? Surely they would ask me how it was - and I can't lie. I can't pretend I've been to a whole continent when I barely know what's outside of where I am now. My comfort zones are cramped but I can't branch out of my own window.  Sometimes I think I'll draw, or write poetry. But it's too much effort. And I can't expect someone else to reach out a hand to pull me out. This story is all about me, this time I spend is how I choose to. Looking around I have things that I want, things that I like. I have friends to call that would love to hear from me and go out for a bit. But -   Oh shit there's so much going on in my fucking head. I don't want to die, I want to fucking be over with these feelings. I want to rise up above this and do some things. Motivation, where did you go? It's easy when I'm at work, the people I work with are great and it's easy to focus on - duh - work. But I come home and want to go out so bad but I end up with nothing when that happens.  I'm rambling. Wish I could count the times that happens. I should change this to "melissa's random ramblings."  i wish that you would move to the sun cause you're like diggin' holes in thin air and we know that can't be done i wish that you would cheat with someone cause you're like diggin holes in water and we know that can't be done bravery and stupidity go hand in hand i guess that makes me the bravest man i was quick to learn but slow to understand well, what can you do my theories are borrowed from somewhere else and i never had too many to talk about but you were real quick, you were quick to point out well, that was borrowed too  Fuck people who aren't honest. With others and with themselves. It's just too fucked up that someone can be selfish enough to not see the people they are seeing as real people with feelings and have cares and the ability to love.   you need a permit if you're gonna build shit and you can't get one so nothing gets built and your house is standing on a foot and a half of silt 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,August,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I hate alcohol and I hate drinking. I like drinking, alcohol hates me. One or the other. Sometimes both. My friend, I need a new group of people to hang out with. Good morals, fun-loving, down to earth kind of people. It's not that I don't have friends, but I need to unsubscribe myself from a whole bunch of them. Tired of feeling like shit, tired of going nowhere. Need positive thinking and the like.   Very hungry, very much want dragonfish. Where's Yang? Please send ESP message to ms.Yang requesting arrival at house so we can Eat Sushi in mass quantities. Mmmmm Yum! Tired need food can't write must generate brain cells soon. lates.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,August,2002</date>
<post>

     
      What a week. Catching the 6:55 all week Sucks and I came home last night and, in the middle of a phone conversation, had to excuse myself because I was literally having a nap-attack. Passed out face down on the couch for almost three hours. But last night was great! My friend Casey's band (other than Pedro) - Seldom - played at the Paradox along with some other good bands. I was expecting to just see like, Yuuki (since he's in the band) and maybe Mike (since...he said he would be there). Usually at their shows, I'm in the corner hanging out and talking to myself. But my buddy from work came with, which could have been weird because I don't think he really listens to emo - plus the situation fast turned me into miss social-butterfly. Mark and Craig showed up which was just awesome! My head was spinning from downing some beer too fast next door, so I stumble out of the bar to find my friends from highschool there and I was just flabbergasted. Ecstatic. Stoked! The only thing I could do was revert to blabbering idiot mode and laugh until I had tears coming out of my eyes from all the stories and shit-talking going on. It was great. I forgot how good we all are at making fun of each other. It was strange because they're all into smoking pot now and I don't really do that much, but they don't drink as much as me; there's just something different about the mindstate you're in when you're stoned vs. drunk - and all the stipulations that come with both.  The show was good...I like going to Casey's shows but not all too often because to me, a lot of their songs sound the same. After the show was out, it took me like a half-hour to say my goodbyes, then J and I rolled out to Jack's to meet up with my boss and her friends. Lord help me, I had three whiskey-cokes. Did NOT need to do that, my head kinda feels like rocks. Since returning from "detox" (melissa style), I've been trying to keep my drinking under control. I think I did pretty well last night although at some point I noticed how I yap yap yap and don't shut up. I hope I don't sound too stupid when I go into auto-pilot like that. If I can get through today without throwing up from drinking too much, or at least not go out - - oh what am I talking about!! Since 11am I've wanted to get bloody mary's at Linda's and that's totally what I'm about to do when I get done with this. Bloody Marys are one of the best cures for any level hangover, at least for me.  Have finished what I need to do all weekend and am trying to find someone to go surf with tomorrow but I really doubt that's going to happen. I don't feel like heading out solo, but need to go before it gets too cold. Would be nice to make it up to La Push soon.   Time for a BM (ha, ha. Not a bowel movement you retard!) - Linda's here I come!
     
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Since last time: Mexico (most recent) Still drinking (but not as much - quantity) Uhhh....  Mexico: Got a free trip to Mexico with one catch: watch a 15-year-old party her ass of while you're down there (no parents). Yeah, it was fun. But yeah, I remembered why I don't want to have kids yet. Whew. I re-lived the days of not knowing how to drink slowly, what puking uncontrollably is like, and not knowing (some)what of what goes on in a man's head. Through the eyes of this girl. Oh lord, on our last day she did 15 shots of tequila. Someone just mentioned tequila the other day at work and I swear I gagged and had to put on my headphones to block out the thought of the billiards hall with their 5 peso shots. EW!  Still drinking: Is this really news? Up until leaving the country, I was on a rage. Woooo! Beer all the freakin' time! Well, not anymore. Since I had to play "parent" (yeah right) for a week, I had a nice detox session. Yeah, I still drank a little but I swear I didn't go very far past the initial buzz. So now I am on day 3 of being back and not concerned in the slightest that happy hour is underway without me.   I skated today. Something that sucks, at least for me, is that when I drink so much I am consumed by it. I forget to head right out of the ferry line after work and go straight to the bars. Instead of spending time feeling good, being active and having fun with friends outside, I choose to hang out at a bar (which might be outside, but still sitting down) and eat cigarettes and drown my liver all night. Wake up and repeat until dead in the face.  So I'm feeling pretty damn good. Being more alert and productive at work which is Good because the Busy Season will be upon us so soon! I'm almost scared of it. Frightened of the thought that - gasp! - I might have to snowboard on the weekends like a Normal Person! Aaaahhh! There is a chance of working four 10's but I can't start thinking that now or I'll have a mental breakdown when it doesn't happen.  Completely forgot about my 100-things list. Started it but it's sitting in a book at my work, I think I'm on like 38 or something. It will get done. It's actually fun because it forces me to think about things that I don't usually relate to ME. Things I push out of my mind, used to be proud of, or happened so long ago I've written them off as someone else's doings. So, it will be an entertaining time for all when I get it up.  I really super bad need to do laundry. You are very happy to be sitting somewhere besides right next to me right now. Adios.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I would really like to have some pictures of toy robots. Digital, for my website. Dunno why, just sounds like something fun to play with. Play with? They're not tangible if they're only on your computer! Yeah...I know.  So I just saw on a couple people's blogs a list of 100 things about them. Since I'm grounded today I think I'll start one and see how far I get. I think I need to order a pizza. MMMmmmm. Food is good. Right now I think I need to just concentrate on generating brain cells. Maaah! Yesterday was a ton 'o fun. I was too shaky (why?) to skate much, but I had fun. I can't believe that the Bainbridge ferry is cheaper than Vashon! I'm calling bullshit on that. I rolled in on pool coping, which was totally not scary. I wonder why I don't drop in? It's like I'm waiting for someone to do it for me, but that's not possible.   It's so cold in here I'm shivering. Yay for August in Seattle! I go order food to be delivered now. Hope that I can finish my 100-things list.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Today started off so weird. I woke up and stumbled out of the bed, out of the warm covers and soft pillows; into the hot shower and my dreams still floating by my eyes. It was the haziest I've ever been for so long after waking up. I didn't feel like talking because I felt like everything was dripping through seratonin running through my thoughts. Does that make sense? Nothing really made sense until about 10:20am. It wasn't like I was going to pass out and I wasn't even all that tired, more just trying to grab my thoughts out of the air and think again. Different than hangovers that are void of comprehension - more like seeing dreams and hearing my thoughts without consciously doing so.  And then today dragged on. Tonight is nice, watching the sunset and wondering where B is. Gin and I talked about doing kung-fu so that would be fun! I'm all relaxed and feeling good after eating yummy swimming rama. Mmmm, rama-riffic! 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I love the Wilco album that I absolutely had to buy with Brian, after we saw their documentary. If you haven't heard the album or seen the movie, do both. Soon. I can listen to it over and over and over and I'm listening to it right Now, ha! Just got back from a Guttermouth show...it was pretty fun. Today was Friday, I had a doctor's appointment after work and immediately after that I came home and started deep-cleaning of The Kitchen. No reason, except that it has really been getting to me that our apartment wasn't cleaned before we moved in. That would usually fully gross me out except that we know our landlord, so it made it less gross. I cleaned out the cabinets, washed all the cupboard doors, etc. In the midst of it all, in my pj's at 7pm (I was cruizin'), my boss calls me to say she has an extra ticket to the show. So I figure what the hell, and go. Didn't need to but whatever. Now I'm home, listening to music that makes me think of Brian, and wishing we could cuddle on the couch.   Instead, I get Melissa time and I feel completely at ease. Tomorrow after skating I hope to get the base of that canvas done. Jackie Chan gave me this hugemongous canvas that was abandoned at her building. Vast amounts of space to be covered, more than I have ever tackled. I'm into details, and that thing is so big I can only hope for beautiful shapes and color combinations. I'm sure it will be along the lines of what I usually do...I'm pretty comfortable with my style and for some time have been too hard on myself to stray from that.  Distance has a way of making Love understandable -  My mind is filled with silvery stars - Honey kisses clouds of love...  I have been in the best mood and don't want to stop. I wish my mind would slow from 100 frames per second to like 20. Imagination stirring like thick taffy, colors blending but slowly and changing into different textures - like something out of Willy Wonka's factory. I can taste the happiness, see the visions of the future so bright I can't help but smile and let it fill me entirely. I have met someone who meets all nine of my needs. Yes, I have a list. Over the years since I was 17, I've kept a list of what I need and what I want from someone. It has come down to these nine things, which if requested I will post but surely I don't need to. Do you know what this means for me? Heart strings being pulled, stars singing to me from the sky and the best thing is my mind feels at ease. I love it. Love love love, you - me.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      a diamond at the bottom of a puddle did you ever stare at the moon - 'til you saw double? i hear you walk away from trouble. good love, there ain't no denyin' bad love - somebody ain't trying... did you ever walk someplace, just to take time? or take the fast road & get going and then the rules break - there's no mistake these are the precious times  I know I've been told he's cheesey but I LIKE evan dando. There I said it - right out loud in my blog.   we got mountains, we got peaches  we got love that makes us mad, love that has to teach us... i looked in a fryin' pan, sang a song i looked at a dying man - he sang along.  So sue me. I like punk, I like rock. But I also like the emotions brought out from words put together that draw more images than just wanting to move your body and feel the noise. I like to want to be somewhere else, to drift off to memories and be reminded of things I pushed down. The things that I don't bring to my own attention. 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Me, again. Me losing my mind while eating spaghetti, in awe of my life right now. It was such a short time ago that I felt down about myself, in so many ways. Tired of me, tired of the same cycles coming around but not sure of how to put on the brakes. I don't usually write about such personal topics, but this guy I met is absolutely the best. The feelings I've been having for the past couple weeks...it just blows me away. To feel like trusting again, to want the closeness I was scared of opening myself up to. So comfortable, and so easy to slip into dreams of moving forward. The future is open, never certain but with a positive mindframe I know that anything is possible. Seriously, I can't remember the last time I was so excited about what's going to happen next. I've been sleeping like a rock, I've been motivated to get out more and stop treating my body, my self - like shit. It's absolutely awesome.   Do I sound sappy enough? Well, it's true and I'm not afraid to talk about it. I won't pretend like I'm not feeling on top of the world. Hah!  And more good things - I found out that I got the position at work I've been wanting. (shhh! It's a secret!!) So I'm excited to move out of poo-dung position and finally have some responsibility, something better to do than sit at my desk and think of everywhere else I'd rather be at the moment...  Cheers!
     
    
</post>

<date>04,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Hello Blog. What's new with you? It looks like you've been avoiding me because you are preoccupied with someone else - is this rumour true?   What if I talked like that to my blog? What if my blog came to life and talked back? Would we all be on acid or would it be the final free-ing of all things inanimate...The things I ponder at work. Another inquiry: when am I winning the lottery, damit! It would be so nice to not be stuck in this rut anymore. God please grant me the patience it will take to fill in this hole I've dug.  I totally can't concentrate. Think I need some center of axis, the spinning is slow but it still isn't enough for me to pass by these windows, catching glimpses of things I want to touch and feel and experience before -woosh- they're turning around again and all I can do is watch as they leave and put in a hope to see them again. When did my mind start this random warbling? As far as I can remember, things occupy my mind-space. Dreams so vivid I can bring them to life, aspirations that have either passed or are still being expected - and somehow they remain on my list of things to do, unaccomplished. Too much? My drive is there, I like to do so much. But is there a need for finishing it all? I sometimes do, and sometimes don't - hope that I'll knock some of the things off my list. But what would I leave? Time outdoors? Energy spent on drawing? Brain cells generating the random nothings that sometimes build into somethings? Ah, I can't decide. But that's the best part - I don't have to!  Please remove your seatbelt and move about the cabin. Your captain has now decided to completely fuck off today and enter the world of make-believe. Auto-pilot has been advised.
     
    
</post>

<date>31,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      You know what's my new peeve? It is fucking cold out, but it's not raining. I can't skate after werk because the fucken sun has gone down. I don't have a car so it's not convenient to go to rain schitty. If it were wet & snowy, I could snowboard. If it were summertime, I could skate. BUT ITS NOT EITHER. Fuck this shite. I have my board at work but I'm too not-caught-up to leave and go skate for lunch. When I transfer out of Ride, and I have more freedom with my schedule, I'd like to go play on the wooden ramps like twice a week, at least. That would be such a nice break from work!  It's Halloween. Can we say big fat wheee? I like bats and devils and evil little crawly creatures, but I hate costumes. I have always sucked at thinking of "what to be" so I decided awhile ago to fuk that. Much happier now. I gotta get my shit together for tomorrow so I can go eat dinner and go get beers. I don't wanna watch tv tonight or go to bed early. (ok, too early?). I don't know what I want.   Kung fu was fun tonight. I am starting to feel stronger with my stances and blocks. Kicking is still not my strength, but it's fun. It feels weird, so many of the things we do with our bodies that aren't natural, but give an inner power somehow. Aaaah I can't write anymore I need to go eat and drink and be merry. 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Ahh, total relaxation sets in. Mind is free and wandering...exploring thoughts that are usually supressed. Not the kind of supression that is because of the fear behind the thought of emancipating, but the holding back of thoughts because I don't want to give them a half-ass effort. I love travelling through my mind. The things coming up, for this winter, are getting me all bright and poppy inside. I love winter because *snowboard*, and I love exploration. Going to new mountains, or ones I don't know that well, excite me. Although I will always love Alpental and Whistler and Stevens, I tire of going there when it is a mediocre day. But if I'm somewhere new, with so much terrain and turns and trees to explore, I can have fun on a groomer day.   Ah, the whine..OF COURSE I can have fun any day! I have fun in the rain. I have fun on ice (sometimes. now, that is a whiney situation.) I get worried of my weekends filling up because I like to be free for other things that come up like, spur-of-the-moment sort of things. Like, hey it dumped and we're all taking off in the morning. Oh man I'm all jittery just thinking about how bad I want it to snow!!  And sooo tired tonight. It's 9:24 and I could just pass the F out. Think I will. It feels good to not have a pile of things on my mind. This week has been a good one, I feel like I'm on a nice smooth road with large windows that take in the scenery and I have a mind that is not clogged so communication inside myself and to the outside world is easier. Sometimes I feel all flustered with just trying to understand my self and why my brain is even in me at all, and then I have to turn around and do things like interact with others. Weird.  And I feel so happy about Brian. For what seemed to me like a long time, I was dating guys and not finding something that felt solid. I was fluttering around and not even thinking that I was coming close to what I needed. I like the feeling of security. I really think that it helps me stabilize something inside me. I wonder if that has to do with how I was brought up? Or how I was with friends growing up? Because everyone is different, some people like to be single and don't worry about dating. Some people like dating, but know they are fine on their own and don't sweat it either way. And then some people don't feel good unless they are with someone. Of Course there are many other ways people can be. Those are just my main categories I go by in distinguishing how people deal. I think that I am comfortable with being in a good, healthy, loving relationship and like my sense of standing on my own and still being myself. In the past I have thrown myself into someone, and died inside as a result. The feeling I get with him, about us - it sends my emotions reeling into all sorts of fun and bright colors and things that conjur up laughter, smiles. It's warm hugs and positive reinforcement. I love it so much, I can honestly say that it is something completely new for me. I am just So Very Happy inside that I feel ready. I am ready, and am excited for what's in my future. I don't dread learning about him, for fear of finding out he's a freak or has issues.   Now I go to bed. Warm soft blankets and lots of pillows and my kitty on my chest, murmuring loves and purrs and drooling on me out of sheer joy. Night.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Fog is crawling on hands and knees, like a toddler around the buildings outside my window. Thick as swamp mud, it creates new visions of the tall silent giants. Full of mornings; coffee smells and tired eyes, hangovers and chatterboxes trying to get used to today. Buildings in this city are sometimes beautiful art but other times ugly expressionless blocks of cement and windows, only serving their purpose to have elevators and rooms. In this mysterious fog however, they are looking at each other through slanted eyes. Not on alert, but seeing like we do. They are free to expression because they are not so much on display as usual, they are not visibile the whole way around and therefore can breathe. People can't see this. People go about in their cars, finding their parking lots and doorways to life. The buildings stand above them, for a few hours - or at least until the fog lifts - they can emminate feeling into the moist air. Whatever they choose. Older ones push confusion and mis-sights into people's eyes. Younger, more attractive buildings breathe dreams into lovers reach, the fog has no limits. They are no longer part of the scene, but helping create it.  But this Fog, it prevents sight. I cannot tell if the sun is rising, or blaring above my head. Gray is changing the colors of everything to just drab. Trees are still sleeping, the birds don't know to wake them up yet. Preventing my view past the freeway outside my apartment, I cannot see the lake and the hill or even the Space Needle. It appears I am on an island where I-5 is the border. The businesses in the big buildings aren't worried about their reports or meetings - their only concern as of 8am is making it through the fog. Don't get eaten by the drab, stay alive! In this weather it is easy to get sucked into bed; warm covers and sweet soft light lulling you back to sleep.  It's lovely creativity floating through me, with the fog in my eyes. I can see only four blocks away in every direction and I love the feeling of cold, expect the feeling of unstability outside because this town wants normalcy. The weather her is anything but. People complain when it's not sunny - or sunny but not warm. Not all of them; some revel in the changes and it gives them energy. People like me, who welcome the seasons and tire of the warmth, the too much sunny days and not enough rainstorms, lightening, and snow in the mountains. 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Tired today. Been tired for awhile. What's the reason? Sometimes I think I'm overwhelmed, but really I should be handling me ok. Maybe I just think I'm used to the work I do but really I'm still adjusting. Whatever the reason, energy levels have been kinda down.   Other than that, things are good. Having fun at work, keeping stress down as much as I can. Been hanging out with Brian all the time and having a great time. Too tired to write about it much now, but hip-happy inside. Like the things we go do, like to make plans and love waking up next to him every morning. So cozy. So lovey. It's pretty much like, whatever we have planned is fun. So I don't dread anything, I don't wish things like "aww, I kinda wanna stay home" or stuff like that. It's good.  Need to go work now...want to take a nap. Zzzz. Begonia wants to play. I love my kitty. She's so well-mannered, and I know she hates it that I work. From the second I come home to whenever I leave, she's right there. It's probably because we live up on the tenth floor, so she doesn't really have much else going on, but she still likes to hang out by my side. When we live in a house or somewhere she can go exploring or hunting outside, she's a little more picky on when we can hang out. I'm sad she can't go hunting. I want the next place I live in to have somewhere for Begonia to go outside, even if it's just a deck. I'm so picky for my little picky girl.   
     
    
</post>

<date>26,November,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I haven't written in quite some time...almost a month. I just heard this song on the radio and wanted to get it up here. I don't actually Like the Flaming Lips. Never cared for them. This song I didn't even really like, aside from the lyrics and the singer's voice.  Do you realize That you have the most beautiful face? Do you realize We're floating in space? Do you realize That happiness makes you cry? Do you realize That everyone you know someday will die? And instead of saying all of your good-byes Let them know you realize that life goes fast It's hard to make the good things last You realize the sun doesn't go down It's just an illusion caused by the world spinning round  Isn't that beautiful? Maybe you have to actually Hear it? I wrote down the lyrics and then looked them up online to make sure I got them right. Now Juno's on. Yaayyy. My cube stinks like fucken burnt popcorn because I can't seem to EVER cook popcorn in a microwave corretly. Weird, eh? I should go back to workworkwork. It's going really good now, I love that I can sit here undisturbed and just plod away. So good. Will be Radical to get outta town for four days! Oooh, I can't wait! I'll be sure to write about it when I get back...good times, for sure.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,December,2002</date>
<post>

     
      How nice it was this morning to go out on a bikeride! The fog was crawling through everywhere, everything was illuminated by glow of steam and sun.  And my honey love comes home today. How long the time was, and how slow it went but yet today here he comes! I think it would have been easier for me, if I didn't feel so sick and out of it all week. I have all these aspirations but can't get them started. Like a lawn mower who doesn't feel like starting on the first or even the second pull of the wire. I keep sitting and dreaming out my window, placing myself as a leaf on the tree across the road. Wanting to not wake up from my thick dreams, waving in the crisp cold breeze. But here I am still. I always am. I need to do things, my dreams I can live in them with no thinking. I can spend a week in my head, just pacing around or dancing alone with the butterflies that are so large and their wings are translucent purples, oranges, bright red and I can touch them. They don't have feet on the ground, but fly and drift around me. I can hear them breathing, but it sounds more like a song or birds than like we breathe.  Ah, I should go wash up. I get so sucked in to my excitement of all that is coming up and going to happen or has the possibility of happening. I am so happy it is December,  happy it is supposed to snow this week, I am so happy to be in love and be loved. I think it's the bestest thing to happen to me, my heart is smiling so big. love!
     
    
</post>

<date>31,January,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Yarrr...captain longbeard here. We're opening the hatchets, throwing the kitty out the window and leaving garbage on our neighbor's stoop. Yarrr.....!  All kitty wants is Attention! Look at me, I have work to do and my mind is sucking on code right now. MMm, that feels like soup. So the kitty will sit on my lap, occasionally putting a paw up on my keyboard. She likes to know that she is numero uno in whatever might be going on with me at the moment. For her benefit, I have moved her throne so she may lounge freely right next to me. Eyes glued on fingers of mine typing, she is in wonder of all I do. Or maybe that's just my side of that story.  This weekend I am so looking forward to! For a fleeting moment there was thought of heading north to the great land of the W-B (read: sooperpipe!). But that was just a play. Tonight, we head east to another great land, this time the one of Mission Ridge. A new adventure - my favorite! There will be friends there, some foods to eat, beers to be a-drunk....And of course the good times! What a life I live. Nothing is more satisfying than being happy and content with what you have in your life. I am going to try to complain less. I KNOW! It's been a habit since forever, probably since before I was born, I had a different opinion. Let's try to lighten the mental load and venture into the - I don't know what to call it. Venture into the place in my mind where I am in the Now? Hm. Guess I should need to think about that one. But I am going to make that effort. One shitty thing about that, is I will be the only one who can note my defeats or conquerings. As you heard, I am not saying I will cut them out completely. More like, watch how often negative things spew out. Let them stay in me, some. This is something so one-sided. Many arguments, objections, exceptions come up even as I type this.  So, let's change the subject! I have made an announcement, so let's just see where it goes, ok?  I am going to go make some yummy eggs and eat avocado on toast. Cheers, Blog!
     
    
</post>

<date>21,January,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I know it's coming - the rush of work that will consume me like I wish for; but until then, I will sit cozy and refreshen my Flash abilities and search for code I need to build new things.  And I LovE listening to Coldplay - song about Green Eyes is so beautiful, like the times in highschool when I would hear Radiohead and think all sorts of thoughts at once, thinking how pure and real and sure I was about standing on my own, about loving. Good music makes my day, it makes any day. The soundtrack to my life...  Cause I came here with a load, and it feels so much lighter, since I met you. Honey you should know, that I could never go.on.without you.  I love this year more than any time in my life, and it's still just getting started. How great is that? Great!!
     
    
</post>

<date>17,January,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I have the most supportive boyfriend, ever. For all the times that I've heard about people being happy in relationships and wondered what it would feel like to want to just Be with someone when I was younger; now I know. My heart is content, it leaps in joy and laughter when I am with my honey. It's true! I can't get enough peeks of us in pictures together and feeling warm fuzzies when he smiles at me like so. And the future is so Bright! I love to think of us taking trips - around the world and even just out to the coast. There is nowhere that I would want to travel without him. Another thing, that I always wanted to find but had never put a face on who I would do it with until now, is going shopping at places to buy paint for the walls in our house, or to buy some matching glasses for the kitchen. I want to buy a house together - do you know that although secretly I have always wished to do that, I was doubting it would happen? Not that someone wouldn't want to, but more like I wouldn't want to with them. Us finding each other, I think, is pure wonderful luck. Or something close to that...hard to describe. Very special and I feel so lucky to be at the right time and feel so right about him and us.  There are things that I get frustrated with inside myself. I don't understand why he says there aren't things about me that bother him. How?? I know that he loves me, but I don't think that that is the reason for him saying that. Now, I don't think that for things to bother him, that he wants to change me - but those things would be OK, too. Am I scary to approach? God, I just realized I don't think I've been this open about my personal relationships Ever, and especially online too. Are you reading this? Do you feel like you're snooping. Ok, fine. Don't stop reading then. See if I care! Ha.  So, what I was saying is that I don't know if I'm that intimidating to approach because I am so harsh, or if there really is nothing. Why can't there be something that he wished I do less, or changed the way I do it? I can't be perfect. I'm not. I don't give him all the love he neeeds. He likes things like snuggling, and sweet things being said. I am guilty of not giving those things enough. It makes me sad inside. Was it something about how my parents brought me up? Why do I feel de-tuned? I am going to see a counselor next week, voluntarily, and think it will be good. I want to make a list of things I want to talk about, and make some goals. Those, I think, I want to define after I start seeing her (like the first day, maybe) so that I can see what it is that is most important, or what I'd want to focus on.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,January,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I want to be able to quit my job. So I can have all the time in the world to lounge about and eat truffles, watch Invader Zim and snuggle my honey. Though my work is very satisfying, I like the interaction with people and my yearning for learning is on the Up here - I never feel like I have enough Time to show B how special he is to me. I wish that we could travel the world, endlessly, covering trails and paved roads, wandering through towering, ancient buildings...watching the world grow around us. With only the two of us, in turn, each sending love to the other's heart. My soul is in love, I cannot type this color that is flowing through me. I cannot verbalize, form words out of these thoughts.  What it boils down to is this: sometimes I wish my mind was a big screen so you could see the little electrons bumping off each other in there, where my thoughts are going after they are created and how they were birthed. Then I wouldn't have to explain myself.  None of this is making sense right now. Right now I am tired, I don't want to work. I want to go home and snuggle with my Lovey and not have to talk. I want us to communicate on a thought-level. I can't think right now. This is all yammering. Maybe I am big WAH right now? Nah, I don't know what I would be for. Except I reeeeeally want a foods. Don't know what kind. I think I will try to read this new sequel table. *FUN*!! haha.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,January,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I just had the strangest sensation run swiftly through my brain.   I'm very much looking forward to yoga tonight. It's something that I have been wanting to try, and hopefully take up, for some years. Tonight should be fun because there is a group of us going (B included!) and I feel more at ease, less self-conscious when I'm not alone. At least with new things. So, I was thinking about what it might be like, how great it's going to feel, etc. and my head is just feeling very good this week. Tempermentally, I have been on the UP. Not much bogging me down or running me in emotional circles. What I start thinking is, wow - wouldn't it be nice to be this laid back and thoughtless more often? I had visions of myself going to a counselor and keeping up with yoga and kung fu - and it hit me. I'm not looking for a Thing that will release me. This IS me. Not that I haven't realized this before, or tried to deny it. But when I get the remembrance, the solid rush of something so...Human...rushing through me, I can't just brush it away.   Nothing seems to hold my short attention span, in terms of activities. People do, long-term plans do. But part of me just keeps seeking the next level of accomplishment, the thing that will cure me of my emotions that get tangled, get into arguments with each other and cause me to Feel. My real goal is to just enjoy life - I love so much of Me and everything that I have been blessed with. It's true - I have so much good in my life, it's disgusting to hear me ever complain. But my brain! It doesn't like to feel the things that go through me, and I never seem to have reins on them. So I plod on through life, having my times. It's good.   Needless to say, I am looking forward to yoga tonight. If it's something we enjoy, it would be nice to go regularly with B. I'm going to keep going with my day - that feeling I just described, it went through me in about 30 seconds and I think it has taken me ten minutes to type it out. 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,January,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Something very strange is happening. Last night I had a dream that I was at a Mary Lou Lord concert, because she had a new album out. She sounded different, like teen pop or something. She was dressed in pink taffeta shirt with sparkly butterflies on it and black fishnet stockings. Nothing that I would actually expect to see her in, but that's what she was wearing. In real life, I actually have one of her albums. Maybe the only one she did? But John just played "speedy motorcycle" - by yo La Tengo but Mary Lou Lord sang that on her album and it was like part of my dream was being played again in my mind, hearing that. Spooky.  In other news, I'm excited it's Friday because that means adventures are abound for the weekend! What will we dream up to do - and what will actually happen? Satellite shows precipitation coming our way - sooner than we had expected, as well. Sounds good to me! But if it doesn't snow I hope to do some skatebording and lounging, having good company.   Ah, what a breath of fresh air it was to ride my bike home this morning. Wasn't aware it was 33 degrees out! So I'm awake now. Where should Holli and I go to eat? 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,January,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Harrooow! And welcome to the new year. I'm back at work, and it's sort of hard to keep my mind on task because I keep thinking of things I want to do when I move into a house. Gardening, cooking, furniture I can buy. Not like I have money to do that now, or should be looking at where to live. Places don't seem to stay on the market for too long here, for rentals at least. And I really hope to move into a house. Or something with more of a yard than I had in Ballardo.  Well, not much to talk about because there is a sueper extreme lack of snow. It's all sheet-ice up there and not too much fun as we found out on Monday. This weekend we were expecting to make it up to Mission and finally use our passes, but forget that. It hasn't snowed and even though the freezing level is going back down, there ain't no precip expected for the next 4 days, at least. I'm hoping to go up to Orcas and ride there or maybe PDX and Newburg. Something! Skating was so so fun last weekend - why do I dork and forget to go out & skate when it's dry? Durr...  Ok here comes an experiment: My work now has a cafeteria. Today will be my first time, ever, to eat at the "new" cafeteria. Report soon to follow....
     
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Sunshine in my window, makes me smiley. Begonia peering through slanted eyes, trying to find where that noise is coming from.  Chocolate melting in mouth with tastebuds eagerly moving in for more. Song on the radio, voice I never will know but speaks in the same language.  It's hard to convey an emotion or thought to someone about something you experience without saying "i, me, myself." It's like a game, to write about things I think or see or feel, but not use those words in the sentence.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,February,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Yaay! Think process is nearing the end for the day. It didn't take me as long as I thought it might, but I just learned a whole bunch about forms and submitting data to the SQL database, and generating automatic emails. Prolly sounds like a lot of nerd garble, but it was fun. Today was a good day! I snuggled my honeypie before taking a nice shower, had a relaxing morning and fun lunch eating with B and Sparky. I never had yummy salad at a restaurant like that before! But you know what I sort of noticed? This is probably just me being a snob because I am one, but I think the better foods I make for myself, the less impressed I am with dishes at restaurants. Example: fish, for me, is hard to cook. So any fish I order, is better than I could do. But if you take that tuna salad I had, though it was very good, I could easily make it exactly like they did. Maybe even better.   See? That's being a snob, right?   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,February,2003</date>
<post>

     
      The fog is thick. It is blowing past my window like I am in an airplane, up on my 10th floor. Birds flying don't know which way is up, I can't even see to the freeway myself. When I look out the window, it is haunting like a ghost to not be able to see that far. How far out/up/around does this white extend? I feel trapped in a bubble, not readily comforted by what I usually take as a mystery, the fog. Not that it helps, having my honey so far away. The tv is yapping, I am sick of CNN. Hearing about the precautions, that "security is being beefed up to 100%" doesn't help - I just want it all to stop. End, you bad thoughts of what Bush is persevering.   I want my honey home, because I miss him and because I am afraid of the east coast right now. I don't feel secure, sitting in my fog. I can't call him if I hear anything, or want to say HI YOU. He is working, he is in a different time zone, and talking over the phone doesn't really make it all better.   I don't like the missing part of this.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,February,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Ol' Dirty Bastard, cracks me up!  And now, I get to build out the rollk2 site........F R O O T Y B O O T S!! Ah, yes. Surely the highlight of my career!
     
    
</post>

<date>03,February,2003</date>
<post>

     
      b l o g t i m e ! ! Hola, blog. Here I am, once again I find myself sitting at my workdesk with all this WORK to be done. It's not that hard today. This past weekend was a five-star fiasco. Smiles from all around, laughter resonates in my ears. We started off Friday night, B & I picked up Marcy and headed east through Blewett pass to reach destination: Wenatchee. (fioncee Matty checked in an hour ahead of us, scoping out hotel prices) That night was pretty chill. Drank a little, but went to bed early in anticipation of blue skies and good snow. When we woke up, it wasn't hard to get motivated to be up & at'tem because on the other side of the curtains, was bright sunshine!   Though it did take a good hour or so to heat up the crunchy topcrunch, we were soon blessed with sunny trails around every bend. I had never been to Mission before, and this was the perfect way to sell me on it. Speedily gliding through cornsnow, I fell instantly in love with the terrain and scenery. Having this be probably the best riding day to date, the four of us rode for a good six-and-a-half hours. I wasn't exhausted at all - I had a few more hours in me, indeed. But the sun did fall behind the hills, woe is us!   On the way home, B called up Mark to get him riled up and it was pretty much a done deal, we had Mark plus Jody on the way for a Saturday night shindig! From that point on, I have vague memory - yet it is fluid like water. Thai food was the buzz of the night, we found "the Thai" restaurant to gorge our faces out with dishes like Cashew nut chicken and Gang Gree. Funny! My guess was that we couldn't possibly find suitable Thai food in Wenatchee, me being a food snob and all; but there we were whooping up a storm and keeping the good times rolling with some de-lish-us foods in front of us. From there we made a pretty large attempt at bowling, until it was realized that the bowling alley had about 9 lanes and every man, son, and brother had already booked all the lanes for the night. (really, what  were  we thinking -- arriving at 10pm, trying to claim a lane?)  Through no fault other than our own, we flocked to a restaurant six blocks away from the hotel and settled in to the karaoke lounge. Although I really can't say Jody & myself "settled". With such Rad tunes blasting, I was dancing up a storm with Jody by my side. At this point, the detailing stops. All that is important, is that the whole weekend I had a lovely flow of good feelings running through me - I didn't want it to stop!  ...I just have a harder time getting up in the morning, when it's overcast or foggy. I'm the kind of person who likes the sun!
     
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2003</date>
<post>

     
      [3/18/2003 10:36:11 AM | melissa dion] Oh Jesus. I can't believe I'm almost Done with this stupid frootybooter site. Just finished up the It'l dealer locator, which had me thinking sort of about our Stupid President. How do we convince other countries to carry our stoopid frootyboots if they hate us? Can I EVER move to Canada? Or maybe when B and I go down south, we'll just STAY in Mexico. That's my latest plan. I could hand in snowboarding in exchange for a seemingly-endless life of "el surf bum". Definitely fathomable.   The past two days, I've gotten great sleep. Still groggy when I wake up, but my new routine of waking up 15 minutes before I Need to really makes a difference on my alertness in the AM.   Fang seems depressed. Can fish do that? I think he's either:  a) tired of his little home in the flower vase  b) sick of having Avril's picture on his home   Both of which I know would irritate me. Maybe...it could be time to take the bratty girl down. Her pouty face can't be anything of help or encouragement to me, now can it?   This month is going by at a much slower pace than February was. I like that! Coming home from work and knowing that I have four hours or so of whatever I want to do ahead of me, I like that! This weekend I hope it's sunny or at least dry so we can go skating. Things have been so lovely with Brian lately. I'm getting excited anticipating his moving in. I'm afraid of feeling cramped, because I already feel like that but he's over and around so much of the time already that I don't think it will be a rough adjustment. Plus, knowing that we'll be getting our *own* place in two months is a good reassurer that I can stay normal, because the light is at the end of our tunnel or whatever you'd think I'm in. I don't feel like I'm in a tunnel!   I wore my old vans today. So of course it rained. This morning was weird, being stuck in an elevator I think is the first time I've ever had an inkling of clausterphobia. Maybe if we couldn't have gotten ahold of anyone, it would have freaked me out after awhile? The whole time I was feeling hot and thinking about how I forgot to put on deodorant this morning. Funny, that was my worry. It would have sucked if we weren't on the bottom floor, if none of our cellphones worked, etc. But they did. A little 25-minute escapade of sorts, then off to work. Glad we made it, I don't like coming in late.   So that's my thoughts of the day. I feel dried up of thoughts. Want to finish my art projects!   When's the next ferry>>?
     
    
</post>

<date>18,March,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Oh Jesus. I can't believe I'm almost Done with this stupid frootybooter site. Just finished up the It'l dealer locator, which had me thinking sort of about our Stupid President. How do we convince other countries to carry our stoopid frootyboots if they hate us? Can I EVER move to Canada? Or maybe when B and I go down south, we'll just STAY in Mexico. That's my latest plan. I could hand in snowboarding in exchange for a seemingly-endless life of "el surf bum". Definitely fathomable.   The past two days, I've gotten great sleep. Still groggy when I wake up, but my new routine of waking up 15 minutes before I Need to really makes a difference on my alertness in the AM.  Fang seems depressed. Can fish do that? I think he's either: a) tired of his little home in the flower vase b) sick of having Avril's picture on his home  Both of which I know would irritate me. Maybe...it could be time to take the bratty girl down. Her pouty face can't be anything of help or encouragement to me, now can it?   This month is going by at a much slower pace than February was. I like that! Coming home from work and knowing that I have four hours or so of  whatever  I want to do ahead of me, I like that! This weekend I hope it's sunny or at least dry so we can go skating. Things have been so lovely with Brian lately. I'm getting excited anticipating his moving in. I'm afraid of feeling cramped, because I already feel like that but he's over and around so much of the time already that I don't think it will be a rough adjustment. Plus, knowing that we'll be getting our *own* place in two months is a good reassurer that I can stay normal, because the light is at the end of our tunnel or whatever you'd think I'm in. I don't feel like I'm in a tunnel!  I wore my old vans today. So of course it rained. This morning was weird, being stuck in an elevator I think is the first time I've ever had an inkling of clausterphobia. Maybe if we couldn't have gotten ahold of anyone, it would have freaked me out after awhile? The whole time I was feeling hot and thinking about how I forgot to put on deodorant this morning. Funny, that was my worry. It would have sucked if we weren't on the bottom floor, if none of our cellphones worked, etc. But they did. A little 25-minute escapade of sorts, then off to work. Glad we made it, I don't like coming in late.   So that's my thoughts of the day. I feel dried up of thoughts. Want to finish my art projects!   When's the next ferry>>?
     
    
</post>

<date>24,April,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Oh, what fun. Liquid, 5150 and Morrow ALL want sites this year, and of course *flash* would be the best method of execution. Why does it feel like work is this big uphill climb? So yay we had a meeting on it and somehow I found myself sitting there, promising to have two comps done by e.o. May. MAY! Ohh, gag. I know they're going to be supereasy, copy sites. I wish I could find a new job that would offer me a bunch of money so I could counter my salary here with something better and realistic. Perhaps this is karma's idea of a funny to play back on me, since I was making absurd amounts of income two years ago, for doing less work. Hmm. Conspiracy.  Different anxiety, the good kind: tomorrow the lease gets signed! Oh fun, what joy! Pity I didn't get to study up on Feng Shui as have been wanting to...hopefully my intuition doesn't fumble the flow of energy too much...  -15 days to go!
     
    
</post>

<date>22,April,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Today I can't help it. I just don't feel like being at work! Piled up around me, requests flooding in, it all seems a bit unbearable. Consumption of chocolate in near future I predict. And why can't stupid Cory stop playing his music all loud? Did we all request to please hear ear-ruining, bad headache-causing music? I wasn't involved in the vote.  Ah, Mexico: 17 days away! Eeek! In the meantime I hope to pack and move all belongings over to the new apartment...if good ole' Fran would please call the agency back so our credit applications may be cleared. I hope there isn't any karma attached to those kinds of things. Late rent...landlord doesn't call the agency back for a little whiles...  Monster is swimming laps. I know I need to change his water! He's all agro and mouthy towards me. Makes me sad.   This weekend was fun, seeing Holly. So glad it was warm out! We had a good time, just hanging out and doing stuffs. I miss her, all the way out in Pullman. Kind of glad she's only got a year of skool left (hopefully just that!) but wonder where she'll go after that? It's funny but nice, that our entire family is all close and we don't have to plan big trips to see each other. 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Blah, my nose is all stuffed. I wish I could portray the amount of snot in my head through these words I am typing.  Being sick sucks. I love eating but this cold has totally taken away my appetite. Stupid cold.   Fang is tired of living in a little bowl. He thinks he wants a nice big pond to swim in. I don't know what he'd do there, but he says he'd appreciate it all the same. What's the difference between the sayings "Just the same"  & "All the same" ? anything?  On the side (le appetizer), I do enjoy spending later evening hours in Barnes & Noble with my honey, exploring books and sipping teas.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,April,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Sun outside, sunny inside. So nice and warm today! Mexico is destined for takeoff in one month, starting today! I can't believe it's here already! The days are going to blow by, getting ready for leaving.  Last night I had this dream that I was walking down the halls at Sammamish with this girl I wasn't even friends with, and I saw Craig and Casey. They were all goth! Craig had some stuff in his hair to make it all spikey and he had dyed it black, and he was wearing eyeshadow and a ripped up t-shirt, then some lace-up boots. It wasn't really Craig because he wouldn't have ever dressed like that, but it was funny to see in my dream. Casey was goth too but he just had on this trench coat, which was creepy. His hair wasn't black, which was good because I would have gotten worried.   Now I am hungry. Foods! So glad my lovey boyfriend is getting me a munchie. Mon-chee-chee! Haa.   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Well, that sucks.   I was just looking up online to try and find out what effects Turquoise has on Cancers, since it is a Saggitarian stone, and I got to find out that the President's birthday is three days before mine.   Am I doomed, Blog? 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Bubbles coming out of my ears, trying to wake up! I need a blast of cold air in my face.  Tonight I get to go see Bowling for Columbine with B & Mark...been wanting to see that for awhile. I have been so much of a recluse lately! I wonder what the moon is doing right now. For awhile I was on the same pattern as the moon - if it was waxing, I had energy. So much of it, I was manic! But if it was waning, I was slow and not full of ideas or motivation. When I am closer to being myself, I don't push my energy I let it be. Perhaps that is why that will happen?  Well, duh. Just looking at my calendar, I see that tonight is a new moon (no moon), and that explains my low energy, want to sleep, and being a hermit! Phew...that is something - following the moon. We're all made of the same elements though so it does make sense that we could pick up on something that is related to us. Also  urlLink here  I found that right before our trip to Mexico, the moon starts waxing so when we're there we'll get a full moon! Last time I was there and it was a full moon, there were parties. People love celebrating the moon! Especially me, because being a Cancer makes me even closer to the moon. I'm a water sign, I can't help it!  So there is my dialogue on the Moon. Yay, moon! On to other topics...Bri moved in here so now my place is Full to the Brim! But it's good. I was just on the phone with my momma telling her about how I feel very much Me with B, and how I haven't ever felt that way with anyone before. But she knows that, and she told me she likes seeing us together because she knows he's good for me. I haven't had any anxiety about him moving in here, but I know I've thought about things from different angles. Does that mean some will come later? Or are we really just that cool? haha, I didn't mean it like that. Really though, I feel comfortable sharing my space with him and don't feel selfish when I need my own.   Toodles, I am going to get ready for the mov-ee. Slumber party tonight!!
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Holy two-boat work schedule, Blog. Very pleased I caught the 6:55 today...  Just found out that spinach and peanuts block your body from absorbing calcium. But not chocolate = Interesting.  Looking forward to Whistler this weekend!! I hope it warms up up there, just checked and it is a rigid 30F. Not exactly what I'd like but hey that's good! Also hoping it stays dry because I would very very much like to go skatepark touring up the hwy as well. Fun weekend coming up with my honey! I love it that we can do anything together & don't get bored and don't run out of words to say. Love that we are going out of town, to forget about things for a few days.  Argh must work must Work! Bogged down in a swamp, must work. Belle & Sebastian are perfect right now.  
     
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Oh Blog. I am getting tired of fixing my posture. I almost told my p.trainer to just tape me up so I can screw all these stretches and exercises. But my doktor wants to stop acupuncture & start on massage, which would be a lovely treatment.  B's birthday is tomorrow and Brian since you read this sometimes, I can't very well write what I got you now CAN I? Hah. Gin and I took the early boat (whee) and ran all over the place before finding what we needed: undisclosed birthday present item here. She sure can come in handy for knowing what to get for people! Such a lovely, thoughtful girl. This weekend is getting all full of stuffs.   And I want a nice new wide skateboard. Very envious of B's new deck...  On the positive, work is seeming accomplishable again. The tables are giving me issues but it's coming along nicely. Stupid MS with their stoopid .NET krap, they were in our office today filming and they were like "oh, cool...so you guys are the web department - can we film you like, doing some real-life work?" Ali and I both despise this attention. Ali more than I, likely, being as she really knows a whole bunch and nobody out there even knows a small percentage of it. Then this guy has to come out and - oh I don't know. I think it was also Vickie Mercer who creeps the entire company out. She came by, then lousy Pius and his droning voice came by With the Cameramen. Just obnoxious.   Ah yes, the positives...getting excited planning someone's birthday. Never done that before. Cute gerbera daisies here by my desk...all bright & cheery. Oooh and we're planning time up at the condo in Whistler - biking yay! Summer trips are looking splendid. I can't wait to go surfing! Want to nail down SD - excited to surf in warm weather. Oooh yes. Longboard skimming across bubbly waves with sunshine on my back, sounds of crashing water and getting wet in my bathing suit. I.Can't.Wait!!
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Limited mobility passenger elevator  Servicing the piling    Such a fun yesterday, canoeing! Seeing the blue heron very up-close, when it was stuck in the reeds...the eagle chasing the seagull...getting stuck backwards in the dead-ended tunnel. Mother goose, large mother goose, guarding her nest and scaring me. Having fields of lily pads surrounding and the sun shining its rays right through the bright green leaves, casting soft glow across everywhere I look. And then having to pee in the middle of the fun.   Rotating scrabble board = trouble. 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Ug. Highly delerious due to lack of proper sleep. Bedtime: 2am. Awaketime: 5:45. Stupid early boat. What in god's name was I thinking? Stupid scrabble addiction. I wasn't even playing with good score last night.    Today:  - work. finish Ride boards...specs & features. need to create interactivity per Tara's req?  - mandatory picnic. no longer care about rumored beer.   - followed by mandatory meeting. hmph.  - acupuncture. maybe she can stick a needle somewhere that will make my body think it has gained sleep?     - sleep, cozy, lounge etc. tonight. highlight of the day!   Reheating hazlenut soy latte was worst idea in the world. Disgusting - took one sip and almost hurled self out of whale.  
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Staying up until almost midnight finishing pages just doesn't work when I have to wake up at 6:30. Lethargic drawl runs through my limbs.  DeathCab is just about all I can handle right now. Enough of stupid new White Stripes, no thanks Cory. ...stupid cory.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
       I am eight years old. Today has not been a very good day. Today has made me want to scream because right now that's what I am doing inside. I hate feeling like my whole life built up to this day has been one big mistake and it's not getting any easier to figure out where I'm going. I hate that when we were putting up those framed polaroids in the kitchen that the sun had to come bashing down and make that loud noise. And I don't hate my kitty but I didn't like that watering pitcher to hurl itself off the windowsill when I opened the window, causing Begonia to leap out of my arms with her claws ripping into my arms, then landing on the lucky bamboo pot and cracking its lovely green varnish.   GRRRR.   Brian's not good at small talk. And that's okay!   JoJos for dinner....that's okay, too. Thanks B for going and getting that because I am stuck here building out my 24 pages of snowboards. Yay.   Don't like how I've been feeling about myself this week. Want to crawl in a hole. Really don't want to go to the picnic on Friday, though beer is a good incentive. Stupid work picnic, stupid boss leaving for vacation so we have to come in on our days-off.  Oh I am full of complaints right now! Let's hear something positive, okay? ...I am looking at beautiful roses that my honey brought me. They smell lovely and remind me that even though I might not feel like it, I can be special.  gag
     
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Resisting the urge to go to scary upstairs cafeteria. Have been hearing good reviews lately from A, but still skeptical. I know there was a reason I was protesting!    Recent thoughts:  - when acupuncture/PT is finished, will maybe do yoga instead of kung foo  - whistler over memorial day/skate tour - very fun  - check into frequent flier miles/san diego surf trip  - when IS cory going to stop playing that g-damn postal service?  - want to go skating after work! it's all sunny!  - look up 2, 3-letter words for scrabble    See all the business inside my head right now? And I'm supposed to be working on these images for the dana site. Thank god the sb site's almost done...this pile isn't getting any smaller!   Excited Holly is coming home! 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Sucks it rained today. SO glad I went out yesterday w/Gin to Burien & Lakewood. It was nice, both weren't even packed and we got there a little late. That little brat that calls me fart-girl was there. He makes me want to vomit, these kids are so good, so young. I love it. Then at Lakewood it was funny, there was this dad there wearing all pads and a safety vest with "Volunteer Patrol" on the back. He was giving me tips on rolling off the spine. Gotta love it! Then we practiced our ollies next to the car and took off. Though I have no desire to hop curbs and skate street, I love that other people do because of the practice it takes to get that good.    And the little girl wearing her Good Charlotte t-shirt, with boots on.   Had a garage sale yesterday. B made $400 off his snowboard gear, etc. Yay garage sales. Boo to the fish & chips at Pacific Inn. Are they only good with beer? Today is a good day for me to get everything cleaned up, positive side of it being wet & can't skate. I can't believe the unpacking process has taken this long. But it feels good, I love everything about this place! Kinda weird that I live in the same building as Jody. I've never had a friend live in the same building before. Glad she keeps her blinds drawn because I like having mine open. I don't think I could be comfortable in my room unpacking everything if I looked up and saw her looking out her window. Ack.  Want to be huge recluse lately. Too much socialization squashes my mind from roaming. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
      One question: WHY would you go to an all-skateboarding event, if you don't even skate? Please submit all responses directly to me. I want to know!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
       MAYDAY, MAYDAY!   Too bad I'm at work today and can't leave flowers on people's doorsteps. That's ok, there aren't really flowers anywhere to pick.   So I am just about all moved in now and it feels So Good!! Very fun place we have now. And a new plan with Mexico: we're going to take a little vacation in October now - fun! It will be a bit of a burden off my back, I can focus on work and not worry about being tight for money. We'll do something superfun for B's birthday still, for sure. Want to have a party! And hopefully now, we can hang out in San Diego for a little weekend. I haven't been there since my 9th birthday. The only reason I remember that is because there was a little bookshop there I got to choose out a book. So I am not too sure what exactly we'd be doing down there, but it would be very fun to find some surf spots and just hang with my sweetie. So fun!   Good updates, we have. Work is a big hairy swamp right now, complete with alligators and wombats coming to get me. A bit of anxiety, and Ali feels the same way. Hope to hear good things about our budget today. Keeping fingers crossed.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Hey! Oh how much do I LOVE getting away like that? Friday night we moseyed up to Whistler, where scrabble playing ensued and I stepped in Stevie's beer-spit. Socks in garbage. Saturday woke up and hmmm, it's a little damp out. What! The tops of the mountains were a mystery, shrouded in thick fog. Pretty scary-looking to go up and ride so we all hopped in the white whale to head North: Mission find Indoor Skatepark. B & me had seen a flyer for an opening-day comp at this indoor skatepark that was somewhere up by Pemberton. Logic told us that if we asked the yokels in Pemberton where this park was, they could point the way. After asking three different groups of people, we emptied our bladders and headed out in unknown direction. According to the most "reliable-sounding" person, if we went "on that road to your left", and kept on it "even after it turns into a one-lane gravel road", we'd find it. We didn't know when, but estimations lead us to believe it was around 60km. So...we're on this dirt road, spirits are high, scenery is mind-blowing. It was SO gorgeous out there, even more magnificent than Whistler. We stayed on that road for quite some time. Road went up, road followed long dropoffs, road was found to have two cute bear cubs chillin' in it. Look, there's the mama! Those were precious.  This expedition, we held up pretty well. Mark was fuming (because his newly-fixed car was getting worked!), though it wasn't easy to tell. I think we all were thinking, at one point or another, that we felt absolutely daffy for thinking that we would find a skatepark out in the middle of ginormous mountains and wilderness. It was just too absurd! After a bunch of outbursts and jokes, the din died down to a few comments here and there, and our token drunk took a nap in the back. We drove about an hour-and-a-half on this dirt road. It was never ending! At a random crane, out in the middle of literally nowhere, we turned around. No skatepark. I know it's there somewhere, Braelorn (sp?) does exist, but all the locals of Pemberton seemed just a little confused as to where it actually IS.  urlLink See MAP   See that river to the left? I think that's what we were following. It was pretty massive. Felt very nostalgic of dinosaurs roaming the earth, if that makes any sense.  We Never found the now legendary indoor skatepark of Bralorne. Maybe next time, right? So we kept driving right on out of Pemberton and I tried to ride the skatepark we knew, but my legs were pretty weak from sitting in a car for five hours. Five Hours!  The rest of the weekend consisted of blissfully satisfying skatepark riding and tourage, mini scrabble tourneys and MMmmm food consumption. Oh god, how I love to eat! And those martinis and the Mongolie Grill....deammmn! I wish I had my own little mongolie grill here in my kitchen. How supercool would that be? "hmm, I'm hungry -- I think I'll go have my pick of whatever I want from my little mongolie-bar..."  I was away long enough to let my mind off on a tangent and not think about anything but where I was. I wish I had the ability to do that at any time. No more worrying about this or that randoms, just being where I am. It was very refreshing to get away from everything.  I am so grateful with what life has given me. I have so much to appreciate and enjoy!!  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      well i'll go to college and i'll learn some big words and i'll talk real loud - goddamn right i'll be heard! you'll remember that guy that said all those big words he must've learned in college = and it took a long time i came clean with myself. = i fell clean out of love with my lover - i still love her love her more when she used to be sober and i was kinder.  Oh my god, this song is making me so sad I can't stop listening to it. Just the ending though. It's all misty out and goddamnit I have to press out these stupid dana pages...too much work. Not enough time. Sooooo, SO excited to venture up to Vissler this weekend! How nice it will be, to have a four-day workweek next week. It will definitely be a feat if we pull off bikes, boards AND skating. Hope the weather feels like coooperating.  Today has been super productive and I feel fulfilled with what I've done today. Look, I'm a cog in the working world! Hah.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      YARR BLOG! First-mate Marcy here, cap'n crunch'n all...  Man I just can't work anymore. Coming in on the early boat is now a staple but Jeesh it's like - how long can I just straight w-o-r-k for? Stoptime. So last weekend was the Best. I cannot get over how much fun I have while surfing. I also cannot figure out how I used to get past bigger waves. Was I just not as worn out? The scene is becoming so big, there were at least 20 people in the water down by the fingers last week. What else is cool is the growing number of chicks doing it. Yay, us! The minority of everything besides pregnancy. And lesbianism. Aaand, what else? I know we're not the minority of everything. Now I'm remembering a lovely conversation with Eli and B and Michelle about things that women really  can  do better than men. Hmph. But yes, surfing was very rewarding, fun, exhilerating - and cute to see B out there too! I love being out in the water, out floating and out pushing myself to new places.   Work is getting under control. About a month ago, I was swimming. Very happy to have that turn around. And my teensy spit of a raise. This company is such a Joke, I swear! Can't wait to go back to skool. Need to figure out what it is I'd really rather do longterm - both of the fields of interest (if I do narrow it down to those two) are pretty specific.   Yelch, time to catch zee ferry. Wondering if I could leave car in parking lot overnight...such a waste, to have missed acupuncture today. Oh well, always tomorrow! I think I'm going to request 15 needles in my wrist alone, this time. Stuipid CT. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Why the Verve, blog? Aaah it's so sad!  Like a cat in a bag, waiting to drown - this time I'm coming down. (talk about Wah!)  This weekend was so much fun! Scrabble is a bad disease sometimes. I am very excited for summer to finally be here, skating at Burien on Saturday was So Much Fun I think I might burst. That is something I needed to do, just hang out in the sun and skateskateskate! It's fun going with the same people too, seeing them learn new tricks. Grrr, that's something I need to do. Was getting quite frustrated! I'd love to get a new skateboard for my bday. Something about bigger wheels, going faster...?  And then surfing - oh yay! I am so jittery for this weekend to come so that me & B can get out there...definitely good times. It felt good to be back in the waves, back with the water. Floating...paddling...looking around and seeing people who love the effort and fun of surfing. Love it. See, now I'm glad I have an extra board - it's very handy for having people come with who don't have their own!  Oh, and the sun came out...glistening off the waves, and then the foamy leftovers from a wave crashing past. Going surfing makes me all excited like when I was learning how to snowboard. And the Sun!  Must get back to work -- wanted to log the fun weekend before it becomes Wednesday.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Oooh, so very Excited to just THINK about getting a new computer. How lovely it would be, to send off my ole' trusty (but outdated) PC away and welcome in a fresh, swifty G4 or such. Not done reviewing yet, and would like to actually Go To a store and talk to some salespersons...Gad, ack salespeople!  Work has gotten back into a lovely pace. It is easier coming in now, and easier to want to leave early, seeing as it has been warmer and sunnier and whatnot.  This weekend my dear Grandpa is having his NINETIETH birthday party! Go, grandpa! B will get to meet my whole extended family, aside from removed cousins and such. Might be around 70 people there? Very excited for this. I get to bring a salad, which I hope to WOW everybody with. I am in love with salads.  Everything has been super on the homefront. Hunny brought home three large, beautiful boquets last night and they really lit up the house! Nothing looks better on the kitchen's sill than a big bunch of yellow lilies, orange daisies and little white whoosey-whatsits. Thanks, B!  And we've been surfing more. I put on my goals for work to go surfing ten times this summer. So far, I've got three and plus one more this weekend. I think I just might make it! There is nothing like leaving everything in my mind on shore, and playing in the water. I absolutely love it. Makes me excited inside, thinking about everywheres to go vacationing and have the opportunity to surf.  Check out my website soon: Day of being made-up at Burnt Sugar (in Fremont) and My New Shoes!! Wheeeee!
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
        You know what bothers me? People that don't return emails or phone calls for almost two weeks, then stop by unannounced and want to "catch up".  I said I was busy working right now, I have no idea what you've been up to lately and now is Not convenient for me to chat - especially because it will mean I can't work, I will have to deviate my thoughts from work...et cetera.  I am fine with people getting busy with other things. I think what I am hurt by here is that I have been a good friend, a good listener, offering advice freely and sincerly -- and then sporatically you pop by to chat -- and you're leaving for another state tonight so I won't be seeing you for another week at least!    Now, is this a dumb rant? I don't know, probably I shouldn't put so much weight on it. Part of me knew feelings like this were coming so maybe I was waiting to release them? Questions that don't need answers, feelings that can simmer and leave.  I think what best describes my feelings is this: I feel like I was a friend as a space-filler for a little bit. Once A. moved in, I don't see you anymore. You're not lonely, not living alone anymore. Maybe you're working more and that's understandable for sure...but can you at least return phone calls and talk to me in some other way besides email and text messaging? Something more personal than popping by real quick when we haven't talked in a couple weeks?  Also this: Cancers are sensitive. To Everything. And we are quick to put up walls against things that hurt us.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      "Everybody is a star I can feel it when you shine on me I love you for who you are Not the one you feel you need to be"   We're going to write Belle & Sebastian to see if they will play at our wedding.  Trying to think of something cunning and a wee bit persuasive...
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Good day to you. Well, my Birthday had a very pleasant elongation. (was elongated?) Friday after work - which I could Not get out of Early as I wished - we hopped in the packed car and made it down to nearly Manzanita, OR. Wanted to camp in Short Sands but of course, those were full. Doh! So we camped in/near Cannon Beach...in a lovely field, in a trailer park. But no worries, we got in late and took off before we paid!  Surfing on Saturday was Whoo-eee Fun! The waves were coming in nice sets, pretty even and then a break every now and then to give me a chance to paddle back out. B and me stayed sort of close to each other, and it was fun to watch him learn. I love that we surf together! He's picking it up well, too.   The Oregon coast is just so pretty. Not like the Canadian Rockies or a nice vase of pink roses either. It's pretty in the sense that you get more of a feeling of vastness when you look out over the cliffs above the ocean. A feeling that you aren't as big and significant. Humbling. Our weather though, it decided to get wet and slightly drizzly on Saturday afternoon. After surfing we hung out and did crosswords on the beach for awhile, and it was nice and warm. Then I swear, as soon as we got in the car, it started raining a bit.  But that was OK! For on Sunday, after camping in the horse area (!) of Nehalem Bay park...no, really. It wasn't stinky or gross. It was WAY more secluded and private than the other sardine-packed sites at this place. Nehalem bay has some 50 campsites, and 80% had kids. It was unruly. So, anyway we camped in the horse area...walked down to the windiest beach in the west and roasted marshmallows. Mellow but uplifting night. After this, we checked out the surf and opted to go East towards Portland and:  NEWBERG!!!  Oh Newberg, you have such a fun little snake run and capsule. And you weren't crowded on Sunday. Too bad I ate a crappy breakfast at some roadside trout-feeding pond restaurant. It completely bogged me down and I was too lethargic to be of any good at the skatepark. B had fun though; it was a good bit hotter out too, with the sun shining.  What fun summer is! Then last night, against warnings of flat surf, us dumbasses drove out to the coast in hope of more fun waves. Alas! What is this? After a super sleep session at the campground in Westport, we groggily awake at 5am to fog and f-l-a-t water. Waves were barely even able to lap at the shore. In disbelief, we checked all spots and called it a morning. I slept as B drove us back into Seattle - made it back by 8:00 - good for us.  That's my adventures for now...more (pictures included) will be published on my website.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Ah yes, summertime is in Full Effect. Sweet, sweet summer...waking to crisp but comfortable air, keeping the windows open all day...Ta-da!  Tonight I leave on the 2:45 (fingers crossed) to trek on down to Short Sands, i.e. Manzanita, for surfing aplenty and to pay a little visit to Newburg. Yayy Newburg! For my birthday, B said we could do anything I wanted. At first I wanted to camp out in E. Washington, but now I'm like - wait. Is that Really what I want to do? It's all dry there...and not really full of skateparks. I think what he would really like to do would be to spend a weekend doing nothing at a nice hotel, somewhere nice - but now we're both so excited to surf and hang out in Oregon. So very glad that B likes surfing. It's much better when your best friend likes doing the same things you do!  My birthday was two days ago and I am still happy inside from it. Never knew they could be so much fun! Went to Beppo's (must post pictures from my *NEW* digital camera on website)(Thank-you, Brian!) and it was a really great crowd of people. Couldn't ask for anything more...then we went to Linda's for some babble and vodka-crans. And to see my sister have some drinks, for once! Good job, sista. Very much looking forward to mini-roadtrip with her next month. I do wish she wasn't going to skool so far away because I miss her, but the times we have together are getting richer. We're growing closer and I love it.  I don't really have time to type much. Man, I haven't documented anything! Work has been 100% full-speed ahead lately. That is a good thing - I am loving it and we are very busy. Thought things would slow down after the k2snow & ride sites went up but golly, no! This week I've been running at 75-80% because we didn't have any break for almost three months. Once I hand in this 5150 shit hopefully ski can come in. Uck, can't write about work in Blog. Sorry.  And I didn't write about Calgary. Those are more pics that will go up on the site. THAT was a vacation. Man...Tues-Sun. That's almost a week away. It was such a break, mentally to get out like that. I was living every minute where I was, to the fullest. Learning to FINally drop in was an accomplishment for me. Never knew how hard I can be on myself. It was easier, having the world's most patient boyfriend there helping me. I can't say for sure that I'd like to go back to Calgary per se, but definitely back into the Banff regions. Those mountains are the most majestic, awesome sight. So powerful.   My mind is high on everything right now. I am having the Best Summer!
     
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Well, well, well. So I finally decide to post again! Good for me. Hi-5, melissa!  Since it has been nearly a month (tsk, tsk!) since my last update, here's the skinny of the phat: This weekend we (hunny, mark & I) are heading out to Plain to visit Eli & Michelle. A birthdays celebration of sorts. I have only met the duo once back in January, but it was good times, down to earth. Excited to get out and slowww dowwwn. We have been on the GoGoGo for the last I don't know how many months.  Let's see: - went to Chelan and met Mark's parents. Great Folks! They have a beautifully awesome little house with plenty of places to camp out. We played scrabble, went out on the boat (lovely cruise) and up to some rocks B & Mark knew of. This is the same place that they historically peed on each other...I hate jumping off of things, and this was I think over 20'. Super deep-blue water, the kind that makes you think the Loch-Ness is lurking under there, but I knew it was safe. We drank some beers, watched some stupid gawkers, Brian did a naked backflip off the rock for them. HA! And then, Then I jumped in. Did it three times, so I hope the next time I go back there I'll have the guts to do it then, too. That was fun, getting over a little hung-up fear like that. So, that's Chelan. Wonderfully relaxation, pleasant memories. Love to go back.  - went hiking from Ozette to Rialta Beach. This was with my sista and my hunny. We camped out in LaPush one night, then left a car there and one in Ozette. It was about a 20-mile hike and we slept two night over it. First night was all sandy, easy walking and camped right there on the beach. I Loved seeing the sea otters enjoying their catch, and the alone-ness over there at Yellow Banks. We're gonna go back there, it was an easy hike in but damn - nobody there! Perfect. The rest of the hike (14 miles?) was a Lot of rock hiking/clambering. I really didn't believe the book when it said we were in for a moderate/strenuous hike. Nuh-uh. But there we were, oh yes, hiking the most technical, most concentrating shit right out on our coast. We had to keep with the tides, many places got drowned in high-tides and luckily we crossed at Just the right times. It was slippery, balancing, serious business. But the campsites, the fires and everything just US was so very worth it. I loved that, and am so glad B and I can do so much together! Cheers to us, honey - we've got many adventures to come.  - ooh and the weekend after that was Marci & Matty's wedding. Beautiful. I don't think I can write too much about this because pictures do more glory than my words. Everyone that came was fun to be around, to meet and par-tay with. (though I really Did Not need those shots across the street!) I had a fun time, dressing up for reals for my first time I can remember. We went to the zoo and out to pizza - it was a grand adventure weekend. Packed with fun. The kind where I come home feeling like I could still do more, if it weren't so close to my bedtime! (and yes, I have YET to post pictures from anything...bad, bad melissa!)  Coming up are still MORE adventures, can you believe it? Me neither. (properly: Neither can I?) Those I can't divulge in yet, seeing as we're not to those days. In-between these days, I have been working. Work is going good though I really want to take some classes. I'm feeling stagnant and everyone is driving me crazy. Do this, change that, add this measly bit of info. I want CREATIVITY here, people! Blarf.  Everything is going so grand, so much love in my heart for everything right now...it just keeps growing and I Love all of it!
     
    
</post>

<date>12,September,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Made a nice little list of things that are better to do tonight than go out. Some light cleaning, some projects, some cards to write. In comes the rain, and with it arrives a lust for hermit-ism. Tonight I organised my file drawer and am baking cookies! They didn't turn out how I wanted (though I'm currently baking the 3rd set, so we'll see) but they still remain pretty tasty: reese's pieces with oatmeal. Had a hard time finding a recipe, seeing as reese's doesn't just  give  you one like hershey's does.   Well. Glad this week is over, I am head-over-heels in love with the atHome for the weekend idea. The past few months have been a flurry of fun, trips, things to-do galore! But I am ready for a pleasant chill-out session. 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,September,2003</date>
<post>

     
      About a week ago I was reading in Discover Magazine, about human evolution and what we learn from studying and examining fossils of our ancestors. At some point in the article, there was discussion of what our  next  relatives will look like, how they will advance from us. From now.  Today, I am sitting at my computer. I have a keyboard tray. I have an ergonomic chair and keyboard. I have blocks under my desk legs, to help elevate it to the proper height so that my body isn't crunched or being forced into uncomfortable positions.  My proposal is that in another million years, what our relatives will be seeing are bone structures that are hunched from sitting at computers, cracked wrists and longer arms from reaching for the mouse. The internet super highway has its impacts!  Disgusting, I know. 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,September,2003</date>
<post>

     
      they're all surrounding, we're both hoping - they're slowly attempting one thing to stand up  with dignity - to walk away  This song haunts me in the morning, with its quiet whispers and jen's voice in the background. I can't believe they're breaking up and we'll never get to see them after nov.2!  Such a great weekend, such a beautiful time we had...  Thursday  was Coastal Kitchen and Man! those guys can cook up some wicked dishes. I ordered up some ginger chicken that had just that right amount of jerk sauce on it, and the veggies were Mmm. B got this BEEF dish but he loved it. For dessert - ohmygod - fresh, sliced fruit with a rum/cinnamon/nutmeg glaze with coconut ice cream! My tastebuds were in ecstasy and I could not stop taking bites. More than savory, this dish was filled with wonderful tastes every bite. YUM. After such a pleasant dinner-time, we weren't ready to go home yet. So we skipped down to the Hop Vine pub, which neither of us (strangely) had been to before. It was a smoke-friendly bar but lucky for us, it was smoke-free (or, relatively) that night. Comfortable air was drifting in from the doorway, and we enjoyed some imported beers they had on tap. I loved that night, it will always stick in my memory. We always have beautiful and easy conversation, Brian and I. I love him so much!  Now for the quick recap:  Friday  I worked from  home so we could go down to Bumbershoot w/Sara & Brendan to get MM tickets for everyone. After work, Nick & Christy showed up, we met up with Mark and Stevie and vroooom! headed down to the show. It's still strange to me that Modest Mouse isn't more popular - that they couldn't even fill up half of the stadium, on a Friday night. Setlist was crazy, too! Along with the four new songs they played (which are great), we got some cowboy dan & trailer trash. Plus others that really get me dancing, but I didn't used to follow the song names, so forget about it.   Saturday  Ohh, lovely lounge at home day! Breakfast at the B&O (used to be restricted, gave it another chance!) - shaking up some good bloody mary's at that place! Nice little hangover cure, they've got. Scones are a Go... Spent some nice time just doing n-o-t-h-i-n-g at the apartment...feet up on the couch, sprawled across the bed, talking about everything and nothing with B...Around 2 it was time to get ready for ye grande ole' Cirque du Soleil. I had never been and neither had B; it was our present to each other. Very excited to go, very excited to have gone. It was mezmerizingly beautiful. Captivated audience we were, I didn't want it to stop. Beautifully intricate costumes and well-played out parts. Equal parts laughter, skill, amazement, gymnastics, and love. Go!   Sunday   It was all about getting out & skating today! Jeezus, how long had it been?? Yeah...seven weeks? SO, we were supposed to rally out to Bainbridge but a flaw in communications led us out to Bonney Lake. That's fine with me! The snakerun/bowl there is just sick, so fun! It felt like no time had gone by, I was loving the nipple, the corner curve, the bowl and yeah! the loup-de-loup. Time flew by there, it was so much fun. We didn't have a bbq that day, but the little dip I took in the lake felt sooo necessary. Love water. Love swimming and being in it. At Eli & Michelle's, I floated a little down the river by their house and it was a little piece of heaven...Just lay back my head, lifting up the feet and d r i f t. Love it!   Monday  Had a little bit of a late waking-up but gathered together w/friends and headed down for Day Two at Bumbershoot. Carissa's Wierd played their second-to-last show and it was Perfectly Sad. Beautiful songs, I had goosebumps the entire show. They played everything I like listening to and more. Last song, it was just the two of them doing a little duet. I am very looking forward to nov.2.  That night was Wilco, and they played two of the songs that I always think of B when I hear. I love that we have our songs, our bands, that we "adopted" for our own. Cute! Bonus round that night, we had time after Wilco to eat foods and catch Pedro! I haven't seen Casey in forever, but it made me happy to see that him & Jen are engaged!! I miss seeing Casey as much as I used to, but am happy he found a girl that compliments him well and makes him happy. He was always wanting that, and really deserves it.  I love everything about what I've been doing. This year has been flying by, I can't believe it...so many things have been done and so many dates to come! I am so happy, so content and so smiley inside. 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,October,2003</date>
<post>

     
      It's never good to wake up with a cold. At four this morning, I knew today would be groggy and tea-infused. I like that there isn't much little updating to be done here at work, the bulk of my projects really are projects and not little to-do's. Lovely.  put it away  check out for the day in for a round of over-exposure the thing mother nature provides to get up & go  bottle up and explode - seeing stars surrounding you: red, white & blue  you look at him like you've never known him but i know for a fact that you have the last time you cried, who'd you think was inside?  It's too bad about him. Such lovely, secret songs...though I wasn't a fan of the whole thing it is always sad to know that there won't be any more.   Ravioli, I like ravioli. Ravioli, it's the one for me!  Excited to start flash 2 class. It's about time, right? I have too many projects, I think, to ever tackle them all. Does that cause anxiety? Liking to have projects and things waiting around to do, but having too many and not stopping the accumulation?  Looking forward to dinner w/B's parents! 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,October,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Hola, Blog.  Seems like I've been ignoring this part of my blog-world. How would you like an update? I am currently: - making lentil burritos - drinking pumpkin ale (Buffalo Bill's Brewery) - waiting on loads of laundry - listening to new OutKast  Returned super late last night/this morning from (yearly) Mexico trip. Drove down to PDX ($140 cheaper tix) on the eve of the 16th. Spent the evening drinking beers with Brian & Mark's friend Casey & his wife Chelsea. Slept little that night, to wake up and arrive at the Portland airport at 4:45am. We were greeted with a lovely $100 fee for the surfboards - !!! I couldn't believe the lady didn't charge us more for that whoppin' nine-foot coffin!   So anyway, normal airport/layovers/sleepiness/mixedwithexcitement ensues, and we arrive in PVR at 3pm - Jalisco time. Hail a taxi for a third of the asked price and zoom our asses to Sayulita.   What a great crew! B, Mark & myself...looking for nothing but surfing, exploring, cheap beers and taco stands. Thank GOD my digital camera now has six movies and 200+ pictures on it. Plus the cameras those guys brought, I don't know if there was a moment longer than ten minutes survived without a photo documenting it! Can't wait to get into work tomorrow and download all of them. Then there's the web documentation...I think I can pull that off without much fuss. Maybe some flash auto-slideshow or insertions? Still thinking...  Our little ten-day stint went by slow, then fast, then all of a sudden we're home today and have work to look forward to (as usual). I think the thing that is really going to stand out in my memory are the waves. They were larger, more consistent and just really so much more  Fun  than I have ever seen them down there! Never thought I would spend my vacation time hanging out at the Beach under an umbrella, but that really was the best plan and once we started, it lasted four days. I could read, wander around to stores for food, or hop in the water whenever I wanted. It's not like our house was that far away - because it wasn't, but it was just So Convenient to bring everything to the Beach and pay the darn $5.00 for the chair & umbrella use.  Emotions, sights and sounds really can't be relived in this blog. Too bad! I'm going to be slammed at work this week & next, not even sure of all the things going on that I missed. Want to get pictures posted and adventures official SOON.  Damn I made a good batch of burritos! I like that there are some things I can cook well. Next I'm trying some squash. I don't think it will be that hard, but I'm already thinking of yummy things to make with it. Soup, bread, muffins, dip?  Between the hour-changeover and being an hour ahead for a little over a week, I'm starting to get sleepy.   Adios.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I wish the world was flat like the old days & I could travel just by folding the map no more airplanes or speedtrains or freeways -  there'd be no distance that could hold us back.  Such an impressive show on Friday! Oh, the songs they sang...the dancing and Love I felt inside! Big smiles, still as I keep listening to Death Cab, I love the pretty pictures they paint in my head as I work. Watercolors, not watered-down, but dauby and blots and such.  Holy cow I have work cut out for me this (two-day) week. Gotta get the going on!  
     
    
</post>

<date>12,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Weird Dream I Had :  I was staying on this farm with a girl who I (really) met in Mexico, she lives up in Kamloops and is name Dominga. We were hiding out in her attic for some reason (it was cold?) and we had to keep covering up the windows with blankets and had nothing but some nails and random items to use as a hammer, to keep the coverings in place. There wasn't really any furniture; sleeping bags were strewn across the floor. There were a bunch of those and it looked like it should stink like a hippie room but it didn't. I don't remember any smells. The two of us were sticking our heads out of this window that was near the back of the room, it was biting cold outside but she had this cigarrette she wanted to smoke and so that window was left open. I smelled it and it smelled like pot, but also like some herbs. So I asked her what it was and she said "thursday smoke". It looked like a joint, and I smoked some and my whole head went upside-down. Like when  you watch a movie and you're looking straight ahead, then the camera pans down to your feet really fast, then spins around in a circle, then you're looking back at the ceiling. That's what happened to me, what I saw, when I smoked it. I looked down from the window where we were and saw that the room we were on was actually connected to a truck bed, like a trailor. But the room we were in was so big! It was almost the size of my apartment, so maybe 600 sq. ft? She kept smoking the joint, and dropping it on the window sill. And she also kept repeating "thursday"...not even looking at me, it was like we were in two separate worlds, really. The truck started to move, and everything was shifting in our room. Now there Was furniture - dressers were sliding back and forth across the entire length of the room, on the shiny wood floor. Dominga kept smoking. We were travelling on a bumpy, rocky dirt road. The blankets were all falling off the windows, and light was streaming in. It was hurting my eyes, it was brighter than normal sunlight. Then we laid back on the sleeping bags, with everything shifting and rolling and bumping along. Looking up at the ceiling, it was like a big patchwork system. It might have even been made out of cloth, so many different patterns and shapes it was like looking at a very close-up view of a model farm or something that is usually very small and miniature.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
      FREE FLU SHOTS. Or, should I say: flu shots "provided by" RM. So if he doesn't see your name on the list, you know he's gonna keep a log in his head about it and if you do end up getting sick, he's gonna terminate you. Yeah, I know...presidents of companies don't  really  have time or interest in keeping up with things like that, but it was in back of my mind. So I got one. Don't know if I have gotten one before, but gee my arm hurts now. Weird how I didn't even know it was going in and now it's all sore. Great. Ran around Greenlake last night so my legs are also sore. I'm just a big sore-ball today. Whee. Oh and I woke up this morning and think I had some vertigo, it was like I was drunk. I'm not kidding you. I had to hold on to things to keep from falling over, and I have felt slightly dizzy/naucous all day. Plus, it's real hard to see straight. (wah!)  Saw thee movies this weekend. Here is my synopsis: #1: Lost in Translation. Very good movie. One of the best I've seen (ever?). Had touching, real moments - or, rather the whole thing seemed very real and plausible. I liked that the girl in it wasn't some skinny, beautiful, make-up-faced girl who talked a bunch of poo. I liked that the end, only she could hear what Bill Murray whispered in her ear. I liked that (I think) they fell in love - but it was a desperate, lonely, out of need for company kind of love. It was sweet, and I had tears in my eyes for one scene.   #2: Elf. Funny! Will Farrell is going on a good track, and I really laughed throughout this movie. Ending got sorta mushy/stoopid but hey - it's rated PG. You gotta expect stuff like that. Don't think I'd buy it, but glad I saw it on a Saturday night.  #3: Scary Movie 3. Maybe I should have actually watched all of #1 and also seen #2 before seeing this? It was funny (not so much as Elf), but about 1/2-3/4 of the way through, I sorta lost interest and felt like it lost the funniness and tried to hold on to a disintegrating story line. Good DVD rental material for sure.  And...here I am back on the rock. My Flash class was great. Now if I can just get six hours in front of a computer on Sundays, maybe I can just morph myself into one...trying to keep up with stretching so I don't get all wah and have to do PT again. I feel like I can't shut up lately. I keep talking, I type into this blog, I call B all the time. What is going on that I can't just think inside my brain and trust my memory to remind myself of telling someone information  Later ? Like I don't have a memory and must transmit:NOW.  Breakfast on Sunday at Longshorman's Daughter. Very delicious, as usual.  Going to try (if I remember!) to cut my hair tonight. Ridden with split-ends. woo.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Ouf. Still with head cold. This thing is determined to get in the way of my work! I have wonderful plans to get this hype section finished, but every day I feel pretty much worthless by 2pm. BIGWAH!  This weekend I start the much anticipated Flash 2 course! Very excited to learn more advanced concepts, esp. because Ali is already having me incorporate them into the sites...yay, me!  And not much else to report on, really...been hanging far low after work, doing a little knitting and trying to get this SQL mail thing straight. I swear, it's right on the tip of my...err - fingertips. No need to bore you with that sheyt though. Also been doing some good reading of a new author B's dad helped us discover. Carl Hiassen. Great stuff, good mystery/drama/law. Highly recommend 'Sick Puppy', which I can very much see being made into a movie.  Saw farewell CW show last friday. That was a sad, beautiful sight. As usual, my eyes welled up during the Valentine song. A special treat was the avril lavigne cover - HA! So many good songs, good shows came from that band, sucks they're not around anymore...  My brain is becoming saturated with congestion and snot, so I must go now.   
     
    
</post>

<date>21,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Oh my god, blog. This weekend did not have enough hours in it. Boo! On Friday, I had to powernap to function, then experiment with vinyl for present-making. Very different than expected. Instead of easy and fast, it was over an hour of figuring out how to make the stupid material agree with me in terms of sew-ing ma-chine. I think I got it, but by that time I was ready to quit and catch a cab with Sara to then grab Gin and go to Dragonfish for some deliciouso tofu pillows and pearl sake. Yum-um!  Saturday was like - woah! Why did I wake up at almost 10am? Guess I WAS exhausted from the week...B and I lazed about until about 11:15 and then took the boat down to southcenter for some extremely efficient shopping. We did marvelous, I am so glad Bri doesn't dawdle about and we both had the goal to go in and get out. Then we came home only to walk downtown for another two-and-a-half hours, where I get a coffee and Bailey's to help out with the last tidbits of shopping...I almost exploded in several different ways, trying to navigate around this crazy town (on foot, even!) and get things Done. But yes, we came home and were both too wiped to cook. (yay pizza)  Today...oh, I can barely even keep typing! Today Holly came to meet me around 10:45am and we walked downtown for just about three hours. Have I done enough walking this weekend or What. Goal today was to get Holly's shopping done and finish my Cards. While the ones for my work-buddies (are out of control. really.), I will still come home to make some more cards tomorrow. But I think I have a beta version down for next year, it will be really snappy. Plus, I took pictures before they are going to be sent off, I think that might help?  Okay I am so over this weekend. I've been working now since 8pm and just want to SLEEP. Stupid busy weekend, too much work to do, so much shopping, and I feel full of spirit but weary. Very excited for Whistler, much more so than for Stupid Sales Meeting. Excited to relax with everyone, for Tandoori, for Sushi perhaps, for some actual riding and not just a couple runs and then backdownforwork. Phew.  Sleep...oh bed, you are so sweet to me...exhausted.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Rant: sick of all the work that is piled on us. Not a chance of creativity to seep out of anywhere. We are busy busy and I have tunnelvision.  Rave: B got me a boquet of cute anemones! They don't smell, but they are so colorful and look like something you could make out of crepe paper, perhaps. Their leaves are clustered and I just Love seeing them by my desk.   Tried making christmas cards with my wonderful printer last night. Looks like although I know tons about web graphics, I have a lot to learn about my digital camera and how to bring in images at 300dpi instead of changing it afterwards. Duh.   Going up to Whistler for a week did nothing but take away from my creative time. I need that! OK back to work so I can do my own work tonight... 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Today sucks. I hate being at work today. All I can do to keep from crying my eyes out is keep my headphones on tight, don't look over to see what is going on across my room. I can't wait for the 4:30 boat to come and pick me up, while I'm sitting in Hunter's car trying to avoid eye contacts and conversations. Just want to go home and curl up in the oceans of blankets on the bed. Sleep, tears, nothing work. I hate that so much work is piled up but my brian wants to divert. My eyes don't want to focus on these screens.  Still hooked on Transatlanticism. It's like a lullaby for me to code to.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      You know what I could do without?  When I'm walking down the hall at work, like over by the mailboxes, for example, and I pass some person I don't know and I get that GRIN. Like saying, hey, I'm friendly. You don't know me, we just happen to both work for the same company, but I can at least smile. The eye contact is never warm, it's just business as usual.  Stupid business.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      What an awesome weekend! B, my dad, Becky and I tripped out to the cabin and did some major nothings. For having such a packed schedule, it was supernice to put in some time for not running around, not snowboarding, not anything. We got in late, had a beer, went to bed. Saturday we slept in until 10.20am which is pretty much unheard of for me...guess I needed it? Walked down to the river which was silently being covered in snowflakes. Took some lovely pictures of everything, ate hot cocoa, played scrabble & hearts, snowshoed (in the dark! with headlamps - very cool), knitted a ton and smiled more. I have said it a thousand times before, but how great is it, how many people can really say that their best friend is also who they want to marry? Words can't spell it out.   Now back on the island - wooo. Monster/Fangfish made it through the long stretch of no foods. I swear beta fish are the best. Low maintenance. And I think I may be able to last with Grandaddy for the morning. Really need to ween myself off of dc4c or I may tire of it too soon. Wear off the shine.   Ah la la. Such a great ad I get to work with - bye!
     
    
</post>

<date>12,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I really like the singer from Iron & Wine. Barely whispering sweet things. Listening to him makes me want to cry for beauty.  Today has blown by. Too many ideas, I can't focus. Need to prioritize and g-o. Finished my belt and now want to figure out what to do with big fun yard of clear vinyl. Need to find time to practice making truffles, I am guessing it won't be as easy as the instructions read. Sort of like fresh spring roll experiment. Wouldn't that be exciting though? It could also equal a big stomach-ache.    Beautiful roses sitting next to my desk. I love them! I love having flowers as company for when I work at home. Hi, flowers!   brainoverload::
     
    
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      So right now, I am officially  "so annoying"  I want to sew, I want to add mexico pics to my website. I want to have a glass of wine and watch a movie. I just don't feel like going to bed yet. Which is pretty out of the norm. I bet in twenty minutes I'll be snuggling up.   Tonight went to new fabric store for clear vinyl. I have grandiose ideas for belts, wallets and small handbags. While there (with only 25 minutes to closing) I had racing thoughts of embroidered pillow/cases, faux fur hats, thick felt bags and things with snaps on them. I hate that I don't know where to find the really good things like belt buckle/loops, neat snaps, etc. Prolly just second-hand or Red Light, right? We'll see. So anyway, I wanted to buy about a hundred dollars worth of things but couldn't justify it. This was purely a present-shopping visit.   And I am STILL listening to Transantlanticism. Tried some Halo Benders but I'm back. When will I tire of it? Soundtrack for December, it seems...  Very excited for the cabin.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Left: why is Mudhoney playing at the showbox? Right: i dunno, maybe it could be good, like you're back in highschool? Left: yeah...sorta skeptical on this though, I didn't like their later stuff...you think it could be fun? Right: Oh i didn't say that. i think it could be, but prolly better to stay home and see if someone else went. showbox is probably twenty bucks anyway. Left: good call.  That is the conversation my brain had when I saw mudhoney on the pollstar.com.   /// i am waiting for you to flee the scene as if you held in your hand the smoking gun and on the floor lay the one they said you loved  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      imhome.imhome.imhome!!  Thank gad I'm home again. It's really terrible, but I'm starting to tire of Whistler. Who does that? Who gets tired of being surrounded by gorgeous mountains and snow dumps? (me.) It really would have been more fun, less lonely, not so drab if B were up there with me. Big fat OH WELL to that because imhome! Really made good time w/Hunter. Left the Delta at 1:40, crossed truck customs at 4pm and dropped him off pretty much at 6pm. Got home, got kisses, went out to Machiavelli with B. Haven't really cared for it the past couple times we've gone, but last night was pretty much good - the spinach ravioli did it for me. And I remembered that although a chianti is what I want, at Machiavelli it's the house red/merlot that is best.   The cat, snuggling and toes at bedtime, finally some good music on the radio...I love travelling and being out but right now all I want to do is nerd out on my computer and drink tea. Mmm.  Can I just say that I hate bro-brahs? I saw so many blowjobs this past week and it's really disgusting. People need to just realise they work for a snowboard company, and that in itself is fun. But they don't need to be so upping each other and kissass. I prolly didn't see all that I could have, being that I was busy and also avoiding most crowds and parties...  Oh and I also have to say that it sucks when you have to go somewhere for a long time and your best friend, your boyfriend, isn't there. So that everything you want to go and have fun doing, is without him. Paints everything a shade of lonely. A shade of appreciating that other friends were there just a little more. I feel so blessed to have such a wonderful, loving relationship. Something that most people should envy. Though I never knew it possible to have such a large love, every day I am overwhelmed with feelings of appreciation, awe, wonderment at what we have.   Begonia really wants to play. She's climbing all over the couch and running around at high speeds. And I can't stop listening to transatlanticism! On the way home we were stuck because my smart ass forgot my cds back at the hotel. I swear deathcab is good in any situation. Ben Gibbard = makes soundtrack to my life. Weird. kexp just played some new strokes song and I sorta liked it. What does THAT mean?  Two days we go to the cabin. Two weeks we go back up to Whistler.  Twenty days and we hop on a plane to Jackson HOle! Wooohee to that! This month is so packed with fun I can hardly think about the work that is also piling up. Stupid work. Stupid everybody wants their own site and we have zero creative realm to embrace. Glad that work is opening up here, would be nice to go do something different, something appreciated.  Gotta clean frog's pad. Feeling responsible for their uncomfortableness. Maybe if we named them...I would attach personality and also more parental responsibility to them? Horrible me.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Fucken can't figure out my new health insurance. I know I'm not pleased with it: I have to pay a deductible on going to acupuncture before my 90% coverage kicks in. Stoopid insurance plans.  In other news, we took our first trip to Mission of the season. Of course it was a great time - eight great friends, in the middle of Wenatchee, with not much to do besides boozin' and foolin' around. Too bad the snow was packed so hard you could ice skate on it. Ok, not that bad, but it was freaking COLD out there! Brrr. Hopefully next weekend brings better snow. Sounds like Stevens has been getting dumped on and I think we're planning on some hooky to go ski tomorrow? (ok not hooky but more fun than admitting to getting morning off...)  
     
    
</post>

<date>12,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hooo, I found my guilty pleasure of the day. In Hunter's folder: Dude Ranch. When did this come out? My senior year of highschool or later? No matter when, this isn't good but IT IS!  Blog, I need to go back to acupuncture. My arm is hurting me again and I don't remember when but I hurt my shoulder in Jackson. I wake up it hurts, I turn it, I'm putting on my clothes and it Hurts. Typing hurts. I am a big pile of uncomfortableness in my arms. Great.  Oh and CP is moving in to the cube next to us. Yay, that. I feel claustrophobic in my large cube with a view.  I can't write now although I want to. Really on a roll today. 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Why, hello there, Blog.  This weekend was Spectacular! Riding at Mission was so so beautiful, sunny and warm...But! Cold enough that we got some sweet fresh powder turns through chutes, across fields and up some step-ups. Best local ski weekend for sure.  And in more exciting news: I AM ENGAGED! Yes, me. I didn't really think B was serious when he asked me, which was funny. He was so sweet and wonderful - I can't remember what he said verbatim but I instantly started crying and everything turned upside down. I actually thought I might fall out of the chairlift. Then I was worried I would drop the ring, or how to tell people I'm going to officially get married. I'm so happy that he did it when he did, everything was perfect. Sunny blue skies and with such good friends. Taking that last run down to the lodge, I'll never forget how my heart felt racing in my chest.  And all day I've been jittery to start planning the where, whos, etc of getting married! My mind keeps drifting off to it all day even though I have all this list to knock out. I know that everything will be perfect - we have the best ideas together.  Ok back to work...>>>>>>>
     
    
</post>

<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Drinking coffee does no good. Not ready for tea. Excited to look at fruit booter pictures for the next couple days as I get this segment done.  Feel like hopping in a car and sleeping in the back seat, waking up and going riding or camping or hiking or Away!  Sounds kinda like this weekend will be.   Drinking coffee drains my mind. Splat * 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ! ! !  I remembered my dream: Where did it start...I was hanging out with Sarah, but this was in 8th or 9th grade and they were living up in Cedar Ridge. We had gone out to dinner with her dad, Scott, Kali and I don't know where her mom was. It was mexican food or something else that was crappy in north bend. Her dad was driving an older vanagon and we had to rig something to get the door to shut, the windows were all hack jobs...it was as if the van would fall apart at any moment. So we get home, and they're living in this brown house, the lawn is nice and green but you can tell they aren't serious about the house. As everyone gets out of the van, Sarah and I are going over to sit in the grass. I look back and the vanagon is slowly rolling down their driveway. (even though the incline was larger and it should have been going faster). I run over and try to stop it because (surprise!) there are a bunch of trucks, new shiney trucks, lined up on the road below. The van's pedals are far from the seat, and narrow like a vw bug's. The steering wheel is skinny and has no power steering in it. This is all moving slo-mo and the dad comes out to help so I get out. Turns out there's this button he forgot to push (no, not the parking brake) that stops it from rolling down the hill.  Then warp to this jungle I'm living in with Dori and Lane and some other people. 1998 or so - I'm younger but still dressing stupidly. It's dark and damp and huge vines all over. Every time I try to swing down a vine or climb a branch there are spiders and furry little things scurrying by. I'm still in nanny-role for this so Lane's by my side the whole time. We were hanging out, coming in-and-out of the jungle for awhile though this part is the clearest in my mind: I'm trying to make my way down to the long dinner table at the base of these trees, but every vine has bats on it or isn't strong enough. Lane shows me these creepy vines that are thick as my arm and seem to grow from the ground up, instead of hanging. I swing my way down to the table, which is darkly lit by candles. We're eating this uncomfortable dinner (it was always stuffy eating with them), when Lane announces something: he wants to teach his classmates about Judaism. Stuart and Dori don't say much, she encourages him a little but Lane is persistent. At this point I am watching this happen, how Lane wants to do something so positive but Dori wants to protect his feelings: what if he's teased? what if he loses focus? So worried, all the time.   I fade from that scene to a house in wallingford I don't recognize. It's one of those house parties that you sorta know the host but don't bother because you know you're going to leave soon anyway. B's there with me, so this is recent. There is a large bathroom, the size of the bedroom we have now and all it has is a pedestal sink, toiled against adjacent wall (but opposite each other); the walls are painted velvety red and it has cream curtains. There is a door in from the hallway and a door out to the bedroom that nobody is in, the lights are out in there. I'm in there talking with B about something, we're not needing to be in the bathroom but the door doesn't lock. Laura from my old work comes stumbling in with (her boyfriend?) and I don't recognize her until she says my name. She's crying, she's really upset about something and needs a hug but she's so happy to see me. Didn't she move down to CA? Why is she at this party? Turns out we're at mikey wolfson's house, not in wallingford but on queene anne. Very strange. B is talking to her boyfriend-guy but the guy doesn't seem right. I can tell B's thinking something like "who the hell ARE these people?" because I feel trapped, like what do I have to say to Laura? She's going on about how She is the original LK, not Lucas. Does it matter? Then all at once she's wasted, she's needing to throw up but about six people come stomping in from the bedroom door, they're needing the toilet, the towels hanging on the wall, the sink needs more soap and we're out of hot water.   These dreams were liquid, they were a resurrection of people from my past that I never think about and this makes me interested in these dreams. I kept dreaming this morning, drifting out of consciousness that I needed to get up and tasting for more dream, wanting to see where I would go next. Fun but strange. Dreams are funny like that.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Oh, and two more things:    ordered NEW 15" PowerBook Friday! CANT WAIT! (our first purchase together, too)    got Modest Mouse tickets FINALLY because we were slackers for so long we were darn lucky they didn't sell out.  ...and I did not succeed in my new year's resolution (#2): make a new meal every month from scratch. I'll do it soon so I can make up for it. It's such a good and easy decision. I Love Eating!   So yay, but boo. I'm doing well with having my sh!t together.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hey. I am on the end of wrapping up a very relaxing yet fulfilling weekend...Friday I had all intentions of staying in and knitting, doing webthings, etc. while B went to Jamie & Jenay's housewarming party. Turns out traffic was bad so when his ride came, they all came up for a bit of wine to wait for it to die down. I had a glass, then I was convinced to join them. It was a friendly enough party. See, I'm still getting to know and warming up to B's outer circle of friends. Half of them I hadn't seen in a year or so, and that was the first time I met them. They are all great people, good intentions and intricite lives and all. Glad I went! Short and sweet - I was back by midnight.  Saturday I went solo up to Alpental and Boy Oh Boy was I glad I did! The snow was so light and plentiful, I rode for a good three hours before the weekend crowds got to me. Taking some first turns down gunmount was just awesome, nobody seems to care about the weekday spots on the weekend? And elevator was great again and again...deep powder, big curvy turns...ahh...That's what I needed to want to go up after work!  Came back, met my mom for some lunch (breakfast for me!) at the B&O. It was nice talking to her, I think our relationship has grown a lot in the past few years. After that I relaxed about w/Bri and felt lazy. Went out to eat w/Sara and Mark at that ummy pizza place down in belltown. It's always good there, great wine - I'm just not drawn to it as often as other places. Having an entire pizza makes for great leftovers though.   Aand today we slept in a tad before going to eat with Mark up at the broadway grill. I need to get some new eggs here (mine are no good) so I can make morning foods at home...it seems silly sometimes to go out because it's so easy to make a really good breakfast at home. Especially when the two-egg meal is around $7. Unnecessary.  For the first time in a long while, February came and I feel like I really lived through January. You know how it is when days or months just fly by? I noticed it ticking by but it didn't drag and it didn't zoom. It was perfect, like a great balance between lazy, artsy, movie/tv-watching, and activities.   And every day I drift more and more in love...at breakfast this morning I felt the freshness of first date and longevity of love that lasts, that grows with time...
     
    
</post>

<date>31,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Today I am in such a bummer mood,. I don't like when I open myself up to someone and really feel like they care about me, when they just end up ignoring me and taking me for granted. Everything in me feels so childish right now. You know what? I was looking forward to going to the show tonight w/Sara but she won't return emails and I know she gets them because she is a freak about checking stuff like that. Did I do something? Am I rude to her? Why does this pattern keep happening to me? As long as I can make friends, they've been leaving me.  Feeling lonely isn't fun. Piled up work is a mask for me to ignore that I have been kinda unmotivated to go out and do things lately. Coming in to work is the mindset I need to change. It seems so different w/Gin gone and I don't know why. I come in, I hide in my corner and code away. I dream of going out surfing, I want to go skate more and be outside and be active.   I don't even feel like typing now. So blah. 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I love lying in bed with my laptop. I love the heater blowing air on my cold toes. I love my fiance and am so excited planning our wedding! The past two weeks I have been working so nonstop, so diligently. It was fun going out last night...so bad of a reminder that long island ice teas are Not Good. Why did it have to taste like a margarita so much? And then I got a second one? Gimme a break.   There are these pigeons determined to build a nest outside my window. They freak out at any movement or loud noise or cat looking at them (like Begonia!). The male will bring a nice long twig to use and the female will break off this tiny little piece and let the rest of it fall to the ground. So far they've built four starts to a nest and then start over. I am convinced that pigeons are not too smart. The girl should have been fed up with the male's competence in finding sticks so far. Or maybe it's the other way -- he's doing a great job, she's just a novice & not too sure how to put a nest together.  Ok I just started thinking this: where do all the birds in the city go when they die? Do they fly out over the water or mountains far away from everything and give their bodies back to the earth? There are thousands of birds, but only rarely do you see a dead one from result of being hit by a car or something. How will I  ever figure out this puzzle...
     
    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Death is such a humbling thing. Getting Casey's email this morning wasn't surprising, I knew someday it would happen. It was like getting punched in the stomach, I curled up in my chair and let the tears come out. I feel so many things about it, from sadness for him losing his mom after such a long, hard battle; I feel more sad that I didn't get to visit her than I did when my own grandpa died. Having the older people in my life pass away hasn't been that hard. Sad, yes...I don't understand my emotions. The cherry blossoms are blowing petals through the wind and I think that karin is in heaven of some kind, with other angels that brought happiness and knowledge to so many other people.   Obviously I don't want to be at work today. It's very hard to concentrate and then someone sends out an email responding to casey's, about karin and my eyes well up. Karin was always interested in who you were, what you were up to, and genuinely cared. She was outgoing, understanding, compassionate...all the things that you would expect and hope for a mom and friend to be.   I would like to talk to casey even though I don't know what I would say except that I love him and am around if he needs me. I can't imagine how I would feel or god, if I'd even want to talk about anything, if one of my parents got cancer and went through all she did. The hard thing is knowing that nothing I say could make it at all better. Things like this you can't fake through your feelings or hope for more experience so you "know what to say" but I feel like I could offer nothing, I haven't been through it.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
       and when I see you I really see you upside down but my brain knows better it picks you up and turns you around turns you around turns you around   I am still in love with the words ben gibbard writes. Beautiful background, teary-eyed foreground. Soon I will become one with my computer. Communicating solely via keyboard.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Come And talk of all the things we did today Here And laugh about our funny little ways While we have a few minutes to breathe Then I know that it's time you must leave  But darling be home soon I couldn't bear to wait an extra minute if you dawdled My darling be home soon It's not just these few hours but I've been waiting since I toddled For the great relief of having you to talk to  And now A quarter of my life is almost past I think I've come to see myself at last And I see that the time spent confused Was the time that I spent without you And I feel myself in bloom  So darling be home soon I couldn't bear to wait an extra minute if you dawdled My darling be home soon It's not just these few hours but I've been waiting since I toddled For the great relief of having you to talk to  ------ instrumental break ------  Darling be home soon I couldn't bear to wait an extra minute if you dawdled My darling be home soon It's not just these few hours but I've been waiting since I toddled For the great relief of having you to talk to  Go And beat your crazy head against the sky Try And see beyond the houses and your eyes It's ok to shoot the moon  So darling My darling be home soon I couldn't bear to wait an extra minute if you dawdled My darling be home soon It's not just these few hours but I've been waiting since I toddled For the great relief of having you to talk to 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Tonight so far: Work. Stopped when Honeypie came home but am supposed to start back up. Do I have a.d.d.? I am so easily distracted, but Want to get this done! I hate that our work schedule is so rigorous. Not fast-paced - rigorous. As in, don't stop, don't think, just get it done! They need it, they will pester you for it. I don't have much time for research, thinking of fun/ideas - no. So taking a bubble bath tonight, drinking some wine was sooo necessary but now it's like ACK! Almost 9.30pm and still don't have a clue of how to re-design tech sections for ride. I started something  last week  but don't like it. The main problem is that I don't like their site. It's so...techy? Not in an up-to-date sense but just rigid and 90-degree angles and not much room for creative. Then they want 'fun' thrown in there. Yeah, right.  So...this wine is good. Anyone want to talk about something  besides  work? Ug. I hope I can find some inspiration in the next half-hour or so, or else I'm quitting and going to bed.  It's been a torrential downpour at some point throughout the day for the past three days, which I LOVE. It's exciting: the booming thunder, huge rain pelting against the windows, big puddles and mini-rivers accumulating and running down streetways and gutters. Don't get me wrong, I like it to be sunny and happy out but the rain gets me excited inside.  And I like making out with Brian. I wish I wasn't so drained when he/I get home from work. It would make the whole thing less annoying and more fun.  And: backtoworking. (wah face.)  >me.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This is terrible. For the past three days all I crave when I'm hungry is PoTaTo Chips! Why? They don't fill me up well, they taste pretty good but make me feel like a big slob...wah.  So now we're putting out a job proposal to this guy to come in and help and I'm having thoughts of my boss not liking my work anymore. It's ridiculous but I can't stop myself from feeling threatened. I think it will be great, having help and we can do more, focus on features on the sites instead of running full-steam ahead non-stop.  Glad to be around this weekend and have nothing planned. It feels good, just having all this time open to do whatever we like. Hope it clears up...Oh! Going dress shopping today! Very excited for this. Hope it's pretty easy, that I don't have to order dresses to try on and such. I know it will be fun, and I'm glad Gin & Hol can help me out because I think sometimes I have a warped view of what I look like? Not that I picture myself fat or ugly, but I think I look good in things that aren't flattering or don't fit me well. This is where B comes in and tells me to change my shoes or match a different shirt or something. Thank god for him!  Ok werk is calling me back (along with the potato chips) ::
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I have been the biggest grump in the entire world for the past 24 hours. I am SICK of being broken, my shoulders hurting, my face looks so great (two black eyes, green-bruised forehead...), it hurts to sit too long, etc. WAH! One thing that I am very lucky about is my husband-to-be is very understanding, sympathetic and is doing his best to turn our smallish apartment into a garden of vases and flowers and such. If I were to be left alone I would probably explode from all these scattered emotions I'm feeling. But then he calls me to say HI and it calms me down...for the most part. Sometimes I'm in this work-funnel and I really don't want to talk. He's still sweet though.  This weekend: I'm starting to get all bummed that we're not doing the lapushe trip with the gang. In about two hours they'll all be loading up on ferries and such and I'll be hacking away at fun code! It's probably mean of me, but I'm glad it's at least raining. I can't surf for at least another week, I can't skate, I can't ride my bike even! Thank god people want to go to movies and keep me otherwise occupied. Scrabble sounds like a good thing to do this weekend, too.  Did I tell you I still might have to get surgery? Yeah. If the ultrasound I get in a few weeks shows the cyst is still in my ovary, they are going in. I am rolling my eyes as I'm typing. Sure hope it goes away!  Back to work. Going in next week actually sounds like fun (!) since I haven't been in now for almost two weeks...
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hi. I don't want to write this out, but I'm going to before I get sick of telling the story all-together and never write it down. So I think I wrote on Saturday, right? So that day went fine. Great, actually - I got all the shopping I needed to get done, done; I went out to Woodinville & brought B his golf clubs and made his day (did I say previously how much I wanted to spoil him this weekend?), got a lunch w/him; went to Whole Foods and got everything delicious for dinner, got more presents wrapped and started on dinner pretty much on time. Full day there! Dinner was great, B was stoked (I think) on all his presents, and we played boggle. There was also some hanky-panky, but I don't need to write about that here!  So things get interesting around 10:00 when I get cramps. I thought "oh, this sucks, I'm going to get my period tomorrow" and we went to bed around 10:30, me still thinking how much I Hate cramps, and these ones were real bad. I couldn't move too well and it hurt to stand up. At 1am I woke up in extreme pain, but thought I had to pee. So I somehow make it to the toilet and I'm doubled over, thinking to myself that I'm really in too much pain to even pee.  Next thing, I'm hearing B yelling "what are you doing?!" "melissa! get up!" and I am facedown out by the computer table, lying on some shoes. My entire body is sweating, I'm cold and my ears sound like water rushing or like tin pipes. I feel my forehead and it's like there's a golf ball above my right eyebrow. My pants are still down to my knees from when I was on the loo. "Why are you bleeding?" - I look down and the wine bottle that fell, I thought it spilled some wine on me. - I am getting the chills writing this. - I tell him it's the wine, and he says "no, look at your fingers - where are you bleeding." I can't move, I'm on my back holding my knees to my chest and B calls 911. I'm crying, my abdomen is just killing me and for the first time, I'm really scared about what's wrong with me. I thought I just had menstrual cramps but something more terrible happened. When 911 showed up, there were two doctors peering down at me, then three more showed up and finally when I had to be put on the stretcher, three came in. Eight paramedics in our little apartment! About 15 times I was asked if I could be pregnant. They thought maybe a baby was in my fallopian tubes.  So, riding in an ambulance isn't fun. It was cold and very uncomfortable. I was all strapped down and really wanted to put my knees back to my chest. They take me to the hospital and find that I was bleeding from a cut that was about an inch-and-a-half in size, and I don't know how deep b/c it is by my right ear. They stick an IV in me, they novocaine up my noggin and I get a real messy wash job done on the cut. By this time I've given blood, had my blood pressure/pulse taken about six times and it's about 2:45am. The doctor comes in to STAPLE my cut shut. I didn't see the instrument but it made that good CAH-CHUNG noise that staple guns make. B took a good pic of it today, it's pretty gnarly.  What next? Oh, I'm injected with fenadril or something and it instantly makes me feel like I'm tipsy-drunk. Pretty funny. The doctors are still asking me if I could be pregnant, but the blood test says NO. (thank god!). Next, they want to do a cat-scan, because now they're leaning towards it being my appendix. I'm not scared of being cut up or needles and stuff, but I really didn't want a surgery. But whatever, it wasn't my appendix. The cat-scan was interesting. B said the control room was all star-trek looking; lots of buttons with lights, dials and whathaveyou. The scan didn't take long, and I was still tipsy so it wasn't bad.  Now we get to wait...and wait...give blood, take some blood pressure...wait...B was SO patient, I felt terrible for him! I at least got to lie down but he had one of those horrible plastic chairs, nothing to lean on to snooze. I think it was like 4:30a when the doctor Finally came in to announce that he thinks I had a cyst in my abdomen that burst, and the blood in there was causing my bad pain. And that I likely passed out in the bathroom, that it burst when I was sitting there. It's still weird that I don't remmeber how I fell or cut myself. Scary too.  Great, so now we knew what it must be but we had to wait for a room in the hospital so I could get out of the ER! Poor, poor lovey - I was fading in and out from the pain meds and he had nothing but the uncomfortable chair and bad TV to watch. I kept telling him to go home because I felt bad but he wanted to stay. So finally, it's like 7:30a and I have a room! I am wheeled on my bed through a maze of different elevators and hallways and find myself in my room. Not a bad room - I had a view of Harborview (that building is Huge!), a little of Amazon and the water. My OWN room, too - no sharing my TV with someone else, or being worried about no privacy. And the electronic bed was a luxury, for the time being.  I think this is the longest blog I have ever written. So I am there, I kinda get to sleep but I have to give blood ten more times, more blood pressure checks, I get to have an ultrasound - which was super cool. I could see my kidneys, my uterus, bladder, ovaries...and the cysts. There were two of those bastards! One had already burst, and I could tell b/c it looked not dense and smallish. The second one was IN my right ovary, and is still there. My doc decided not to do surgery b/c my body will likely take care of it itself. Go, me! So I got to come home today just at noon - I had been there just about 36 hours!   Not much else to tell - of course I had visitors, and B was so sweet through everything. I feel so terrible b/c even though there is nothing I could have done to prevent any of it, it still happened on his birthday.   What a blog this is! That should keep you up-to-date for awhile. I have to stay home and be unactive for awhile, so I doubt there will be much else to report on until I'm a little better. Going to figure out a new layout for dillo site now (hopfully). Wish me luck!
     
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Oh my god, I just posted and saw I didn't write ANYTHING in April. Holy crap have I been that busy? Way to go, me.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, HELLOOOoooo.  I have been doing so much running around and thinking about everything for B's birthday, it's been so fun! And I really think that I did a good job so far on everything this year. I don't want to say much about anything right now in case for some reason he comes home and decides to check on my blog before we eat dinner or something strange like that. Speaking of dinner, he requested that I make spaghetti. Now, I think I'm a pretty competent cook but something tells me that he's scared I'm going to fuck it up or try something new that's no good. Spaghetti is a safe bet. He doesn't even want me to make the sauce!  Oh, I better get going on that...I AM going to make the sauce, and it's going to be damn good too. I'm even going to make the garlic bread. And I have to shower still...oh, augh! I don't need to have a panic attack about getting everything done. Stay calm...breathe...  Did I tell you how good Belle & Sebastian were? SO GOOD: I danced my ass off (in boots!) and sang along to every song. It was so fun so fun. Too bad they only come to Seattle every three years or whatevear. Weird, we just had a slew of shows and I can't think of anything coming that I care too much about seeing. Hm.   Started making list of people to invite to the wedding. I have to keep on myself about these things, I forget how fast time flies and once July hits, the summer is going to breeze by. Bye!
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I MISS CARISSA'S WIERD!  Still stupid that they broke up. It's been so too long since they played and I could cry knowing that they won't ever play again. Stupid getting a bimbo's burrito with Jenn making your burrito and all those gnarly tattoos but NO MORE music? No sense. No music, Yes burritos. Wasteland restaurant, swallows your musicians. Saw someone today who looked exactly like you. Funny how the years go by.  Who keeps me smilin' all day through? Who cheers me up when I feel blue? Who makes my wildest dreams come true?  MY HONEY DO!  hee hee. I love that! LoveloveLOVE  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>