<Blog>


<date>28,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>27,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>27,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>27,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
         Using mathematics to explain everything. 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>26,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Anyone (not just BlogTeam members) can leave comments in response to any of the main posts directly from this page.  Just click on the Comments link below the relevant post, fill in your name and leave a message.  Primitive, but simple.  Enjoy! 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       A shocking photo of Douglas "Doug" McConnell has appeared over the internet giving a frightening insight into the Stadium Rock Dreams of the Be-Spectacled Self-Proclaimed Soft Rock Saviour.  Rick Parfitt is said to be beside himself.   
    
    
</post>

<date>25,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>25,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>25,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I've Made It!!! 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
         Credit to my Dad for finding this. 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       When I'm hungry, only one eatery can satisfy my needs:    
    
    
</post>

<date>25,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       He's coming home, he's coming home, he's coming, Panda's coming home!    "Being back in the UK makes me a sad panda." 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Find yourself wondering what Guy and Scott get up to all day? Finally the answer.  All you really need to know about panda's summed up in one flash animation.  Sort it out boys!   urlLink http://www.thebigsmoker.co.uk/pandalove.html  
    
    
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Just saw  urlLink this  on Slashdot - apparently some American Biotech company has created a fish that glows red in the dark.  All very scary for various reasons, but the fish itself looks  urlLink quite pretty , in an eerie unnatural sort of way. 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       As promised, here's a picture from the Oilers vs Flames game I was at last weekend.  Unfortunately, I was too busy cheering when the fights were going on to take photos of them but this one was taken just after the Oilers scored the winner in overtime.     It's bloody freezing here at the moment (-20 degC plus wind chill) so it's just as well the nearest off-licence is just across the road from the hotel!  
    
    
</post>

<date>21,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Sounds like Graham's dirty past is catching up with him and the Canadian government do not approve.  Oh well, see you on Thursday mate.  For webspace, this blog has been upgraded (free of charge) to a Blog*Spot Plus account, which provides us with 25Mb of space to fill.  There should be a new "Upload File" button on the "New Post" screen in Blogger.  Just ensure that pictures are:  1) Sensibly trimmed, i.e. no more than 500x400 pixels. 2) Compressed in a web-friendly format, .GIFs and .JPGs work best.  The picture of "Bob" below gives and idea of the maximum size that works well over a dial-up connection.  If in doubt, just post it and I'll trim it later via FTP. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Just to update everyone - I'm not being allowed to leave Canada and have been placed under house arrest with armed guards at every door.  But with a bit of luck (not to mention my history of successful covert ops) I should manage to escape back to Aberdeen at some point on Thursday.  Oh and if someone could give me access to their web space I'll post my pictures from over here.  As it is I'm too lazy to arrange doing this myself. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Bob deserves a special mention as he has a had a long hard fight but come out the other side as (say it together) A WINNER. So, Well Done Bob!!!     
    
    
</post>

<date>20,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>20,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
         'nuff said. 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I know JB is having some problems posting messages on this so I'll do it for him.  Me, JB and Stu got fucking monged last night (2 for 1 drinks at the 'nage - don't order 9 drinks - THEY GIVE YOU 18!!!).  Anyway, I was drunk in work this morning.  John vomited in the shower and I dunno what happened to Mr King. Jesus, I feel like ass. 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       In light of recent events, the colour of this blog will  have  to be changed.   Complete and utter spaz. 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       At last! A detailed analysis of the airspeed velocity of an  urlLink unladen swallow . 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       T-shirts are passé, we need Panda Attack  urlLink BBQ Aprons ! Nice. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Lets not push the panda too far.  It could go horribly wrong.     I think that is brilliant.  Can we get t-shirts.....can we?..........please.  Check them out  urlLink here   The boxers are my personal favourite.  that is where you need the warning!!! 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       HOW CAN WE JOIN??!     
    
    
</post>

<date>17,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Hello All.  Thank Christ......I am no longer on the west coast.  what an almighty waste of time it was!  Anyway, I'm back in Aberdeen and I look forward to seeing you all (esp the new panda) at 7pm in the Caley Thistle tomorrow.  I'm gonna find a photo to put up too!!     boudy getting some love?  
    
    
</post>

<date>17,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
         A Big Gay Panda.  He's also a sexual deviant who can't handle his Martinis for toffee. 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Greetings from Edmonton!  Just contributing what will no doubt be the first of very few posts.  If I get a chance later I'll stick up some of the pictures from the (ice) hockey game I was at over the weekend. 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       For the benefit of family members struggling with what to get me for Xmas, my Amazon.co.uk Wish List is  urlLink here . 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I have just invited Graham, Cormac and John to join this blog in the hope that it might be fun.  Graham is in Canada just now, so I don't expect to hear from him until he gets back. Cormac is bored on the West Coast of Scotland, so he should have time to contribute some humor. As for John, this site should provide a much needed vent for his intense sexual frustration. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Only just getting time to play around with this wonderful shiny new weblog. Thought I'd try to link an image first, but as I am much too shy to post a picture of myself, here is one of my Girlfriend, Debs:     It would appear that it works :-) 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Experimenting with Blogger. So far, so good. 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Anyone fancy joining Claudia this Christmas?!?!  Happy "Disco" Christmas Everybody!    
    
    
</post>

<date>23,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Dear Friends, I just wanted to bring to your attention that I feel the year of the Cormac is coming to an end  and as such I feel it is appropriate I leave that name behind.  I was going to go with a symbol but all the good ones had gone so....Cormac - has gone.  Long Live "DISCOBOY"!!!  Also I am trying to get my logo sorted, let me know which one is better.     
    
    
</post>

<date>23,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
         "It don't matter if you're black or white..." 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Need to bring balance to The Force?   
    
    
</post>

<date>22,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Scott "Mangler" Morrrison Cormac "Disco Boy" Booth John "Killer" Murray Graham "The Stalker" Watts Stuart "Jack" King Doug "Tubby" McConnell  Check what happens when you type in Guy Hepworth  urlLink here.  
    
    
</post>

<date>19,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>19,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       What the fuck's a stettler?!   
    
    
</post>

<date>16,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>15,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
         Soap or Pebble? Im bored of this now. 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>12,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Hey Everyone,  Gosh this blog is getting big isn't it.  Anyway at the moment it seems to be a site for pictures and JB making fun of scott.  I can't think of anything funny so I am settling for a picture (It's the hurricane that hit the US in September).  Sorry.  
    
    
</post>

<date>12,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Its because before Debs, he got head from this lucky lady:    Oooh that really must've been a toothy blow job. 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Whilst we're on a panda bandwagon...   
    
    
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
         Guy looks smug, but why has he got a small man perched on his shoulder peering over his new lady? Am worried that she looks like my sister.... GUY! 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
         Apparently she's called Cat, but in this photo she's been Pandafied! 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
         This. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I am posting a message only to move that awful picture.  It may be accurate, it may be funny, but it is also sick and that is too much.   urlLink   
    
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Dad: Nothing on TV again son?  JB: No Dad. Oh well, shall we watch Mum's chuff?  Dad: Good idea son.     And there was much rejoicing. 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
          Arf! 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I keep getting this message:    
    
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>08,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       You playing tonight at Dr Drakes? JB 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Not really, but at least I can spell John's name correctly.  And here's an educational tree:     Update: Nice try JB, but changing the spelling now isn't going to help you... 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Q: Why did the baker have smelly hands? A: Because he kneaded a poo.  I thank you. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       For all your stapler needs:   urlLink http://www.virtualstapler.com/   Wow! 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
         John's happy face. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
         I don't know why I find it funny, but I do. 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Tasty!   
    
    
</post>

<date>29,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       AND WE SHALL ALL LOOK LIKE THIS!!!   
    
    
</post>

<date>27,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
          Cormac Booth is a "normal" boy who lives at 77 Acatia Road, but when Cormac eats a flump, he turns into DISCO GEEK! Check those white socks mo-fo! 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>27,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>27,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
          According to JB. Oh yes sir. 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Requires Flash and sound...   urlLink  Enjoy!  
    
    
</post>

<date>26,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The Penguin Game seems to have inspired everyone with lots of furious penguin-bashing going on overnight (ooh-er).  Unfortunately, I have once again, upped the ante:     592.6!! Come On!  First person to smash the 600 barrier gets a Mars bar. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Play the game  urlLink here .  Instructions:  Click mouse to drop penguin. Click mouse again to make the Yeti swing.  Tricky to get the timing right. Post best scores as a comment. 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>16,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>16,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Comments should now be working again.  "Post-It Saturday" was indeed a triumph. Stationery cupboards everywhere will have to re-stock their Post-It supplies in anticipation of the doubtless increase in demand for the sticky buggers and their new found use.  I was very drunk. Felt like crap yesterday.  Congratulations to Cormac for getting a hand job... I hope you got his phone number ;-) 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       For those of you who missed the sight of Mozz in town covered in Post-its, then tough!  You also missed the careful placing of other sticky items on Dirty Bitchaz's trilby hats - AWESOME!   Oh and Muc got a (half) handjob on the dancefloor..... Yes Scott, that's right 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Tomorrow I officially loose the www.mobilepartyunit.co.uk domain name. :-( 'Tis a sad day indeed. Perhaps one day it shall rise from the ashes, perhaps not.  The cryptic message reveal (apoligies for the crappieness):  U Oar Al Gay  "You are all gay"  Since none of you got it, you are all gay.  
    
    
</post>

<date>15,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This is a post from Woody.  He was too feeble to put it on the site himself and so asked me to do it.  Watch Guy as he holidays in sunny California!!!!  Enjoy   urlLink http://sandiegozoo.org/pandas/pandacam/  
    
    
</post>

<date>15,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Absolute thieving bastards, MPU Forever!!!   
    
    
</post>

<date>15,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Unemployed Discoboy strikes again. Anyway, is the answer to the cryptic message "U-bend-oar-al-michael-barrymore".  Roughly translated to You bender, al michael barrymore.  Doesn't make much sense.  Is it a computer joke Scott? 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hi Everyone, Just a quick note to say that, JB,  I am sorry to say that neither of your supposed googlewhacks are correct.  For a two words to be a googlewhack, they both have to be in the dictionary.  Since neither 'sizemic' or 'retract.......cation' (or whatever that first one was) appear of dictionary.com, neither of your pairs are googlewhacks.  A helpful tip, is that is you type in your pair on google.com, once the search is complete, the words will be underlined if they appear in the dictionary (in the blue bar).  Also if the possible googlewhack webpage is a dictionary or word list of some sort, then they are disqualified.    Try harder next time.  Anyway,if you want some examples of real googlewhacks: try 'hippocampi wallpaper' or 'bibliophilic sandwiched'.  I am still unemployed incase any of you wondered. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Mozz Missing once More, it is believed that this is due either to wank or modern jazz.   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       They guy running BlogSpeak, the service that powers the Comments on this blog, is having problems.  To quote his site:  "BlogSpeak is currently down because the bastards that host it decided to suspend my account. I do not know as of yet when this situation will be resolved. If you don't want any JavaScript errors on your pages, take the code off for the time being. Thanks for your patience."  So blame me if your browser acts funny on this page, I can't be arse removing the script yet. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Say what you see!   First person to decipher the message wins 5 points. 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Its not very interesting though.  retractification superfluous - brings up a slang dictionary  sizemic superfluous - brings up a crap website 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
           
    
    
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       You will need:  A printer A piece of paper A pen A scanner A computer  and   urlLink www.fontifier.com   Results are not bad...    Although I appear to write like a 9 year old... 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Didn't turn out as well as I'd hoped, but it wasted 10 mins of a slow afternoon...   Was going to try and make him dance, but didn't. 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hello.  DiscoBoy here!  Just wanted to call John a cumdumpster and show you all a picture of my new kitchen.  What do y'all think?!    
    
    
</post>

<date>05,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Disco Bitch Disco BoothDisco Bitch Disco Booth Disco Bitch Disco Booth   
    
    
</post>

<date>05,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Conclusive Proof that I am in fact Dead.     
    
    
</post>

<date>28,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Here's John proudly showing off his new purchase from Friday night's tupperware party...    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       After lengthy discussions with my learned friend Mf Forsyth we have decided to call all people for what we will term War in Westburn Park.    The time: tomorrow Saturday 12 noon The place: Westburn Park/ Victoria Park(maybe better with more obsticles) The people: everyone on this email list and whoever you guys can get.  The teams: Split between Aberdonians and the rest. NOTE that everyone has to come along as if not then fun will be ruined for all ie Murray - girlfriend, Wabber - rugby, everyone  - any excuse. Special guest apperance for the out of towners: Mr C Cheeky Ogilvie   RSVP    cheers doug P.S. from Cormac - YOU ALL HAVE TO COME!!!!!!!! Booze and XBOX round at JBs after I think. 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It's the Middle East's answer to Gareth Gates!   
    
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Debbie has sent Scott to Qatar. Here's an angry old man who has just said "you love it you slag....   ....Now NAFF OFF!" 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       UPDATED:    
    
    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Variation on the ridiculously popular penguin game posted here a few weeks back.   urlLink Click here . 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>21,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Discuss....    
    
    
</post>

<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Obviously before Robin ate them all. 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I was hoping to have time to create some sort of animation/picture to celebrate Guy's homecoming; the return from the land of "gangstas" and "thugz".  Unfortunately, I'm running out of time (got proper work to do) and my imagination is in a rut.  I got as far as this:     I may get round to making it move at some point, but for now I've decided to use it to launch a caption competition.  What do you think Guy is thinking or saying in the picture? Can you think of any good slogans that could accompany this picture as a poster campaign?  Post suggestions as comments, best entry wins a beer. For the artistic amongst you, you can obtain a bigger version of the file  urlLink here  for editing. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Go on, give him a wave! 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
         (Credit to JB for the idea) 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Look Closely...   urlLink Click Here . 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Check this out.  Plenty of reason's why single folk shouldn't stay in on Valentines Day:   Click Here .  Woody found this, credit should go to him.  Though he was too inept to put it up so he should get slandered too. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Hello, I'm Batman.  When I was just a child, my parents were murdered right in front of my eyes.  I made a solemn vow that day to commit my life to fighting crime.  I've sacrificed my childhood and any efforts toward personal enjoyment.  My nights are spent in deadly combat with everything from common street thugs to grotesque psychopaths.  What little sleep I ever get is usually interupted by horrible nightmares of brutal murder and my waking up soaked in sweat.  I fight a war that can never be won.  I strive toward a goal that can never be reached.  I am haunted.  I am relentless.  I am tortured.  Won't you be my valentine?   
    
    
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Proof:   
    
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The Blog seems a bit quiet just now.  I do not approve.  As a display of my disapproval, meet Angry Gary Coleman:    
    
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       In the morning, when Cormac's new "friend" asked for a shower, he was happy to oblige...  *UPDATE* Due to paranoid, over sensitive type folk (who shall remain nameless), the picture accompanying this post has been removed from the front page and can be found  urlLink here . Apparently it's Not Safe For Work (=NSFW). 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey Everyone.  Just found  urlLink this  on the intenet.  God Bless Sport's Illustrated.  Choose your favourite girl from the bar at the top and post them as a comment.  Sweet Mercy! 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This is the weirdest thing ive ever seen, its safe for viewing at work.  urlLink Click Here .  The site does, however, clarify this below noted site:  urlLink Click Here . 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
          This is what GAJ will look like in the near future if our Spandex and PVC looks don't work out and Gary fails to die in an horrific armchair accident and thus denying Tim his place in the almighty TAJ! Ps Andy's the bird. 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I had initially thought that one of the scariest things I had experienced was Toni Baxer sticking needles into my abdomin and eyes before sawing my foot off..... or was that a dream.... or was that a film...... anyway but now its definitely Ashley growling "you wan pie?"  URGH! sends a shudder down my spine as if Lesley Fraser had licked me urgh.  No thank you very much i do not wan pie. 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       You wan pie?   urlLink Weebl & Bob   Watch them from the very start...hours of humour... 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       WAZZ AND MAZZ MAKE JAP DVD NIGHT!!!! Like this paper plate, they are proud to promote literacy.   
    
    
</post>

<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       WAZ AND MAZZ TURNED DOWN DVDS FOR TACOS AND SEX!!!! Like this dog, they are humiliated.   
    
    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Following Tuesday's fiasco that was my guitar playing, John and I have decided to put in a bit more effort for next week.  Not only will I be writing the chord sequences in BIGGER WRITING so I can read them, I may actually practice the songs in advance.  I think the "3 song" approach will work best; 2 of John's own and a cover song.  But frankly we're too lazy to pick a song to cover ourselves, instead we are giving you (yes, you) the opportunity to pick "A Song for Muzz and Mozz".  Suggestions should be posted as comments. The winner will be picked by JB and myself unless there is an overwhelming majority for a particular song.  Good luck, and get voting! 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
        /points to tag line and cries quietly. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
          I think it's fair to say that last night's performance was "distinctive". My fingers are killing me this morning. Ouch.  
    
    
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Courtesy of the  urlLink bbc .  Some notable omissions include: Cunted Pissed Shitfaced Wankered Rat Arsed  Personal Favourites: Boogaloo Dot Cottoned Locked out of your mind Monkey-full Nicely irrigated with horizontal lubricant Saying hello to Mr Armitage Shedded [as in "My shed has collapsed taking most of the fence with it"] 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It was my first band practice in >5 years last night, and I finally managed to conquer the basics:    Muzz and Mozz - Back Together Tour, begins tonight @ Dr Drakes open mic night, after 10pm. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ever wondered which horrible affliction you would be?  Wonder no more! Find the answer  urlLink here . 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
         What is this strange chicken theme? 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>19,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
          Also, check out this:  urlLink http://www.nbpl.net/   It's not even a joke.  the use of beer and pong at parties has only just begun my friends.  But can we please do it at someone elses next time.  Guy has a nice long table..... 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Sorry it's a day late. 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
          Shit Yeah.  Turn up any time after 7.30pm 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Apparently we are playing  urlLink this  at Cormac's on Friday, so get practicing! I have also recently purchsed  urlLink this  XBox game complete with 2 dance mats. I'm sure that once we've had a few drinks, we will all be dancing like fools! 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Click Here . 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Nest of Death provide the support.   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Under construction:  urlLink www.johnsongs.co.uk  
    
    
</post>

<date>13,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink  Click here  Short video (30 secs), sound required. Broadband recommended 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
         ... with his "Back to the Fuschia" 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Seamless!!!    
    
    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
          come back here with my tankard!!! 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       come on you slags 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
          No but it is fucking scary.  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Just tried to go to www.johnsongs.co.uk and it simply didn't come up! What does it mean?!?!? Does someone already have it?!?!? Is it under construction by some other John?!?!? Will boudy be a panda in the morning?!?!? Will boozy be slapping it to pornos?!?!? Will wazz be having a celebratary wank?!?!? AGGGHHHH I Don't know! 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Thanks for supporting me last night, it was well appreciated and my sincerest apologies for making you all listen to that other bloke drone on before me. Big Up the German contingent!   
    
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I met Sven Goran Eriksson yesterday at Manchester airport. Shook his hand and took his picture. Unfortunately I only had my mobile phone camera with me, so the quality isn't great.      
    
    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Front row seats to a Flyers game: $145  Replica hockey jersey: $225  beer and hot dogs: $22  Picture of you and your friend acting like a couple of FAGS in Sports Illustrated: PRICELESS! 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
            It would appear Captain America is a wanker. 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Pointless, but she does jiggle. 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well in case any of you were wondering when I (Cormac the Skald???) was going to snuff it...read on to find out more about me!   urlLink http://sunsite.berkeley.edu/OMACL/Cormac  
    
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink http://www.uua.org/uucf/jmur-con.htm   bizarre 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
         It's Beadle Time!  Sure has been quiet round here lately. 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       SEAMLESS!!!    
    
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
          Sorry to be random, just wanted to get that stupid fucking chicken picture off the top of the site. 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Friday night, just before the duck flew South:   
    
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Looks like JB, Doug & Gary were snapped by the Belmont Street photographers on Friday night.  Check out the Belmont Street  urlLink website , look under the section "what did you do?", dated Friday 21st May, the boys were caught in the Wild Boar! 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So, all you folks with digital cameras... where are the pictures from Friday, eh? 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This is a picture of the very rare "Nemesis Gibbon".  Notice how it wears the Nemesis t-shirt, even though gibbons aren't actually allowed on the ride.    
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       My legs are in agony!   I hate fishing. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Is it just me, or does this donkey look a bit smug?   
    
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         I know it's a bit crap, but I had some work to do, anyway I think the message is the same.  Scott is a giant hom.  Let's see how long it is before he strops and takes it off!!! 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
          What does everyone think of Cormac's new apartment? He is leaving soon and I thought some of you might like to be able to find out a little bit about what he is doing and be able to keep track of him once he is gone.  Check it out  urlLink here  and  urlLink here   
    
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Following a short break from the lime-light, John Murray is back!     The details: The Belmont Cinema Bar Belmont Street Aberdeen  The show should be starting around 9pm. Arrive early to drink beer.  
    
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
          What does everyone think of my new apartment? I'm leaving soon and I thought some of you might like to be able to find out a little bit about what I am doing and be able to track where I am once I'm gone.  Check it out  urlLink here  and  urlLink here  
    
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Blogger have just overhauled their system and as a result, my blog now looks shiny and new!  New features include the new comment posting system! 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       JB rated very highly on the Mong-o-meter!    
    
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       An old one, but a good one...    
    
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
          Beckham Penalty!    
    
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Go on, you know you want to!   
    
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Have you seen this man? Last reported skulking around the Manchester area. Carol Vorderman suspects she has a stalker.    
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hello everyone, I'm back from my short break in sunny Manchester!  I can confirm that I did in fact go on every major ride at Alton Towers and I have pictures to prove it!  Although, after 10 years of torment, I have to say that the Nemesis was a bit disappointing. Air is good, but Oblivion was the best.  Managed to get sun-burnt again.  Leeds seemed to be a bit of a sh*t-hole, one big building site.  Here is a picture of me and Debbie with our new friends:    
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Imagine my surprise as my tv switched itself on and emanted an other worldly glow....   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Clicky clicky on the radio buttons to see the effect...        Before...     After...    
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm pretty sure I emailed everyone, but on the off chance I forgot, here's the poster for the Wazzamatazz Air Guitar Birthday Piss Up:   urlLink    Click to bigify.  Everything kicks off on Saturday afternoon...  EDIT: Big version of the picture also available at  urlLink www.grahamwatts.net . 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ....and there were shouts of joy.   I'm off, thought this photo was appropriate.  Let me know how you all are, like I say I dunno how easy it is going to be for me to stay in touch, but I'll do my best.  I'll miss you all very much.  Look after yourselves and I'll see you sometime soon.  Meanwhile feel free to view my minimal progress on the  urlLink blog  and the " urlLink Voyage of the Odyssey " webpage.  This is The Booth, signing off. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         He's not been working late in the Deen at all!     He's opening a Tokyo TV Dining Facility!     AND HE NEVER TOLD US!     Dick!  
    
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hello boys and girls,  I am now slightly unbeleivably in Tanzania. When I went on holiday with my family a few weeks ago I had a rough idea that I would stay if i could find anything worthwhile to do, but i sincerely didnt think I'd find it, but i kind of did albeit in a terribly unpaid fashion. Nevertheless the job is cool, and the people/landscape/food is brilliant.  So there we go, I stayed they went. If all goes well I'll be back in Spetember so its not a proper good bye a la Cormac. Feel sorry for not updating you all on things before I went and milking the departure for at least a piss up but I didnt really know i'd stay. In fact Revolution had me shifted on for work all this and last week. Whoops. :P  Anyway hope you are all doing well I'll start sending out some proper emails the next time I have a large task to do at work. In case you dont know my email is johnprimrose (at) hotmail.com and as scott or cormac could tell you I'm always on MSN.  Take it easy  John  Look at this if you havent already  urlLink www.rockpapersaddam.com  
    
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       According to Eurogamer.net, Microsoft has officially  urlLink announced  the UK release date for Halo 2 on the XBox as being November the 11th 2004. 2 days later than expected and 2 days after the Americans. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Great news from  urlLink Slashdot!  The Monty Python & The Holy Grail musical has been confirmed along with some of the casting! Tim Curry will play Arthur, King of the Britans and David Hyde Pierce (Niles from Frasier) is to play Sir Robin.  More info  urlLink here .  And there was much rejoicing.... . . . . . . ....(yaaaaaaaay) 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I knew it...    
    
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Just testing mailing to the blog from my phone. I hope it works. 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Click to big it.  Mairi,  urlLink here  is one of the piccies taken with my new phone for you to get an idea of it's capabilities. I think you'll agree, despite the good picture quality, Graham still looks like a smug git. 
    
    
</post>


</Blog>