<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
          urlLink http://edition.cnn.com/2004/SHOWBIZ/Music/06/01/britney.china.ap/index.html   No, really. This is what American women wear when they need to go to the store for some milk. Seriously. The French wear even less. I wouldn't lie to you. Here's a protest sign.  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         "The Book of Bunny Suicides: Little Fluffy Rabbits Who Just Don't Want to Live Any More" by Andy Riley (Plume)      Comedic scribe Riley ("Robbie the Reindeer," "Smack the Pony," and the forthcoming Disney feature "Gnomeo and Juliet") has put together a delightful illustrated volume of creative self-destruction in the tradition of Jules Feiffer's "Sick, Sick, Sick." See the bunny make optimal self-negating use of helicopter rotors, jet turbines, windmill blades, fat guys in chairs, falling stalactites, common household toasters, and magnets strategically placed in front of cutlery stores. For the inner sadist in everyone.
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i finally saw  being john malkovich  last night. very, very weird, but very, very good.  HIGHLY RECOMMENDED!      what movie should i see next? 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink http://edition.cnn.com/2004/US/05/30/saddam.gun.reut/index.html   The magazine quoted a visitor who had been shown the gun, which is kept in a small study off the Oval Office where Bush displays memorabilia. It is the same room where former President Clinton had some of his encounters with former intern Monica Lewinsky.   I hope Koizumi visits soon. There's a blowjob/soapland/"She caught my gun in her mouth" joke in there somewhere and my non-Japanese ass can't find it.  Also, thank you CNN. The story would just not have been complete without that last line. No, really, it had to go there. It completes the piece....  ...jackasses.  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink rui  says that  urlLink lindsay lohan  won the feud.  urlLink hilary duff  has therefore been downgraded to feuding with  urlLink avril lavigne , who finally gave up trying to feud with  urlLink britney spears  b/c  urlLink britney  was so busy being rich and successful that she didn't even notice. no one is feuding with  urlLink christina aguilera  b/c researchers still haven't proven conclusively that you can't catch VD from feuding. 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink un-be-lievable!  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Currently our older youth are awash in a culture that promotes evil, occultism, lust and power for its own sake. The magick world-view is all around them. It is promoted in Television, movies and music and increasingly on the internet. Witchcraft on the internet is often coupled with pornography. Ask any teenager to open the latest anime&rsquo; site such as the Japanese version of Dragon Ball Z and one can find EVERY kind of pornographic material. Teens are readily playing the older game of Dungeons and Dragons and Magic the Gathering. Think about it. We now have several major TV shows where the heroes are witches, vampires, and movies where the good guys do supernatural feats. In our insecure family structure of today, much trauma has been handed to our children. Witchcraft and practices of the occult promise them the ability to control their lives, when their lives are spinning out of control. People always seek to ease the trauma they are in, and fairy godmothers are not at all what they seem to be!
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i saw an affront to mankind at best buy.  pet sounds  remixed in 5.1 surround sound. sigh.     they released a stereo version a while ago, which was mediocre. for instance, they used some of the wrong tapes (e.g., brian sings the bridge on "wouldn't it be nice" instead of mike, and i think one of the verses has the couplets in the wrong order). the original was in mono, partially b/c brian wilson was deaf in one ear. the stereo remixes were supposedly approved by brian, but he's been an occasionally-obese mentally-ill cheesebrained acid casualty since 1966. on the liner notes for the  friends / 20-20  double CD, he was even mixing up some of the songs.  some days i just want to go buy a bunch of LPs and an  urlLink old turntable with a crank  ("crank up the music" anyone?) and go live in a cave. 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
          Unrelated: The goonmeet did not go as planned. The trip to SeaLife Park, however, did. We're planning a trip to "Hot Stupid Chick/Dude Beach" for next weekend... aka "Sandy Beach". We assume all the dumb hotties go there because they think "Oh, this must be the beach with sand. I don't think I like the other kind....".  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       saw  the day after tomorrow . it was entertaining. :) the dick cheney character alone was worth the price of admission! 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       One teaser picture before I actually make a page with all of the interesting or pretty pictures from Mom's visit. It's probably interesting, and DEFINITELY not pretty.      Off to a goonmeet to goon around! 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Crazy.jpg  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       as i was leaving work, i noticed this car fishtailing out of the parking lot. upon further examination, i realized it was an unmarked police car. huh. 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       hollywood sure loves to destroy the capitol records building!      here's a shot from further back:     if that's downtown LA in the background, does that mean the twister is going north on vine? i think it does... 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       major decisions made on  urlLink less-than-credible sources ?! que surprise! 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        The AP poll found that six in 10 who qualify as overweight under government standards say they are at a healthy weight. Only a quarter of those who are obese consider themselves very overweight, according to the poll conducted for the AP by Ipsos-Public Affairs.
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ugh. remember cardinal bernard law from boston? the one responsible for all those molestation coverups?  urlLink he's got a big fancy new vatican job . "It's pretty offensive for most Catholics, and the timing couldn't be worse," said David Gibson, author of   urlLink The Coming Catholic Church   (Harper San Francisco, 2003). "They're just cleaning up the mess in Boston and closing parishes, and he's getting the ultimate golden parachute. He's getting a beautiful apartment in Rome in one of the four major basilicas in Christendom."
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       can you say " urlLink ethics violation " ?  someone wrote this to  urlLink eric alterman  (a blogger for msnbc): Yesterday, prior to watching the Sox get vivisected by Oakland at Fenway last night, I was listening to The Radio Factor on my way home from work.  Now, I've followed Bill O'Reilly's career since he was just a baby megalomaniac on Boston TV.  It would not now surprise me in the least if, one night on TV, right there during The Memo, O'Reilly declared himself to be the Grand Duchess Anastasia.  So, I was not entirely shocked to hear him declare to a caller that he'd "destroyed" three institutions: Jesse Jackson's political operation, the ACLU, and rap music.
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       does anyone in this administration talk to anyone else before  urlLink blindly announcing things ? Some allies of the Department of Homeland Security within the Bush administration and members of Congress criticized Attorney General John D. Ashcroft yesterday for issuing terrorist threat warnings at a news conference on Wednesday, contending he failed to coordinate the information with the White House and with Homeland Security, which has the job of releasing threat warnings.
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
           clara : ruiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiii  clara : go get me a burrito!  clara : i'm tired! and hungry!  clara : i want a burrito!  clara : i want chicken and black beans and greeen salsa and sour cream and lettuce  rui : heehee, i thought you wrote "go get me a bimbo!" at first!  clara : :)
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       looks like  urlLink the UK needs  one of those grants to combat goth culture! (and no,  urlLink i didn't make the grant up ) i hear that rui wanted to go into politics until she found out that "government pork" was just an idiom.   urlLink LEARN TO DEFEAT THE STORIES YOU TELL YOURSELF THAT HOLD YOU BACK! BLARG! BLARG!  sorry. i think i slept on my brain wrong last night. we should write a pseudopsychiatry book like that. "learn to defeat the hamsters that crawl in your ear while you sleep and nibble on your brain to turn you into an insane recluse who survives on whatever lizards and beetles crawl into your death valley cave while you sit in the shadows and sing 'dixie' all day long" 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       so does anyone have big memorial day wknd plans? i intend to see  saved  and  the day after tomorrow . i saw a bad review of  saved  somewhere, which is disappointing. supposedly, in focus groups, people who had gone to catholic skool loved it.  the day after tomorrow  is " urlLink retro cool ," whatever that means. and the guy who starred in  bubble boy  and the freaky bunny movie ( donnie darko ) is in it.  apparently the reaction of both  urlLink iraqis  and the  urlLink pentagon  to bush's announcement that abu ghraib would be razed was "WTF?"   urlLink falling cloud cover could explain global warming . i wish we could get some falling cloud cover in seattle. it's fucking raining again. and it's supposed to rain all fucking weekend. ugh. i really, really hate the damn rain. the scary/hilarious thing (seattle lie #1) is that people here insist it doesn't really rain all that much. (seattle lie #2 is that the nine months of miserable depressing rain is made up for by the the summers.) meanwhile, it's 70&deg;F and partly cloudy in pasadena, and it'll be in the 80s and mostly sunny next week.   it must suck to be the BBC's  urlLink stock photo of a fatass .  ooh!  urlLink john kerry used to run a cookie shop !  here's  urlLink how to tell if you're rich .   if you want to find out how stressed you are,  urlLink fortune magazine has a quiz !  and speaking of little things that cause stress, how 'bout some  urlLink active noise reduction  to shut up your computer's fan?  and speaking of computers, the NYT just discovered that  urlLink video games based on movies tend to suck . also, i wish i had a filter on my internet that would black out any mention of "the sims."  and speaking of 21st century filtering technology, RCA has designed a DVD player that  urlLink skips all the good parts of a movie . i propose we use this technology in reverse to cut out the dull filler between the violence and the cursing and the NWS. 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink article   hey, gray and bunny, don't forget your  urlLink traveling papers  if you want to use the T. 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       the FBI is interviewing prominent neocons to find out who gave ahmed chalabi the classified information he slipped to iran.   oh, an i saw  shrek 2 . it was great! 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       There's a baseball team in Japan called the " urlLink Nippon Ham Fighters !"  Except I think the 'Ham' part is the city, the team isn't the 'Ham Fighters.'    Gossip around the courthouse is that Lisa Frank lives in Tucson, and she's a huge bitch!  She's very litigious.  How can a woman who designs techni-color detritus for little girls be so horrid?!  ;)       Brian just got Starfox Adventures.  It's OK, but one of the characters has anthropomorphic boobs that are really disturbing.  Damn furries.      
    
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink http://msnbc.msn.com/id/5069848/site/newsweek/   and the candor and accuracy of maj. gen. geoffrey miller's testimony before the senate armed services committee is  urlLink in question ...   urlLink http://www.msnbc.msn.com/id/4733368/site/newsweek/  Bush, for his part, has to wake up to reality. To borrow a phrase from conservative columnist Pat Buchanan, the president has to quit &#8220;succumbing to the whispers of neocon tempters about Churchillian immortality&#8221; and look at the options actually in front of him. If he wants the help of the rest of the wide world, he&rsquo;s got to quit coddling his cozy little circle of  friends. There can be no guarantees for favored companies like Halliburton and the American oil interests. And if we want peace with Iraq&rsquo;s neighbors, especially Iran and Syria, we&rsquo;d be wise to quit threatening them, and prudent to give up the notion we&rsquo;ll be creating major military bases right on their borders. Finally, Bush, and Kerry, too, had better realize that Iraq is not going to be a beacon of democracy in the region anytime soon. It&rsquo;s enough just to keep it from becoming a black hole. So let the Iraqis choose who they will as leaders, and live with it
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
           clara :  urlLink http://sargentwelch.com/product.asp?pn=WL430-27_EA   clara : the comparative eye set is only $12, and much freakier!  clara : if i were a manager, i'd get the eye kit and put the jars on my shelf, and amke a sign saying "i've got my eye on you!"  connie : you'll be a manager one day  connie : you'll have the eyes  clara : hehe  clara : when you start your cult, you should have a room of animal eyes preserved in jars. that can be the room taht you meet people in.  connie : that would be awesome, along with my throne and strange cult attire, and weird spastic lighting, it's enough to get anyone to sign over their life savings
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink yay!  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       "oh, my.. what's this..? good lord! i  do  have a  urlLink backbone  after all!"   urlLink here's some tips  for how gray can deal with his 9 cursin'-like-sailors babies. the suggestion for teenagers is to make them contribute a dollar every time they curse, and to further punish them by spending the money on a family activity that they are required to participate in (although, strangely, the article seems to consider the family activity to be a *reward*). and as if you all need another reason not to reproduce, apparently it's quite common for small children to have biting problems. as in, they bite you. human wormbabies are revolting in every respect!  and possibly  urlLink all the dinosaurs died at once ! There's no question over whether an asteroid hit. The roughly 6-mile-wide (10-kilometer) space rock carved out the Chicxulub crater off Mexico's Yucatan Peninsula. Previous work uncovered a global layer of material that had melted and then hardened when the impact vaporized terrestrial rock. Robertson and his colleagues argue that superheated stuff was blasted from the crater into a suborbital path around Earth, generating a "heat pulse" upon re-entry.   "The kinetic energy of the ejected matter would have dissipated as heat in the upper atmosphere during re-entry, enough heat to make the normally blue sky turn red-hot for hours," Robertson said.  All unprotected creatures were "baked by the equivalent of a global oven set on broil."
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I get the feeling that if I let another day go by without posting this image:  That Rui, Clara, and Gray will capture me and charge me with "Witholding Ham", an offense punishable by Sadie snu snu.   Create your own Bush campaign banner:   urlLink    If only there was some way to add  urlLink this guy  running along the banner...  Oh well. Have fun!  Here's a sneak peek at the goldmine:  http://128.121.115.83/something/blingrice.gif http://paintedover.com/uploads/2/cheney2.gif http://paintedover.com/uploads/2/chap_bush.png 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Check out the mutatomouse...ain't it cute, ain't it so cute for mutant soup?  urlLink mutatomice.bmp  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       john ashcroft says there is a 'credible' al-qaida threat to the US in the next few months. sources say that in a week, the threat will be identified as john kerry, who will then be shipped to a secret military prison on the international space station, where geneva conventions clearly do not apply.    urlLink avril thinks she's brilliant. kelly osbourne lectures on the evils of drugs.  blah blah blah.   people may be able to get  urlLink face transplants  soon! this surgery is only intended for people who are severely disfigured (for instance, those monkey-faced twins who played "michelle" on  full house ).  and speaking of people and lower primates, here's an article on  urlLink human DNA vs. chimp DNA .  last night, i dreamed i got a new keyboard for my computer (my current one has wiring problems due to being dropped a lot, so maybe that's why it was on my mind). anyhow, this keyboard was the most ridiculously designed thing EVAR. it had way too many additional buttons, and they wanted themto be customizable, so you had to put the appropriate sticker ("my documents" or "my music" or "my bacon") on the button you wanted. the stickers didn't stick very well. then, the buttons were secured by velcro in case you changed your mind in the future. also, it was about 2x as big as a normal keyboard. i highly recommend that you *don't* purchase this model. in the real world, i'm considering going wireless, but (a) i don't really want to be changing batteries all the time, and (b) it's a recipe for disaster -- i'll take the mouse with me when i answer the phone, and i'll set it somewhere and i won't find it for months. "how the hell did *this* end up in the freezer?!"  here's the  urlLink winner  of  the swan . rui's trying to get one of the networks interested in her reality show idea. it's called  last ham standing . various people compete to see who can go from glam to ham the fastest without ending up in the hospital. in addition to junk food and sedentary activities, the show will provide plastic surgery to worsen contestants' looks, dental reconstruction to british-ify their teeth, and counseling to destroy any self-esteem the person might have.  and i'm glad the media is finally acknowledging  urlLink things like this . and  urlLink this .   ugh. i'm hungry, but i have a meeting in a few minutes so i can't go get food. and there's another meeting after that. it'll be 3PM before i can assuage my hunger! 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
           
    
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       crips and bloods in newark, NJ, have declared a  urlLink truce . you may all now commence trying to remember how to make the "blood" gang sign. 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       a 37yo arkansas woman  urlLink just had her 15 th  kid . she started when she was 21.      Their children include two sets of twins, and the parents have stuck to the letter &#8220;J&#8221; for their names. There is Joshua, 16; Jana and John-David, 14; Jill, 13; Jessa, 11; Jinger, 10; Joseph, 9; Josiah, 7; Joy-Anna, 6; Jeremiah and Jedidiah, 5; Jason, 4; James, 2; and Justin, 1.
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink http://www.pasadenastarnews.com/Stories/0,1413,206%257E22097%257E2162184,00.html?search=filter   From Jess... well, and this Techer who is here in Hawaii. 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       who would have guessed that a  urlLink clown named "spanky"  might be a creep?  and in case you forgot:  urlLink we're all gonna die .  and  urlLink blair and bush need to get their stories straight . 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       NPR is committing a lot of time to campaign ads this year, including a shout out to Factcheck.org. You can listen to the article at  urlLink http://www.npr.org/features/feature.php?wfId=1905069   Oh, and I stubbed my toe so hard it's bleeding. 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       "this is  TOTALLY  embarassing. remember how i completely dissed you last year?  urlLink well... "  next friday:  The Dark Side of Harry Potter   Written by: Natalia Olenicoff    The Prisoner of Azkaban reveals darker troubles for Potter    The latest Harry Potter film, set to hit the big screen on June 4th, is said to have a refreshingly different feel to it than the first two films. Critics have commended the new film for delving into the darker side of the young wizard&rsquo;s story. Unlike the first two films, which entertained the audience with fantastical Disney-looking sets and characters, The Prisoner of Azkaban is set predominantly in a dark, rainy world, where Potter seeks out his parents&rsquo; alleged murderer who has escaped from the prison. In this film, Potter&rsquo;s character exhibits more of his inner turmoil over his parents&rsquo; death and his predestined role in wizardry.   Fans of the first two films should not be disappointed by the series&rsquo; darker third installment, though. Director Alfonso Cuaron whipped up another extraordinary adventure film with enough magic to make even the most committed realist wish for a magic wand. 
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i got the new alanis morissette cd. i've heard nothing but good things (apparently the record label guys are barely restraining themselves from doing an insane happy dance). i also got the new loretta lynn cd that jack white (from the white stripes) produced and arranged. am i the only person who thinks jack white looks like beetlejuice? anyhow, old guard country is back and finding it has more in common with indie rock than new country.  part of the first alanis track just reminded me of something from  the downward spiral . weird. the record's not bad so far.   disney just can't win: Conservatives threatened to boycott the Mouse House last year when it was revealed that the movie company's subsidiary Miramax was funding the Bush-bashing film, "Fahrenheit 9/11."  Now that Disney is refusing to let Miramax distribute the Palm D'or winning flick, liberals are organizing a boycott against it.   "You are censoring one of the most important filmmakers in America," reads a petition being circulated by Democrats.com and signed by more than 20,000 people. "This is unacceptable in a democracy. As consumers, we are not powerless. We will protest with our wallets - by boycotting Disney products until you agree to distribute Fahrenheit 9/11."
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink american bandstand is coming back ! brian wilson is going to release SMiLE! wilson phillips has a new record! I'M SO CONFUSED!!!   oh, and the hearsts (think william randolph hearst, hearst castle, patty hearst) are trying to make a  urlLink conservation deal with the state  for their 82,000 acres of land (along 18 miles of the PCH) near san simeon. 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       it's much later than i thought it was. i expected it to be around 4pm, and i looked down and it was 6pm.   i rented  freaky friday  this wknd b/c someone told me it was entertaining. it was entertaining, but i spent the whole movie wishing someone had waxed off jamie lee curtis's moustache. i liked the part where after the body switch, the teen-in-mom's-body looked in the mirror and screamed "oh my god! i'm like the cryptkeeper!"  (suspension-of-disbelief question: would a ~15yo nowadays actually know who  urlLink the cryptkeeper  is?)  oh, and i forgot to mention in my upcoming-movies paragraph of my earlier post that the weather destructo movie (sorry, can't remember the title) is coming out memorial day wknd. bunny reminded me. you should all go see it. 'cause disaster movies rock!  (i'm sure it can't top  10.5  though! they  used nukes to seal the san andreas fault ! and CA was split open from santa monica to barstow! barstow!!!)   god, i'm so exhausted today. i'm tired, rui's bloated, i think gray's in a coma from too much cake and "baldur's gate," and jamal? jamal found the beach with the hot girls. THE FATES ARE REVERSING THEIR COURSE! keelhaul the starboard! avast to port! raise the boom and load the scurvy dogs into the cannons! yaar!  oh, remember that oregon lawyer arrested for involvement in the madrid bombings? "teehee," the FBI giggles girlishly, " urlLink it wasn't his fingerprint at all ! we are, like,  SO  embarassed!" the pentagon refused to comment, since it was late to its pedicure and it has a big date with whoever is the new chalabi tonight.  here's where to live if you want to live in one of the  urlLink best places in america . 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       an  urlLink interview with billy corgan  on the state of rock today.  Is it impossible for a great icon to come along again?  What we&rsquo;re going to see now is a different archetype rise up. It&rsquo;s not going to be the Elvis archetype; it&rsquo;s going to be something we can&rsquo;t even imagine. It&rsquo;s going to be someone, maybe, who&rsquo;s more spiritual, somebody who doesn&rsquo;t want anything to do with corporate industry. Somebody who&rsquo;s an Internet star. Some kid who makes tapes in his bedroom and says, "F---the world. This is my version of it." And then people will latch on. All the music factories in the world can&rsquo;t manufacture that kid. To me, Elvis was the innovator. We&rsquo;ve basically just been watering down Elvis. We&rsquo;ve lost the desire to support individuals. In the early &rsquo;90s, you had six or seven top people&#8212;Courtney [Love], Trent Reznor, Soundgarden, Alice in Chains. We all got assassinated because we didn&rsquo;t live up to some sort of idealism that never existed: a perfectionism of rock and roll attitude mixed with drug addiction. So what replaced us? Kids who looked the part, acted the part, but they weren&rsquo;t saying the same things. They&rsquo;ve been successful, so why would the next generation go back to what we used to do? 
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       in 1998, crayola added a crayon color called "beaver." discuss in the comments.  clara : in 1998, they added a color called "beaver"  j.ro : ......okay, we'll talk more about that when you get home  j.ro : I mean, there's no way I can be WS with a straight line like that.
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
           Clara : my protozit never turned into a zit  Bunny : gray needs a colon redirection  Clara : it's just a bump under my skin  Bunny : it faded away?  Bunny : my big forehead zits also disappeared  Bunny : without really erupting  Clara : it never really lookd like anything, i could just feel it lurking under the skin  Bunny : it was a roundworm!  Clara : could be!  Bunny : or better yet, a tapeworm larva  Clara : it will burrow into my eyeball and see all that i see and know all that i know!  Clara : then it will burrow into my brain and run my life  Clara : i'll just be along for the ride  Bunny : won't that be great?   Bunny : i want to be the host of a superintelligent tapeworm larva  Clara : you'd better be jealous!  Clara : me and my larva are so cool!  Clara : we're gonna have a hit sitcom called "me and my larva"  Clara : and a broadway musical!  Clara : a circus act!  Clara : and you'll be all larva-free!  Bunny : we can replace the today show!  Bunny : larva-free! nooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo  Bunny : give me back my larva
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       someone at work brought in cookies. i tried one. they taste like nothing! it's so weird!  highly not recommended!  maybe they're sugar-free low-carb diet cookies designed for ascetics. yeesh. there's also some scary-looking licorice. it looks like a tube of licorice filled with butter, and given the unpleasant cookie experience, i'm not going to risk it. yecch. 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink this is the scariest book excerpt i've ever read . seriously, it's terrifying. stephen king should read it and take notes.  rui's favorite diva is crying:  Jessica's Waterworks  Jessica Simpson has taken some time out from her non-stop stumping duties (her latest moneymaking gig: pitching breath mints with little sis Ashlee) to come clean about why she was recently spied crying outside a Los Angeles hotspot. "I did have a run-in with a bouncer at an LA nightclub because he was doing something that wasn't very nice to somebody who was in my entourage," Mrs. Nick Lachey tells Access Hollywood. Jessica has an entourage? Jessica knows the word "entourage"? "I was bawling," the dizzy, overexposed "Newlyweds" hottie admits. "He made me cry and Nick came to console me ... He was a big man. He scared me."
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink article  Witnesses said Jewel went on a tirade of insults from poking fun at fat people to others with no teeth. At one point, she asked the audience to yell requests and then told them to "shut the hell up."   "I saw her live in Boston and it was the greatest show I&rsquo;ve ever been to," Dion said. "I don&rsquo;t know if she was having a nervous breakdown or what. She told everyone to stop looking at her teeth and look at her breasts."   Jewel was on stage for about an hour and played only four to five songs. Halfway through the show, Dion said Jewel began to talk about Zoloft and Paxil for about 10 minutes.   "She said she saw a better audience at a barroom brawl and that all drinkers and smokers were sinners."    Dion said Jewel came out for an encore, but instead of singing one of her hit songs, she yodeled for a minute and then left the stage. 
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       the new  harry potter  movie is supposed to  urlLink actually be GOOD . i found the last two to be kind of dull. this one has a new director. i think it's the guy who did  y tu mama tambien , which i never actually saw.  The first scene of  Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban  removes any doubt that the famous child wizard is growing up fast. The camera glides toward a light pulsing in the night, then through an open bedroom window, where Harry is hiding under his covers, playing with his wand and hoping to God he doesn't get caught. Wait a minute.
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       from  urlLink news of the weird : Although 50 countries (including Japan) have now banned American beef because of inadequate mad-cow controls, the U.S. Department of Agriculture not only has declined to order widespread testing but has even prohibited one farm, Creekstone (Campbellsburg, Ky.), from voluntarily testing. USDA said such conscientious testing would imply that America's entire 35 million yearly slaughters should be tested (which the industry says is too expensive, even though Japan requires universal testing for its beef). USDA said it aims to test only 40,000 cows, up from 20,000 for the last two years (although it has been unable for nine months now to document those tests in response to a Freedom of Information Act request by United Press International). [New York Times, 4-10-04; United Press International, 12-24-03]
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ...is over at  urlLink jamal.sexhamster.com  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i'm thinking of getting a new computer desk with more drawers and such. any suggestions where to look to find one that's not too pricy? i'd like several drawers, and a place underneath it for my subwoofer.   here's the stupidest one i've ever seen:     i mean, the basic design of the desk is fine, and stupidity-free. my objection is the inexplicable shower curtain thing.. 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    
    
    
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       so, i was sitting at my desk working diligently, and my boss poked his head in, and said "hey, wanna go to a mariner's game?" so i got to go to a baseball game! they lost. badly. they have a nice stadium though!     
    
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink http://www.thesun.co.uk/article/0,,2-2004232453,00.html  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink no one's sure what the problem was, but everyone's leaning towards blaming rui...  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink IMG_7502.JPG   I'll put more pix up later... and I'll tell you about the Pad Thai with a side of white rice and fresh uncomfortable.  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink internet internet internet  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       vincent gallo's  urlLink  brown bunny   
    
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i managed to get a good 9 hours last night! and i had a wacky dream. first, i had a houseguest coming to stay with me who was really really finicky. like, the A/C (which i don't have) had to be off, every window in the apartment had to be closed, and anything that made noise in the night (eg, the refrigerator) had to be unplugged, 'cause he was so picky about sleep. then, there was a part where i was walking down the street with my parents, but i've forgotten what happened there. then i was at a fancy restaurant. and then i was at a mexican grocery store, and i could speak spanish, and the girl at the door let me have a free container of godzilla themed chorizo. and then i woke up.  the advanced celebrity skinniness research institute has found a new technique for making the olsen twins look  even skinnier ! stand 'em next to jack osbourne! note the protruding shoulder blade of the twin on the left:      here's an entertaining excerpt from the  urlLink toothpaste for dinner  guy's latest mass mailing: it is friday and that means that, at nine o'clock in the morning, most  of you are already at work slacking off. it's okay. one of my favorite things to do used to be to make sculptures out of liquid paper by painting over a bump over and over until it built into a statue an inch high or so. but i quit when too many statues got inadvertently lost or broken, shuffled under some papers or knocked over by a coffee mug. too many broken dreams, too many smashed-up fantasies to keep going!  before i started to conserve my "free time at work" for answering emails and drawing pictures, i used to produce great anthropomorphic animal charts for any assignment for which i was required to make a chart. the weirdest part about work was that nobody ever said anything about it. here i was, drawing faces and legs on pie charts, and i guess people thought i was just some kind of misguided clip-art user and they felt kind of embarrassed. NOBODY EVER SAID ANYTHING ABOUT IT. that is kind of oppressive, i think it is why i stopped doing it. you would think that reasonable adults would see some data surrounded by illustrations which clearly reference the tone and manner of childrens' books, and see that my powerpoint illustration was not only absurd but a little bit insulting to everyone who read it.
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Stop the Presses Again : Thirty-seven years after its anticipated release, an all-new studio recording of SMiLE&#8212;often referred to as the most famous unreleased album in history&#8212;will be made available worldwide by Nonesuch Records on September 28, 2004.  SMiLE will be produced by Brian Wilson and will feature the ten-member band that has supported him on tour over the past five years, augmented by The Stockholm Strings and Horns.
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink $2.4trillion?!  Asked what might make them change their minds [about their refusal to vote for the $2.4trillion budget], one of the moderates, Sen. John McCain, R-Arizona, said, "Some of us could get killed in tragic accidents."
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink coffee. cigarettes. troy.  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink http://www.msnbc.msn.com/id/5013751/  It would also have been a blow to Brazilian efforts to win more backing for its fight against the illegal mahogany trade from the United States, the biggest market for  a wood so valuable it boasts fatter profit margins than cocaine .
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       yes, this is millikan:   
    
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    
    
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i really didn't want to get up this morning.  gray made me some armor last night in  ryzom . where by "armor" i mean "hotpants." i learned how to make swords, and now i have way more hitpoints. i also have a lot of crap in my inventory, 'cause you have to make stuff to get points to learn how to make more stuff, and no one wants quality 2 daggers, and you can't sell items you make to the NPC shopkeepers. which seems stupid. i realize they want to encourage players to interact, but it seems like they could do the same thing by only having shopkeepers buy your stuff for really low prices. that way you could sell all the useless crap you make while learning how to make decent stuff, but once you had decent stuff to sell, you'd try to sell it to an actual player instead. anyhow, i'm running around with a quality 2 dagger in one hand and a quality 2 sword. there's not really blood, so i'm just dancin' on the corpses. except when i get attacked by a pack of gringos. then they dance on *my* corpse.   apparently there's a big to-do in sacramento because  urlLink someone is trying to open a hooters restaurant .  "We are opposed because of the location and the fact that the company uses the Hooters girl to market their sex appeal," Lim wrote in an e-mail to The Bee. "We would be sending the wrong message to the elementary kids within walking distance from the establishment."
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Superstar Madonna is poised to shock fans on her upcoming Re-Invention tour - by being "electrocuted" live on stage. The American Life singer is planning to make a series of bold statements in the controversial concerts, and has come up with a show that will make pal Britney Spears's raunchy Onyx Hotel tour look tame. As well as being "frazzled" in an electric chair, Madonna will also screen video footage of the corpses belonging to victims of the war in Iraq, perform sexy lesbian dance routines and have scantily-clad pregnant women dancing along to track "Papa Don't Preach." 
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink http://www.msnbc.msn.com/id/5015320/  A list hangs in the Gundens&rsquo; office as a reminder of just how much rides on their work. The list, a collection of notorious typos found in the Bible, features one prominent error from a 1631 King James edition: &#8220;Thou shalt commit adultery.&#8221;
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink http://www.worldbeardchampionships.com/  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
           rui : where is kat in france again?  clara : grenoble  clara : which i may have misspelled  rui : ah.  rui : ok.  clara :  urlLink http://www.ville-grenoble.fr/   rui : cool.    clara : mardi 25 mai, ne manquez pas la fete de voisins!!  clara : Tuesday May 25, do not miss the festival of the neighbors!   Invite your neighbors in the court, in the hall, or in your apartment, the festival of the neighbors it is the occasion to share one convivial moment and to know.  rui : this is why kat has no neighbor-friends!  she misses the festival of the neighbors every year 'cause she's in boston!
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink the ham gadget   and kat is in boston:    rui : gray went to the airport in his spiffy red shirt with a red rose for kat!  clara : ooooh! how exciting!  clara : when was she landing?  rui : we were discussing whether or not that was "too much."    rui : i think they're back, but i don't think they're answering.  ;)  clara : given all his pining, i think that's entirely appropriate. it's a wonder he didn't get himself arrested for waiting in the airport lobby naked with three hundred roses and an inflatable mattress.  rui : heehee.  rui : he said it was gonna be "like a rocket launcher" when he saw her.  clara : a lot of hot air was going to come out of his rear end?   rui : he coulda gotten arrested for bringing a weapon into the airport!  rui : no, silly.  clara : :)  rui : think like a breeder!  clara : i knew what you meant, ruihamster  clara : i was making a *joke*  clara : i guess law skool removes your humor module  rui : i *know* it was a joke, clarencehamster.  i was  pretending  to not know.  
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       have any of you actually read  urlLink  the da vinci code  ? i'm mildly curious, but i have no intention of paying hardback price. i'd be interested enough to read it if i found a $2  50   used paperback copy... i mean, wtf: The book casts unflattering light on the Catholic Church, accusing church leaders ... of covering up the truth about the Holy Grail, which Brown says is Mary Magdalene herself.
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i think i played too much ryzom last night. i dreamed that i was running around killing yubos. i was trying to learn "crafting" last night so i could make some armor, but there was a bug with the raw materials merchant and i couldn't buy raw materials, and running all over the island hoping to prospect materials that might do what you need is... not very fun. gray probably likes it, but then all he did in "morrowwind" was mix potions. i can kill the bat-things now, but not the gringos. also, someone gave me magical earrings, so my character is now prettier than gray's!  some  urlLink religious groups are up in arms about the movie  saved  . i read somewhere that in early screenings, it made christians uncomfortable, and catholics thought it was hilarious. i therefore assume that my catholic upbringing is whyi'm anticipating it. it's supposed to be in theaters on the 28 th . The film is a &#8220;dark comedy,&#8221; starring Mandy Moore and Macaulay Culkin, about students at a Christian school who turn on one girl when she becomes pregnant (after trying to &#8220;cure&#8221; her boyfriend of homosexuality).  &#8220;It&rsquo;s like those monster-vampire-high school kind of movies, only here the monsters are Jesus freak teenagers,&#8221; Michael Stipe, R.E.M. frontman-turned-movie producer, was quoted as saying. 
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm working in the top floor of the TransAmerica building this summer!       But sadly, it is only the top floor of the  Tucson  TransAmerica building, located at the dot:       I didn't know Tucson had a "Garden of Gethesmane"!  Maybe I'll go check it out. 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink http://news.com.com/2100-1024_3-5215599.html  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Relatives of troubled pop beauty Britney Spears are seriously worried  about her mental health - after she rushed off stage in Berlin, Germany in tears. The Toxic superstar, 22, has been struggling to cope with her huge workload as she continues her Onyx Hotel tour in Europe, and sources close to Britney fear the situation is only going to get worse. Britney is reportedly desperate to return home to her mother Lynne after suffering the worst reviews of her career for the raunchy stage show. But with contractual obligations preventing her from ditching the tour, miserable Britney is getting more and more depressed. And the depth of her anguish was clearly demonstrated when she ran off the stage in the German capital and fled to a waiting car, before ignoring fans as she ran into her hotel. A source tells British newspaper the Sun, "Dozens of fans were waiting for her outside the hotel. She rushed straight past them with her baseball cap pulled right down over her eyes. But everyone could see she had been crying her eyes out on the limo journey. Her mascara was streaming down her face."       Maybe she's upset about this:   Antonio Banderas was so moved while watching his eagerly-anticipated new movie Shrek 2 with Justin Timberlake, he ended up sobbing and holding hands with the pop hunk... Banderas says, "I was kind of crying at the end of the thing. It was kinda funny because there's is a very romantic moment at the end of the movie. My character says, 'I wanna cry,' and I was crying. Cameron Diaz was (to the left) and Justin Timberlake was (to the right), and he said to me, 'I'm crying too!'  urlLink So we held hands for a while .    urlLink http://quebolu.galeon.com/imagenes/britney.jpg    Wait, there's more!    urlLink Britney Spears says she doesn't think she's remotely sexy.    She says that while people may think she has a glamorous life, she's often really just trying to survive.   "I don't consider myself sexy at all," the 22-year-old pop star told German FHM magazine, claiming she couldn't understand why she had become the subject of so many men's fantasies.      However, she said she does think women who are confident about their sexuality are sexy, and that she has secretly been just as sexually active as Janet Jackson.   "I may not brag about it as much," said Spears. "But as far as sex goes, I've done similar things to what Janet Jackson has done."     
    
    
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Pope John Paul II was born "Karol Josef Wojtyla" on May 18, 1920 in Wadowice, Poland. He was the second son of a retired army lieutenant named Karol Wojtyla and a schoolteacher named Emilia Kaczorowska Wojtyla.  He had one elder brother named Edmund (a physician) who died from scarlet fever at age 26. He also had an elder sister named Olga who died in infancy. His mother died from kidney disease and heart failure in 1929.  In high school, the future pope became interested in literature and especially acting. He acted in several local plays before enrolling in Krakow's Jagiellonian University. While at Jagiellonian, he studied Polish literature and was a member of the Krakow Theatre Brotherhood.  In 1942, he began studying in secret for a life in the priesthood. In 1944, members of Krakow's "underground seminary" were captured and executed by the Nazis. The Pope himself narrowly escaped death (as soldiers failed to notice him hiding behind a door).  He was ordained a priest in 1946 and in 1978 became the first non-Italian pope in 455 years. At age 58, he was also the youngest pope in more than a century. Read the details of his ordination in the October 16 "Deming Headlight".
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i just saw an email where someone was bitching about how badly they needed A/C in their house. in seattle. come  on , people!  it's the pope's birthday. send him a card.   here's  urlLink how to keep your desk job from making you fat and sad .  gasoline is fucking expensive in menlo park, ca. of course, EVERYTHING is fucking expensive in menlo park. the energy department forcasts that prices won't peak until june.      and  urlLink carbonated beverages can give you esophageal cancer . The researchers found similar trends worldwide. Countries with per capita annual consumption of more than 20 gallons   [that's .58 sodas or other carbonated drinks a day]   of fizzy soft drinks also had rising rates of esophageal cancer.
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink new pill makes you thin, tan, and horny      and since rui is still stalking jennifer love hewitt:  Love Hewitt's Pitt Disappointment  Hollywood actress Jennifer Love Hewitt has been filled with disappointment, after one of Ashton Kutcher's Punk'd pranks fooled her into believing she'd make a movie with Brad Pitt. The I Know What You Did Last Summer beauty met with an actor posing as a casting director, who excited her with the prospect of starring in a false World War II epic called Wages Of War as Pitt's sister. But her smiles were soon wiped away when the 'agent' revealed he'd lost a ton of money on a bad Super Bowl bet and his life was at risk unless he paid up immediately. When the two 'debt collectors' charged into the office, a visibly shaken Love Hewitt attempted to exit the office, moments before learning it was all just a prank. And while she was relieved to be safe, the lost opportunity to work with Pitt was clearly disappointing. While recovering from her trauma, she asked Kutcher, "I'm not really gonna get to be in a cool movie, am I? Darn it!" The episode aired in America on Sunday night. 
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink article  But in recent years, many election officials have been building a variety of hurdles to make it more difficult for students to register and vote. In May 2002, the city council in Saratoga Springs, New York, shut down a polling place at Skidmore College, forcing students to travel off-campus to vote. That same year, a judge in Arkansas tried to block 1,000 students at Ouachita Baptist University and Henderson State University from casting ballots, ruling that they must vote in their hometowns -- even though the deadline for absentee ballots had already passed. And when students from the University of New Hampshire showed up at the polls on Election Day that year, poll workers handed them a pamphlet warning them that voting locally could affect their financial aid and taxes. The scare tactic worked: Many students left without voting. 
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       so, i was looking for a new game to play yesterday, and gray suggested   urlLink ryzom  so far, you run around killing baby animals to build up your l33t killin' skilz, and hoping the animals don't bite you to death before you kill them. in that sense, it's a lot like nethack (which i gave up playing after one too many incidents where i passed out from starvation and got nibbled to death by a newt).  gray and i were both female characters, so i got to play that fun trick on him where when you walk by some random guy, you say "hey, random guy! my friend thinks you're  totally  hot!" and then they guy stalks your friend. (i had to do something mean to gray to make up for the incident where he laughed at me when i accidentally removed my clothes in the middle of the village during some confusion with trying to put my armor on!)  one problem with playing as a female character is that the male characters do tend to follow you around. it's really annoying to be killing something to gain experience, and suddenly, some random character comes up to "help" you. i signed back on after gray went to sleep, and this guy first started "helping" me kill things, and then sat on the ground and tried to chitchat while i was busy trying not to get killed. it's like, look, i know i took my clothes off earlier in the day, but it was an ACCIDENT! i was not trying to come on to everyone else in town! sheesh!  if anyone else is interested in playing, you can download the game from  urlLink fileplanet   (fair warning: it's ~1 gigabyte and you have to wait in line to d/l on the public servers) . we're on the "windermeer" server in the town "kaemon." i'm playing as  cryptgrrl  and gray is playing as  xiaoh . he claims was going to be "xiao ham", but there was some kind of UI confusion and he got truncated. (secretly, i suspect it means "xiao ho")  interested in taking a temporary  urlLink vow of silence ? "What's the problem?" the vet technician asked me.  I frantically gnawed at my hand in reply.  "She's saying that Sasha is chewing off her bandage," my husband explained.   The technician looked puzzled, but continued. "How long has the dog been doing this?" he asked me.  My husband stepped in. "Look, she can't talk."  The technician was stricken. "I'm so sorry," he said.  "Well, she can talk. She's just not talking today," said my husband, in a tone that suggested a dog with a busted leg was the least of his domestic problems. 
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
          urlLink http://news.bbc.co.uk/2/hi/europe/3722321.stm  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i got veggies at the store today. i think i may try to eat only fruits and vegetables this week.     oh, and on the beach boys song "vegetables," one of the people chewing on vegetables in the background was none other than paul mccartney!  i also got a bottle of french pink lemonade:     last year, gray and i would've BOTH gotten sparkling pink lemonade, and we would have been like "yay! girly soda!" and jamal would've been like "i'm gonna go lock myself in my room and watch  24 , 'cause even being in the same room as that beverage is too emasculating for me!" 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink do *NOT* feed brussels sprouts to sanitary monkeys !! 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Mom's here. I'll be away for a while, so sorry if I don't respond to AIM/ICQ/etc.   Snake? Snake?  NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!!!!!   VVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVV 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        LA Convention Centre security staff were left flat-footed and red-faced yesterday as two unknown perps had it away with a copy of the MGS3: Snake Eater demo code. The one level demo, on display at Sony and Konami's stands is almost certainly being duplicated as we speak. Will you see MGS3 first at you local car boot sale?  The LAPD are investigating the incident and are looking for two 19-20 year old males. The code snatchers were able to gain access to the PS2 demoing Snake's hotly anticipated jungle rumble by cracking the perspex case on one of the pods on the Sony stand.  According to eyewitness reports they achieved this by leaning heavily on the unit before simply ejecting the disc and doing a runner from the convention centre - possibly not how Snake would have done it, but apparently effective.
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
           this is a victorian representation of helen of troy. i guess the RRHRG was born 150 years too late... 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       well, this morning got off to a scandalous start:    kat : I'm going to rope Gray into trying this when I get there. I think karla will like it.
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        DEAR ABBY: I recently became engaged to a man I thought was the salt of the earth. Then I moved in with him. Well, he's not the man I thought he was. I now know that almost everything he has told me is a lie.  He's 12 years older than he said. He never went to college like he claimed. He told me he was sterile, but I discovered he has four children. He pays child support for two of them who are very young, so he'll be obligated for a long time. His parents are both living -- not dead like he told me -- and he's not an only child; he has two brothers who live across the country.  My mind is spinning. We're supposed to be married in three months. I'm seriously thinking about breaking the engagement and moving out, but I still love him. Should I stick it out and hope for the best, or listen to my gut? --SECOND THOUGHTS IN INDIANA
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink an interesting-sounding movie  Mexican film director Sergio Arau has taken the thought as the starting point for his film Un D&iacute;a Sin Mexicanos (A Day Without Mexicans). "On May 14," runs the poster's tagline, "there will be no Mexicans in California." The tagline for the Spanish language version of the poster reads: "Los gringos van a llorar" ("The gringos are going to cry"). 
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
          urlLink here's the article  it was from.  oh, and  urlLink be sure to wrap your children in cotton wool so they never ever get hurt ever ! seriously, doesn't it build character to get hurt sometimes when you're a kid? i mean, if you fall out of the tree and break your arm, that's probably the most effective way to learn to be careful when you're climbing the damn tree. there was actually a kid in my grade skool class who broke BOTH arms when he jumped out of a tree. and once i was swinging upside-down and i slipped and i went flying and landed on my head. that probably explains a  lot ... and the chains on the swings would give out every so often and you'd fall on the decomposed granite. that hurt. ok, why the hell did i even LIKE the swingset? once, my grandfather told me the cracks in the dirt under the swingset were the beginnings of volcanoes, and i was terrified of volcanoes after reading that book about the farmer in mexico who's plowing his field, when a volcano opens up, and his ox falls in, and pretty soon, there's this huge volcano and everyone has to flee. it was a true story, i think. i don't know why anyone thought it would be a good idea for a  children's  story.. i used to have volcano nightmares.    clara : kat's gonna be too late to stop gray and parmesh from getting married:  urlLink http://www.msnbc.msn.com/id/4980388/   Rui : yep!  clara : oh, wait, there's a 3day waiting period. so it depends on whether or not they're able to get that waived.  clara : how suspenseful!  Rui : oooooh!
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       so, i finally got around to getting my free bus pass from work. (i picked a great time to finally get it -- the damn thing expires in a month!) and i'm planning on a bus adventure this wknd! only trouble is, i don't know where i want to go. any suggestions? you can look at the  urlLink bus timetable ! i've considered going to the "experience music project," wandering around the shopping district again, and going up to fremont. i may take my camera with me to document my crazy journey, but i feel a little awkward running around with a camera taking pictures.   and if one histrionic singing simpson sibling isn't enough for you,  urlLink jessica simpson's little sister ashlee is putting out a record.  rui says ashlee simpson is cooler than jessica, and that she got all the smartness in the family. i argued that when your competition is jessica simpson, it's hard  not  to be the smart one in the family.   according to  urlLink this article , charlotte, NC, is the 10 th  worst city for dating in the US. however, honolulu is the 10 th   best :  Honolulu, HI : Honolulu ranks first in the diversity index category, which rates the likelihood of randomly meeting someone of a different race or ethnicity, and scores the highest in the dining out category as well. Honolulu has the lowest number of lingerie shops per capita, probably because no one's wearing much clothing to begin with.
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
           j.ro : There's a personals site for anime fans. It's really sad. I mean, REALLY REALLY sad  clara : "40yo man seeks 18yo girl who likes to dress up like sailor moon" ?  j.ro : Oh, so you've seen it  clara : no, just guessing :)
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink is pop princess britney spears ready to be a stepmother ? 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
         person 1 : let's meet on tuesday to work out the details  clara : sounds good  person 1 : i'll let you set it up, clara  clara : ok, i'll do that  person 1 : pick whatever time is good for you.   person 2 : i'd prefer the afternoon  clara : definitely  [I set it up for 2PM]   person 1 : well THAT time is no good at all!  clara : when are you free?  person 1 : let ME pick the time!  [person 1 sends an invitation for a 10AM meeting after we agreed to do it in the afternoon]   clara : um.. can we have the meeting in the afternoon..?
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Lansbury Slams Decision To Remake 'Manchurian Candidate'  Angela Lansbury has registered her strong displeasure at the decision to remake the classic 1962 film The Manchurian Candidate, in which she starred with Frank Sinatra. In an interview with syndicated columnist Liz Smith, Lansbury, best known in recent years for her starring role on the TV series Murder, She Wrote, remarked: "I'm so unhappy. I'm so sorry they had to mess with something that was so perfect." In the new film, set for release on July 30, her role is played by Meryl Streep. "I have great admiration for Meryl Streep," Lansbury told Smith. "She'll probably be very interesting. I just wish she hadn't chosen to do it."
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        spider-man 2  was great! go see it! woo!  *someone* is  urlLink losing wall street support . meanwhile, someone else is  urlLink missing the photo-op boat . supposedly this has been happening a lot. isn't there someone who gets paid to make sure they don't screw these kind of things up?  britney spears  urlLink wants to have four or five kids . courtney love is  urlLink so broke  that her website has gone offline -- they don't have $5,000 to get it back up. lindsay lohan's father has been  urlLink arrested AGAIN . (right now, hilary duff is screaming at her father to get himself arrested so she can get some of that good ol' free publicity.) and here's some daily weirdness for ya: An anonymous hotelier is spilling the beans on celebs in a forthcoming book called "Hotel Babylon," and here are some tidbits from it that appeared in London&rsquo;s Mail on Sunday: Michael Jackson once ordered 48 bottles of Evian to bathe in. He also brought his own chef, who made him kiddie food, such as fish sticks.
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Israel's High Court orders changes to the route of the country's West Bank separation barrier. Details soon.   1) It must be moved closer to the Green Line. 2) It must have a section that looks kind of like a wang.  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       matt sent me  urlLink this article . there are sample mp3s at  urlLink http://www.earthology.net/albums.htm . 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink http://www.dimensionsmagazine.com/dimtext/kjn/people/heaviest.htm  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink paris hilton buying a copy of her own sex video  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Matt :  urlLink http://hosted.ap.org/dynamic/stories/T/TERROR_SUSPECT_DEPORTED?SITE=MIDTN&SECTION=ASIA&TEMPLATE=DEFAULT  damn ashcroft cant do anything right
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       seriously, wtf?       urlLink the article  is about how humans are utterly irrational decisionmakers.  and matt sent me  urlLink this . 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
          ...wait... everyone has cable now, huh? Nevermind. 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       slate has an article about  urlLink der furor .  the supreme court is protecting americans' right to pr0n.  i'm goin' to the promised land, i mean socal, for my birthday. i've got beach boys songs in my head! not even the good ones, but i don't care! wooooohoo! roscoe's house of chicken and waffles, here i come! i took my family to roscoe's once. i had my mother halfway convinced that they had a "special events" room in the back (that you could rent for a birthday or something) with a cage of chickens (like, say, a lobster tank) so you could pick the chicken you wanted them to kill and fry up. then she thought about it and realized that that was insane. roscoe's! venice beach! hot wings! amoeba! 3rd street promenade! melrose! chinese theater! sam ash music! hollywood mall! rodeo drive! jacoranda trees! sunset blvd! scientology center! wooooooo!!!!!~~~!!!!!!~!!@!1111!!!! ok. i had WAY too much coffee. i apologize.  i rented the first spider-man movie last night. there's something disturbing about kirsten dunst.  here's some more "nader is no progressive articles." i can't see them at work (i forgot my salon password), so i don't know whether or not there are any hilarious cake-but-no-frosting stories. i hope there are.  urlLink article #1   urlLink article #2   from the daily show: But Bremer didn't leave before taking care of some last minute odds and ends, like completely changing the Iraqi legal code to include 97 new edicts on subjects ranging from the death penalty to the Iraqi tax rate which he says can be no higher now than 15 percent. And also -- this is true -- drivers can only use their horns in the case of an emergency and must always keep both hands on the wheel, he says, God forbid you lose control of the car while you're driving into an embassy. 
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink more pr0n for everyone!  for now at least... 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink if reelected, bush plans to cut funding for the programs he's supporting out on the campaign trail . hey, remember four years ago when we were all arguing over what to do with the surplus? 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
           clara : from the internet: "Let's get one thing straight. I love Beyonce. That video for "Crazy in Love" is ridiculous. It makes Britney and Christina Agui-lame-a look about as sexy as a Janet Reno/Rush Limbaugh amateur porn clip."
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
          it sort of sums up tech in a nutshell.    This is a cool article:   urlLink http://www.cnn.com/2004/US/Northeast/06/28/corporate.id.theft.ap/index.html  It's about some paralegal who stole a law firm's identity.  Squirrelly paralegals!  Can't trust 'em.  I think I almost interviewed with Fish & Neave, the firm in the article.   
    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
           Ok, this guy is definitely one of the guest stars on The &#8220;X&#8221; Files &#8211; he must be one of those alien block-head shape shifters, only this guy got in some kind of cat fight before they snapped his mug. Actually, this is Chris Kemp, and the real story behind his arrest is almost as weird as an &#8220;X-Files&#8221; plot. Kemp, arrested by Gresham County (Washington) PD after a homeowner returned from work to the home he shares with his mother and allegedly found Kemp inside the house, wearing his mother&rsquo;s clothing, including a leopard-skin hat and matching scarf. Kemp allegedly had punched holes in the walls, stolen money out of Christmas envelopes and was in the process of moving kitchen appliances around when the homeowner appeared. The homeowner made Kemp sit down and wait for police to arrive, who promptly arrested him. We understand you could hear the cops laughing hysterically as they drove away.
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       on  urlLink ads that make you go "ew!"  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       so, i accidentally clicked on the "browse the corporate directory" button in outlook, and since the window was open, i decided to see how many claras there were in the list. there were seven, including myself, but the vast majority of them were, judging by last names, asian! there's more ruis than claras, fewer grays, slightly fewer jamals, vastly more connies, vastly more lizs, vastly more matts, and only one person who is listed as kat (though there were tons of people with names for which "kat" might be a nickname).  oh, and liz, do you remember the name i couldn't remember last night at dinner? it was quetzacoatl.  the  urlLink fda has approved the use of leeches . the more things change the more things stay the same, eh?      apparently  urlLink plastic surgery is increasingly popular among african-americans . the reason i mention it is because of this snippet of the article: Tanisha Rollins, 29, an administrative assistant in Dayton, Ohio, thought nipping and tucking was only for "rich white people and Michael Jackson."
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        elvis used to crank out albums every six months, but then again, his day job was eating sandwiches and drugs.
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i got the new brian wilson solo album last night. brian may have been a genius in 1966, but this album is TERRIBLE. i mean, the music is bad, the lyrics are bad, his voice is bad... i'm dreading what  SMiLE  is going to sound like when it's released. ugh. i think they should just hand the songs from  SMiLE  off to someone like the shins who will actually make a good album out of it.  is there really NO ONE online? or is trillian being weird? it swears i'm connected, but not a single person on my contact list is on.  the vet's trying to get my mom to take the dog to UC Davis to have its vitamin and mineral levels checked. my parents' neighbors spent a fortune taking their dog to the vet, and then to a specialist (who insisted on redoing all the same expensive tests), and finally they realized that the only thing wrong with the dog was a few rotten teeth. vets are awful.    urlLink slate says  kim jong il outfoxed bush.  richard perle looks like the undead:     the WINKING-'CAUSE-HE-THINKS-YOU'RE-CUTE-AND-YOU-HAVE-A-PURDY-SMILE undead!  what this country needs is some  urlLink bold & decisive waffling !  and  urlLink britney spears may be pregnant ! well, according to a tabloid.  The News of the World reported that Spears in expecting the couple's first child in late December. The report said that Britney would like to be married by November, well before the baby is born.
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       They all started maaaaahing at me when I stopped to take a picture of them. The sheep farmer was nearby and probably planning to get his pitchfork to kill me, but I sped away on my bike. haha!  urlLink 106-0646_IMG.JPG  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ...I'd link, but I'd be surprised if it isn't on EVERY front page around the world.  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink sheesh     jamal : Uh... clara? If buildings are falling and planes are crashing into shit and poisons are being released and etc etc etc... I don't think that's a terribly good day to vote. That might just be me, tho  jamal : I mean, I read the article and it seems to be phrased as "If really bad shit goes down, we should have a plan". Am I missing a passage?  clara : the concept isn't bad. i'm just not sure it should be in the hands of the people who brought us the "exploding beer coolers" terror alert. :)  urlLink http://www.time.com/time/magazine/article/0,9171,1101040705-658292,00.html   clara : i bet the next terror alert is going to be about terrorists sneaking into canada and strapping bombs to canadian geese just before they migrate south
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
         This is the first year I simply CAN'T go.   ;_;  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
           Rui : what's OB session?  Clara : wha?  Rui : in that tom tomorrow strip.  he mentions some kind of "ob-session" in iraq?  Clara : it's just "obsession" split over two lines  Clara : with a hyphen  Clara : are you SURE you have a lit degree?  Rui : ahhh.  :)   Rui : i told you i have a headache!!
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Mr. Angel Jones, 27, was convicted of aggravated assault against his girlfriend, specifically, biting off most of her nose in a rage; he admitted the nose was in his mouth but said that due to her using weight-loss medication, her nose had become brittle, and that it just fell off (Toronto, May).
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       my mom sent me these pictures today. apparently my parents got to ride in the sidecar of a barely legal russian motorcycle!   urlLink picture 1   urlLink picture 2  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       possibly, you shouldn't base your case for war on what you heard from  urlLink some dude named al-libi . however, this image seems to prove conclusively that it's all france's fault:      when a reporter asked VP dick cheney about this collusion between al-libi and france, the man a heartbeat from the presidency had this to say:     
    
    
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink http://www.alternet.org/envirohealth/19045/  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
           Jamal : I spend a lot of time complaining about how boring my life is, then I start telling stories and I realize "Oh, wait. My life is actually kinda cool"  Jamal : So if you go to Waikiki to play DDR because the arcade down there is the ONLY place down there that stays open until 2am the hookers think you're crazy and the security guards and police wave at you as you go by.   Clara : hahaha! awesome  Jamal : Some will even strike up a conversation.   Clara : the hookers or the cops?  Jamal : And one whore (who was CRAZY hot) got into a limo and one of the hotel people came out screaming at her and kicked the side of the limo.   Clara : um...?  Jamal : "IF YOU STEP ONE FOOT ON MY PROPERTY AGAIN I'LL BEAT THE SHIT OUT OF YOU! GET OUT! GET OUT!!!!"  Clara : hehe  Jamal : I looked at the other whores and said "nice guy." they giggled.   Jamal : I can't go back. The pimps think I'm 5-0 and have threatened me =(  Clara : have you ACTUALLY been threatened by pimps?  Jamal : But other than the whores, cops, drugs, foreign travel, lesbians, etc my life has been fairly boring  Jamal : Yes.   Clara : wow  Jamal : And they called me a faggot because I wasn't buying  Clara : your life is not boring  Jamal : Some of them are stuck up bitches. If you aren't Japanese they don't want NOTHIN` to do with cha!  Clara : really? crazy  Jamal : Yeah. Between sets of DDR I walk around, and one of them exposed her boobs and said "Anata! Anata!". I tried to joke with her after that and she just had none of it. I asked if she was only interested in Japanese guys and she was like "yeah"  Jamal : Oh well. The cops are more interesting anyway  Jamal : I mean, they are PISSED.   Clara : so you wander around hawaii and get flashed by hookers?  Clara : and then insulted by pimps?  Clara : your life is not boring. :)  Jamal : Well, they weren't flashing ME  Clara : ohhh  Jamal : I was caught in the crossfire  Clara : hehe  Jamal : She was flashing the Japanese.   Jamal : And then I saw some cops cautioning some working girls.   Clara : so you've been hassled by the hookers and the pimps. have you been hassled by the cops?  Jamal : Oh well. I think I'll go back in... November. Everyone should have forgotten me by then  Jamal : No. I look like a tourist.   Jamal : But ASIDE from the whores, drugs, cops, pimps, swordplay on campus, white sand beaches, strippers, tsunamis...  Clara : ...hawaii is TOTALLY boring?  Jamal : Hawaii kicks the shit out of SoCal. I've never had so much fun or been so close to crime in my life.   Jamal : Oh, and the homeless. Jesus, how can I forget the homeless.   Jamal : and the dolphins.   Jamal : ASIDE from all that shit, my life is pretty boring.   Clara : we should have gotten an apartment somewhere insanely crimeriddled last year :)  Jamal : It has to be the RIGHT kind of crime  Jamal : Victimless.   Jamal : There was only one death in my neighborhood last year, and that was totally that one dude's fault
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Jamal : I need to find lesbians for when you visit  Jamal : Are you at work?  Clara : nah, i'm at home  Jamal : I would go down to Waikiki, scatter some Berkinstocks and call "Heeeeeeeeeeeeeere lezzy lezzy lezzy" but I don't think that'd work  Clara : hehehe  Jamal : It's so much easier to get black people. Just plant a chicken leg.   Jamal : One of us will be by in a minute to smack you for wasting good food.   Clara : you could try yelling "hey look! it's eliza dushku! and she just took off her bikini top!"
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink This game  looks really sweet.  Someone should play it and tell me how it is.  or maybe I'll play it after my party  "I found a hunter made freinds with him then stab him in the head 3 times he dead I cut him up and eat him I survive for about 6 days with that hunter and I use his cloths to bandage my wounds and use myself." -Vessol  link goes to fargo's review on gamespy. 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink this is a funny short film . probably NSFW. 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       from  urlLink sanitydeprived.blogspot.com , we have the following:  Aaaaaaaaaand it's fixed.    urlLink Sex Hampster  Kickass News Dumbass Daily Goth Blog  I have to do SOMETHING with my time...come on...  [listening to: Some garbled version of "Ain't no Mountain"] L@T3R ^|^V(H  African Toad [12:19 PM]  ---------------------------------------------------   An evil sexful hampster stole my last entry   Basically. I hit "Post" and then it decided to freak out. This is the second time it's happend...there is only one possible reason...  EVIL HAMPSTER WHORES!!!  Or maybe This Panda...  [listening to: Wat da Hook Gon Be, by Murphey Lee (ha!)] L@T3R ^|^V(H  African Toad [12:23 PM]  
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       From  urlLink The Scientology Handbook :  I can't see how this can possibly fail:    What the shit.     I hope someone involved in this was really, really high    
    
    
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Gray : I told people at work the shelley story as a cautionary tale to the chinese girls.  Clara : the shelley story?  Clara : you mean "don't date guys who chew tobacco" ?  Clara : or "don't trust random guys in the computer lab about italian desserts" ?  Gray : the second one.  Clara : hehe  Gray : it was funny, because the american guys were howling with laughter when I told it, and the girls were like "what's that"?
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink when do papers publish the f-word ? and  urlLink why did they unseal the jeri and jack ryan divorce papers if both parties objected ?  spyware may be  urlLink illegal  soon. and  urlLink here's an article  on how to combat it. a utah court  urlLink blocked  a state law against spyware. i heard that rui has been going around installing all the spyware she can in hopes that she'll soon see nothing but bacon ads featuring elijah wood, and she'll never have to put effort into finding NSFW again!  and the japanese government is investing billions in  urlLink making the movie  AI  come to life . A year ago, neuroscientist Mitsuo Kawato called on the Japanese government to commit 50 billion yen ($446 million) a year for the next three decades. The dream: an Apollo-like program to build a robot with the mental, physical, and emotional capabilities of a 5-year-old child.
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       so, the review period is coming up at work. i went to a little class on how to fill out your review form (why couldn't they just give us a document to read instead of putting us in a room for 90 minutes?!), and it turns out the review process is a lot like hovsepicks, except more complicated.  and britney spears has  urlLink confirmed  that she's engaged to her skeezy dancer boyfriend with the pregnant ex who used to be on  moesha ! so, how likely do you think it is that they won't actually get married; if they do get married, how many hours do you think this one will last?  the michael moore megamarketing continues! there's an  urlLink article on mtv.com  where he encourages kids under 18 to sneak into the movie, since the man is trying to keep them out.  "I have encouraged teenagers to go see this movie," Moore told MTV News. "Sneak into this movie. Get in by any means necessary. If you see me near a theatre, I'll help sneak you in. Just get into this movie, because it should not be R-rated. And if your parents object, tell them I said it was OK. I'll write you a note or something."
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       the gubernator wants to  urlLink terminate your pets .   urlLink let's stop aging !  Q:  What do you think is a reasonable expectation of progress in this department over the next 20-30 years?   A:  I think we have a 50/50 chance of effectively completely curing aging by then. I should explain that I mean something precise by the suspiciously vague-sounding term "effectively completely". I define an effectively complete cure for aging as the attainment of "escape velocity" in the postponement of aging, which is the point when we're postponing aging for middle-aged people faster than time is passing. 
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        After five weeks of Democratic attempts to rework the president's military spending plan, the $447 billion bill was approved last night by the Senate. A proposal by Sen. Ted Kennedy that would have required the administration to estimate the number of U.S. troops who will be in Iraq at the end of next year was defeated 50-48. Two Democrats crossed party lines to vote against the proposal -- Zell Miller and Joe Lieberman. Lieberman also announced that he was going to become a Methodist in hopes that Republicans would like him better.
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       PERSON.............................. TIME AT HALF STAFF  Sitting President or................ 30 days Former President  Sitting Vice President or........... 10 days Sitting Chief Justice or Retired Chief Justice or Current Speaker of the House  Sitting Associate Justice or........ From death until burial Current Cabinet Secretary or     Former Vice President or Sitting State Governor  Current Representative or........... 1 day Current Senator  Other High Officials or............. By special order of the President National Tragedy                    
    
    
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
           
    
    
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i arrived home today to discover that bunny had left me this message:    Bunny : hey poopy  Bunny : there's this oncologist in my lab and today he spent most of his time talking to various doctors about a patient who's got some kind of weird gel coming out of her ass  Bunny : and meanwhile i'm sitting right there getting all excited
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Val Kilmer isn&rsquo;t impressed with Brad Pitt&rsquo;s machismo.  The hot-headed star of the upcoming &#8220;Alexander&#8221; has taken some pot shots at his better-paid, better-liked rival Brad Pitt.   &#8220;I saw those pictures of Brad Pitt,&#8221; Kilmer told the London Express, referring to the &#8220;Troy&#8221; star looking buff and muscular. &#8220;That&rsquo;s all air-brushed in, you know. He&rsquo;s a nice guy, but he&rsquo;s a wimp.&#8221;  Pitt went through rigorous training to get into shape for &#8220;Troy.&#8221;
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ....to  urlLink not pay back your court-ordered restitution ! 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       An article in Nature says "Biologists seek approval to send fruit flies by post".  You'd all better be glad I don't work with fruit flies. Maybe I could get access to them though. I mean, if i can get access to fish embryos I don't see why I couldn't get access to fruit flies just by requesting them at the fruit fly production facility on campus. Expect a package to be buzzing your way, hams.  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i realize this was already on fark, but... Heiress Paris Hilton reportedly told a Kansas City radio station that she is in talks for a lead role in a proposed sequel to the 2000 film Dungeons & Dragons, according to the Dark Horizons Web site. "Sounds like fun," Hilton reportedly said. "I'll get dirty."  The first Dungeons & Dragons movie tanked, but a proposed sequel is reportedly on the drawing board. Joel Silver (The Matrix) produced the first film and also developed House of Wax, the upcoming remake of the classic horror movie, in which Hilton has a small part.
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink scary  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink here  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hmmm... Gray wants more naked anime chicks.  ...but really, I should put a warning or something.     There we go.  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
         urlLink white chicks   comes out today.   have you guys been following the  urlLink jack and jeri ryan scandal ?  here's eric alterman's quote from outer space for the day: &#8220;The [9/11 commission] report said that Mohamed Atta did meet with an Iraqi Intelligence Agency, or agent, in Prague on April 9th of 2001.  We've known this for a long time."  -- urlLink Rush Limbaugh 
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       HELLO I AM NEW TO THE INTERNET WHERE CAN I BUY SOME WINAMP?  Ok.  After several heated phone arguments, death threats, and pleading, I am now back on the internet at home.  The following things which have been suspended in my absence may resume: Clara may resume making fun of Rui. Rui may resume being mad at Clara for making fun of her. Jamal may resume posting pictures of naked anime chicks. Liz may resume posting every once in a while. Clara may resume posting left-wing political rants. Rui may resume posting important celeberty news updates. Jess may resume posting comments that are much more horrible than the original post. Kat and Clara may NOT resume posting gross pictures of infections. The Blog as a whole may resume attracting hot goth chicks.  That is all.  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        "Sure, of course."  -- First Lady Laura Bush when asked by the Boston Globe May 21 "whether she would invite a married, gay couple to a state dinner at the White House." Mrs. Bush's press secretary, Gordon Johndroe, interrupted to say he could not imagine such a situation arising. Johndroe also accused the reporter who asked the question of "trivializing an issue that people are seriously trying to debate in this country."
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
          "help! help! karl rove has an electric cattle prod this far up my ass!"  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
           j-ro : Defamation (written libel) occurs when somebody publishes as fact something that is false, is "unprivileged," and harms somebody's reputation by making him the object of hatred or ridicule, causes him to be shunned, or injures him financially or professionally. So unless Moore's critics call him a liar, a felon, a murderer, a chiseler, a Nazi, a child molester, tax evader or any other false statement that is objectively provable, they'll likely not receive a court summons from his lawyers.   j-ro : I've got $5 riding on Ann Coulter saying ONE of those things
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink  fahrenheit 9/11  is keeping its R rating . michael moore doesn't really care one way or the other, but does a happy dance at capturing yet another headline.  yet another  urlLink article  about the more anorexic of the olsen twins. i'm waiting for someone to leak her current weight so we can all gasp in horror.  inclined to pick your president depending on which band supports which candidate?  urlLink here you go !  the testimony of two FBI officials  urlLink contradicts ashcroft's testimony  in front of the 9/11 commission. lately, i've been seeing a lot of people refer to the 9/11 commission as some kind of highly partisan witch hunt, despite the fact that it's half republicans and half democrats... you can read about it on  urlLink wikipedia .  and the justice dept just wants to let you know that " urlLink these aren't the  droids  memos you're looking for . we can go about our business."  jamal thinks yasser arafat and dean revel bear no resemblance to one another. can anyone find a good picture of the dean to prove him wrong?  j-ro : Uh oh... Billy Boy is saying that Arafat might not be... "all there"  clara : dean revel looks just like yasser arafat  j-ro : Uhm....  clara : ?  j-ro : I wouldn't say "just like"  j-ro : In fact, I would say "not much like at all", but that's just me  j-ro : The nose, mouth, and eyes are different  j-ro : It's like saying you look like Lisa Loeb  clara : nah, you're crazy  j-ro : Because you look like Lisa Loeb  j-ro : ?  clara : no, because arafat totally looks like the dean  j-ro : The best I'll give you is that the Dean looks like a frenchman trying to impersonate Arafat to sleep with his wife  clara : ask bunny. she's seen them both in flagrante delicto
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Slate has a weird habit of updating whenever they damn well feel like it, so this story about  urlLink Moore and the likelyhood that he'll use his ninja lawyer squad  didn't immediately get paired with  urlLink the story that Clara mentioned .   I find this funny; the two articles together are the OP/ED equivalent of calling someone a pussy on the playground and then daring them to do something about it. It's also weird that it appears in freaking  SLATE . I thought they'd keep quiet about it like TNR.   And for little miss interrogation pants: Yes, I have a comic with a LOT of gay material. No, I'm not gay. Yes, I read TMNT. No, I'm not a furry. YES, I used to read Catwoman. NO, I don't... oh, wait. Um. Yes. Yes I do. But it's HALLE BERRY!!!! Not furry.  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i just saw this huge guy. like, imagine two pro football players walking side by side. that's what this dude looked like.  last night i dreamed that jamal and i were watching some awards show (like the grammies or something) and making lewd comments about the celebrities on the red carpet. hey, there should be a show that MST3Ks joan rivers's red carpet show. god, joan rivers is scary. when i was a little kid, i watched  i love lucy  or something in the mornings, and afterwards, joan rivers's chat show was on, and she terrified me. i saw her on some interview show recently and she was talking about how she had gotten an eye lift that had gone slightly wrong and left her unable to close her eyes all the way for a while.  from a slate article: For most people, the idea of partying in the business-class lounges at JFK with a bunch of frequent flyer program addicts would probably not appeal all that much. But even though I rarely indulge it, I'll admit to having an airport fetish. Back when I was a young aesthete, besotted with all that was tacky, the kitsch I loved most was a category I dubbed "the Superbland." The Superbland was anything that was so lacking in character (innate or borrowed) that it screamed with existential nothingness. Office cubicles were Superbland. Modest, non-brand-name khaki pants with pleats in the front were Superbland, especially if paired with muted-color cotton/poly blend plaid shirts (the plaids had to be small). And airports were the mother of all Superblandness, providing a frisson (albeit an ironic one) of excitement. 
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink seriously   and the skinny olsen twin has been  urlLink sent to a clinic  to learn how to eat a sandwich. 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       did somebody say "dreadlock" ?      did somebody say "ear hair" ?     
    
    
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Recall in our hero's last post that he found a new series called  Comic Party . Recall further that  Comic Party  was about doujinshi (fan made comics). So, imagine our hero's delight when he finds Comic Party doujinshi! That's right: fan comics about a series about fancomics. What's funnier? It's professionally produced by CPM. I just coundn't resist that through the looking glass shit so I picked up a copy. The girl behind the counter grinned.   She knew what I was in for.   A bit more background: Comics Party has about 8 characters. One main guy, his crazy friend, and several women between the ages of 18 and 25. Total people? ~8. Total penises? 2. Everyone got that little fact in mind?   Within the first 5 pages there's allusions to some non-consentual sex. BETWEEN THE TWO GUYS. Oh, one of the girls wants "models" for her yaoi doujinshi (fan-made Gundam Wing comics. Okay, not always GW, but whereever there are two Japanese men being drawn having sex the spirit of Duo is not far away) and one of the guys was perfectly willing! The other guy's opinion didn't really matter.... *shudder*. The third story featured pictures of "Crazy Friend" offering his almost nude body to the main character. Then two stories later the main guy has to draw himself and his partner (no, not the female partner!) getting freak nasty for a fan. All in all, about 1/3 to 1/2 of the stories feature the only two Y chromosome possesing characters in various compromising positions. "But," you say, "that's okay, right? I mean, the other stories have to be about what happens when all the female characters go over to each other's houses after a long day's work and relax with two or more glasses of wine and some soft music and low lights and maybe a jello pit and some pillows and babydoll tees, right? There should be equal time, right?"  Wrong.    WRONG.   Not even the angry girl with short hair tried to get some lesbian action, and if there's anything that I've learned from my 24 years on this earth it's that cute evil girls with short hair are ALWAYS 2 drinks away* from a girl-on-girl adventure. The authors weren't having any of that shit. I flipped over to the table of contents to see who wrote each story and sure enough: all of the authors were women. No wonder the clerk at Waldenbooks grinned like that.   I give it 3 stars.    *or "me asking them out".  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
          Lesbians are  urlLink fat, sad, and lushes !  :(   
    
    
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink diebold article  O'Dell does admit "we made mistakes." But he chides the geeks for demanding a level of security that doesn't reflect the real world.
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       sacramento was ehh. it would have been better if they hadn't decided to drag me on a $%^^&#@!!! long-ass nature walk in the heat after i got ~four hours of sleep. (i ended up going to sleep late and then i had to wake up early for my hair appointment, and the sleep i  did  get was unsettled. hint: don't read  rosemary's baby  before going to sleep -- the book's good, but it'll give you weird-ass dreams) we rented  the triplets of belleville , which was really cool. and i got some nifty bookends. oh, and we had bacon sandwiches for lunch on sunday!!! hmm.. perhaps the bacon sandwiches explain why my stomach is so unhappy this morning... (or maybe it was the fact that i ate flan, more flan, boysenberry pie, a grilled sandwich with cheese and smoked salmon, chocolate mousse, steak, more pie, and THEN a bacon sandwich this wknd...) liz and i got food at the cheesecake factory yesterday after i got back. (thank you for picking me up at the airport!) afterwards, i went home, thinking i'd watch whatever tv my computer had recorded over the wknd, and apparently NONE OF THE SHOWS I RECORD HAD BEEN BROADCAST DURING THE TIME I WAS GONE!!! so i got miffed and went to see  dodgeball . it was entertaining. i don't remember any opening credits, so either (a) there weren't any, (b) the projectionist messed up somehow, or (c) i fell asleep for a few minutes during the previews.  upcoming movies (what am i missing?):   fahrenheit 9/11   white chicks  (revlon sent them "white" makeup in drums!!)   urlLink spiderman 2   (tobey maguire nearly didn't get the role!)  i, robot   king arthur 
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
         The live launch can be found on  urlLink bbc  http://www.bbc.co.uk/newsa/n5ctrl/events04/sci/spaceship1/launch21jun.ram 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       There's a big Norwegian ship mining salt in Boston harbor. The Norwegians are coming to take over! Get the bear mace.   urlLink 106-0633_IMG.JPG  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        The best thing about the Barrons is the way that, no matter how few roles Jordan wins after countless auditions, they refuse to take any advice from the professionals and experts they encounter along the way. One woman tells Jordan she should absolutely memorize her monologue before an audition, and Jordan gets defensive about it. Another suggests that she should go on Accutane for her acne and get a hairstyle, which not only horrifies her and her mother, but sends them both into shock over how shallow Hollywood can be. Have these two even caught a glimpse of Lindsay's Lohans before? Wake up and smell the Olsen twins, guys! 
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       is dead.  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       If you've seen drawings of a little girl with a bloody boxcutter floating around the interweb, this is why:     See the girl in the "Nevada" shirt? That's (supposedly) "Girl A", the little Japanese girl who cut up her friend because she called her fat. DO YOU HEAR THAT RUI, CLARA!? DON'T CALL JAPANESE GIRLS FAT!  Also, this week's (I know, it's not that regular) "From the Internet".       And finally, I bought the new Comic Party doujinshi. It's very gay. Very, VERY gay. I don't mean "gay like something a jock doesn't like", I mean "gay like two men having sex".  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Me: Love you Grandma Gmom: Huh? Me: I love you Grandma. Gmom: You know I cant hear good.  Me: LOVE YOU GRANDMA!!! Gmom: Oh, your dad sent me flowers. Me: THATS NICE. Gmom: You sound just like him. This is Jamal, right? Me: (thinking: how the fuck could  you  tell?) loudly: YES. Gmom: Well, Ill let you go. Im so happy you remembered me.   Me: Ah, ok. ILL SEE YOU THIS CHRISTMAS!!! Gmom: What? Me:  CHRISTMAS!!!  Gmom: Love you too. *click* Me:   
    
    
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
         "People will come into my office in tears and say they've been against abortion their whole lives," he said, "but they'll make an exception for themselves."
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        The body of Paul Johnson, the American hostage beheaded by terrorists inside Saudi Arabia,  urlLink has been found  in the capital Riyadh, the Associated Press reported.
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       thank you, msn slate. thank you for putting a  urlLink GIANT NAKED PICTURE AT THE TOP OF YOUR PAGE WHILE I AM AT WORK !  britney spears is supposedly gonna  urlLink marry  her boyfriend. they've been "an item" for two months. and when they hooked up, he was involved with someone else. who was pregnant with his child.  kerry wants to  urlLink raise the federal minimum wage  to $7/hr. assuming a 40 hour week and two weeks a year where you don't work, that makes a yearly salary of $14000.  you can read about the  urlLink slander of george soros  if you want.  cheney  urlLink backtracks .  clinton had to  urlLink sleep on the couch  for two months after the lewinsky scandal.  and the west is in the middle of the  urlLink worst drought EVAR . or at least the worst drought ever for 500 years. &#8220;If you&rsquo;re a betting person, you will bet that we will come out of this drought next year,&#8221; Webb said. &#8220;It&rsquo;s a very severe event and these things tend to end fast. There are other indications, though, that suggest that this drought could persist for as long as 30 years.
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       rui wants to have a caption contest for this pic:     
    
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       we had an insane thunder/lightning storm last night!     
    
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Have you ever wanted to hurt people? Here's how you might go on a spree using the latest in self-defense technology.   urlLink http://robenselfdefenseproducts.com/index.html  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ok, yesterday, one of the  urlLink MSNBC bloggers  wrote about some NYT journalists who were claiming that as members of the press, they could not be compelled to appear in court and be questioned about whether the quotes they attributed to some person were exactly what the person said. now, this person was NOT an unnamed source. the person was named in the article and knew he was going to be named in the article. it was entirely on the record. so, basically, the journalists are full of crap in this case. now, the part i need help with is this response, which was posted today:  Name: Tracey Fooshee Hometown: Atlanta  Thanks Professor Reynolds. It seems to be yet another desperate attempt to keep a grip on what is hopefully becoming a sharp decline in power.  I'd much rather have a modest, well policed, ethical and professional media willing and capable of turning their powers of scrutiny inward as frequently as they do on others but, sadly, it appears that is too much to hope for. Curiously, these kinds of claims of exemption from people wielding immense power are what gave rise to the media's influence during the Nixon administration. Are we witnessing a similar kind of corruption? 
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       madonna had decided to become modest. and she wants to be called "esther."  urlLink seriously . 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ...that my recently re-installed copy of trillian won't let me add his icq # to my contact list! 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       does anyone else find the idea of  urlLink genetically modifying people so they don't cheat  on their wife/husband/boyfriend/girlfriend/whatever to be profoundly creepy? maybe we should just all take drugs to turn us into personality-free zombies. oh wait, that's what prozac and ritalin are for. right.  read about a variety of  urlLink documentaries . The movie is catching on, he says, because people increasingly sense that the the world is facing real problems. Yet when they watch the news and read the paper, they don't have a sense of why it's happening the way it is happening. Documentaries try to make sense of the big picture, he says, and viewers welcome the engagement such films provide even if they don't always agree with a film's conclusions.
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i fell asleep again after my alarm went off and didn't wake up for nearly an hour. it's not good for the brain to go from sound asleep to panicked that fast!  here's an  urlLink article on clarence thomas . ( login :bselig  password :bselig)  and you can go here to  urlLink ponder the general suckiness of movie remakes . although i disgree that  mr deeds goes to town  was a "delight." for a movie described as a "screwball comedy," it's painfully slow and pretty much unfunny. i never saw the adam sandler remake.   the 9/11 committee has concluded that the US was unprepared for 9/11  urlLink in every respect . "On the morning of 9/11, the existing protocol was unsuited in every respect for what was about to happen," the commission's staff report found. "What ensued was the hurried attempt to create an improvised defense by officials who had never encountered or trained against the situation they faced."
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       "Don't fire until you see the whites." "...of their eyes?" "Whose eyes?"     Today marks the 10th anniversary of Roger Ebert's overall favorable review of  Fear of a Black Hat . I would have celebrated June 3rd, the 10th anniversary of the  release  of  Fear of a Black Hat  but... well... the MAN fucked up the dates on me! Yeah! So grab a glass of Booty Juice and pet the P.U.S.S.Y.! WEAR YO` HAT! IT'S RAINING BULLSHIT, G!  Even the president is getting into the spirit of this great day:   "I'm gonna kiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiick your black ass / G's gonna kick your black ass!" 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
           
    
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       here's an  urlLink article  about the marketing of  fahrenheit 9/11 . 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       have any of the rest of you used flat panel displays much? i know gray has one. does the screen seem... sparkly(?) or grainy to you? something about it looks funny to me.. hopefully i'll get used to it. it takes up a lot less desk space, except for the fact that the old monitor is still here looking at me mournfully... 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       so, i was rudely awakened by the downstairs neighbors this wknd. i think the woman was talking loudly on the phone (either that or she was talking to herself or watching tv). eventually, i gave up hope that she'd stop on her own, so i broke out the international signal of apartment noise-related fury and stomped on the floor a couple of times until she caught on.  after that, i had a weird dream. rui and i had decided that instead of me flying to tucson or her flying to seattle, we should *both* fly to london for the wknd. it was 10:20 at night the day before my flight and i was in a panic trying to find an open bookstore b/c i didn't have any kind of guidebook to london. i was freakin' out! i think i was stressing about flying home this wknd. i have to use alaska again (gray! tell your dad to tell SWA that i need later friday-night flights to sacramento from sea-tac, ok?). and the early times at which the bookstores close around here.  john kerry has raked in  urlLink $100million in three months . many people are advising john kerry to just  urlLink stay back and be invisible , letting the bush campaign self-destruct. also, it's  urlLink harder to reach voters nowadays . there's more tv channels, we get so many political mailings that they all go straight into the trash, and increasing numbers of people refuse to participate in telephone polls. on the other hand, it makes it easier to send targeted messages. like, if i wanted to reach the "rui" target demographic, i could broadcast my pro-ham ads on the ham channel, whereas i would reach the "gray" target demographic by showing pro-cake ads on the cake channel.   speaking of political mailings, never ever donate money to anyone. i decided to participate in the giving campaign at work last year, and ever since, i have been *bombarded* with political mailings from anyone who thinks i might possibly be interested in giving them money. and they're very creative at making the mail look actually important so you don't throw it out instantly; your first thought is "crap, is this jury duty? or did i forget to pay my bills for six months? is there a warrant out for my arrest?" when really it's just the american ham foundation trying to solicit donations to buy sandwiches from the olsen twins. Additionally, i get bombarded with mail from companies who took my address from our domain name registration and think i'm a corporation. i get tons of corporate credit card offers, cell phone package deals for 50+ users, big office supplies catalogs... i'm tempted to start stamping "deceased" on them and sending them back, but i've heard horror stories where they report to everyone that you're deceased and pretty soon the coroner shows up and tries to drag you to the morgue. well, not actually the coroner thing, but i've read articles where the "deceased" message gets to the wrong people and your insurance gets canceled or something.  9/11 was originally to involve  urlLink ten airplanes instead of just four , and they wanted to hit targets on both the east and west coasts (including the tallest buildings in CA and WA).   urlLink pearl jam's gone acoustic !  j.ro suggested adding a link to the kim jong il blog, but it hasn't been updated in six months.. it's funny as hell though. i'm trying to remember to add the comic he suggested too. the rest of you should suggest sidebar links (comics, blogs, random stuff) too. or anything to put on the sidebar. there's lots of space!  and gray is evil. yesterday i tried to IM him and he was all "i'm leaving, ham!" and then today he managed to sign off in the second btwn when i opened a window to type a message and when i hit "enter" to send it.   EEEE!!!! i just got an awesome email! i have to go do the i-get-a-huge-new-flatpanel-monitor dance! man, now my normal-sized monitor at home is going to feel even more cramped. i'm far too cheap to buy a LCD monitor for myself. i've been thinking about trying to clear space on my desk. for instance, i never use the printer. i've actually been toying with the idea of completely rearranging my apartment. like, i could put my bed in the dining area and have what's now my bedroom be the computer and guitar area. it might help the yapping/snoring neighbor problem. i'd probably just find out that the other neighbors are noisy 5AM breakfast-eaters or something. i think the people next door think i'm weird and creepy. i was looking at a strange object on the fire extinguisher box (it turned out to be a broken bicycle reflector) just as the neighbors opened their door, and i think they thought i was standing right outside their apartment staring at their door. sigh. here's my apartment in ASCII (for no good reason):     +------+------------------+   | Clo-    CDs             |   | set               Bed   |   +------+                  |    |      | D                |   | Bath | e                |   | room | s                |   |      | k                |   |      +-    +---+-      -+   |             Clo| Closet |   |             set|        |   +------+     +---+--------+   |                         |   | Gui-           Kitchen  |   | tars                    |   |                         |   |               ----------+   +------+          TV      |   |      |                  |   | Coat                    |   | Clo-               Gui- |   | set  |             tars |   +-------                  E   |                        R/   |              Futon    I/|   +-DOOR-----------------F/-+  
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       -Ive found a new manga series that I really like!  Comic Party  is a quirky little series about the world of Japanese doujinshi (fan comics) authors. The characters are really cute: theres the boy who wants to dominate the worlds culture through doujinshi, the main characters girlfriend who carries a  NAIL BAT  (FFVII style), and Chisa, the cute crazy girl. When a heavy cart shes pushing goes out of control and is sort of dragging her behind, she doesnt just say Oh shit! or Get out of the way!. No, its I cant stop this thing! Or global warming! Or the recession! Chisa falls powerless before the merciless law of inertia! all said while said cart rolls uncontrollably. The little shout outs to the fandom are cute too: from the fact that the doujinshi they make in the comic actually ARE based on real anime/manga/game series like  To Heart  and  Parappa the Rappa  to the inclusion of anime fan stereotypes like Fat Sweaty Bastard Who Doesnt Shower During the Entire Goddamn Convention and Has Never Heard of Deodorant and is a Complete Dick. Seriously, he gets around to every fucking con.  The animated series, of course, is completely devoid of all of the humor and insanity of the comic. Its looking like  Love Hina  started a trend. Also, both comics need more titties.   -I wanted to tell Clara about   urlLink Boku no Futatsu Tsubasa  , but I didnt think that she wanted to hear about a comedy manga that starts with incest and then gets weirder while she was work. The English scan-lation can be found at http://www.adtrw.org/tsubasa.php. Oh, and the slang for she had sex with another girl seems to be she pushed her down. Clara, stay the hell out of Japan.   -If you like Dragon Ball Z, youll like  urlLink ButtLord GT . If you hate Dragon Ball Z but were forced to learn something about it, youll probably be highly amused by  urlLink ButtLord GT . http://www.atomictoy.org/comics/buttlordgt/buttlordgt.html">ButtLord GT  -AD Vision, Gainax, and WETA (the guys behind the special effects for Lord of the Rings) are coming together to  urlLink completely fuck up one of my favorite series, Neon Genesis Evangelion . Yes, the original  Evangelion  has its share of problems, but its fun as all hell to watch and did break the giant robot saves mankind genre wide open during the mid 90s. Having them cut it down to less than three hours and then change the cast/story to allow more white people in it (Asuka was hafu, all the other main characters were full Japanese) is like hearing theyre going to redo  I'm Gonna Get You Sucka  for a 30 minute TV episode and cast Jen and Ben in the lead roles. Urg.   
    
    
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink interesting  Kerry has already rewritten the history of what it means to be a Catholic in politics: the last Catholic candidate for President on a major party ticket ran up against suspicion that he would be taking orders from his church. This one is finding his beliefs under fire because he won't.
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       a group called "move america forward" is trying to  urlLink pressure movie theaters not to show  fahrenheit 9/11  . michael moore, miramax, and lion's gate were overheard giggling and exclaiming "OMFGLOL! you can't *buy* this kind of publicity! yippee!"  here's an editorial about  urlLink john "let the eagle soar" ashcroft .  and if we're gonna put someone else on the $10 bill, why not ray charles?      a group called "FaithfulAmerica" is planning to  urlLink broadcast a TV ad in arab countries  featuring a montage of american religious leaders (christian, jewish, &amp; muslim) apologizing for abu ghraib.  anyone seen any interesting lightweight entertainment news today? only thing i saw was yet another rumor that jennifer aniston was pregnant. i think that's just the default story on slow entertainment-news days, but if she is, i'm sure she and brad will come up with an appropriately horrible name for their offspring. i knew a girl in high skool who had been named "felidette" b/c her mother was named something ended in -dette (bernadette, maybe?) and her father was named felix; maybe jen and brad should consider "braddifer." or, they could go with the "famous animals" theme that led courtney cox and david arquette to pick "coco." i'm not sure i know the names of many other famous animals... i guess there's "lassie"... "shamu"... "mr ed"...  hey, here's a question for you all. i've always enjoyed the previews when i go to a movie, but some people seem to hate them with a passion. my feeling is that i like to know what's coming soon (either to see it or to avoid it...), plus they're entertaining, plus it means the movie is about to start and you don't have to sit through the stupid advertising slideshow anymore (does anyone actually pick a realtor because of an out-of-focus slide they saw before  bubble boy  started?). i mean, i hate it when they run video ads for products before a movie, but it seems entirely appropriate to show movie previews. do any of you have strong feelings against movie previews?  i had a weird dream last night. i don't remember most of it anymore, but i do remember that when i looked in a mirror, my nose was enormous. i mean, not just a big nose: it was like the sort of crazy nose you'd find in a picasso painting. it was a relief to check it in the mirror this morning and find it nose-sized.  speaking of noses, you should head over to  urlLink awfulplasticsurgery.com  and take a gander at the picture of lance bass's new nose. it looks awful. i mean, before he was kind of goofy-looking but his features went together ok. the new nose just looks alarmingly weird with the rest of his face, and it draws attention to the fact that he has kind of strange eyes.  oh, and if you look at your profile on  urlLink blogger.com  (you may have to create one first!), it'll tell you how many times you've posted, how often you post, how many external links you've posted, how many words you've written, etc. etc. kind of interesting. 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
         I've been browsing through the new itunes. First irritation is that since I have a french credit card, I apparently must want to view the site in french. I suppose it's not the most enormous of errors, but I find it does get on my nerves. However, to be fair, everyone does this. It seems that apple hasn't managed to get anyone to play nice, so a great many albums are partial and the best songs aren't on. I wasn't particularly surprised that they didn't have "Pays Bleu" the french version of "Durham Town" by Roger Whittaker. Actually, I was surprised that they had  anything  by Roger Whittaker. They have craploads of his stuff. I was dissapointed to find that they don't have Sophie Ellis-Bextor! She's even on Universal International. (don't be surprised if you've never heard of her, she's unknown in the US). Plus they don't have most of the good Kylie Minogue stuff, so no Fever for me. Possibly the worst travesty for a french launch is the omission of Noir Desir, even though their popularity has been somewhat dimmed when the lead singer beat his partner to death in Lithuania. Thankfully, I can still get "There She Goes" by Sixpence none the Richer and drive Gray bonkers. Manu Chao has only one song, but in three different versions. 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       here's an  urlLink answer ! 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       you know how we always say the japanese are weird? at least they don't keep  urlLink rasputin's genitals pickled in a jar  like the russians do... 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I got the best spam EVER today:    Sometimes avocado pit for wakes up, but beyond corporation always borrow money from chestnut inside ball bearing!A few bubble baths, and blood clot behind) to arrive at a state of spiderbeyond abstraction panics, but beyond diskette brainwash garbage can inside.Sometimes for grain of sand prays, but razor blade defined by somnambulist always reach an understanding with fetishist around cough syrup!When light bulb about is lowly, hole puncher related to bur pork chop behind.fundraiser for ceases to exist, because impresario inside fighter pilot laugh and drink all night with ballerina of. rep columbia perimeter prescript deaf annihilate fabian    It... it expanded my mind like Goatse! Yes, images of lava from Hawaii coming soon. And turtles. And dolphins. No more whales, tho.   
    
    
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       rui sent me an interesting  urlLink lawblog . 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       an article about the courtney cox / david arquette baby-naming debacle linked to  urlLink this web page . 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       rui emails me from work sometimes. today, she sent me this: Thanks to you, Brian now calls me &quot;ruibert.&quot;  As in, &quot;Ooooh, Ruibert! Where did you goooo?!  We have to leave now or else we'll miss the start of the movie!!  Stop primping already!  Nobody's gonna see you - the theater's dark!&quot; 
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       aren't you glad your parents weren't celebrities? courtney cox and david arquette have named their first offspring " urlLink coco ." which is a fine name for a sign-language gorilla, but...  and in shocking news, researchers have concluded that angry men who have trouble controlling their anger  urlLink probably shouldn't drink .  michael moore and lion's gate films are  urlLink trying to get the rating for  fahrenheit 9/11  reduced  from R to PG-13.   urlLink new necropolis found near cairo .  i've got a splitting headache... 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       are your children acting up? why not cure them by  urlLink sending them off to a south american reform school with a violent child molester who thinks he's on a mission from god ?  why isn't this illegal? 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This is Wolfram (man), who is engaged to Yuuri (man).   Also, he's so pretty that men in hospitals make miraculous recoveries upon seeing his face.  They're like "Aaaaah! So pretty!!!!" and hop up because they wanna hit it.  Yuuri and Wolfram spend a lot of time talking about how pretty the other is.  We won't even mention the naked man-pile.  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink article  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink seriously  (login: poenews@poenews.com / poenews) 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         JOHN KERRY SAVES DROWNING HAMSTER Jul 31 2004   JOHN Kerry once rescued his children's pet hamster from the sea and gave it the kiss of life. The rescue happened during a family sailing trip when the family's pet labrador knocked the hamster's cage into the sea.  Kerry then dived in and pulled the cage to the surface with an oar before giving mouth-to-mouth resuscitation to the tiny rodent. The tale was told by Kerry's daughter Alexandra to show the human side of her dad who some have branded as dour.
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       no, really.  urlLink 19th century albinos .  oh and here's a followup to the story about  urlLink bush getting erratic and paranoid , but no other news source has as much as mentioned it, so i get the feeling it's bullshit... 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ...so I came within about, oh, one foot of a MASSIVE gash running along my back today. Instead, I got really, really lucky and instead have a fun story to tell the family about how Matt surfed over me like he was in the General Lee and I was Boss Hoss. The feeling of "Oh SHIT" you get when you look up and see another person's board over you... damn. 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       someone looked up " urlLink rui wang sex whore " on google.co.uk and ended up on our website! hehehehe! 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i have a caption for this, but it's so NSFW...      look! i made a photoshop when i got home!     
    
    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       they've invented  urlLink shark repellent . so now, when you're stranded in the ocean thousands of miles from land, you can die of exposure/exhaustion/drowning instead of shark.  those of you with windows:  urlLink install your security updates .  here's an  urlLink article  about how john kerry consolidated the messages of the eight other democrats in the primary in his speech last night. best line from the article: I feared before the speech began that its delivery would be pure Joementum
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       bush's new theme is " urlLink we've turned a corner " which sounds an awful lot like, "ok, yeah, the past four years kind of sucked, but things might be getting better!" the problem with turning corners is that you don't always know what's around the corner. for instance, once i turned a corner and there was a deer!     
    
    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       MSNBC has an article on people whose pets try to interfere with their romantic relationships: Gavriele-Gold tells the story of female client who had a boa constrictor named Crunch and went through various boyfriends over the years. Often she and her boyfriend at the time would end up in the bathtub together and the snake would slither down the shower curtain, surprising the unsuspecting suitor. On more than one occasion, she was forced to call the paramedics to prevent the man from going into cardiac arrest.
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       so, my throat is jsut getting more and more uncomfortable. so i google "tonsil surgery" to read about it in case the doctor decides to cut my tonsils out. and stupid google decides that the search result i want to see is "mother of tonsil surgery boy asks: why did he die?"     AAARGH!     also, this throat business was NOT this uncomfortable until i started taking those stupid green pills. i think the damn surgeon gave me pills to hasten the necessity of surgery! he's thinking "woohoo! one more tonsillectomy and i can afford a new mercedes!" also, my ears are hurting.  ALL DOCTORS ARE QUACKS!  that said, i'm going to keep babbling, 'cause i can't go home for 15 minutes or so. well, i could, but then i'd have to wake up early. and i'd rather stay a little later and get my [CENSORED! TOP SECRET! NDA!] finished and be able to get a full night's sleep.  MSNBC seems to be hinting that  urlLink nanotech is the new dot-com . that is, it's a fancy technology thingee that investors don't understand at all, but somehow think will make them rich. so if you want to make money off of nanotech, you should start a startup now, pay yourself a lot of money to be CEO, and then wait for the nanotech bubble to collapse so you can retire.  here's paris hilton's side of the story of her breakup with nick carter (from the backstreet boys): Both parties agreed the breakup took place over the phone, with Paris getting bonus points for revealing her epiphany and subsequent unorthodox counsel. "I was getting my makeup done [for a photo shoot], and it just hit me: I love Nick, but I need time alone. I called my psychic, and I asked her opinion. She thought I should be alone, and I agreed with her." After the split, she went "straight to the Kabbalah center" in L.A. and picked up a new red string bracelet to help her "deal."
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i came into work late to check something, and you know what? the janitorial staff has been mopping the floors. and they have "wet floor" signs up. but you know what they *don't* say? " piso mojado ." i mean, ever since  forever  in my life, "wet floor" signs have been bilingual! so weird! it's like a foreign country up here!  they'll be sorry when a spanish-speaker slips and falls and sues them to death!  also, " piso mojado " has the bonus that it rhymes with " &iexcl;cuidado! " which makes a way cooler sign than "warning! wet floor!" 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
          
    
    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         clara : god, work sucks  j.ro : =)  clara : rui and i are trying to think of a billion-dollar widget  clara : like those coffee cup sleeves  j.ro : Are you at work?  clara : no  j.ro : Pussy Magnet  clara : :)  j.ro : I'll buy two  clara : knowing your luck, each one will attract a lesbian :)  j.ro : then I will buy THREE  clara : :)  j.ro : So one of them can hold the camera to record what the other two are doing
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink giant microbes!  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
           
    
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
           
    
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        The consensus here in Boston is that Kerry had better not lose. He&rsquo;s got the money, the enthusiasm of Democrats across the country, and a boatload of statistics that put him on top. Carville shudders to think of the consequences of Kerry&rsquo;s loss for the party. &#8220;If Kerry loses, I don&rsquo;t know what will happen to the party,&#8221; he says. &#8220;The rank and file will feel totally let down by the Washington Democrats.&#8221; As for Bush, should he lose the election, Carville cackles in his inimitable way that Bush will be to the Republicans what Jimmy Carter was for so long, an object of scorn and ridicule. &#8220;We&rsquo;ll be running against him in 2012. They&rsquo;ll never be rid of him.&#8221; 
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        garden state  is only showing in NY and LA.  the manchurian candidate  and  harold and kumar go to white castle  are out this wknd though. 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
          john kerry:&nbsp; so like this?&nbsp;  aide:&nbsp; no, no, you want to hold your arm up in more of a straight,&nbsp;unbroken line when the President walks into the room.&nbsp; and keep that thumb up. john kerry:&nbsp; oh.&nbsp;    
    
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i think the EarNose&amp;Throat doctor was a quack. i've been on the antibiotics for two days and there's been no appreciable change in my throatgland situation! essentially, the quack concluded taht maybe i had lingering strep in my tonsils, so i should take antibiotics for two weeks and see if that fixed it. when i've taken antibiotics before, they've kicked in faster than this. and i'm taking six pills a day! sheesh! on the other hand, the right side is now hurting more than the left side, and before the pills, it was the other way around. so.. maybe that means something?   rui sent me  urlLink this NYT article  on  harold and kumar go to white castle   there've been a lot of articles recently about the shocking fact that  urlLink compressed music doesn't sound as good as uncompressed music . how shocking! i wonder if anyone has told these guys that even CD-quality sound is compressed? i was reading a seattle newspaper the other day, and they had one of these compression articles a page away from an article about how, actually, if you really want good sound quality, it's going to be on vinyl (and even *that* is compressed!), but the guy writing the digital-music-should-be-cd-quality article apparently didn't talk to the vinyl-4evar guy. if you want to hear some awesome sound quality, come visit me and i'll play you a record that was recorded live-in-the-studio with one pair of microphones (to properly record stereo sound, you use figure-8 mics at ninety degrees to one another) and no electronics in between the amplifier and the machine that cut the master disc. it's awesome.   the sunburn has peeled off my forehead and now is just peeling off my nose.  this article is  urlLink scary as hell . supposedly, bush is on antidepressants to control erratic behavior.  Tubb prescribed the anti-depressants after a clearly-upset Bush stormed off stage on July 8, refusing to answer reporters' questions about his relationship with indicted Enron executive Kenneth J. Lay.  &#8220;Keep those motherfuckers away from me,&#8221; he screamed at an aide backstage. &#8220;If you can&rsquo;t, I&rsquo;ll find someone who can.&#8221;  Bush&rsquo;s mental stability has become the topic of Washington whispers in recent months. Capitol Hill Blue first reported on June 4 about increasing concern among White House aides over the President&rsquo;s wide mood swings and obscene outbursts.
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink target is selling kabbalah bracelets . 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       make sure your computer monitor has a herpes inoculation before you click these links.   urlLink link 1   urlLink link 2   urlLink link 3  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So the death star is approaching us from saturn...      and the only way to save ourselves is to get one of these computer in a headset things and disappear into a beautiful, perfect escapist, crack-burning virtual world. yay!        
    
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink One Ham  to rule them all ,  One Ham to find them, One Ham to bring them all  and in the darkness bind them. 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink good grief!  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink link  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       the throatdoctor thinks i may have hidden strep in my tonsils taht is making my throat feel all weird all the time. blarg. 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
            Yep. That close.    
    
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
           
    
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i found the perfect place to live while rui and i were in LA. they built new apartments on  urlLink sunset &amp; vine  across the street from amoeba music and the cinerama. on the ground floor, there's a border's books and  a baja fresh ! sadly, the website won't tell me how egregious the rents are, so i'm going to have to email them. i bet it's insane. i don't really care, except that everyone keeps saying that they don't think the rents are as insane as i think they are, and i want to prove them wrong wrong wrong.  ah.  urlLink someone's blog  says 1br's start at over $1550/mo. which is not nearly as ridiculous as i thought it might be.  unfortunately, i already submitted the "send me more info" form, so now i'm going to be spammed with info i don't care about. dammit.  i have an appointment with the throatdoctor tomorrow -- my throatglands have been sore ever since the last time i had a throatdisease, so the doctor thought i should go see someone who knows about throats. i'm guessing it's allergies or stress or something, but the doctor said she didn't think it sounded like allergies or stress. but then, she's not a throatdoctor, so what the hell does she know?  the whole LA trip felt very surreal to me. i think it was because my sleep schedule was off (i woke up at 3:30AM to fly to burbank on thursday) and i spent four days gallivanting all over town. there were points where we were driving and i kept thinking i was in seattle and then i had to remind myself that we weren't and my brain was just utterly confused. i mean, in four days, i went to: burbank airport (2x),  LAX (2x), santa monica (2x), venice beach / muscle beach (2x), shopping on melrose, amoeba (went in 2x, no parking 2x), hollywood & highland mall, colorado blvd (2x), warszawa, nova express (got coffee once, no parking once), el portal, equator (caf&eacute; in pasadena), beverly hills, west hollywood, drove along the PCH past malibu (2x), random drive east of arcadia, little tokyo (i got 2kg of those rice-brick things!), and probably more that i've forgotten. the hotel was in arcadia, which was not exactly central to the gallivanting. it was, however, nonmurderghettoey. dodge stratuses (strati?) guzzle gasoline like crazy. oh, and i drove past the old tenement at 210 south catalina; i was surprised to find it still standing.  i read  rolling stone  on the flight to LA. they had an interesting article on how the dean campaign imploded (at least i think it was in  rolling stone  -- i read a bunch of magazines). it was really interesting. apparently dean and trippi (his campaign manager) hardly talked to one another and trippi was paranoid about losing control, so he wanted to be included in every meeting that anyone had about anything, and he refused to go to iowa even though he's supposed to be an iowa caucus strategymaster. and everyone who worked for the campaign was scairt of trippi, so when he did something stupid, they were afraid to suggest that maybe it wasn't the best course of action.  oh, and al gore seems to be fat again:     maybe it's just a bad photo? 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i'm back. i had a lovely four days in socal. i flew in thursday morning and wandered around for a day and a half until rui flew in friday evening. it was very warm and sunny. i got a sunburn! i should take a picture of my watch tan so you'll all believe me. :)  after i flew in on thursday, i went to pasadena to get a goldstein's bagel for breakfast. i was wandering around eating my bagel when this girl stopped me and asked, "excuse me, do you live around here?" and i replied that i used to but that i no longer did. she asked where i lived now, and i said seattle. then she said something like, "ah, ok, that explains it." and the conversation was clearly over. does anyone have any idea what the hell this was about?  I was mistaken for an amoeba records employee at the store, and once at the airport on the way back (i was wearing an amoeba shirt). i was also mistaken for an employee in a vintage t-shirt shop on melrose. and an italian guy gave me his phone number on the beach. i gave the number to rui when she showed up, but she didn't seem to want another boyfriend.  i spent several hours at the beach in santa monica on friday (where i got sunburned) and several more on saturday (where i got a sunburn on top of my sunburn). the ocean rocks.   food i ate: - el pollo loco - goldstein's bagel - warszawa - el portal - gelato - a sandwich from this awesome shop in beverly hills - ice cream at venice beach - roscoe's fried chicken
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
            Someone needs to grayscale Clinton's face and put it on a red t-shirt. I'd buy two.          
    
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Kill the humans! Eat the humans! Enslave their pets!!      
    
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       They're trying to get the DNC juuuuuust right.  There's a lot of last minute tweaking going on, some of it arousing suspicion.     urlLink  http://english.aljazeera.net/NR/exeres/9FD55FF1-CD66-40BC-8453-C65D9CE709BE.htm   Short version: the Al-Jazeera banner is missing from the convention and no one seems to have a good explination why. Of course, the only source I've found on this is Al-Jazeera, but still...    Also, the latest On the Media floats (and shoots down) the idea that conservative bloggers were targeted to be booted from the convention.     Before I forget:     TEXAS: firmly on the "Do not mess with" list.   
    
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
           
    
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink This is why I don't go to cons anymore . The girl with the pink hair talking about angels? Yeah. THAT'S who I'm always stuck in line next to.    
    
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Awww, look at the cute monkey...apparently it walks exclusively on its hind legs.      
    
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink conjoined freak reptiles !  the 9/11 commission's report is going to include details of  urlLink missed opportunities to prevent it . The most significant signal appears to have come in April 2000, when Niaz Khan, a Briton of Pakistani heritage, walked into the FBI&rsquo;s office in Newark, N.J.  Khan told agents that he had been trained by al-Qaida, the terrorist network that carried out the Sept. 11 attacks, and that there would be a hijacking in the United States or on a U.S. airline.  He said he had been sent to the United States to join al-Qaida operatives here. Even though he passed two polygraph tests, FBI headquarters did not believe him and let him go.  &#8220;I told them before the 9/11 &#8212; more than a year&#8221; ahead of time, Khan told NBC News. 
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
           
    
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
              GWB : ahem...  these aren't the droids you're looking for! iraq and al qaeda are the same thing! john kerry hates america! buy a gas guzzler! it's pronounced 'nuk-yoo-ler!' eck!  say, this patented halliburton mindcontrol brainbroadcaster is awesome!  Impertinent Advisor : um.. mister president? that was 'etc.' not "eck." it's an abbreviation for 'et cetera.' it just means you're supposed to keep broadcasting the same types  of brainwave propaganda.  GWB : how dare you criticize me?! security! take him to darth cheney's dungeon of doom!  Impertinent Advisor : noooooooo!!!!!  GWB : now where was i...  dick cheney is a cuddly teddy bear of a man!! deficits don't matter! michael moore is fat! 
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
          
    
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         " urlLink kate beckinsale plastic surgery "  " urlLink eliza dushku wallpaper "  " urlLink dushku "  " urlLink gantz vampires "   
    
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink seriously . 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Index of /~lutris/fire  &nbsp;    
    
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink michael jackson has fathered quadruplets . 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink link  Researchers gave 322 patients underarm injections of either Botox or salt water.   They received 12 to 14 injections per armpit. Although injection site pain was the main side effect, lead investigator Dr. Dee Anna Glaser of St. Louis University School of Medicine said the needles are so tiny that most patients weren't bothered.   A month later, 75 percent of the Botox users reported a significant decrease in sweating, compared with a quarter of the placebo patients, said Glaser, who is to present the study at this weekend's American Academy of Dermatology meeting.   Patients could get additional rounds of injections every few months, but 43 percent got relief for a year from the first treatment, Glaser said. The median duration of response was about six months.
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i'm the first one here. it's craziness! most of the hallway lights are still off!  i giggled at this headline from MSNBC: Moran: Spy czar won't solve 9/11 problems
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i'm waking up early for the next couple of days so that it's not so shocking when i have to wake up early for my airport shuttle on thursday. well, my alarm went off at 5AM and... i fell out of bed. well, it was more like half "fell" and half "leapt." and i don't know what the hell i was dreaming, but i have a distinct recollection that the leaping had something to do with george w. bush. perhaps he had postponed the elections indefinitely in order to protect democracy and gov't stormtroopers were breaking down my door to rough me up 'cause i had registered to vote and was therefore a threat to democracy.  and  madonna  esther may start  urlLink releasing songs in yiddish . oy vey.. i hear sexhamster's next record might be recorded entirely in klingon. and for some reason rui thinks this means that we need to use audio samples of  urlLink klinger's  lines from M*A*S*H.  and we're a top search result for " urlLink homeland security sucks " and " urlLink asean funny photo ." well, #60-something for the "asean" one. also, we're a top search for " urlLink free pictures of sexy supermodels who are naked " 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
           gray's mom : The air conditioning repairman fell through the ceiling today and got a hideously broken arm and paramedics and fire trucks and cops came and now there is a hole the size of a man in my ceiling.
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i had weird dreams last night. i mostly don't remember them much, except there was one part where i was being chased by carnivorous salmon. see? weird.  they're still thinking about making  urlLink a 4th indiana jones movie . He said fans shouldn't lose hope. "It's still a project that's very much alive. It's in the writing stages right now. George Lucas is working on a script with a writer."
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink FAGGOTS ! The Doody family from Wolverhampton has been crowned The Faggot Family in a national competition, and to kick off their reign they will launch National Faggot Week. 
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i was driving past a church today, and they had a big sign up for summer vacation bible camp. the camp is called " urlLink lava lava -- where jesus' love flows ." so jesus' love is like 750&deg;C molten rock? um.. i think i'll pass...      
    
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       something terrible nearly happened to me today. i went to the strip mall down the road to get coffee. i was wandering around and ended up in the petsmart, where i  nearly bought a hamster or a mouse or some sort of small pet ! they just look so non-evil in their little cages. also, the petsmart was less crappy than the petco where i bought satan -- for instance, the boy rodents and the girl rodents weren't all in the same cage trying to create future generations of rodents -- but still, that's the last thing i need to deal with right now! also, ferrets are apparently legal here. oh, and i saw some fish that kat would love -- they're transparent, so you can watch their hearts beating and their guts working. they were pretty cool, but i don't want to deal with an aquarium.  want to be trendy? then join in the fun of  urlLink this weird new trend ! 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       britney is still insisting on no pre-nup, and the wedding may happen as soon as next month.  urlLink yeesh .  congress is proposing forcing cable companies  urlLink to offer channels in themed groups  so you don't have to pay for everything just to get your special interest all-bacon channel. despite repeated requests, however, they refuse to help jamal get his pimping internship to pay for cable.   we're the #6 search result on dashbar search for " urlLink free fuck ".  and this prank was a bad idea:  urlLink link   here's another one for the political "is it true?" files:  urlLink supposedly, GWB's nickname for karl rove is "turd blossom."  is this true? does anyone know why? and did anyone ever track down any more information on that story about ralph nader's mother not letting him eat cake with frosting on it? 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink seriously.  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ....has an "it's okay to be gay" episode. I... don't know if this&nbsp;exchange was translated right:&nbsp;  &nbsp;   &nbsp;     &nbsp;  ...oh, and GANTZ decided to get a plot. A crazy plot. With dinosaurs, pop stars, Walter Mathau, and vampires. This is some fucked up shit.    
    
    
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       our blog is a top search result for " urlLink hookers waikiki ," a top search result for " urlLink midget boobies ," a top search result for " urlLink pictures of mary-kate olsen  skinny because of cocaine addiction ," a top search result for " urlLink lindsay lohan nipple ," and the  #1 search result  for " urlLink bunny ranch bridget powerz "      
    
    
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink a workout in a pill ! YES!!!! 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink new doomz !     Doom 3 is scary: A couple of times &#8212; embarrassing but true &#8212; I physically jerked my head back from the screen. But there's other good stuff in there, too: The id team has paid a lot more attention to storytelling and voice-acting in Doom 3 than they have in past games. This isn't just a run-and-gun scenario; there's actual plot points and stuff. There's a more cinematic sensibility at work too &#8212; watch for some nice virtual camerawork in the cut scenes. And of course, the creature design has that signature sick flair that one expects from id's artists, who almost certainly were badly mistreated as children. 
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i had ice cream for breakfast. if they insist on dragging me to work, like, two hours early, i need SOMETHING in my stomach to be coherent for the meeting. and all i had was ice cream and carrots, so i went with the ice cream.  also, there was some horrible bird outside my window this morning. i woke up an hour before my alarm, and every time i started to fall asleep again, the bird would make the horrific bird noise. ugh. i knew i should have brought my red ryder BB gun with me when i moved here!  martha stewart got five months in prison. if you really care, she's going to  urlLink give barbara walters an interview . also, she's trying to be all terminator or something; after the sentencing, she vowed, " urlLink I'll be back ." she also gets five months of home confinement, two years of probation, and a $30,000 fine. interestingly, the fine is less than the $51,000 she made on the illegal stock sale.  enron's employees may have been screwed out of their retirements, but rest assured,  urlLink the lawyers will be paid ! if rui ends up being one of these multimillionaire lawyers, i say we all go live in her poolhouse and make her buy us stuff! i want an audi TT and a team of sanitary monkeys to detail it 2x a day! and all the baconshrimp i can eat!  lance armstrong has leapt from 6th to 2nd place in the  urlLink tour de france . woohoo!  slate is wondering today whether  urlLink math counts as a sport . as a former mathlete, i say, "hell no! i'm not a jock! stop calling me a jock! if you don't stop insinuating that i'm a jock, your firewall's gonna be so full of java that your ROMs will overload!" the last time i bought sneakers, all the sneaker stores wanted to sell me sneakers that looked like i might play a sport in them, so i just kept looking until i found sneakers that loudly proclaimed, "don't even think about hinting that i might engage in a sport!" or something like that.  o'reilly's thinking about  urlLink going to london and suing  anyone who criticizes him.  you know the crazy lady who recently admitted herself to a psychiatric hospital? maybe what she needs is someone to put just  urlLink one or two more straws on the camel's back, eh ?  shockingly,  a cinderella story  got  urlLink bad reviews ! cnn says it's "about as appealing as rush hour on the hollywood freeway." (you can avoid that rush hour by taking sunset to mission to fair oaks to california to tech. there's still traffic on sunset, but at least there's more to see on the way.) so, i think we made a good choice by backing lindsay lohan in the feud.  mean girls  was awesome and  freaky friday  was entertaining. whereas duff has made  a crappy cinderella story  and  the crappy lizzie mcguire movie  and  cheaper by the crappy dozen . rui was really mad at lohan the other day b/c she saw a picture where she looked terrible. "goddammit," rui raged, "we picked her side in the feud and she'd better keep herself lookin' purty!" rui then picked at some of the flaking skin on her face and regarded lohan's photo doubtfully. "i suppose she does have a purty mouth," she conceded as she chewed thoughtfully on a three inch strip of skin peeled from her left cheek.  does  urlLink msnbc  load right for any of you? the bottom of the page keeps getting cut off.   jessica simpson is now  urlLink claiming her IQ is in the 160s . maybe she's trying to get out of the music biz and become a professional mathlete. if you have three cans of "chicken of the sea" and then you buy two more cans of "chicken of the sea," how many cans of chicken do you have? 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
           clara :  urlLink http://www.wwwildcats.com/images/bodyart/fish.jpg   [NSFW]  Rui "Fisty" Wang : it's gonna be something horrible isn't it?  Rui "Fisty" Wang : it looks photoshopped  clara : yeah  clara : it's still funny :)  Rui "Fisty" Wang : it's sort of funnier that it's photoshopped...  like, they couldn't find someone hardcore enough
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
           clara : hehe! have you seen the mountain dew spy vs. spy ads?  clara : i always liked spy vs. spy  j.ro : no tv  j.ro : ivory tower, remember?  clara : oh, right  j.ro : I wish the tower got cable  clara : you should steal some  j.ro : how?  clara : cleverly  j.ro : clearly  clara : you could apprentice as a pimp and use your pay to buy cable.  clara : like, maybe an established pimp would let you pimp for him on tuesdays and thursdays and you could keep part of the money.  j.ro : The pimps hate me  clara : well, you shouldn't have burned your bridges!  j.ro : I don't DELIBERATELY anger pimps!  clara : hehe  j.ro : Are you saying I should have bought a whore?  clara : no. then you'd have LESS money for cable.  j.ro : but the pimps are mad beacuse I don't buy  clara : have you tried jedi mind tricks?  j.ro : Yes. Apparently I'm a "nerd faggot"  j.ro : They're not nice people, pimps
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        P-chan: Oh, one of the comics I'm reading. GANTZ. It makes no sense. All is has is violence and naked women. I have no idea why I'm reading it.  P-chan: It's up to chapter 121.  Gray: I'm trying to imagine the writer... Maybe he saw this one episode of 'Jackson' where Jackson picked up a car or something.  Gray: "All is has is violence and naked women. I have no idea why I'm reading it." Oh, I think you do. I think you do.   GANTZ really is crap. I mean really  really  crappy. I get the feeling that this is going to be the new  Ninja Scroll  or  DBZ : the series that, when I say that I like anime, people say "Oh yeah? Have you seen ______? It's so awesome!" and I cringe. Before you ask, NO, I have not seen Ninja Scroll nor do I have any real interest in seeing it. GANTZ though... it's terrible... but you just can't look away. Let me introduce you to the main characters:      This is our hero, Kei. When we first meet him he's all excited because a homeless man is going to be run over by a JR light rail train. And I don't mean "distressed", I mean "Shit, gimmie some popcorn! This is gonna be awesome." He's a real rolemodel      This is our hero's friend, Masaru. He's the goodie goodie. He wants to save crazy homeless guy and manages to get Kei to help. Oh, how noble. Guess what, bitch? The joke's on you: once you help crazy homeless guy off the track, no one is there to assist you and Kei! KERUNCH.     Kei and&nbsp;Masaru wake up to find their heads attached to their bodies and said bodies not under the wheels of a train. They're in a small room with some other confused people who remember dying and... a black ball. This is not ordinary black ball, this is GANTZ. GANTZ commands them to kill aliens for points; when they get 100 points they can leave the room and return to life. Oh yeah, and then Titz shows up.     This is Titz. She has a real name but I'm not going to double-click the page where she introduces herself. She killed herself because she thinks she's worthless and that's probably the second most intelligent decision she's ever made. I've put up with crappy female characters before, but it seems that Titz is there solely to 1) Talk about how much she loves&nbsp;Masaru and 2) have breasts. If the artist could get away with just a pair of boobies tattoed with "I love Masaru" he could save a lot of wasted time drawing the rest of her. Of couse, since she's hot, Kei falls in love with h-.... Kei really, really wants to fuck her and that's the same thing as love, right? Of course it is! But Titz ain't having any of what Kei has to dish out; that's probably the smartest decision she's made.   So that's the first  ONE HUNDRED CHAPTERS  of  GANTZ . They go out. They kill shit. Other members of their "team" die, but they were extras anyway. Kei moons over Titz, Titz moons over Masaru, Masaru is all noble and shit. If you don't like violence, gore, and so many tit shots that I've lost count;  GANTZ  is not the story for you. If you like plot, character development, strong female characters, and romantic dialogue better than "I like... pets. PLEASE HAVE SEX WITH ME!" stay the fuck away until chapter 120 or so.   GANTZ: So Bad It's Good. Sorta.&nbsp; urlLink http://www.omanga.net/?cid=gantz   Next Week:  Yakitate!! Japan     &nbsp;(What, you thought *I* named her that?)        
    
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink teehee!  In his published testimony to the committee, Cassell pointed out that lower courts around the country are hastily cooking up ways to comply with Blakely. Some, believing themselves unable to depart upward from the guidelines, have imposed lower sentences than they'd like (hence the West Virginia drug manufacturer who saw his sentence decrease from 240 months to 12). Some have ruled that under Blakely, judges cannot depart upward from a fixed sentence but can nevertheless go downward. Others have simply put their jurors to back work&#8212;determining the truth of each of the aggravating factors once considered solely by the judge. Prosecutors are scrambling to figure out ways to keep defense attorneys from scoring reduced sentences based on Blakely arguments. ( Watch tomorrow's Martha Stewart sentencing for some serious Blakely-palooza. ) As Cassell puts it, calling this situation a crisis minimizes the efforts of serious judges on the ground who are hard at work making sense of the decision. 
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       be sure to alienate your friends before you find yourself stuck  urlLink shelling out $300+  (per friend!) to attend their weddings in proper attire! and that's  not including  the present! and your friends are assholes, so everything they've registered for is over $750. so at this point, you're shelling out over $1000, and you haven't even factored in jewelry and shoes and travel and the cost to your sanity of putting up with bridezilla for an entire day! see! so if any of your friends start to act like they're thinking of engaging in matrimony, do horrible things to them immediately. you can always apologize after the wedding.    urlLink here's a clip  from the today show of some guy swallowing a camera pill that films your insides. if you ever wondered what the inside of the esophagus or the small intestine looks like while the human is still alive, here's your chance to find out!   urlLink nick lachey and jessica simpson want to reproduce . or possibly adopt a teenager from a developing nation. so, what's scarier? the idea of jessica simpson being a mother, or the fact that britney spears is going to be a stepmother if her engagement doesn't implode?  time to reboot! 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         kat : I'm trying to think of something to put in a card. My ex got type 1 diabetes. I can't really say "Get well soon", since you really don't.  clara : ah. that sucks  kat : So I send a "That sucks" Card?  clara : is there a "don't forget your insulin" card?  kat : I was thinking more "So did you ever get curious and taste your urine to see if it's actually sweet?"  kat : But I don't know if that would be appreciated.
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i went to chipotle for lunch. the line was really long. when i got to the salsa, i asked for the green salsa as usual, and the lady clarified "the green tomatillo salsa" but with a heavy mexican accent, which prompted me to respond with "s&iacute;" rather than "yes." at that point, i was afraid i would have to conduct the rest of the transaction in espa&ntilde;ol, and i had no idea how to say "sour cream" in spanish. "lettuce" i could manage, but not "sour cream."  clara : um.. la blanca  lady : que?  clara : um.. la grasa de leche que est&aacute; vieja  lady : que?!  clara : c&oacute;mo se dice "sour cream," goddammit??! o, y lechuga, por favor.
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       stephen hawking and kip thorne  urlLink BOTH lost the bet .  does anyone else have people-drowning-in-the-ocean dreams? i also had a dream recently where someone was using a canoe to sled down a snowy roof and was heading right for me. the canoe and the snow makes me think they were canadians, so i blame kat.  also, have you guys noticed those stupid fin things on cars? they're like tiny shark fins stuck on the back of the roof of the car, and i mostly see them on BMWs and audis. they really look ridiculous. i suspect it's the result of someone deciding that they're too posh for their rice rocket nowadays, but they can't quite let it go. actually, i hardly see any rice rockets up here. i should try to buy some used 747 wings on ebay and weld them to the top of my car.   ack! i'm having a coughing fit! aargh! *hack!* *hack!* *hack!*  in case you're too stupid to detect your political leanings on your own, slate has a  urlLink quiz .  after hearing recommendations from all sides, i finally watched an episode of  joan of arcadia  the other night. it was the whiniest show EVAR. remember season 6 of  buffy  where she spent at least half the season sulking? IT WAS WHINIER THAN THAT! and at least  buffy  had anya for awesome comic relief when willow and xander and buffy were all whining at each other. now i just need to go through and watch all the episodes of  arrested development  that i've got saved on my hard drive.  and everyone seems to love  anchorman . is it really that much better than it appears to be? gray, you are assigned to go see  anchorman  and report back to the blog.  kerry  urlLink http://slate.msn.com/id/2103764/ " target="_blank">gave his talk  to the NAACP today. bush admits that he avoided them 'cause he was  urlLink scairt .  and  urlLink bear meat is the new pork . hey, gray, if you come visit me, we can go to the  urlLink crazy meat store  and buy  urlLink bear meat ! or maybe not. it's about $50/lb.  Le Monde interviews LeMond, who apparently  urlLink hates america .  today's celebrity weirdness:  Paul McCartney reportedly went ballistic because someone left lilies in his dressing room and he thought they were using up his oxygen. The former Beatle supposedly also demands that all floral arrangements &#8220;must also be as full at the bottom as they are at the top, and he doesn&rsquo;t like tree trunks, so indoor trees are forbidden,&#8221; according to the London Mirror. But a source who knows the singer says, &#8220;If those demands are true, they must be coming from his wife [Heather Mills] because Paul himself is incredibly down-to-earth.&#8221;
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
           Matt :  Pop beauty Christina Aguilera has allegedly fallen victim to a devastating hair loss disease.  - xtra dirty!  clara : are they sure it's not from overbleaching?  Matt : "They don't know if it's alopecia, the disease, or if it's from wearing extensions all these years. Her hair is falling out. Her new look is supposed to cover up the hair that she's already lost."  clara : how scandalous!
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink garry trudeau went to yale with george bush .  Trudeau said he penned his very first cartoon to illustrate an article in the Yale Daily News on Bush and allegations that his fraternity, DKE, had hazed incoming pledges by branding them with an iron.
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       avril lavigne doesn't seem to quite understand how this celebrity feud business works. she started off decently by calling hilary duff a "goody-goody," but she seems to be  urlLink trying to start a feud with prince charles  now... next, she plans to feud with a herd of sheep, or possibly the great wall of china!     
    
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       telling blonde jokes to blonde people  urlLink MAKES THEM DUMBER ! let's try to get research money to see what happens if you lock paris hilton in a room and tell her blonde jokes for, like, a week straight. 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       it's something of a momentous day. that is, it's the 1yr anniversary of when i started work. woo. this means that i have to bring in one pound of M&Ms for others to consume. (you're supposed to bring in one pound for every year you've worked here) if i were slightly more evil, i would have bought a big bag of M&Ms and then thrown in a small bag of skittles just to screw with people. anyhow, i need to steal someone's chair so i can put this ugly watermelon-patterned bowl out in the hallway.  i also finally got my WA driver's license, which i was supposed to do 11 months ago. the picture was surprisingly good. my caltech ID picture was good too. perhaps taking good ID pictures is my hidden talent. sadly, i don't think it's a terribly marketable skill. it's also recent, since i don't like my CA license photo (taken when i was 16), and let's not even talk about my passport photo (taken when i was 17). yeesh. the process of getting the license required waiting in line to talk to a dude, then taking a test on the computer, then waiting in line AGAIN to talk to the "i passed" lady, and then getting my photo taken, and then waiting AGAIN for the temp license to print. much waiting. someone at work had sent around a "random numbers from the driver's guide that you should memorize" document that was very helpful. it's a pain to read the driver's guide and try to pick the numbers out of the text. so, anyhow, i am now a legally licensed driver in the state of WA, instead of the outlaw that i've been for 11 months. i also registered to vote. so, how long before they want me for jury duty?   urlLink are you tired? tell us why!   courtney love has been  urlLink institutionalized . let's all cross our fingers and hope she'll be transferred to a facility near tucson and rui will end up being her court-appointed attorney!  the senate voted 50 to 48 to  urlLink stop wasting their time with the gay marriage amendment . even  urlLink lieberman  was against it! "Isn't that the ultimate homeland security, standing up for marriage, defending the right of children to have moms and dads, to be raised in a loving environment," said Senator Rick Santorum of Pennsylvania, who was a key sponsor. "That is what this debate is all about."
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
           
    
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink your brain is weird . 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       fair and balanced? if you're interested in seeing  outFOXed , see if there's a  urlLink moveon outfoxed party  in your area. otherwise, i think you have to buy it on dvd.  rui and i had a codependent4EVAR moment earlier today -- i went to email her and she had just emailed me a couple of minutes beforehand. she's going to be housesitting and taking care of a cat; she's worried that the cat will die in her care. she also informs me that "bunny" is a nickname for "bernice." i think bunny has a new nickname.  sara jane olson (the woman who had been involved with the symbionese liberation army and was a fugitive for 30 years) got her 14-year sentence  urlLink thrown out . she'll be sentenced again in a the next couple of months.  click  urlLink here  to read about the state of sci-fi on tv. there's a  buffy  animated series in development! and since most of the cast doesn't really have anything to do nowadays, they'll be doing the voices. SMG, despite not having much to do nowadays, won't be participating; maybe she's busy filming  scooby doo 3 ? and  doctor who  is coming back to the BBC in 2005, which you guys probably don't care about, but i always liked the show. and: "The Man with the Screaming Brain" STATUS: Due in 2005 on the Sci-Fi Channel  We don't know much about this upcoming Sci-Fi-Channel movie beyond that the writer, director and star is Bruce Campbell ("The Evil Dead," "Bubba Ho-Tep"), and that means this meal will be especially tasty for those who like extra cheese. Campbell plays a wealthy businessman out for revenge after a mad scientist replaces part of his brain with that of a Russian spy. It's a story ripped from today's headlines!
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       you can read about  urlLink read about  outFOXed   here. it's a documentary about fox news.   urlLink hmm...    urlLink the marriage amendment vote appears dooooomed . doom doom doom doom doom do-doom doom.  it's amazing how shitty the US track team is  urlLink without their supersteroids .   urlLink more courtney love troubles . among other things, her former legal team is suing her for unpaid attorney's fees. oh, and here's  urlLink more courtney love craziness .  if i were in charge of designing the next generation of computers, i would design them with necks, so that i could throttle them when necessary.  remember that french woman who was attacked by a band of antisemites on a train? turns out she's just  urlLink crazy  and she made the whole thing up. speaking of crazy people who made the whole thing up, what ever happened to that girl who pretended she was kidnapped but kept sneaking back to her apartment to check the weather?   urlLink sales growth is higher at posh stores (neiman marcus is up 13%) than at the non-posh (walmart is up 2.2%) . It's axiomatic that rich people are likely to be more optimistic and confident than those with less money, so the raw differentials aren't that surprising. But in the past few years, the readings for all income groups have generally moved in the same direction. If the economy were undergoing a broad-based expansion, if a rising tide were lifting all boats equally, you might expect that trend to continue. But the views of the rich and poor are moving in opposite directions. The split results-the growing pessimism of the poor and the growing optimism of the rich-suggest the economy's improvement isn't helping everyone.
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink weirdness  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       My hand hurts so I don't want to pimp  Yakitate!! Japan  today. However, the manga is too crazy not to share. Coming to the blog soon:  Large Japanese Men    Crazy Faced Old Men    Angry Nuns    ...Brad... Pitt...?    ...and bread. LOTS of bread.  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Matt : [ urlLink link ]  you should put these photos side by side and ask who is uglier on the blog
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i think  urlLink bush seriously pissed off the NAACP  by refusing to speak at their convention... (he's the first president since the '30s to skip it, btw)   urlLink pelicans are being fooled by mirages  in phoenix. "They try to land on the water, but it's asphalt and it's 'Bam! That doesn't feel so good,"' said Sandy Cate, director of the Arizona Game and Fish Department's wildlife center at Adobe Mountain in north Phoenix.  Wildlife experts believe the endangered birds are experiencing a food shortage along the West Coast and are heading to Arizona to find fish. 
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink If you hate music, click here!!!   Each of the track lists has samples of each song. It's... painful. Stay away from "Bring Me to Life" and "Hey Ya" 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ron reagan jr. will be addressing the democratic convention on the importance of stem cell research during the primetime broadcast.  urlLink no shit . The Kerry adviser said Reagan's appearance at the convention would communicate to the American people that the Democratic ticket of Kerry and Sen. John Edwards "won't put ideology in front of sound science and let politics get in the way of what is best for the American people."
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
          (hint: the woman is lynne cheney)  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Letterman's Top Ten List: Top Ten George W. Bush Complaints About "Fahrenheit 9/11":   10. That actor who played the President was totally unconvincing  9. It oversimplified the way I stole the election  8. Too many of them fancy college-boy words  7. If Michael Moore had waited a few months, he could have included the part where I get him deported  6. Didn't have one of them hilarious monkeys who smoke cigarettes and gives people the finger  5. Of all Michael Moore's accusations, only 97% are true  4. Not sure - - I passed out after a piece of popcorn lodged in my windpipe  3. Where the hell was Spider-man?  2. Couldn't hear most of the movie over Cheney's foul mouth  1. I thought this was supposed to be about dodgeball 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink really . 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
          
    
    
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
           Rui : if i were gay, i would never tell my parents until i had knocked up a girl and HAD to.
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink SONIC.jpg  um.....yyyyyeah.   urlLink calvin.jpg  Can't stop here; this is Zorgon territory.    urlLink imagek.gif  I'm... I'm gonna burn down the building.    urlLink example.gif  Why are they so stupid?   urlLink bebopmovie.jpg  I wish this wasn't just a photoshop.   And finally: MAN FAYE WEEK CONTINUES!!!  urlLink Manfayeass0882.jpg  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        In the summer of 2001, when much of the Republican and Democratic policy community was obsessed with missile defense, [John] Edwards urged more attention to terrorism. The North Carolina senator had such limited luck pitching an OpEd article on terrorism to major newspapers that the piece, warning of poor cooperation among federal and local law enforcement, ended up in the weekly Littleton Observer, circulation 2,230 -- four weeks before the Sept. 11 attacks. 
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i hate my downstairs neighbors. they are pure evil. she seems to be incapable of talking at less than 130 decibels, and he snores so loudly that it wakes me up.  someone sent an email to a social email list here asking about learning to rollerblade, and there's all these people insisting that you HAVE to wear $400 worth of protective gear if you dare venture outside. when did people get to be such wimps? when i was a little kid, i would rollerskate without a helmet or kneepads or wristpads or elbow pads, or an entire protective kevlar suit, or a trained professional to rollerskate for me while i sat in a bulletproof box filled with cotton wool. and, yeah, sometimes i fell down and removed large quantities of skin from my knees and bled a lot, but so what? a scraped knee isn't gonna kill you. neither is falling on your ass. and you look ridiculous with 600 lbs of protective gear on.  here,  urlLink read more about keira knightley . they made her  urlLink bulk up  for the movie. with exercise, i imagine, not bacon.  does anyone else feel like, whether michael jackson is guilty or not, that district attorney tom sneddon is  urlLink way too personally involved in the case ? the more i read about things he's saying or doing w.r.t. the case, the more my brain thinks "witch hunt!"  ok, i keep seeing good reviews of  anchorman . wtf?! somone go see it and try to justify all these good reviews to the rest of us...  i've got a splitting headache. i suspect it's from not sleeping because of my neighbors. aargh! who has suggestions for revenge? i'm betting kat will suggest something involving butyric acid. at the moment, i'm stuck with "stomping on the floor until they fucking stop whatever the hell they're doing down there." oh, the revenge suggestions have to take into account the fact that my apartment is above them and i don't want to destroy it in the process of revenge. like, if i introduced 10,000 cockroaches/hamsters/ferengi to their apartment, they'd be miserable, but so would i, so that'd be no good, you see? also, everyone else in the building is fine, except for the people in the other half of the building who have loud cult meetings sometimes. but they don't do it that often, and i don't want to mess with a crazy cult. 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
          or why I giggle so much when I see it. 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       people who live near madison square garden have been told to stay inside during the GOP convention, and to stock up on food, water, and any required medication.  urlLink seriously . 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink article  In Jacksonville, election officials are now investigating charges by Dario Cruz and his wife that GOP organizers illegally marked his registration form and dozens more as "Republican" when he went to register to vote for the first time.
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink howard dean is going to debate nader  on NPR on friday. i hope someone asks ralph about the cake incident... i REALLY want to know if that's true.  and, again, why can't they make 4 oz. cokes?! i want *some* coke with my burrito, not an entire can! aargh! i'm going to go throw the rest out now.  and you should all learn from my mistake: NEVER GET LIME JUICE IN A PAPERCUT. it's one of those things that hurts way out of proportion to any damage that could possibly have been caused.    urlLink some crazy computer programmer is trying to visit every starbucks.    urlLink only 57% of americans read a book last year , down from 61% the year before. Speaking of Kerry's "better hair" comments, we hear that wife Teresa wasn't crazy about the line. (Smart woman.) The Senator, who repeated the line at several stops Wednesday, told reporters last night that she scolded him, "You just lost the bald vote." 
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i installed my new RAM and it did something horrible. all the machine will do now is start to boot and then BSOD. i'm posting this from work while i try to look up a solution to my problem. computers suck. 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So the new XP Service Pack is gonna roll out soon.   From  urlLink Cnet     Downside:  For one thing, this service pack is late. Had it arrived just three weeks earlier, the world may have been spared damage from Sasser and other viruses. And the download isn't small. For someone who hasn't downloaded a Windows update for eons, the file can top off at 270MB, but Microsoft estimates that most downloads (for folks who have been good about running Automatic Updates) will come closer to 100MB.  As with any service pack, we wouldn't be surprised to see a couple of compatibility issues between SP2 and some apps already installed on your PC. Microsoft assures us it's doing everything it can to combat app compatibility issues, but we suggest exercising caution and waiting a few weeks tdsfo see if there are any major problems with SP2 before installing it.   
    
    
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i tried installing the new mobo, but it just does this crazy endless reboot cycle thing. I AM NOT A HAPPY HAMSTER! WHERE'S MY COMFORTING BACONVAT?!   UPDATE:  ok, i managed to get myself out of mobo hell. then i had to deal with network hell. now i just have videocard hell and why-does-my-cpu-think-it's-crappy-and-not-l33t hell.      
    
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Oh, and if Clara doesn't post sometime this weekend... her computer is fucked.    
    
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       jamal and i agreed that you and i have to go on a mission from Glod to get the band back together and then we have to take a busload of groupies to mesa verde in colorado. ok?      
    
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         clara : i love tv ads for drugs where the side effects are far worse than what they're curing  clara : "this drug cures light allergies. it causes explosive diarrhea in 87% of test subjects, and spontaneous death in the remaining 13%"  Connie : yeah, like here is something for allergies however it will cause migraines, vomiting, and congestive heart failure  Connie : oh my god! codependent!   clara : CODEPENDENT 4EVAR!
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       so, i got teh d00mz last night. it's very cool and creepy. my computer, however, is not happy with running it (it sucks when the lights go out and you're in a red fog and three guys are trying to kill you and all you can see is lag). i talked to gray this morning and he said that since it's been 18 months, it's time to buy a new mobo. fry's has a mobo deal and a RAM deal this wknd, so that's probably what i'll be doing this wknd. it'll be a pain in the ass 'cause it involves pulling most of the components out of the computer. but teh d00mz should run better! if you don't hear from me this wknd, i fucked it up.  i think rui's passing through seattle this weekend. we're going to hang out for a few hours. she's heading up to canada with her parents, eh?   urlLink bill clinton will appear on  the daily show  , but will skip SNL.  apparently there are springsteen fans who are shocked and angry that springsteen is supporting the democrats. do they *listen* to what the man is singing?  here's a  graph of  urlLink all polls of bush's approval rating . and  urlLink electoral-vote.com  has new polling data.   urlLink job growth was not good . wall street is not happy.  OMG!  urlLink rick james died !   urlLink GWB opposes legacy college admissions . ponder that.   urlLink the world's hairiest man had his ear hair removed  so that he could hear. 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       this is so delightfully evil:  urlLink so evil   oh and here's a blog showing how  urlLink terror alerts always seem to come when GWB's numbers are down .  also, here's a  urlLink fool's map of the world . 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
          
    
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So for my first post I thought I would share a dream a colleague of mine in the math department had:  In his dream, he saw Ronald Reagan dressed in pink cowboy attire rocking slowly in a rocker. My friend asked Ronnie why he was so happy; Ronnie told him that he wanted to thank god for making him gay and letting him run an abortion clinic.  The morale: Dont fight god's plan for you. You'll just end up doing it in the afterlife and in the meantime he'll give you Alzheimers.  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Matt: i guess #1 Matt: ok P-chan: The first story? Is that your final answer? Matt: final P-chan: Can you tell us why you picked it, Matt? Matt: i dont believe that NCSU sweaters are gang clothes anywhere and I dont see you asking a hooker about the intracacies her trick Matt: but its mainly a guess Matt: i really hope its the I one though Matt: the thought of people out there asking for I is hilarious P-chan: Well Matt, while you're wrong about the NCSU wear not being gang clothes (they are), you ARE right about which story is real! Congradulations, you get a Sexhamster account!!!!!!!!  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         clara : did you read about that lady who could swim in antarctic waters for hours and not die?  Connie : the mutants among us!   clara :  urlLink http://www.doversolo.com/antarctica.htm   clara : "Battling dysentery, she swims a 15-mile stretch of the Nile, pushing through raw sewage and rotting animal carcasses"  clara : this sounds like your sort of extreme sport!  Connie : ugh!   Connie : why would someone do that?   Connie : what is the great accomplishment in swimming a sewage tank? 
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink link  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
           
    
    
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i got all my hell-work done. i was here until 10PM last night, but i got it done. i am *so* leaving early on friday to play teh d00mz.  bush told a roomful of top pentagon brass that his administration would not stop looking for ways to harm the US.  urlLink seriously .  the LA times has an  urlLink electoral vote flash thingee  that you can play around with.  teresa heinz kerry is cool: While in Monroe, Kerry and Heinz Kerry also visited Baumgartner&rsquo;s Cheese Tavern, where Heinz Kerry walked around the store with a Limburger cheese sandwich with raw onions and mustard on rye. She waved the stinky sandwich in the face of everyone around her.  &#8220;This is how I&rsquo;m going to get some privacy on the bus,&#8221; she said as people recoiled with scrunched-up noses.  Heinz Kerry explained that she doesn&rsquo;t like cheese unless it stinks. &#8220;Cheese that doesn&rsquo;t taste is just empty calories,&#8221; she said.
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Matt, this one is for you.   NPR has a fun little show called  Wait, Wait, Don't Tell Me . It's a super cheesy news quiz, but it has Mo Rocca so that's okay. One of the segments on the show has a celebrity listen to three strange news stories and attempt to guess which one is real. I thought it might be fun to do something like that with some of the experiences I've had since coming to Hawaii (and, most importantly, since I started using public transportation. Jesus.)   So, Matt:  urlLink here are three stories . One of them is real. The other two are crap. Tell me which is the real one and YOU get a SH blog account, courtesy of our sponsor Claraham. 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
           
    
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
           
    
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink SUVs are actually illegal on a lot of CA streets . someone should enforce this.   urlLink current electoral vote predictor . or you can read about  urlLink poll numbers .  britney spears is.. well, read for yourself: Don&rsquo;t be surprised if you see thrift store shoppers wearing belly-baring designer clothes around Britney Spears&rsquo; hometown of Kentwood, Louisiana. The crooner is doing some major closet cleaning, and is sending the outcast stuff to a local Goodwill. 
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       it's a  GTA: san andreas  screenshot:     
    
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         See, Wolfram isn't REALLY gay, it's just that he was engaged to Yuui by accident and it hurts his pride to think that ANYONE would stray on him. Yeah.     See, Gunter... Gunter... um.  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink NK missiles can now hit the mainland.   
    
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       here's a  urlLink TIME article about doom 3 . have any of you bought it? i don't think my computer's powerful enough to run it. my cpu's the "minimum required" and i'm don't remember if i have 32 or 64 megs of RAM on my video card... 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       there's a mailing list at work for questions about where to go in the seattle area for certain goods and services and most of the questions are fairly innocuous ("where should i get my subaru serviced?" "can anyone recommend a dentist?"). every once in a while, some guy is forced to ask for an OB/GYN recommendation for his wife. but the question that just showed up takes the cake: "i'm looking for a good doctor for hemorrhoid removal in the area. any recommendations?"  it's fucking freezing in here. also, it's cloudy and grey outside. blech.   urlLink ted koppel and jon stewart faced off  at the democratic convention.  germany has  urlLink really weird muggings .  kat, you may have to face up to the fact that  urlLink kirstie alley is gray's soulmate : "I don't consider fat a disease. I mean, c'mon, who had the (expletive) gun to my head? Nobody! What gene in my body says I have to eat four cakes instead of two? It's a choice."
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i heard a nasty rumor that tonsils can take months to stop being swollen even after you fix whatever's making them all inflamed. stupid fucking asinine human immune system.  here's a link to a picture of  urlLink someone's removed tonsil . 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       matt sent me  urlLink this . the sound quality is really good. 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         j-ro : Oh, Eliza Dushku is gonna pose for playboy. Neat  clara : are you serious?  j-ro : Wait, goddamnit. Why would anyone link an article dated APRIL FIRST. Asshats.  clara : :P  j-ro : sorry  j-ro : If this had been an actual Naked Dushku Event you could have turned to your radio for further instructions.
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
          The purple haired person with the tiarra? That's Gunter. Yes, that's a man.  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       my tonsilmedicine is causing a terrible taste in the back of my throat. i wasn't sure if it was the cause, but then i looked up the side-effects and that's one of the possible side-effects, so that's what it is. or possibly my tonsils are going septic? plus, i think the antibiotics have killed off all the digestybacteria in my guts, so i feel sick. and my throat is still uncomfortable. doctors are all quacks! i found a  urlLink web page on tonsils  that mentions diptheria. i think i have diptheria. what's diptheria? nevermind. i looked it up. i don't have diptheria. it sounds awful.  they found  urlLink a new tomb in cairo . 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       this wknd SUCKED. i spent the entire time running back and forth to work every couple of hours, and then the lab thwarted me, 'cause just when i was almost done, they shut down for maintenance. goddammit. i am so incredibly pissed off.  hey, jamal,  urlLink clinton's gonna host SNL sometime next season .  here's an article on  urlLink how to steal an election . or something. i'm too pissed off to read it, but it looked interesting for when i'm calmed down. 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Mostly I speed because I need to keep my brain active. I'm sorry, but if I have to drive 60 I'm going to fall asleep. The reason the freeways in Seattle move so slow is because the other drivers are beating their kids, putting on makeup and holding a cell phone conversation. For those of us who are actually DRIVING, 60 is too slow. If you're doing 10 other things, 60 is about right.
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink the shocking article ! 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ... but fails to realize that YES, a dollar spent in Iraq IS a dollar not spent here NOW. No amount of talking about the "greater good" or whatever is going to get you around that. The question is whether or not it's worth it as preventative and as an obligation. I liked Kerry's speech, but that isn't to say that there aren't  urlLink some problems with parts of it . That, however, is the nature of politics.  Hmmm... I can't find the mp3 anymore on Google. If anyone wants it, I still have it (and Obama's. BTW, what the HELL country did Obama's family move to because it sure as fuck wasn't America... or anywhere on Earth.)  
    
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        A senior spokeswoman for the National Archives denied a report Friday morning that Archives officials have cleared former Kerry-Edwards campaign adviser Sandy Berger on charges that he withheld documents from the 9/11 Commission.   "In spite of what the Wall Street Journal said, the National Archives really isn't commenting on this case because it's under investigation," Susan Cooper, chief spokeswoman for the Archives, told NewsMax.com.
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       the government of  urlLink iran  is friendlier to transsexuals than the state of  urlLink florida .  and  urlLink sandy berger has been cleared of all charges . 
    
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ok, so  urlLink the bush administration has made us infinitely safer from terrorists *and* al qaida is going to blow up NYC ? logically, shouldn't only  one  of those be true...?  in related news, you can read  1984   urlLink online .  so, now that we've seen all the pictures of john kerry in a clean suit, do you suppose they'll start showing us pictures of people in clean suits while talking about terrorists working feverishly in labs trying to create nuclear/chemical/biological weapons, allowing us to draw the conclusion that john kerry is in league with the terrorists? 
    
    
    
</post>


</Blog>