<Blog>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hmm. here is an interesting email i sent to sam pieter. posting it here for archiving purposes.  may 16   i am at that convergence zone between rediscovering everything and intellectual dreariness. its like im on the edge of a cliff, waiting for the right moment--perfect combination of wind velocity and direction, precise positioning of feet, the delicate balance between bodily tension and relaxation has been achieved--for me to take flight.   began feeling this way last year, during my birthday, or maybe even before that and shared this with ditas and she just looked at me like she knew this feeling and that it passed her by and that she wasnt changed by it (she is 40 this year). would i feel the same way when i reach 40??? i sure hope not!   ronnie's death was like the blank wall for me... no its not a blank wall. its more like the wall of lamentation where the jews just sit, stand, squat in front of it, grieving--all thoughts, all aspirations, all will leaving them and just giving in to grief, facing the deep, formless void we know and call as grief...   but now after 3 years, my tears have dried up and i no longer find comfort in the reserves of my sorrow.   so i turn away from the wall and find myself hungry, thirsty, greedy for everything--love, friendship, empirical science, theoritical science, sex, mathematics, rain and wind, the taste of mangoes in a hot summers day...--everything that was and wasnt before he died...   this is all so confusing and exhilarating   urlLink speaking of sam 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      and to those who can read Filipino and can appreciate Filipino humor, here's something from  urlLink Pugad Baboy  and to those who can't, something from  urlLink mark fiore  
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      today, in delayed telecast of course, the whole country saw  urlLink how Filipino wonder Manny Pacquiao beat  into submission a great boxer from the land of the  urlLink aztecs  and  urlLink mayas , Marco Antonio Barrera. it was a great fight. Pacquiao, he of the speed and the power. And Barrera he of the great heart and courage.
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      sheesh. i slept through the darn leonid shower! grrr. but to those who live on the other side of the world, you might just have the chance to watch it. please check out the  urlLink rednova news   have fun!
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      today is the first day of my blog life :-) and it is my birthday too. to start off this nice, hmm, rainy day, let me direct you to a  urlLink van gogh painting  which is also my favorite :-) and oh yes, later at 1:45am, November 14 there's going to be a starfall, courtesy of the Leonid showers. 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Christmas is not  really   my favorite time of the year. It's up there in my list of least favorite times of the year (top of the list is my monthly dysmenorrhea). 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      "We gave up any thought of flying long ago," is the first line of Korean poet  urlLink Kwang-kyu Kim's   poem entitled "Going home in the evening".   then, here's a poem from Denise Levertov, an American poet, called  urlLink The Secret   and oh here's a lovely lovely  urlLink poem by Federico Garcia Lorca  although one reader said it was the worst translation of the poem he has ever encountered. I'm now looking for other translations, although whether it is better or not I would have no idea since I speak only one word of Spanish and that word is not even fit for polite company.  and to wake up from this stupor, here are some articles from  urlLink Mark Twain on the German language , with his usual sardonic wit. Learning the language must have traumatized him in his childhood.
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I once had a lively discussion with a friend on circumcision, although he prefers to call it 'human genitalia mutilation' and then he would launch into a passionate discourse on the attendant psychological effects, not to mention the violation of a child's right to his foreskin, of such mutilation. Anyway, I just had it from a reliable source that the biblical precedent of circumcision was in the Old Testament (a pause here while all self-respecting Christians sift through their worn and dog-eared copy of the Old Testament). So, as I already said, in the Old Testament when Saul was a king and David is still wet behind the ears, it came to pass that David asked the hand of King Saul's daughter for marriage. King Saul, true to his form (which form, I decline  to elaborate for fear of being torched on the stake as a heretic--which I am-- or as a witch--which sadly I am not) asked for the foreskins of 100 Philistines as a dowry for his daughter. Of course, David, true to his form (which form, I decline to elaborate for fear... oh you know the rest) killed not 100, but 200 Philistines, circumcized them (flaccid penises aren't difficult to circumcize? forgive my ignorance but I've never circumcized anyone before) and presented to King Saul his grisly gifts of love (a point in inquiry--one wonders what cut design David used to unburden his dead enemies, was it a German cut, or the St. Bernard cut? what, there is no St. Bernard cut? I must have been thinking of something else). And so it came to pass that all men shall suffer mutilation or face humiliation because a drooly lovestruck he-man decided to marry the daughter of an AR king.   I am now seeking membership in an organization that will end and eradicate the practice of circumcision the world over. They exactly have 3 other members. 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm now in the research stage on  urlLink tea and the art of tea drinking  and although some might tell me, "Just enjoy the tea", I'd enjoy it more if I have some trivia in mind like: A tea picker in Assam, India is paid only around $1 for a 12-hour workday, picking and delivering an average 54 kilograms of tea leaves.  Enjoy your cup of tea!
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      and here's a joke i received at 4:50am today... so don't be surprised if im going to be extra-weird today :-)  "It was the mailman's last day on the job after 35 years of carrying the mail through all kinds of weather to the same neighborhood.  When he arrived at the first house on his route, he was greeted by the whole family there, who congratulated him and sent him on his way with a big gift envelope.   At the second house they presented him with a box of fine cigars.   The folks at the third house handed him a selection of terrific fishing lures.    At the fourth house he was met at the door by a strikingly beautiful blonde in a revealing negligee.    She took him by the hand, gently led him through the door (which she closed behind him), and led him up the stairs to the bedroom where she blew his mind with the most passionate love he had ever experienced.    When he had had enough they went downstairs, where she fixed him a giant breakfast: eggs, potatoes, ham, sausage, blueberry waffles, and fresh-squeezed orange juice.    When he was truly satisfied she poured him a cup of steaming coffee. As she was pouring, he noticed a dollar bill sticking out from under the cup's bottom edge.    "All this was just too wonderful for words," he said, "but what's the dollar for?"    "Well," she said, "last night, I told my husband that today would be your last day, and that we should do something special for you. I asked him what to give you." He said, "Fuck him, give him a dollar."    The blonde then said, "The breakfast was my idea."   You dont want to know from  urlLink whom this joke came from . 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      There are shades of how much embarrassment one is willing to suffer. Or shades of self-deception. Or shades of desperation.   The important thing is that one  knows .
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Its a crazy week this week. After the  urlLink Chinese New Year's  festivities comes the  urlLink Dinagyang Festival . This, of course, wretchedly caused havoc in traffic. I think I've walked from one place to another enough kilometers to make up for my swimless days.  Speaking of Chinese New Year, my Chinese Astrology Personality is   The general description about this person is prudent, cautious, intelligent, self-conscious, self-concerned and innovative.   One word for people born in this month is  stubborn .  These people are often very stubborn. They are very determined and are willing to accept any challenges. They work very hard to carry a project through and are unwilling to give up. This type of people has a strong urge to complete tasks and hate to leave anything unfinished. Most of them are serious and have a strong sense of justice and responsibility. It always leads them to success. They are very cautious and think slowly before they act. Their overly honest and stubborn attitude tends to make them appear very impatient and inflexible. But generally, they are nice and kind. They will not express their discontent to other easily.    While you, Sam, is   The general description about this person is stormy, passionate, independent, intuitive, diplomatic, social, clever, free, leadership, energetic, self-motivating and ambitious.   One word for people born in this month is  intuitive .  These people deal with life through their intuitions. They move confidently along their feelings or instincts. They are proud and dignified. They set high expectations or goals on themselves in order to achieve perfection. Their concentration and efforts are very persistent. They are serious and active about their work. They enjoy leadership and have lots of energy to take on more responsibilities at work and at home. It is difficult for them to compromise or accept other peoples’ ideas as they handle things solely with their intuition. They are very independent, but they need a lot of attention from other people in their social life. They have the ability to associate with different people by creating an intellectual atmosphere. They need to be accepted and be at the center of attention. They are very impractical about life, as they are not easily satisfied. Their expectations keep growing, which create a lot of worries for themselves.    ... ... ...  Um...  You're right Sam, astrology is a silly, mindless thing.  
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      "... a poem should be like proving a theorem to be true--a beautiful, structured, logical set of axioms, and equations and givens to prove that yes, if  a  is equivalent to  b  and  b  is equivalent to  c , then  a  is equivalent to  c ..."  wrote this to sam in the summer of 2003. i was gabbing about poetry and mathematics and the parallels between the two disciplines...  and here's something from Virginia Woolf, a mood in which I'm in right now:  "I want to think quietly, calmly, spaciously, never to rise from my chair, to slip easily from one thing to another, without any sense of hostility, or obstacle. I want to to sink deeper and deeper, away from the surface, with its hard separate facts. To steady myself, let me catch hold of the first idea that passes."  
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       This is work that is alive,  Effervescent, free, liberated, Gloriously enlightened,  True, and great. Do you think it can be attained By people who shut the door And sit quietly with blank minds?                                                                    - Liu I-Ming  Its from that Zen link (see below).   
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today I'm in the mood for concentrating my mind and I once read that there are 4 ways to concentrate the mind. These are:  1. Drinking tea. 2.  urlLink Meditation . 3. Taking a  urlLink walk . 4. Feeding fish.  I've done tea-drinking  and  reading my materials on teas.   I walk a lot.  I walk and walk and walk but still not reaching the sun. What's there in a long walk, after all?  That's an old poem I wrote while I was in the university and was in one of those infinitely bored moods all college students suffer from once in a sober while.  I don't know how to meditate. I do, however, pretend to be still asleep at 9am as my alarm clock goes off for the nth time. It's not meditation, but it's the nearest thing to 'stillness in the heart of chaos' that I can find.  I don't have a fish to feed. I'm afraid to feed fish. Last time I did, I killed my nephew's gold fish when I overfed it.  Hmm. Two out of 4 is 50%. That's more than the GNP growth of the Philippines in the last 2 quarters. That's not too bad. Not bad at all.    Warning to all readers:   All links in this page may or may not actually refer or correspond to the highlighted words and phrases. Discretion of reader is required. Whatever. 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      These lines from Matchbox Twenty's Mad Season should sum up my year's past neatly:  I feel stupid - but I know it won’t last for long I’ve been guessing - I coulda been guessin’ wrong ... ... ... You figured me out - I’m a child and I’m hopeless Bleeding and broken - though I’ve never spoken I come undone - in this mad season  In this mad season There’s been a mad season Been a mad season.....  :-)
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      To all my friends, here's Joni Mitchell's Woodstock song, in remembrance for the years past and a reminder for the years ahead. Have a meaningful and happy life :-)   I came upon a child of god He was walking along the road And I asked him, where are you going And this he told me I’m going on down to yasgur’s farm I’m going to join in a rock ’n’ roll band I’m going to camp out on the land I’m going to try an’ get my soul free We are stardust We are golden And we’ve got to get ourselves Back to the garden  Then can I walk beside you I have come here to lose the smog And I feel to be a cog in something turning Well maybe it is just the time of year Or maybe it’s the time of man I don’t know who l am But you know life is for learning We are stardust We are golden And we’ve got to get ourselves Back to the garden  By the time we got to woodstock We were half a million strong And everywhere there was song and celebration And I dreamed I saw the bombers Riding shotgun in the sky And they were turning into butterflies Above our nation We are stardust Billion year old carbon We are golden Caught in the devil’s bargain And we’ve got to get ourselves Back to the garden
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I don't know, but when it comes to writing an entry to my blog I fail miserably. I can write letters, I can write poems decently and I can even chat hilariously (crabby) but when it comes to blog writing I just go 'poof!'. Nothing. Nada. A very deep well without water.  Oh well. There are things one must learn to accept. I guess this is one of them.   Speaking of chat, I've some philosophical bullshit tract about it. But guess what? Yes, you are right. I don't know how to write it in a wonderfully witty blog-entry form. 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well he is back.                  Well, what are you scrolling down here for?  He is back.  That's it.   The pictures will be up and about in a little while.
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      He is somewhere in Florida, looking up at the stars with his 20cm-retractable thing... its called a telescope, for those who are wondering what is so short a thing to retract.   Looking at stars. Deep space probing. Being able to call a star or a space object by its proper name and not just identifying it by the tip one's fingers. Explain event horizon in layman's terms and be unconsciously poetic about it. That's dear Sam, the nearly-pro astronomer.  Well, if you get back, send me the pictures of the stars ASAP, will you? Move your office furnitures around, dust is gathering underneath your chair and table. Open your emails, youve probably reached the limit of your account memory (thank me that I didnt send you anything via email)  And update your site. Its getting so stale lately that flies have moved in and they're not paying the goddamn rent.  Give my love to T, P and B too.   Oops! This is a weblog. Not a private conversation between us. Ooh. Bad me.  Hehehe. 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        You are Lucy!    urlLink   Which Peanuts Character are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    Umm. Yes, I already announced I am Lucy.
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       There are Zen students who are in chains  When they go to a teacher, And the teacher adds another chain. The students are delighted,  Unable to discern one thing from another. This is called a guest looking at a guest.     - Linji (d. 867)   Ah the bliss of cluelessness. I would be clueless, if I could, and live in clueless heaven. Sigh. 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Two things:  1. I'm addicted to  urlLink praises  given to my poems.  and  2. I'm ADDICTED to praises given to my poems.  I've other addictions. But these two will suffice for now. You know how to look for me in there.
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Anamnesis   Pronunciation : "a-"nam-'nE-s&s  Function : noun  Inflected Form(s):  plural an·am·ne·ses  /-"sEz/  Etymology : New Latin, from Greek anamnEsis, from anamimnEskesthai to remember, from ana- + mimnEskesthai to remember -- more at MIND 1 : a recalling to mind : REMINISCENCE 2 : a preliminary case history of a medical or psychiatric patient   and the poem is  The green of a new leaf gleams,  an upturned face seeking  elusive kiss of the finest rain deepening into the soft skin of night  longing, longing beyond endurance.  I would have loved to write you a poem, about you  and the way we remembered us, then reading it, you'll find  that it is already inside you and the silence in you  will crack into a fiery  song of love...  We hold each other the way earth holds the fallen leaf.   December 1998 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Random thoughts on how to love beyond culture, biases, bigotry beyond the pigment of our skin or the margins of our sex beyond the fear & darkness even beyond the random killings that one hears or reads in news--- I break stride. 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       and Sex   I know it does make people happy, but to me it is just like having a cup of tea.    -Cynthia Payne (b. 1934), British housewife, brothel-keeper.   Remark, 8 Nov. 1987. Quoted in: Sunday Correspondent (London, 24 Dec. 1989), after Paine was acquitted of running a brothel in Streatham, South London, in the "sex-for- luncheon-vouchers" case   A person could very well take one or the other, not that it makes a fig of difference; but seeing the way my sex life is going (which is  nowhere ), I might as well enjoy a cup of tea.  
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       One of the most striking differences between a cat and a lie is that a cat has only nine lives.   - Pudd'nhead Wilson, Mark Twain  
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The brain is in auto-pilot. I think I'm going semicomatose. I could use a shot of gin right now. Instead, all I have in the fridge is Lite Coke! Who the hell drinks Lite Coke at 1 in the morning? Grr. More importantly, who drank my regular Coke and changed it with Lite Coke??? Jesus F. Christ, people don't have no respect anymore. 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Finally installed Sims (the ultimate game for control freaks, and in my case, a micro-level practice in world domination) in my PC and i hope to be joyously addicted to this game for a few weeks, at the least.
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      there are 3 things i believe in (and there aren't many things i'm a believer in): (1) i definitely believe that we are made of stuff stars are made of. (2)  that i absolutely know nothing beyond death. and (3) that cherry-flavored Coke is actually cough syrup.
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
            urlLink What Classic Movie Are You? 
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am  this                ESTJ  - "Administrator". Much in touch with the external environment. Very responsible. Pillar of strength. 8.7% of total population.  
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
                I have issues with...        nature  domination  father  mother  pleasure        urlLink Take Word Association Test    I certainly have issues with  nature  (It's fucking unfair),  domination  (It pains me that my destiny to dominate the world is being undermined by the underground cocroach rebellion. ),  father  (no comment),  mother  (no comment), and  pleasure  (It is overrated.) 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
              Conscious self
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      is just around the corner. A perfect time for self-flagellation. We have the perfect hot weather for humility too--and for washing away the sins one has collected for a year.  Heaven (or hell, whatever your pov is) will have a great time declassifying this year's collective penance, with Verdi's arias in the background.    Me, I'd rather wash away my venial sins in a beach full of people and dogs.    I shall confess my sins of   sloth  ( After 6 months, I should take out the moldy unmentionables from the refrigerator. )   pride  ( I shall try to lessen the frequency of me saying, "It is not my fault. It is your fault."  )   gluttony  ( Eating too much junk food is definitely bad for the skin. )   covetousness  ( In a randabout way, please refer to the post on angst & love below. )   lust  ( Really, I should stop watching Russel Crowe's or Mel Gibson's films on the basis of the square-inch of bare skin they show in their respective films. )   wrath  ( I should begin to forgive that nerdy, snotty, grinning kid in kindergarten who beat me in arts class and therebly caused me undue insecurity that hounded me way into adulthood. )   envy  ( I will never forgive Monica Belluci for looking the way she does and causing an alarming dearth in the world's supply of sex appeal and transluscent skin .)
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Now that I'm finished with the conference paper, I suddenly found myself without reason to stay up late. But since I slept the whole afternoon away (from 12:30pm to 8:30pm, to be exact), I couldn't get back to sleep now. So now I have this headache that just won't go away. It is slight and doesn't bother me much, but it quietly does make sure I am aware of its presence.   *Looks down*  Hmm. The post on love is so juvenile in its suggestion of angst. I must have written it when I'm half-drunk. God knows I'm more lucid full-drunk than half-drunk.   Umm.   It was posted at 2.53pm. I don't think I was drinking at that particular hour. I don't care then. Haha. 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      You must never, if you could, fall in love with someone you think is perfect for you, someone you  want  to belong to. Because, more often than not, he is no longer available. It is good for the heart when one gets together with someone less perfect, less 'Mr.right'. Then the only thing you lose is your celibacy. 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'll be gone for a few days. Hafta attend a national conference and present some papers.  So no blogging during these days (crowd goes wild) and no exhorting for comments (crowd goes wild again).   Will you all miss me? (crowd nods their heads. then snickers behind their hands)  Take care! See you in good time! (crowd collectively swallows their boo's)
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is a better evaluation of my mental health:  "Karen, you are mildly left-hemisphere dominant while showing a slight preference for auditory processing. This overall combination seems to indicate a well-working blend of logic and judgement and organization, with sufficient intuition, perception and creativity to balance that dominance.  You will at times experience conflict between how you feel and what you think which will generally be resolved in favor of what you think. You will find yourself interested in the practical applications of whatever material you have learned or whatever situation you face and will retain the ability to refine whatever knowledge you possess or aspects of whatever position you are in.  By and large, you will orient yourself toward intellectual activities and structure. Though not rigid, you will schedule yourself, plan and focus on routine and continuity of operations, rather than on changes and disruptions. When changes or disruptions occur, you are likely to consider first how to ensure that such disruptions do not occur again in the future."  I know all these. But it's so nice to see it in print. The program is called BrainWorks. I'll email the program to you, if you are interested. Just leave a message somewhere.
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      " Your IQ score is 115 . A person whose IQ score falls in the range of 111-128 is considered to be "above average intelligence".  Your IQ score is based on your scores across 12 distinct aspects of intelligence. Like everyone, you have a unique intellectual makeup, with strengths and weaknesses that affect your methods of understanding, communication and relating to others. According to your results, your greatest intellectual strength is Processing Speed."   urlLink So how smart are you?  
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yahoo! The commenting button is back. It seems that haloscan.com was rewriting all its members pages (whatever for, I've no idea, maybe its just one of those obsessive compulsive things) hence the day's worth of my frustration.   I realize one thing, blog is not fun if it's not interactive. In other words, for all those who usually click on this site to see what I'm up to, WILL YOU PLEASE LEAVE A COMMENT?!   I promise not to nag you when I run into you.
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've temporarily turn off the commenting button in this blog. I clicked on the the tabbed kfv's notes and voila! I see the June skies in my blog. I'm happy.  Now to change the language of my date entries to Dutch (Belgium). 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well it seems I can't do anything until haloscan.com cleans up its mess. Until then, let us continue our conversations  urlLink here .    I'm going to miss my skies-in-June-inspired blogsite. Sigh.
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I dont know what I did by creating that little demon shadow of  urlLink myself , but it seems that when I created that thing with a new template, this blogsite automatically recreated itself. NOW I COULD REALLY SCREAM!  Btw, it's haloscan.com that's making all these troubles. I can't download kfv's notes because we are all "waiting for haloscan.com...."  Oh god.
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      To those who can actually load and read and appreciate the color coordination of kfv's notes, it's a good thing you can.  I've been trying to load my blogsite to no avail.  I dont know why. I can open my blogger account and actually post something here, but when I try to preview kfv's notes, nada. I think I want to trash something into pulp. Shitty shitty thing to happen to me. 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I don't know about you people, but  urlLink this  one really cracks me up--in a stitches-on-the-side-at-the-same-time-teary-eyed way.   I've never read a blog with "boob" and "poop" and "dilation" mentioned so many times in it. I want those too!!!  
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I think I got color-overdrive. Leaving the format as is, for now. Comments and suggestions (on font, colors and margins, mind you,  not  the kinky kind) are very welcome. The font on the entry title btw is a precious and it's called Eras Bold ITC. The main text is Trebuchet MS. No commonplace Arials and Times New Romans for me.   Meanwhile, weekend is knocking on my CSS-addled brain and a film called  Cold Mountain  beckons. The other night I watched  Gothika  (starring sp's ultimate fantasy babe: Halle Barry). Robert Downey Jr should have worn a brown paper bag over his head in this movie. 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm learning the ciphered language of blog templates and discovered 'proprietary named colors' in one of my meanderings. Things to learn: cascading stylesheets and encoding images.
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      There are few things that stir me, most of them mundane and pedestrian--sunset skies streaked with salmon pinks and seaweed greens,  stir-fried vegetables cooking in a wok over slow coal-fire, my nephews and nieces' whispered  i-love-you's and fierce hugs, an explanation of event horizon, news of unjust and brave deaths. People, in their banal and petty ways, rarely affect me.  But there is one person who has affected me by his compassion and sense of humor, by his world views and his openness, by his intellect and his ability to cut through layers of bullshit and get to the heart of the matter... After all this time, he has moved me and its just now that I realized that.   Sometimes, I can be a total dork in the dark.
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
            You're  The Fellowship of the Ring !   by J.R.R. Tolkien     Facing great adversity, you have decided that your only choice is to unite with your friends and neighbors. You have been subject to a ton of squabbling and ultimately decided that someone humble is your best candidate for a dangerous mission. You're quite good with languages and convinced that not all who wander are lost. If you see anyone in black robes on horseback, just run. That's just common sense.      Take the  urlLink Book Quiz  at the  urlLink Blue Pyramid .    
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today is Monday. It rained. And some boring radio dj played a Carpenter's song with these lines: 'rainy days on mondays always get me down...' I cringed. How much more clichè can this day get?   At 8pm I waited for a colleague in a public plaza (don't ask me why our rendezvous was a public plaza...maybe to emphasize the point that we are just colleagues?) and of course, it began to rain. I transferred to a makeshift restaurant, such as one found sprouting in all sorts of public places when it gets dark enough. And I watched as the rainwater level on the sidewalk get higher... and higher... which was a normal hellish little thing in my country.    I ignored the semi-flood and pretended to read some Japanese literature while taxi drivers, jeepney drivers and all sorts of persons thronged the restaurant as they tried to harangued the resto owner-cum-cook-cum-cashier-cum-all-around-boy-friday into some sort of a magician's dance as he served the whole of us rice, stewed fish, chicken adobo and Mountain Dew (the only soda he had on hand). All at the same time. I think he cooked in between. I could learn a thing or two on the art of multi-tasking from this guy. He was almost god. A sweaty and harassed god. A multi-tasking, sweaty and harassed god.  Anyway, the point of this story? The point is that the colleague was late and I was forced to read some Japanese literature in the middle of makeshift resto with the radio blasting some slushy Carpenter's song on rainy mondays while floodwater is rising.  How much more  urlLink cosmic  can  that  get?  A happy note: Today I bought 5 books,   Star Wars: Rogue Planet  by Greg Bear  Dune Messiah  by Frank Herbert  Human Evolution: Physical Anthropology and the Origin of Man  by Gabriel W. Lasker  Exploring the Cosmos  (3rd Edition) by Louis Berman & J.C. Evans  and, (because I'm a masochist)   An Anthology of Japanese Literature   from the earliest era to the mid-19th century   Today is heavy intellectual shit. Other days, I would like to get something from Nancy Friday or Harold Robbins (so yeah my idea of trash is preteen, sue me). 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm now working with a Mozilla Firefox browser.  Finally, no more 30 seconds wait for a browser to open. No more hang-ups while in the middle of reading a deeply engrossing page site on  urlLink String Theory . And coolest of all, no more multiple browsers for multiple sites. Instead I can now browse multiple sites in a single window. No more 'gnashing of teeth and pulling of hair' sort of histrionics when I'm online. I am FREE! And freedom never looked better than an iconized dinosaur head.  
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's one of those dreary days. The weather has been humid and hot, just like any other March's day. Most of the time I just switch to auto-pilot and there's always the urge to lay on a hammock and sleep beneath the humming flies going crazy in this heat.   Most of the time, I work like an animal.  Sleep is no respite. It just became another arena for persistent daemons that won't go away to torment me.  
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Nutrition Facts    Calories  200  Total Fat  19g  Saturated Fat  3g  Cholesterol  0mg  Sodium  190mg  Potassium  85mg  Total Carbohydrate  5g  Protein  4g  These are the ingredients of my poison. 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The pictures from the  urlLink Florida Winter Star Party  are up.  The one I most recognized among the pictures is the Horsehead Nebulae found in Orion. Also known as Barnard 33, the Horsehead is one of the most famous of all dark nebulae.
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink   :: how jedi are you? ::    Whohoo !
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So I am a pool brat.   But I've been spending two hours everyday of this summer season in the pool: rain or shine, with or without my period, perky or dog-tired, happy or miserable. And that should be enough reason for me to demand the minimum standards set for a swimming pool to assure me of a stress-free, serene and lovely swimming time.  1st. Pool water must be clear blue. Not milky-blue nor milky-white nor milky aqua. I should be able to taste chlorine when I inadvertently drink water while breathing. Not the tepid tasting water.  2nd. Shower rooms must at least look clean. No slippers should be allowed inside the shower rooms.   3rd. Everyone should be required NOT to use sunblock lotion and moisturizers while swimming. It causes the pool water to turn milky. Everyone should be required to use a swimcap. Floating hair is not a pretty sight.  4th. No eating or drinking in the pool. Gee.  5th.  No dating either. Okay, some dating. But can they please do it OUT of the pool? Not IN the pool. They cause unnecessary traffic. And all that touching going on. Please. I am an unwilling celibate, for heaven's sakes.   There. I've said my piece.   Ciao for now. Going to the pool now. 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       It is marvelous indeed to watch on television the rings of Saturn close; and to speculate on what we may yet find at galaxy's edge. But in the process, we have lost the human element; not to mention the high hope of those quaint days when flight would create 'one world.' Instead of one world, we have 'star wars,' and a future in which dumb dented human toys will drift mindlessly about the cosmos long after our small planet's dead.            - Gore Vidal    According to general relativity, the presence of any massive object bends the time-space fabric. What does it have anything to do with us? Only this: at a smaller scale, in an infinitely smaller scale like the human scale, each of us is interconnected to the other. More so when we interact. Our interaction with each other 'bends the time-space fabric' of each of our lives.   And to you Sam, you may not be massive, your physical presence may border on the infinitesimal and the theory of relativity may yet to be empirically proven, but you do bend someone's time-space fabric halfway across the planet. Happy birthday!    
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       "A mentat!" Mohiam muttered.   This is the 5th sentence on page 23 of the nearest book I grabbed. Instructions originated from  urlLink TechGnome's World , fed through  urlLink Reckless Writer .   The book is  Dune Messiah  by Frank Herbert.  The instructions are:  1.Grab the nearest book. 2.Open the book to page 23. 3.Find the fifth sentence. 4. Post the text of the sentence in your journal along with these instructions. 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      To Sam Pieter and Christy, thanks for showing me the way, the truth and the life. What would this blog be without your tips and links to Mozilla Firefox, Antivir, Babelfish (you should see how this blog read in Korean!) and a plethora of psychobabble tests?  Today the pool is closed. So I'm staying home for most part of the morning and going to my sister's later in the afternoon. I should spend more time with my nephews and nieces. For the most part, they are smart and sweet and like to play with me.  Other times, they just pester me with questions and/or requests for playing with them. If you've kids of your own, or nephews/nieces of your own, you know how tiring it is to play the same game over and over with them especially if the game includes an image of you making grotesque faces and making noises to scare the hell out of them and running after them as they run away screaming at the top of their lungs. If you havent played this game with any of your kids/nephews/nieces, don't begin. They absolutely love being scared half of their young lives by you.   Kids are a weird lot. They always speak what's on their mind. They are great gossips: they update me what has been happening in both their houses, which of their friends had tantrums, which neighbors' dogs they fear most. They are my fashion gurus. They know which color of shirt looks nice on me. They also know what length of skirt I should be wearing (exactly 3.5 inches above the knees) and which color of lipstick I should wear (L'Oreal's Sugar Plum Sheer).   They also know what to say to an aunt who is never there and make her feel guilty because she wasn't home when Adrienne fell and scratched her knees, or when Eric got a medal for being diligent, or when France got sick and vomited all over her parent's bed, or when Ricardo sang the whole theme song of the film, Shrek.    I am as guilty as the cat who got caught with a fish in its mouth and should do my penance. 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Two months off the pool doesnt pay. Now I ache everywhere: upper arm muscles, leg muscles, thigh muscles. The encounter with the pool is also strange. I keep telling myself:  pull, pull, pull, breathe. don't forget to breathe. kick harder. relax the drop of the arms. stretch out your body--think streamline.  the other side of the pool is stationary, it is not moving farther. breathe deeper. hold on to the air underwater longer. regulate the bubbles. relax. relax. relax. you know how to swim. life is good. now just pull on a little harder. no, the water is not going into the googles, everything is blurry underwater. whoa! the kid swimming beside me just streaked by. jesus. this is going to take me forever... 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Finally, there are public vehicles plying the city! And just to get out of the house, I went straight to the mall and bought--of all things--2 reams of bond paper, 3 plastic envelopes, a double-sided tape, and a notebook (which I probably don't need because I still have about 5 other clean notebooks--but I am a compulsive notebook-buyer, so that's not  your  problem).    Anyway, I'm back online and I decided to do a google on me and guess what I found? I am on the net! And I saw my picture when I was still in high school. Gee. (No can do guys. I am  not  putting the link in here.)  I'm listening to Vivaldi's Four Seasons. He is one of the 3 classics I actually find easy to listen to (the other 2 being Chopin and Brahms). He is great background music while one is doing some Excel worksheets.  For narrative reports, I find 2000 Maniac's MTV Unplugged tape particularly helpful.   I decided to go back to the swimming pool this week because   I am growing love handles.  I need a challenge to my mind, & not of the intellectual sort.  I want to use my lovely swimsuits again and to see the shape of my head as sculpted by the silicone moulded cap. I need the time alone with myself.   And the last reason is the most relevant for me.
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Have nothing better else to do, so I'm downloading a good  urlLink antivirus program  (it is free and so far hasn't bothered me with pop-ups on penis enhancers); took Christy's advice and  urlLink gaped the void ; a bit of  urlLink egotism  ; and learned something new on the biological and physical origins of humankind, specifically that   urlLink Ardipithecus ramidus   is the oldest known hominid fossil aged at 4.4 million years.
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       And    Putting the finishing touches on what is creatively called A Problem Tree.  Fine tuning an already streamlined Logical Framework.  Sniffing the  just-came-out-from-a-third-world-factory  smell of my new  urlLink Sony Ericsson Z200 .  Downloading the  urlLink Mozilla Firefox  installer so that I can change the web browser of my office's notebook.  Subscribing to some cool drawings linked from  urlLink Reckless Writer's  site.  Joyfully tearing out the wrapper on a Vochelle Bittersweet Fruit & Nut chocolate.   and trying to ignore a particularly ornery Dutchman online (which I'm failing at since he is talking about his son  urlLink Brent  who turned 1 last April 4)
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Back in the rut and trying to make something out of the jumble of a meeting notes I have with me. This past week I've learned three things:  humility patience endurance  and the value of a remote control.  
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Saffron. The scent and the color.&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      As to my sense of humor, it has been labelled many things: weird, pragmatic, macabre, borderline and non-existent. But this picture of Mr. Bean, the guy I sincerely would like to hit on the head because of his cheekiness, made me laugh out loud. &nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Ants and ant eggs are not sour. I should know. &nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       May's end is nearing and here's a song from Natalie Merchant. I hope everyone had a great summer, like I did.          These are days you'll remember. Never before and never since, I promise, will the whole world be warm as this. And as you feel it, you'll know it's true that you are blessed and lucky. It's true that you are touched by something that will grow and bloom in you.       These are days you'll remember. When May is rushing over you with desire to be part of the miracles you see in every hour. You'll know it's true that you are blessed and lucky. It's true that you are touched by something that will grow and bloom in you.       These are days.       These are the days you might fill with laughter until you break. These days you might feel a shaft of light make its way across your face. And when you do you'll know how it was meant to be. See the signs and know their meaning. It's true, you'll know how it was meant to be. Hear the signs and know they're speaking to you, to you. 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       All through the loneliness of night I know that I want freedom more than anything else. I would like it shared--sharing separate and equal freedoms with a companion. A companion who would be with me where I now am alone--on trips, walks, at the theatre, or home.    Helen Barolini, Learning to Meditate 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    This is my yet-to-be-christened dinosaur. He doesn't speak English. He is Thai and eats chillies for breakfast.&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      At zero degree Kelvin, or what is known as the absolute zero, the atoms of the air itself become solid.  And light  slows  down.  Now that is ubercool.  I'm sure this has a life-altering effect on us. Haven't found out yet what it is. I'm going out of the country for a few days for a study program. By the time I come back, I should be able to come up with something.
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
           urlLink Which Rock Chick Are You?     Never heard a song of hers. Never heard of her, period. But I like the  honest, independent, determined  thing.
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The past few days had been harrowing for me. A deadline I couldn't seem to beat. An online discussion which has become bullish. Walking alone from the pool because my swimming partner has left for Bali, Indonesia. A post office that has become a blackhole of packages sent particularly to me. A cold that progressed from a simple runny nose to a barbwired throat.   But today is Sunday. I have at least a day to unwind and prepare for the week ahead. Going to the sister's again. Going to listen to the nephews and nieces chatter about their lives. Going to let them help me finish the cards I'm making. Going to eat pasta with a sister in Afriques, a tiny pasta restaurant which serves mean Amatriciana. Going to give my mother a hug because I forgot it was her birthday yesterday. Drinking lots of water to fasttrack the cold onto its thankless way. Going to watch Russell Crowe (yet, again) in his Roman skirt (the  Gladiator ) or in tight tights (in  Master and Commander ) or in lovely tuxedoes (in  A Beautiful Mind ).  Check him out at the end of this page.  Hello another hell week, I am so ready for you. 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      1. TV evangelists in shiny fuschia-and-purple suits. With lemon-yellow ties. Yes, I swear this is true.  2. People who can suspend their disbelief indefinitely.  3. People in perpetual state of suspended disbelief who attend (and go epileptic at) evangelical rallies.  4. Miracle-healers.  5. People who can suspend their disbelief indefinitely.  6. People in perpetual state of suspended disbelief who believe that their diseases have been cured by the miracle-healers.  7.The proliferation of TV evangelists and miracle-healers in a 3rd world country like mine. (Okay. So, somebody already explained this to me, in terms of the politics and economics of quasi-religions in a Catholic country like mine. But I need one more point to add to the 10 Things I Cannot Fathom. So there.)  8. The popularity of these TV evangelists and miracle-healers. They are so popular they are on prime-time TV. Along with all the Filipino, Taiwanese and Mexican soap-operas that litter television space.  9. Why cranberry juice is godawfultasting.  10. Why love and technical progress reports do not exactly mesh together.
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      A poem from  urlLink Cubert  whose poems can make me laugh. I, who rarely laugh.   You've Got To Love A Girl Who Can Drink A Pint    I see a mate, he's watching me, Scanning with his eyes... That pretend aloof, That look away, The small laugh as I sigh  One pint down, well through two, I've been here 30 minutes; I came to drink and think of you In the company of strangers.  I hear the smallest mundane talk And feel the importance of simple pleasures; I came here seeking a sense of you And came to understand my treasure.  I listened with your ears, Tried to see them with your eyes; These men with talk of cars and beer, These foreigners stuck in time.  Third pint and I've decided I'm having a lovely time.  I borrowed this pen from the barkeep, I wrote this on a coaster; I felt a sense of agelessness As I sat here getting older.  I'm caught inside my own dream, My vague imagining of home; I couldn't have a better fantasy That wasn't in your arms.  Slightly pissed and beautiful, Exchanging lovely smiles; Indeed, indeed, I see the love For the girl who can drink a pint.  I've come, I've loved, I'll come again, I've uncovered what I needed... Thanks for the thoughts, the air and flowers, And the pen to keep my secrets.
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      A flying hummingbird fills my desktop. I am so gushy and corny and pictures of flowers and toothless babies bring tears to my eyes. I hope this icky, weirdy mood ends soon. Or else, I will lose whatever friends I have. &nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Good mornings are composed of these:   a well loved pillow in one's arms or between the legs  playing out loud and singing-in-the-mind Red Hot Chili Peppers'  Parallel Universe   the smell of cooked eggs and dried fish wafting in  a hazy dream, in color, of a face leaning down to claim a kiss from me   a face , in real color now, leaning down to claim a kiss from me  the sound of waves outside one's room  well-rumpled sheets (i have anal tendencies, but rumpled sheets rule!)  thinking first thing in the morning that one is in love and is loved back  swimming early mornings and meditating as one stretches out to become streamlined, to feel one's healthy body move   to realize one has woken up safe and alive and have friends    
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Transcend essence and function. This means that when we are practicing, we do not divide the internal and external. Nor do we discriminate north, south, east, and west. Rather, we take the four quarters and the eight directions and simply transform them all into a great gate to liberation. Clearly, then, essence and function are not divided. As there is not the slightest outflow, the entire body becomes fused into one whole. Where, then, would delusion be able to arise?  - Chinul (1205)    
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Van Gogh's painting. I am in love.&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        How is an ankle unlike a consequence?    Something to do for you people while I am away and flowing.  The sun will burn out after 5 billion years. I will not take  that  long.
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Going away for a week. For a break. Yes, a break. That means: no computer, no printers, no quarterly finance reports, no emails, no phone calls (yes, turning the cellphone off too), nothing that is remotely work-related.  I am going to bring my sarong, my swimsuit and goggles, my sense of fun with me. I am going to bring Umberto Eco's The Name of the Rose and finally finish reading it. I am going to bring a diary and write again. I am going to take notes on sunset colors, cloud formations and tinges, the taste of seaspray, the feel of sand between my toes. I would watch star formations during clear nights. I am going to listen to June rains before I go to sleep. I will enjoy the cool cotton bedsheets and the scent of newly-washed pillow-cases.  I am going to flow.
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The drama queen that resides deep inside of me speaks:   Somebody out there must have created with hate. Someone malicious and faceless diligently studied the configurations and many facets of pain, its weight in gold, the price to pay for the pearl of an egg—carrying the exact replica and maps of this malignancy going round and round the universe, cackling to itself, smug like the old witch of our fairytale nightmares. To feel like a caged animal, bending down to one’s knees—moaning, coldly hating this cyclical, malicious pain. She can’t claw out this barbed wire, festering inside her. She tears out her fur/hair. She hisses at the great black silent universe. Not this. Not this. Not this faceless enemy that can do whatever it wants with impunity. Not this. Not this. Not the groveling for mercy: scraps and spitted out mercy. 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      A most exciting thing. Venus will transit the face of the Sun on June 8. The beginning of the transit will be seen over Philippines, Japan and Australia. Observers in eastern North America, the Caribbean, and most of South America will see only the end of the event after the Sun rises. Too bad, for Dutch astronomers in Curacao, eh.   Observers with a clear sky in eastern New York and New England will see at least 120 minutes of the transit. That number drops to 60 minutes for observers on a line curving from north central Minnesota to northeastern Florida. None of the transit will be visible from the Mountain states or the Pacific Coast.For more information, check out the articles in  urlLink Astronomy .&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      As you all can see, I've done everything I wanted to do with this site. Well, almost everything. I've decided to do away with the haloscan comments for the meantime. It really is too complicated for a 30-minute site-retouching. Well, everything's here: the mood meter, all the previous links, and even the Mozilla Firefox button.   Oh yeah, I've done away with the sitemeter too. It really is too addicting. Sometimes I spend more time checking out who visited the blog than actually doing some blogging in the site. It is unproductive work. Therefore it must go.  The hair is still crazy-frizzy. The weather is steadily growing grey. But hey, I've retouched the site. That should count for something. Now I can sleep better at night. Concentrate better at work (yeah yeah yeah). Feel a lot better now for giving in to my innermost fetish: pink.  And oh yeah, comments on the way this site looks are very welcome. Please. Don't be polite.
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I still have to make manual changes in the templates because it seems that the template comes with a comment chastity belt (yes Christy, that conversational piece from your blog got stuck in my brain for some reason) and no one can post a comment on the site unless they have a blogger account. Knowing the people who regularly post comments here, I might as well leave the commenting button off. Which of course I don't want to do, since you all know my pov on the interactiveness of a blog being based mostly on the commenting system  But this will take time and a lot of pulling of frizzy hair and I have no time right now. And can you imagine this, I must figure everything out! Ogad. The way it goes, I might as well go back to the old template.   I need help. Badly. 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      and i realized that I MUST change this site's looks. Grimly I picked Thisaway Rose. Republished the whole thing. There. Finished. View the blog. Zero comments. Feels like being a newborn baby--naked, fuzzy-haired and really pissed off.   Of course, I took everyone's advise, I kept a copy of the june-skies template. Just in case I want people's comments to fill up my life. But I doubt it if I'd go into that much trouble. People are people, they will soon fill this one up with new, really witty, really funny comments (yes, I am a very optimistic person, bordering on i-can-suspend-my-disbelief-indefinitely type).  Now I must go and swim the hell out of my lethargic and lazy muscles. 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Because I can't quite concentrate on work (believe me, I tried), I decided to change this blogsite's looks into something really really garish. Which I was able to do (the new blogger push-button publishing is really designed for idiots, thank you). BUT, I lost all the comments. Now I'm trying to figure out the instructions from Blogger Help (which they forgot to configure for idiots like me) how to change template and retain the comments, to no avail. I couldn't understand a damn thing. 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Eating chocopeanut-flavored ice cream for the last 3 days.  No, I don't need to know the caloric content of sinful ice cream.  Eating glazed peanuts, peanut crinkle and peanut candy bars. No wonder my shit looks and smells like peanut that has been left too long in a basket which in turn has been left to the tender mercy of tropical weather.  It's pretty interesting, I tell you. But not as interesting as the time when I had jackfruit fever.  Anyway.    Yesterday I watched Kill Bill Vol. 2. Can't help but compare it toVolume 1 which was a fine masterpiece in the details and peculiarities of how to kill people. Though in both films, Uma Thurman shone as a very good killer. I liked the fact that when she kills, she uses grace, intellect and strength.  Life should be lived like that: gracefully, not moronically, and with strength...    Um..     Whatever. 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Girlfriend and I were talking about evolutionary flops before breakfast this morning. Actually she was  ranting  about it. Parts of the conversation follow:   She : There are at least two insects in which I feel evolution has failed them.  Me : Um. (Brain gears are whirring. Thinking: Uh-uh.)  She : First, beetles. Why, when they are walking or flying and they happen to fall over or land upside down they cannot turn right side up - even though their life depends on it. They just spin around and around and around. Don't they get dizzy?  Me : *shrug*  She : And ants! You know I like ants and can talk about them at length. But why do they find food that is 100 or 1000 times their size and their weight and move the food vertically (against gravity) and try to push and pull it into holes that are way too small. I think ants are brillant - but they fail in this particular area.  Me : Um.   She : Third, moths and other flying things that fly into lightbulbs or hot objects, only to be burned to a crisp.  Me :  I'm sure I don't know why they don't learn their lessons very well.  (I said this very quickly and in a very tiny voice. You dont, in  any  circumstance, want to interrupt someone who needs to rant about insignificant insects  before  breakfast.  Not  if that someone is usually laidback and cool and believes that every animal in the world has a purpose in the grand schema of things.  Not  if you value your life more than the insects.)  She : And mosquitoes. They have been around for thousands of years. There are a thousand varieties or families of mosquitos. It just seems like their life expectancy, in relationship to human interaction, would be alot longer if they would just stop buzzing. Imagine how much more blood they could suck if they didn't buzz in our ears!  Me : Um... Yeah... Want some breakfast?   urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
            urlLink Which Rock Chick Are You?      Hmm. I did this test more than two months ago. I did it again in the hopes that I get to be someone real hot like that girl Sam said I should look like. Man, I  am  consistent.    
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Finally, text formatting! Now I can change the color of my text like  this . Or italicize it like  this . Even do a  bold  thing like  that . And. oh. my. god.&nbsp;text fonts! As in now I can use  arial  or  courier  or  verdana ! I even have the choice to make my fonts  huge ,  large , normal,  small  or  tiny ! Never thought that  'tiny'  can make me go olala with pleasure. Oh happy days are rare. And to have the chance to enhance the text of my posts, never mind that content-wise my blogposts border on the idiotic in its crusade for triviality, is such a treat I can forego great sex for the next 11 months without actually complaining obnoxiously.   And btw, for those who are using the Mozilla Firefox browser, a latest version is in the offing.  See ? I'm not depressed. I'm being helpful. To which some ungrateful people would respond by running to the forest and would rather be torn limb to limb and chomped on by  beasts &nbsp;in plain view of little animal-children than being helped by  me .      
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I guess I do. Or I wouldn't have done  urlLink this . Or maybe I'm just bored out of my wits and have nothing else better to do.   Wackiness: 28/100 Rationality: 40/100 Constructiveness: 30/100 Leadership: 80/100    You are an SEDL--Sober Emotional Destructive Leader. This makes you a dictator. You prefer to control situations, and lack of control makes you physically sick. You feel have responsibility for everyone's welfare, and that you will be blamed when things go wrong. Things do go wrong, and you take it harder than you should.  You rely on the validation and support of others, but you have a secret distrust for people and distaste for their habits and weaknesses that make you keep your distance from them. This makes you very difficult to be with romantically. Still, a level-headed peacemaker can keep you balanced.  Despite your fierce temper and general hot-bloodedness, you have a soft spot for animals and a surprising passion for the arts. Sometimes you would almost rather live by your wits in the wilderness somewhere, if you could bring your books and your sketchbook.  You also have a strange, undeniable sexiness to you. You may go insane.    I'm not  yet  insane? Excuse me while I go and get a second opinion.
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      "A model's life ain't easy. We must look 100% perfect, 100% of the time. And if we got caught by the cameras in the act of.. um, answering the call of Mother Nature, we must, at all cost, keep on smiling the smile that will launch a thousand toothpaste endorsements."&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      "I wish he would hurry up with the camera. I'm getting a crick in my neck."&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      "Want a romp in the branch?"&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      'Im too sexy for this tree."&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      NASA's Hubble Space Telescope captures the iridescent tapestry of star birth in a neighboring galaxy in this panoramic view of glowing gas, dark dust clouds, and young, hot stars. The star-forming region, catalogued as N11B, lies in the Large Magellanic Cloud (LMC), located only 160,000 light-years from Earth. With its high resolution, the Hubble Space Telescope is able to view details of star formation in the LMC as easily as ground-based telescopes are able to observe stellar formation within our own Milky Way galaxy. (text and image from  urlLink rednova.com )&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        "Pools of sorrow waves of joy Are drifting through my open mind Possessing and caressing me..."    a day in June, 1991  I am walking under the fine drizzle of rain, one bright afternoon thinking about the North Pole and how I would like to be that cold and chapped and happily doing oceanographic sampling. I am absolutely tuned in to all my oceanographic classes--soaking up things like plate tectonics, sedimentation, the water's asymmetrical molecular structure, atmospheric heat budgets, the Coriolis effect, sea ice and icebergs, T-S diagrams, geostrophic currents, the equilibrium tide... It is an absorbing geek world. I fit quite nicely in this geek world.     "Sounds of laughter shades of earth Are ringing through my open views Inciting and inviting me..."    a day in October, 1995  Waking up to a cool and crisp mountain air. Breathing in the cleanliness of a bright morning which has just began. Feeling warm inside my blanket, my hair in a high ponytail. He stirs on the bamboo bed where I was well loved the night before. He comes to me and breathes into my neck. The world itself beginning to stir noisily: the sounds of children going to the creek to take a bath, protesting squawks of chickens and chicks, the dull whack-whack of firewood being chopped... The sound and scent of mornings...    "Jai guru deva om Nothing’s gonna change my world Nothing’s gonna change my world Nothing’s gonna change my world Nothing’s gonna change my world..."    a day in May, 2004  It is hot. The craftstore is cool, a welcome respite from the heatwave that lies oppressively over  Khon Kaen. Sorting through some woven clothing material. Smiling at the tourist shirts with the cute water buffaloes print. A girl comes to me, her eyes smiling, offering me a green dinosaur. A sauropod, a  Brachiosaurus . I smiled back at her and took the dinosaur home with me.  
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Really, at two o'clock in the morning (2:25 a.m. to be exact) what interesting things could I possibly write about?    after two minutes of introspection   Hmm. I think I have a very boring life. Interesting things happened to me 10 or 12 years ago. But I couldn't remember what they were. Ah yes. A very interesting, life-altering thing happened to me last summer. I should be grateful.  Yes, I am grateful . I fell in love.  I remember when I was younger, I was in college, I used to wake up at one o'clock in the morning and go outside of our house and look at the sky. Nothing interesting really, just a weird way of trying to get back to sleep. I used to bring my diary out with me, just in case something brilliant and witty gets written by me. Nothing ever did. All I had to show for the nocturnal mind forages were a couple of doodles which weren't  that  good in the first place.  I also remember falling in love, twelve summers ago. He had beautiful teeth.   I remember losing my belief in the concept of God at age 15.   I remember my grandmother telling me nonsense things about suns and clouds. They are nonsense now. But when one is 5 years old and don't know any better, everything that a grandmother holds to be true, make sense.  I remember trying to add three and five, when I was 4 years old. That was a traumatic experience. I am still trying to block it out of my memory. In consolation, I have had the highest possible grades in Integral Calculus and Advance Algebra when I got older.  I remember riding a train at age 3 because I was such a bratty papa's girl and he had to bring me with him during his travels because my mother can't stand my tantrums which will last for 8 hours.  I don't remember much before that. But my mother certainly remembered what a difficult child I was.   Well, I'm going to bed now. 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ...and I really have nothing edgy or witty or sarcastic or even funny to post. I am, simply, quite surprisingly, just happy. It is not my normal mode, the happy mode. My normal mode is grouchy, sarcastic or grim. Rarely happy.  Damn. This world is so fuckingly good. 
      
</post>


</Blog>