<Blog>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I had such a great day! This evening was especially great since we went to visit the Zekec family.  Back before Jeremy and I met, he tutored them in Engish.  They really are precious people who came here from Bosnia during the horror that was going on in the 90s.  They aren't Muslim, so I don't really know the extent of their hardship.  I suppose anyone would want to desperately flee a war torn country.  They had a birthday party tonight for Vinkho and it was really fun to sit in a room full of Bosnians while they were all speaking Croatian!  Valeria, the seven-year-old daughter, translated some for us.  She sooo adorable and she loves Jeremy. She runs and jumps in his arms everytime she sees him.  (He'll be a great dad, won't he?)  It really is nice to see them doing well and having more than they would ever have over there.  My heart really goes out to them.  Maybe God has big plans for a future ministry that we can be a part of someday.  Perhaps working with refugees in the country. While we were there I prayed for God to bless them and bring them to the saving grace of knowing Jesus.  I would love to see the Spirit move in their lives.  I feel in my heart that this will happen someday.  Please help us pray for them too.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      The best way to have cranberry sauce is cooked in cherry juice.  I think we had just about all you can have for Thanksgiving, but I couldn't stop eating the stinking cranberry sauce.  I had it for breakfast this morning as well.  I hope you all had a great Thanksgiving!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I had to wear my scarf and gloves and leather coat today.  This is the freakiest weather I've ever seen.  At least in PA and NJ you could pretty much expect it to be freeeeeezing after November, but TN is so unpredictable.  Last week it was 75 and last night it was 25.  Our kitties are freezing their little cute butts off.  I bought a basket to put all my books in, but now I don't have the heart to use it since Fiona claimed it as her royal bed.  I put a towel in the bottom, so now at least she'll be warm!  For Phoebe, she sleeps with me. On my back, on my butt, on my stomach, between my knees, between me and Jeremy...anyway she can to snuggle up.  I think it's really adorable.  She's definitely a mommy's girl.  I think it's just because I never turn her down.  No matter what I'm doing--eating, sleeping, studying--she's right there to sit on my lap.  Anyway, I do love the fact that Jeremy radiates heat for my own sake at night.  I don't think he notices that I put my cold feet on his legs while he sleeps (shh).  This morning was painful, though.  I was buried so far under the covers that when Jeremy came in to say goodbye before work, all he could see was my hair and sleepy eyes.  Our apartment sure is cute, but not very warm in the bedroom.  We'll probably bust out the space heater tonight.   So Mommy and Daddy, I'm really looking forward to coming to Nashville tomorrow.  Too bad I have so much to accomplish before the end of the semester that it's going to cut into my play time.  But I know it's going to be a time had by all regardless.  So, what am I responsible for in the kitchen?  Can I be the taste tester and watch Jeremy do the cooking since he's so stinking good at it? Haha.  I think I would like to be put in charge of the jello mold.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Is finally mine.  I am the proud new owner of the best professional clarinet, as far as I'm concerned, in the world.  Grenadilla wood. Silver-plated keys. It has the works.  I can't believe I actually have one now.  My husband definitely spoils me. We joke that this is not only my Christmas present for this year, but also for 2004 and 2005! Eh, we'll see (just kidding hunny bunny).  I'm so incredibly grateful, so I'll sacrifice some other things for it.  Now, the problem is I have to find out some way to play it after college since I'm not going to be here for very much longer.  I was thinking about trying out for a spot in a city symphony, or maybe even a local community symphony somewhere...wherever we live.  I think it would be really great to keep playing since I enjoy it so much and since I'm getting better all the time.  Plus, now that I have a professional clarinet, I think Jeremy would kill me if I didn't play after college.  Maybe I could give lessons to beginners... right, like when am I going to have the time for that!  Oh, I know, between my Biochemistry and Gross Anatomy classes in medical school.  You know how some people make money in college and graduate school by giving hair-cuts...well, I'll be the crazy lady who gives clarinet lessons in her scrubs.  On a completely different topic, I'm trying to pick up the hobby of embroidery again.  I bought a pattern and I'm going to try and have it finished before January, when my friend's baby is due (since it's for him).  I feel like I'm turning into an old domestic housewife!  Gee, if it weren't for Bethany, who can do every sort of domestic sewing (well, not really so much sewing as knitting) possible, I'd totally feel alone.  It's nice to know that other people close to my age enjoy such hobbies.  Embroidery, and I know this sounds funny, makes me want to have a baby.  I always dreamed about making little things for my baby while I carried them.  You know, the little bibs with their names on them etc.  So, since I can't have one yet, I'm going to practice by making things for other people's babies. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      So I'm at the age in college where I don't know whether to call my professors Doctor so-and-so or not.  What makes it even more confusing is the fact that I'm married to a staff member at the college, so when he calls them by their first name, shouldn't I be able to? I even attend social engagements with some of the professors here.  They're actually quite fun to hang out with.  We have dinner together, go to musical events together, canoe together etc.  There are some that I would never in a million years call by their first name, but others have asked me to.  I guess some of them don't know what to think about me either.  I could have graduated last year, but I'm still here working on a second major.  The fact that I'm almost 23, I think, lets the professors put their authoritative guard down.    On another note.  For those of you who want to see some updated pictures of me and the family, you're going to have to wait till after Thanksgiving!  But I promise there will be some here soon!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      To  urlLink Passions . I only get to watch it about 1-2 times a week, but really that's all you need for Soaps.  I've never been addicted before, but in spite of my obsession, I'm really annoyed at the show.  First of all, why in the heck is Sheraton Crane underwater for 5 episodes? Oh, and she doesn't die, by the way.  Also, I really think that everyone is too ditzy to see the truth when it is right in front of them.  Seriously, how long is it going to take Luis to catch on to Beth.  I mean, I understand that daytime soaps are notorious for being incredibly slow.  I've been watching  Passions  on and off for about 6 or 8 months, and the show seems like it has only progressed about 2 weeks.  My last complaint is how I can let myself watch this show, actually enjoy it, while all the time knowing it's probably one of the cheeziest shows on TV.  I have to say, though, it's not as bad as  Will & Grace . 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today has been one of those crazy crazy days.  I have to tutor Physics in about an hour, so you can't expect much from me tonight!  I have Ohm's Law down pretty good, but I get a little confused when it come to that Kirchoff guy's stuff.  I think it's the algebra that gets me.  Go ahead, ask me anything you want about elementary circuits.  However, the key word is  elementary .  I know what it means to be parallel and in series--but I'll leave the rest to those smart Physics guys.  You know the ones I'm talking about. Heck, you may even be one.    So I wrote an entire Spanish paper for today about the day I got engaged.  I think I did a good job, but we'll see.  My Spanish convo class is really fun.  I just wish there was someone in there, besides la profesora, that knew way more than me. Then I think I could actually become better at speaking.  When two or three people are not exactly fluent (except for Lindsay!), there's a lot of silence and hand gestures (not to mention the wrong words).  So I think fluency will have to wait till I can actually live in a Spanish speaking country.  I hate hate hate marriage and family and I have a big test in it tomorrow.  If Miss Jan says the p and v word anymore, I am going to throw-up.  It's not like I can't handle these words, it's just that I don't want to hear her say them, oh, 43 times a class.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've had a very introspective and thoughtful day.  I've been thinking about my small life, the relationship I have with the world, with God, and even with myself.  I think it was brought on by watching  Night and Fog  for my English class earlier.  If you've ever seen this grim picture film about Auschwitz, then you probably know why I'm feeling the way I am.  Graphic scenes of starving men women and children whose bodies are so frail they don't look human anymore will cause anyone to have a day like I'm having.  I am constantly surrounded by all of my daily problems--marriage and family test, getting a paper back in faith and freedom, nothing good in the cafeteria to eat, having a million things to accomplish this week--but I must confess right now that in comparison, my insignificant bundle of problems is childsplay.  Actually, I'm grateful for reality checks like this because I start to evaluate things that are not really related to the thing that caused me to think in the first place.  I need to have thoughtful days more often because they lead to maturity, not only emotionally and intellectually, but also spiritually.  Sometimes I go through an entire week without thinking about anything else besides what I have to do for my classes and the chores I have at home.  Painstakingly sad.  I completely loose touch with reality and, more importantly, what is most valuable in life--loving God and loving others.  I may always lead a small life, but I want to live it as Kathleen Kelly said: " valuable , but small".
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is a picture of Ralphy.  We let him go about 30 minutes ago. I poured some hampster food in the grass outside, so maybe he can find it and not starve. I don't know why I can come to terms with the fact that wild animals can take care of themselves!        
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Nothing much happened this weekend. (I think I'm supposed to write something for everyday, but let's just face it, Mon-Fri is about all I can handle.)    So I've decided to let you know what I did.  1.)  Jeremy and I had a romantic date with PRAXIS. We get to administer the tests and make a car payment in $ in eight hours on Saturday.  2.)  I went to bed at 6:00 PM on a Saturday and didn't get up till 8:00 AM.  Hey, there's a first time for everything.  3.)  I read in my book,  Free to Choose   4.)  We went to the Knoxville   Borders   to lounge, check out GRE books, have a Chai. On the way home the Hot sign was on, so we had  urlLink one  of those too. (If you don't know what I'm talking about, then you are not from these here parts)  5.) Of course! Went to  urlLink church .  I like my church a lot. Our pastor went to same high school that Jeremy did in California.   (Most weekends include a romantic date, so maybe this coming Friday will work out!)   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      He is the most adorable little mouse that I have ever seen, or as we have been calling him, mousy.  Jeremy finally cornered him, but instead of putting him outside, Jeremy's mousy has a little home  inside .  I know it's a little wierd to be hosting a common household rodent, but let's just say that Jeremy has already named him.  Ralph.  Which I expect will evolve into Ralphy pretty soon.  I don't think it really matters if it's a boy or girl.  I mean we'll probably never know.  Anyway, Ralphy has his own kitchen kettle with matching skylight glass lid (it has a hole in the top for air), a kitchen towel, a bottle cap full of water, cheese, bread, and a carrot nubby.  Do mice eat carrots?  Well, Ralphy has one if he wants it.  Before I left for work today he was nestled in a little gray furry ball--sleeping.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well everyone when I learn how to post correctly I will start blogging. Till then!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Welcome to the wonderful world of Mandy. Well, I think it's wonderful. I've decided to cave in and join the bandwagon. I have a blog. Not just any generic blog, but a blog full of exciting and wonderful ideas, hopefully pictures at some point, and my ever valued opinion (cough). To all my friends and family, I hope this is a way that you can better keep up with this crazy Samoan girl. So sit back and enjoy.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, apparently I've been told (by Waunita) today that I'm well versed.  Believe me, people know where I grew up and they also agree that I don't speak Cocke Countian.  I'm actually quite relieved when people look at me funny after I tell them where I'm originally from.  I usually try to bypass the whole thing by just saying, "Yeah, I grew up about 30 min. from here", but most people ask me where. Then I'm exposed...and people are astonished.  Don't get me wrong, I'm nothing spectacular, but you have no idea with whom people are comparing me!  Anyway, I'm glad to be me.  And I'm also glad to be from Tennessee (even the most backward part).
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      So we found out last night that we have an opportunity to go to Venezuela and Mexico in the Spring for missions trips.  One of them is even a medical missions trip.  I'm really excited to see what God has planned for Jeremy and I in the future!  It would be great if we could go on both of the trips, but I know it's going to be a huge time commitment on top of my 9 credits of Spanish, Gross Anatomy and Zoology.  But hopefully something can work out.  Help us pray for this great opportunity.  I still can't decide between D.O. and M.D.  I keep hearing mixed messages from different people.  Namely, the D.O.s don't like the M.D.s and visa versa.  Personally, I think they're both great and they just need to stop competing with each other and start working together.  Even more frustrating is the fact that people have no idea what a D.O. is anyway.  You do, right?  So I've got some big decisions to make before June.  I can't apply to both programs because they don't like those lukewarm students.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I realized that after I posted the picture link that it didn't work.  I'll figure it out eventually!  Maybe I'll get Don to share some of his HTML smartness, but I have a feeling it has nothing to do with that crazy computer language.  Oh, well.  You'll see them soon enough.  Thanks for visiting my blog Marie and Jakob! I hope you guys are having a steamy hot time in Africa.  I'm so jealous.  But I shouldn't be since I've been offered so many invitations to occupy the available backseat of your Land Rover!  I can't wait to hear from you guys again soon.  And for goodness sakes, get to a place where it's cold...it's the middle of winter (haha).  Just finishing up finals, so my brain is a little fried.  I'm going to end up on Dean's list (at least that's what I'm expecting)..so all in all it was a fairly good semester.  Yeah!  T minus 4 days till we go to Basking Ridge!!  Other than that I'm sorry to disappoint you with my blah blog.  I can't really come up with anything cute or funny or interesting....lalalalala. EXCEPT, Saddam looked like crap today. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just wrote a blog for today and lost it.  Agh!  If anyone know what I'm doing wrong please let me know.  I just seem to hit the wrong button sometimes and can't retrieve what I wrote.  If you know whether or not I can get my blog back, let me know!!!  I'm not sure if this works or not.  I'm playing around.  But, go  urlLink here  and see if you can see a picture!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Phoebe is being a little bugger lately.  Now every time we go in the kitchen, she insists on having her little tablespoon of milk. I've created a monster.  Jeremy says that I spoil her too much.  I said, yes.    Jeremy is a nut because when told to make enough food for 40 people at this luncheon today for some students... he did it.  Now we'll be eating mac and cheese forever.  Tisk, tisk.  He didn't listen to me when I said that 1) 40 people won't show up and 2) not everyone will eat mac and cheese.  It's a good thing he's so stinkin' cute.  We're counting down the days till NYC!! Casi, casi!!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      My chemistry test, my insane paper and a good performance in band last night are at the top of my accomplishment list. Whew. Now I can relax. Wait...now I have to write another paper due on Mon. as well as prepare for an interview in Spanish.  On top of this I have another research paper due  in Spanish  next week.  Apparently no one got the memo to not book everything all at once for Mandy Anderson.    I'm really excited to finally take Jeremy to NYC!  We have three free nights at the Comfort Suites, so why not?!  He mentioned that he wants to go ice skating at Rockafeller Center, which I though was an excellent idea.  How sweet.  Of all the years I spent in NJ, I never did that.  Plus, I'm really excited for my old friends to meet Jeremy.  Hey, do any of you have any good ideas for a Christmas card picture since we have to take it this weekend?  If you do let me know (email me).    A little bird, well, Todd Howell from the  urlLink channel 10 news , told me that it was going to snow tonight. Yeah, yeah, I'll believe it when I see it.  But I'm sure the stores are flooded even as I write making sure they won't run out of milk and bread during the dusting.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      My lip is practically cut on the inside from playing four hours yesterday.  The new R-13 is a little challenging for the chops. BUT! Tomorrow is concert day!  I'm nervous, as usual.  You know, being first chair is not all it's cracked up to be.  Sure it's great to walk out on stage all by yourself and get comments like "why were you the only one late?" Haha.  Anyway, I'm looking forward to everything but  Sleigh Ride , which will undoubtedly be (like it has been in every other band concert on the planet EVER) a nightmare. So come and get yourself some chapel credit!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      A complete nut.  This is my beloved English 301 professor who likes to drop the F-bomb and call it a "literary term of expression...that when used intelligently it is not the same as saying f*** you."  He said it eight times in class last night.  Apparently it's not as "bold" in Ireland as it is in America, and since he is Irish-Catholic, he obviously has the right to say it in a Southern Baptist (no doubt) college class.  Furthermore, he has belittled the blog, much to my chagrin.  He was talking about how some people publish their pathetic poetry on their blogs.  Well.  So they may.  But don't smack down the good blogs out there at the same time.  Granted, this one may not be one of them, but it satisfies my need to feel important.  By the way, I am so over his class.  Just go ahead and give me the freaking A.  I've earned it buddy.-+
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Bummer.  Anyway, I was ranting on the fact that I have a ten page paper due tomorrow in the hardest class I've ever had in the honors program.  It's a book critique on a book I absolutely hate (which should make it good to critique, right?).  The problem is I've never been good at critiquing before.  I think I have this mechanism inside of me that makes it hard for me to substantiate my opinions.  Don't be mistaken, I have opinions. I just don't know if I have ten pages of opinions on one book.  Sigh.  Plus, I've had all semester to write this paper, yet I always manage to wait till the last minute.  This is why I'm not ready for medical school.  I need a butt-kicking job first.  A job that will force me to plan ahead and to get my "ducks in a row" (I've heard this phrase too many times in my life).  Just when I feel like so many of my "ducks" are "in a row" I have to go and add more "ducks".  It's hard being a senior and having to worry about honors program requirements, my honors project and a second major.  These "duckies" better "row" soon or we are all in a heap.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is the last blog till after Venezuela.  So have a great week next week and I'll be sure to report what  has happened there when I return.  I can't believe that after this weekend I should be almost home free on my honors project.  I have to plug in some major hours before we leave unfortunately.  When it's finished maybe I'll let you guys read it.  Do you even have a clue what Boron Neutron Capture Therapy is?  You can look it up on the internet if you want to get a heads up, but the intro of my project is baby language about the chemistry and physics behind the project.  My whole 1 1/2 years work has focused on the cytotoxicity of certain synthesized boron compounds on MDA breast cancer cells.  I've gotten some good data over the past three semesters so hopefully I can find some statistical significance verifying (or not) their safety  in vivo .  BNCT is not widely known and it's one of those cancer treatments that looks amazing on paper, but for the past 40 or so years, researchers have been missing something in their trials.  Either they kill people because the gammas are too strong or they don't have a safe, effective compound.  Okay, I guess I should give you the simplest version of how the therapy works.  Here we go.  Boron (in the form of some compound) is injected into the body.  Hopefully it will collect into cancer tissue more readily than normal tissue (I can't elaborate on that because it's more than a mouthful.) The key is having it be non-toxic in the body, but highly toxic after the radiation hits it.  Once the cells are irradiated, the ones that have the boron in them basically explode (remember this is on the cellular level).  Boron, being so excited about the radiating starts emitting alpha, beta, etc. particles which ultimately kills the cell.  Dr. Kabalka, the stronghold of BNCT in the area, says that all we need is the right compound.  Well, can I just say that there are an unlimited amount of compounds that can be sythesized using boron, and we need to come up with something better than trial and error.  I'm hopeful about this treatment in the future, but we need more hands on deck and more money for this therapy to really take off.  Unfortunately, there have been too many blunders, so the government is not just handing out the money on this.    Okay.  Adios for a while!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have always been an avid fan of Grainger.  Or, as I like to call him, Percy.  We're on a first name basis.  So I have my second chance at struggling through the Posy since I've already played it once at Messiah.  This time around is a whole lot better.  The part in the 4th movement that goes dodiladidado dodiladidado dodiladidado dodiladidado dodiladidado do da lalalalalalalala etc. is coming along quite nicely.  I know I can play this lick because I used this as my audition piece and I got first chair last year.  It's just that either my brain or my fingers is having a slow day and it takes both of them having a fast day to pull it off.  Needless to say, by concert time, I'm going to house it.  Now the problem is making sure other people can play it too cause dang if I'll have it only be me.  Too risky.  What if my reed cracks?! What if I knock over my stand! What if...!  I don't even want to entertain those ideas.  Maybe someday I'll be able to play the Molly (as in  Molly on the Shore !)  Todavia no.  Let's talk about Spanish.  Yeah for me! Yeah that I got into a freaking 400 level Spanish class without taking the prereqs!  Wow that's a great accomplishment!! Oh, joy! I'm so wonderful! DON"T BE FOOLED.  It takes me hours to read the literature in there and I seem to have a problem taking notes in class.  I have enough problems just listening. The Spanish-English dictionary is my new best friend and I'm sure Jeremy's tired of hearing, "Honey how do say..?"  Well, apparently the whole department thinks I can do it since it took every professors vote to get me in there.  See, this is what happens when you squeeze a WHOLE major into 3 semesters.  So I've made up my mind to succeed, or to die trying! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      And my dad just sent me a new pair from Hawaii along with some chocolate covered Macadamia nuts, a  crazy shirt        hooded zip up thingy, some soy stuff (I have no idea), and some cookies.  Do you know what this means!?  This means that I'm going to be over dosing on chocolate for the next two weeks (if you can even do that).  I think I ate about 30g of fat of this stuff already...for breakfast! (Dang, you know, the summer is so far away and I'll wear it all off before I go out on the sailboat in my swimsuit). If any of you remember the last time I had my quarterly package, then you know exactly why I can't stop eating the stuff. Plus the flip flops are so cute.  I've been wearing the same dollar store beaded pair forever now, so I think it's time I retire those.  There are other reasons why I should retire those as well.   But don't worry, that still leaves about 3 other pairs not including the new ones.  I think these are designer ones because they have a little tag on them that says when the sole should wear out, and if it does before that, there's an address where I can send them and get them repaired.    So one week from today, Jeremy and I will be arriving at the airport at 5 AM headed for Venezuela.  I think my Spanish is going to be fine, I'm just a little nervous about it.  I seem to be doing really well in class, though.  I'm starting to speak more and say things more correctly.  Maria, who is the Venezuelan wife of the pastor in charge of the trip, said that my accent is as good as hers.  Well, if there's anything I do have, it's the accent.  I have Jeremy to thank for that (thanks cutie).  He makes me repeat my vowels. Oh, in class the other day we saw  La Celestina , which is a horrible medieval precursor of Romeo and Juliet, starring none other than Penelope Cruz.  She was awful.  She sounded like a mouse, and she had this awful pouty look on her face the whole movie.  You know the face.  It's the one where someone is trying to look seductively cute but it miserably fails.  I wanted to smack her.  What does Tom see in her?  Are they still together anyway?  I can't believe he left Nicole.  Que lastima.  So here are some things you can pray for about the trip:  1.)  That the people will be receptive to us and the reason that we are there 2.)  That we may be instruments of Him and not let our own flesh get in the way 3.)  That we will be healthy and strong 4.)  That we may minister effectively to their medical need 5.)  That I don't accidentally give out the wrong medication!  Thanks!  If you would like to see where we will be please go  urlLink here.   We are working in Maracaibo and the weather should be quite favorable.  I've heard it's like an eternal spring.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Si tienen algunas sugerencias sobre esto, por favor, dame una llamada o una carta electronica.  Bueno.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I think this is my new favorite color.  I got this Victoria's Secret lime green robe as a late Christmas present (since it went from $78 to $29 like nothing after the Holidays).  Some people say yellow is the happy color, but that bright Wal-mart smiley face yellow hurts my eyes.  Lime green is much better.  It's a relaxing color to look at.  Maybe it's just because of my robe.  Every time I see lime green I think about my fuzzy, comfy, warm, cute, snuggly robe.    My zoology lab deserves some blogging.  It was wild.  We took the guts out of a live termite in order to see the vast array of flagellates that are in symbiosis with it.  I made my lab partner squish out the guts since I figured I hurt enough little bugs as a child.  Oh, plus I was one of the few in the class to actually find an amoeba from the amoeba jar (they hide...and they're  very small  ).  Other cuties included paramecium and euglena and the euglena has the cutest little tail....um...sorry...cutest little  flagella .  My parter today also said he saw two protozoans  conjugating .  Do you know what that means? (giggle)   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay, I started drinking diet coke a couple of years ago because I was going through this fat phase and now that's all I can drink.  I really can't stand regular coke because I feel like the sugar is just coating all of my dental crevices, and we can't have that on these newly white stripped teeth.  So it's a good thing that there's more than just regular diet coke.  There's caffeine free diet when I need only bubbly fixations (opposed to when I need pick-me-up bubbly fixations).  There's cherry diet, vanilla diet, and this new great lime diet.  I think it's absolutely fabulous.  Mmmmmmmmmmmm.  I watch it though.  I only drink diet coke when we go out for dinner or when I buy my lunch at the Eagle's Nest.....or when I eat lunch in the cafeteria...or when I can sneak it into the buggy.....or... oops.  Plus my water habit is slacking a little because my poor little Nalgene is still soaking from having a lime in it a little too long (over the Holidays).  Let's just say that it was a little furry when I found it.  Yuck.   So have I ever told you about my job?  I have this lovely little job at the library that I've had since last summer.  I work in the media center, which has to be the easiest minimum wage I've ever earned (nothing like the time I slowly tried to kill my self by working at the nursing home).  I work with really great people too.  Waunita is so sweet and Donnie is a great boss.  He calls me Mrs. Anderson and we always laugh about how I'm the important one on campus and not my husband (cough).  I've learned how to use excel really well, and I get to do lots of cool things on campus like videotape events and look all important and stuff.  I taped chapel this morning.  On top of all this, I really feel smart spending so much time in the library.  I can navigate around and actually help people.  Like this guy sitting next to me who didn't have a clue where to start when looking up fetal alcohol syndrome (I hope he can't see this!).  So don't be fooled, I know more about the library than just checking out videos and taping.  I've been  well   trained.  Highly trained, in fact. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      That got your attention didn't it?  Well, we've been expecting it for quite some time now, but it really is shocking to find out for sure.  We found out yesterday and couldn't be happier! I can't wait to start shopping for baby things and figuring out what the baby looks like every week (that should be easy since I have my gross anatomy book with a chapter on development).  In a few days, limbs are going to start to form.  How wonderful is that!  Tiny baby arms!  The due date is sometime in September.  Wow there's so much to do before then!  I really need to prepare myself since this is a huge deal for the family.  My sister-in-law and her husband are ecstatic, since she's the one having the baby (gotcha).  I can't wait to be Auntie Mandy!  It's too bad that we'll probably be living in Philly in September :(
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm nervous.  I'll be the only bilingual person in the pharmacy and I have to be responsible for handing out the right medications! That's a little crazy. Plus, I have to make labels for all the meds, including what they are and when to take them, in English and Spanish.  Oh, it was really funny the other night when I went to the meeting with all the doctors and nurses and the lady speaking though my name was Jeremy (she's Venezolana).  This happened because when the pastor was introducing me he was calling me Jeremy's WIFE, but she didn't hear the wife part.  The funniest part was the fact that neither I nor anyone else corrected her.  I meant to, I just could never get a moment and I didn't want to embarrass her.  So, we're leaving on the 2nd of February and we'll return on the 8th.  This means that I'll spend my birthday down there.  But I'll be 23, which is nothing special.  You know, I wouldn't be so nervous about the Spanish except for the fact that every Latin and South American country has their own way of saying stuff.  Plus, there are words that are very very offensive down there that aren't in Spain.  I hope I don't use  figar  instead of  molestar .  That could be very bad.     
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      And every time I tell Jeremy to look, it stops.  Don't you hate that?  On to other things. We're contemplating another new car.  I really don't understand why since we just bought a car last February, a Saturn Ion, which I really think is a great car.  The problem is we've been putting a lot of miles on it and Jeremy says that we should think about trading it in soon (he's taking manangerial finance so maybe he knows what's up). I have no idea about this kind of stuff.  I just know that if I work for  urlLink Quest  starting this summer, they will give me my own stinking car, a gas card, and another credit card for misc. items.  And we wonder why healthcare costs are steeply climbing.  I just want to say that, yes, I understand that I'm using Quest as a money making scheme to pay for medical school, but it's not my life dream to work for a company like this.  But don't tell them that.  I hope to escape after a while with an exorbitant salary that will buy all that my medical school heart desires.  Plus maybe Quest will teach me some things about the working world which can only help me in the future really.  What is the deal with plastic surgery?  Dr. Phil  had a special show last week all about women who have had many plastic surgeries.  One woman didn't even look human anymore.  Today, I read at  urlLink CNN  that Olivia Goldsmith died of complications due to a plastic surgery mishap.  What is happening to us?  Whatever happened to growing old gracefully?  Women are actually dying to get their boobs to look bigger, their face to look tighter, and their butts to look like they were 15.  I admit that I have, in the past, wanted certain parts of me to be different, but I don't think I'd risk my life for it.  Albeit a small mishap %, the chance is still there.  And would you like to be remembered as the woman who died of cosmetic surgery?  I sure wouldn't.  I actually feel sorry for her.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've been going from sun up to  way  past sun down the past two days.  When our prof told us that it would only take 2 hours to prosect the posterior crural region, she lied.  It took 4.  So on top of my already prescribed 4 hour lab, my partners and I had to do an additional 4 hour lab (on our own).  These two labs add up to a work day.  Shoot me in the head why don't you.  AND I smell like formaldehyde forever.  My shoes, my backpack, my books, my clothes, my hair.  I immediately go home and shower and I can still smell it.  HOWEVER, I will thank myself when I'm in medical school since gross anatomy will not be a novelty.   Oh, the pictures from last blog should work now if you tried them before and didn't get anything.  We we're trying to take all these pics for our Christmas card, but ended up using the Rockefeller picture because these were all a little blurry.  They're still fun, though!     
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I hope you enjoy these funny pictures taken in front of our Christmas tree.   urlLink Here they are. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It doesn't work. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Go here to see if you can see a picture.  Remember, I'm still learning!  A funny  urlLink picture. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Dear Friends and Family,  We hope this letter finds you doing extremely well!  We are writing with some exciting news that we’ve already shared with some of you: we’ve recently been given the incredible opportunity to travel to Venezuela for a medical missions trip.  Our pastor, along with the pastor of a sister Hispanic congregation, has been forming a small team to go to Puerta, Venezuela this February 2nd through 7th.  Our two pastors will be leading evangelism and training for local pastors there, while the doctors and pharmacist host a clinic for locals, making great use of donated medical supplies and prescriptions.  Puerta is a rather poor, rural community where the people do not otherwise have access to medical attention or medicine, so the turnout should be tremendous.  As the clinic bustles with patients eager to receive help, Jeremy will be interpreting for the doctors, and Mandy will be assisting the pharmacist.  We believe that these tasks will help the clinic run more smoothly and will provide opportunities to share the love of Jesus with these precious people.  This kind of ministry is close to both of our hearts, and we feel that the Lord has many more such trips for us in the future.  We are asking you to please consider supporting our team in this effort to reach an under-served people.  Your fervent prayers for our entire team are by far the greatest support you can offer us.  When you pray, please ask the Father not only to protect the whole team, but to equip us to be effective in every aspect of ministry while we are there.  Please pray that the Lord will touch the hearts of those who do not know Him, and that He will further reveal Himself to those who already walk with Him.   Please do not feel guilty if you are unable to support us financially—we sincerely mean it when we say that your prayers are of utmost importance to us.  If you are able to help fund this ministry, though, every donation helps.  The estimated cost for us to join the team is between $2,200 and $3,000.  Please ask the Lord what He would like you to contribute, and know that we do not want you to feel any pressure from us.  If you feel the Lord is calling you to help financially, please do not hesitate, since this trip was a recent development for us and is rapidly approaching.  Please make any checks out to Jeremy Anderson.   The Lord bless you!  We will be sure to follow up and give you a report on what God did through us when we return.    Love,  Jeremy and Mandy Anderson    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Based on experience I would recommend these fine products:  1.)  TRESemme: it's cheap, yet a pretty good shampoo.  Don't bother spending $18.95 on a bottle of shampoo if you don't need too.  However, I wouldn't recommend going in the total opposite direction with White Rain.  2.)  Humectress by Nexus:  Well, now you're going to have to fork over some decent bucks for this, but I think it's more important than shampoo.  You can buy it at hair salons, and don't trust it from the drug store (it's usually more expensive there anyway).  3.)  Clearasil daily facewash is my personal favorite after trying tons of face cleansers.  Also, the spot treatment is really good too.  If you have sensitive skin, I would go with the unscented kind.  4.)  Oil of Olay daily moisturizer.  This is so essential.  Get on that has some sort of SPF protection.  When you're 40, you'll thank me.  5.)  Organic Body wash is excellent.  It's expensive (but hopefully you can make up for that with the price of the shampoo :-)  Buy it at health food stores like Wild Oats etc.  If you can't get this, Oil of Olay is your next best option.   6.)  If you don't own a loofah by now, you are definitely behind the times.    7.)  MAC makeup is the best.  I don't really wear a lot, but they have great colors and cover-up that can perfectly match anyone's tone.  I'm a yellow :-)  8.)  Norelco makes the best men's electric razors.  I just bought one for Jeremy.  9.)  Okay, I know that White Rain is not the best at everything, but they do pretty well with the mousse.  I think it's my favorite because it's not too stiff and it smells great.  10.) Don't ever buy anything from Avon.  I hate them.    11.) Sobie curl formula is the best best best with naturally curly or wavy hair.  I've been straighting my hair much less the past year and wearing it curly, and this stuff is the best I've ever used.  It's really hard to find, though, and I haven't been able to find it in a while!  So if you do, let me know!  12.) Victoria's Secret has the best lotions and body sprays.  One of my favs is Endless Love.  Classic.  Plus, check out the lipsticks and lip pencils there.  I seem to prefer them over MAC.  Well, that's all I can come up with right now.  Gotta go work-out! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So they have names, ladies and gentlemen.  My two special dead friends whom I will know quite well by May are named after Antony and Cleopatra (or is it Anthony?)  Today was the first day of lab and I got to spend quality time with Tony.  I won't go into all the details, but I was really shocked that fungus would still want to grow on him.  This just proves that they are not picky at all.  So we took care of them with a little bleach water.  Other than that, he looks about as good as you can look 6 months after death.  He's a little guy, which makes it easier to turn him over.  Man, I'm not looking forward to turning him over with only my two lab partners (they're girls, too) during our extra prosection lab(even if he is small).  Let's just say it can be messy if you don't do it right.  Stuff can fall out, juice can leak onto your shoes, that sort of thing.  Plus during our 4 hour lab I got the total heads up on fertilization.  Details that I have never known before.  It is so complex.  Most people think, "Oh, yeah, the sperm gets in the egg and poof!", but let me tell you, it is so detailed that I need at least 12 colored pencils to draw it for you.  On to another topic.  Jeremy is applying to Eastern U. in Philadelphia for a MBA program in international economic development (or something like that).  I'm really excited about this and I hope that Qwest will land me somewhere near there when I graduate.  When he's done with the program, more than likely we'll end up living in another country for part of our lives.  I think that would be excellent.  But before I get too excited I have to go to med school.  It a good thing that there are so many in that area.  Wow, us...living in Philly!!  This could be really great.  Don't worry, though, we are keeping the door open to possibly living in Mexico next year.  We'll see what happens.  I really think Jeremy is perfect for this program and they would be idiots not to take him.  Should I tell that to his admissions lady?  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have 9 credits of Spanish this semester.  If I don't consistently dream in this language, I will be shocked.  I've had dreams in Spanish before, but they've always been me listening to someone else speak it while I tried to figure out what they were saying.  This isn't exactly what they mean when they say that dreaming in Spanish is a sign of fluency.  I think that requires  me  speaking in Spanish.  I am glad, though, that I'm pushing myself when all I need is one stinking class to graduate (and I could have already taken it).  I've also decided to go a little further and take Gross Anatomy.  I know you're thrilled because now you can hear all of my cadaver horror stories in the future (i.e. foot fungus, funky things growing where they shouldn't, how I accidentally cut off one of his/her fingers, things like that).  I'm honestly looking forward to most of it.  I'm not exactly thrilled about wearing formaldehyde home, but spending 4 hours a week with two dead bodies is my idea of a good time.  Okay, I'm going to go exercise now.  It's kind of dumb to drive to the SAC (student activity center) and then work out, but it is soooo cold outside.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I was a little busy over the Holidays to say the least.  I managed to visit 6 states in the course of our journeys, but now I am safe and sound at home snuggling under our new 650 fill ultimate down comforter.  This has been the best Christmas ever!  Last Christmas was great because it was the first Christmas with Jeremy, the Christmas before that was, well, not so great, so I'm happy that they are looking brighter  as time goes by .  (Play it again, Sam).  The New Year looks exciting and Jeremy and I brought it in with a bang.  I took a nice bubble bath, we sipped some little bubbly drink, and then watched the ball drop. It was fabulous to be home, alone! The babies are really happy that we're home too.  Febie is glued to my lap.  I suppose I should tell you what my resolutions are.  Well, I'm drinking more water (gotta keep up with this modeling stuff), reading the Bible every day, and exercising 3 days a week.  I really can't loose any weight, though, because the doctor says that body fat shouldn't be below 14% (and mine is), so I hope to gain a little muscle.  Exercising is really for my health not my weight, since being a size 2 is skinny enough.  Why did I ever worry about that before?   I really need to get cracking on this Honors project since I have to turn it in early (b/c of Venezuela). So pray that I will find the strength! It's looking good...I just need to put it all together.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I know I wrote about this a while ago, but I just wanted to include this picture of this really cute little girl (even though she has her hand over her mouth)!       
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My Quest endeavors are continuing even though I haven't been talking about them.  I sent them my resume and Pam seems to think that I will have no problem getting one of the positions as a full-fledged sales representative.  Let me tell you a little bit about what I think is going to happen.  In a couple of weeks I'm traveling over to beautiful Williamsburg to visit Pam and perfect my resume (I want to make sure it emphasizes exactly what Quest wants to know about me.)  Next, I will hopefully be selected to participate in the profiling, which I can do online.  This test basically can predict how I will succeed in the company based on the profiles of their most successful sales reps.  Next, I will go for a formal interview which hopefully will let me know if I'm hired or not.  I think this is going to be sometime in April.  In June, training begins in several different locations including NYC, PA, and NJ (I think).  But the greatest thing about training is I get a salary while I'm there! I can't tell you how much or you will hate me.  But, anyway, this is actually a really needed thing since Jeremy is leaving his job to move us to Philly this summer and training for me is quite extensive and lasts till August.  After that I will have my own territory and work on commission!  What a sweet deal.  Now I can pay off loans, be a wife, read books  I  want to read and get myself some extra sanity stored up before medical school.  Speaking of med school, the hopefuls are Temple, Jefferson Memorial, and PCOM, which are all located in Philadelphia.  I think Jeremy will probably have a job base there (while he's not traveling abroad).  And, Philly has more hospitals per mile than any other place in the world.  I just need to decide if I'm going for D.O. of M.D. since there are pros and cons to each.  I'm so excited to get out of college it's crazy.  I want to be out of this fish bowl as soon as possible and start really experiencing life.  For those of you who are worried about me going to med school...don't.  Jeremy is going to make me go, even if I'm kicking and screaming to go back to comfortable life with Quest.  I think, in the meantime, Quest is going to teach me some very important lessons which will only help me succeed more in medical school.    Glory to God for all of the blessings He continually brings into my life!!!  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      President Netherton is finally getting a good snow head on his shoulders, but I'm not so happy about it.  It's snowing pretty hard right now and look who cleaned off the car (but by the time I went all the way around...it was coverend again) and got my little self to work only 10 min. late.  Folks, if we can't count on snow days when there's even a hint of snow, what  can  we count on here in the South?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I passed!  I passed!  My honor's project passed!!!!!!!  There are some corrections I need to make, but nothing too major.  I passed!  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I took an email quiz today and it said that I am 58% Dixie.  Whatever that means.  If they would've asked me these same questions about 10 years ago, then I bet I would've been 100%.  Whatever that means.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've flubbed up the format of my blog and I don't know HTML well enough to fix it!  Help me please.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Amanda Anderson Dra. Wilkerson Español 415 17 Febrero 2004 Los Símbolos Circulares en la película El Norte 	Una manera poderosa y significa de llevar un sentido profundo es el uso de símbolos en literatura o en películas.  Muchas veces,  un tipo de símbolo especifico se usa por todas partes de una obra.  Además, es posible que los varios símbolos tienen más de uno significado, y en el fin, es aparente que un sentido más fuerte es implicado.  Por toda la cuenta en El Norte, el tema de los símbolos circulares es muy evidente, y también tiene connotaciones de algo más importante, algo en relación al círculo de la vida.  Como la cuenta progresa, cada símbolo tiene su propio sentido inmediato, pues los símbolos llegan a tener un sentido profundo en el fin.  Eso es uno de los aspectos más creativos de la película, y después de todo, el mensaje completo es claro. 	Durante el principio de El Norte, hay escenas que describen la cultura y la manera de vivir de la gente indígena como Rosa y su familia.  En una escena en la casa, la madre esta preparando una cena por amansar masa en queques redondos y cocinar en una cacerola redonda encima del fuego.  El significado es que estas cosas reflejan el tipo de vida, la manera de vivir, para mucha de la gente indígena en este tiempo.  Como el círculo de la masa y la cacerola, la vida en ese momento consiste de patrones círculos.  Es decir que la vida para Rosa y su familia continúa dentro de un círculo de trabajo duro, de miedo, de ineludible pobreza, y de injusticia.  Entonces, el ciclo de la vida dura para las indígenas mal tratadas y usadas les parece como si nunca va a terminar.     	En los años ochenta en Guatemala, el ejército tenía mucho poder e influencia.  Básicamente, los soldados instilaban mucho miedo en la gente a través de la manipulación, propaganda, y actos horribles.  Muchos de los habitantes rurales fueron matados y torturados.  En El Norte, un símbolo de peligro son los faros en los vehículos del ejército.  Antes de la muerte trágica de Arturo Xuncax y los otros campesinos, los faros aparecen en la oscuridad como círculos de un agüero malo.  Una escena similar ocurre antes de que la madre de Rosa es agarrado por el ejército.  Los faros demuestran la idea de la lucha de la gente inocente y últimamente la destrucción de la vida inocente.  	Un símbolo que tiene mucho significado religioso son las cuentas del rosario.  Además, la continuación del tema circular se puede ver no solo en las cuentas sino que también en la escudilla donde se ponen.  Cada cuenta, en la religión católica, representa una oración diferente que se debe rezar todos los días.  El ciclo de la fe y esperanza en Dios continúa durante la vida como las oraciones continúan cada día.  Es posible que la escudilla represente esta manera de creencia y oración constante, como la construcción de la escudilla misma. 	La más profunda sucesión de símbolos en El Norte es la sucesión de la luna, la cabeza de Arturo, y el tabor en su entierro.  Mientras las imágenes pasan como un rayo, el tono es bastante serio, y es aparente que las escenas diferentes tienen un mensaje más general y más importante.  Como las imágenes siguen unos a otros, se puede ver la idea de un ciclo en la vida de Arturo.  Desde la luna como una luz en la oscuridad, y la cabeza como símbolo de la muerte, hasta el tabor como un símbolo que, quizás, lévate el alma hacia el cielo, cada símbolo representa su propia parte en el circulo de la vida.  Entones, una manera de interpretar estos símbolos es la creación de la vida en un lugar secreto y oscuro, la aguanta y sufrimiento de la injusticia de vivir, y por último, el sonar del tambor en la marcha el cuerpo hacia el sepulcro, pero también la marcha del alma hacia el cielo. 	La puesta del sol también es un símbolo circular, pero también es un símbolo del fin de la vida.  El mensaje general es que la vida continúa en ciclos hasta la última puesta del sol.  Como la salida y la puesta del sol, la vida hace un viaje desde el nacimiento hasta la muerte.  Pero antes de la muerte, el ciclo de vivir continúa como las estrellas y planetas continúan circundar en la galaxia.   	Los aspectos circulares llegan en el fin con la conclusión que para Enrique, el ciclo todavía continúa y para Rosa, el ciclo ha terminado con su muerte.  Para Enrique, quizás la dificultad nunca terminará hasta su muerte.  El ciclo de pobreza no ha sido roto cuando Rosa y Enrique llegan a los Estados Unidos.  Por lo tanto, el ciclo de vivir no es parado aunque la geografía es diferente. 	La película tiene una variedad de símbolos circular que representan varias ideas y temas a través de la cuenta.  En el fin, el mensaje complete es muy claro.  Los símbolos son objetas significas que representar no sólo represente las ideas diferentes, pero represente también el retrato más grande del círculo de la vida.  Nacimiento, la lucha terrenal, y la muerte son toda parte de la naturaleza circular de la vida.        
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      In Venezuela I was one of the pharmacy workers who actually got to converse with the people.  Oh, by the way, it's not  de nada , it's  a la orden .  I was wondering what the funny looks were for every time I said thank you.  Dialect.  Shoot.  So we must have handed out over 1000 prescriptions.  It's unbelievable that what you and I take for granted, they hold in high value down there.  For example, tylenol is fairly unimportant to us, but there are people there who don't even have money for regular pain relief.  I remember one man in particular who had traveled down the mountain 7 km just to see us.  I ended up giving him extra tylenol because at 77, I knew that climbing back up that mountain was a chore for him.  We didn't have too many severe cases, just many children who needed more nutrition and anti- parasitic drugs.  Jeremy knows more about the real condition of everyone since he had the priveledge of interpreting for Aleesha, a pediatrician.  Over all I was happy that I could understand most everything (after I had to ask them to speak slower).  But the one thing I didn't learn was how to say that Pepto would turn your you-know-what black.  Not sure if I want to know!   I'm kind of walking in the clouds today because I had to stay up last night to finish my honors project.  (For those of you who know me...some things never change, right?)  But I turned it in today! Yeah!  I think they're going to like it even though I know there are still some mistakes in it.  But now all I have to do is get caught up in everything else.   This weekend is going to be awesome.  Happy Valentines Day!  I get to go to a 5 star hotel in Atlanta tomorrow with my cutie pie.  They have a pool, hot tub, full service...I think I'm just going to sit in the hot tub for 3 hours.  I can't wait to relieve some of the stress of school!  Don't worry, it's not officially a pleasure trip since the reason we have to go down there is because of Jeremy's job.  But we're definitely making the most of it.   
    
    
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        
    
    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I had the best birthday I've ever had in Venezuela...ever.  What was so ironic, though, was the fact that I forgot it was my birthday until my loving husband reminded me at lunch.  He was afraid that I would be upset that he didn't say happy birthday when we got up...but no...I had no clue.  See, that's one of the great things about what we were doing down there.  I was so captivated and so busy that I totally forgot about my own life (including my honors project!).  So, I expected some cake back at the mission house with the rest of our group, but, oh no.  Instead they quietly moved the chairs around in the sanctuary (while I was busy talking to people...I seriously didn't notice and even if I did, nothing looked suspicious) to set up for a little "shin dig."  Then I went to the bathroom and the next thing I know I heard my name over the speaker.  I got to the sanctuary for the surprise of my life.  EVERYONE from the church had stayed and they were all singing to me in Spanish.  Then they sang to me in a funny English. It was AMAZING.  There were like 50 people there.  I was so honored and deeply touched that the next day we were talking about it and I started to cry.  I've recorded this feeling as a time when I've definitely felt loved.  So what started out as forgetful turned out to be unforgettable.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I love Febie and Fiona.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm having trouble with the centering.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Jeremy and I at the Mission House     Iglesia Bautista en La Puerta      What an awesome experience.  I'm going to have to tell you all about it in installments because there is just so much to say.  But I hope you enjoy these pictures for now!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      You are in bed and I am stuck at this computer for the 4th straight day/night...I don't even remember.  Yo tengo celos.  I will be glad when tomorrow, um, today, is over.  Three cheers for Boron Neutron Capture Therapy.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The Hormone Hostage knows that there are days in the month when all a man has to do is open his mouth and he takes his life in his own hands!  This is a handy guide that should be as common as a driver's license in the wallet of every husband, boyfriend, or significant other!   DANGEROUS: What's for dinner? SAFER: Can I help you with dinner? SAFEST: Where would you like to go for dinner?  DANGEROUS: Are you wearing that? SAFER: Gee, you look good in brown. SAFEST: WOW! Look at you!  DANGEROUS: What are you so worked up about? SAFER: Could we be overreacting? SAFEST: Here's fifty dollars.  DANGEROUS: Should you be eating that? SAFER: You know, there are a lot of apples left. SAFEST: Can I get you a glass of wine with that?  And my personal favorite..... DANGEROUS: What did you do all day? SAFER: I hope you didn't over do it today. SAFEST: I've always loved you in that robe!  Pass this on to all of your hormonal friends and those who might need a good laugh! Or men who need a warning. And remember. Money talks.  Chocolate sings . 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I got my graduation instructions in the mail today!  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      You're not tired of  urlLink them , right?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Pray for me.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      All four directors in Philadelphia should receive my resume sometime this week.  I'm kind of nervous about it but I really think it looks good.  I can't wait to go look for places to live in May!  Speaking of May, let me know if you want to come to my graduation party on Sat. May 8.  We're either having a pic nic at the dam or having a get together at Glenmore Mansion.  You'll get an invitation soon.  Happy Tuesday.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      These are in order of importance:  1.) Spanish paper about "El Norte" and "Nueba Yol" 2.) Rough draft of paper about "Camila" and "De eso no se habla" 3.) Rough draft of my seminar hypertension paper.  Did you know that hypertension might be correlated with type A  personality, hostility, and anxiety? 4.) Work on tweaking my honors project  I really really really want to go to a movie tonight.  And if I work really really really hard, I may get 3 out of the 4 things done.  So, Jeremy, can we go see "Girl with a Pearl Earring" tonight if I do? (pease)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm writing Spanish papers.  Phoebe was so cute this morning.  She was sitting in my lap playing with my curls.  She loves being a baby.  Because she was so cute, I gave her a whipped cream dolop (very small one) on a dish.  She loooooves it.  One last thing, go  urlLink here  and see some new pictures of my dear friend Becky, who will be going to UK for a masters program! Go Becky!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I can't wait to have some breathing room and a nice couple of days in Williamsburg.  I'm going to see Pamela and we are going to tweak my resume and get this process started.  She told me that it's probable there will be positions open in Philly.  Speaking of Philly,  Jeremy went there this weekend and absolutely loved it.  I always told him that PA was a great state, and I think he believes me now.  He's practically accepted, we're just waiting on the official letter.  Getting your MBA is no easy job, though.  At the end of his program he has to spend 4 mos. in a foreign country (I probably already told you that) and I don't know whether or not I can go with him.  We'll see when the time comes.  Remember the whole D.O. or M.D. episode?  Well, I think I'm leaning towards M.D. now and Jeremy looked at some of the schools up there for me.  I like Jefferson because 1) I know someone there (does anybody know David Assis?) and 2) they have control over many of the medical facilities in the city.  But making money will have to come first.  Oh, and Jeremy looked at some houses while he was there!  I'm so excited at the thought of being a home-owner.  Maybe we can have a dog!  And a little garden in the back!  And a DISHWASHER!!!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      A: Loosing it a few days before you need to get your picture taken for the president's report.    Ummm.  The picture day has come and there is no makeup.  It's not like I have a lot, just a small little black case, but that's why this is bad...I just lost practically  all  the makeup I own.  Plus my band concert is tonight.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Will someone please tell me why a particular student won't use her own advisor to proof read her honors project?  Why does she have to use mine?  Now my advisor is all tied up with  her  this afternoon while I remain on the back burner.  Oh, did I tell you that the copy for publishing is due Monday?  Yeah, so pretty much I have to "come and find [her] tomorrow" and maybe she will have some time to talk to me.  You know, I'm so tired of this crap.  BNCT is starting to mean nothing to me, and that's really sad since I've spent almost 2 years on this project.  If I had it to do all over again, I would have chosen something else and I also would have chosen not to do it at UT.  I felt so disjointed there.  My advisor was here, and she has never been to the lab with me before.  My "advisor" down there was helpful in the beginning, but just let me go on my own after a while.  So I pretty much was on my own down there.  Oh, and since when did a honors project become a mini Master's thesis?  I am an  undergraduate  student folks...hellooo.  I'm fairly smart, but I have not been taught these things before.  Give me a break.  AND the honors council needs to get their butts in gear and actually read my paper.  Two out of the three did (and though the third guy is really nice) he admitted that he had not read my second draft.  He said, "well I just trusted that you and your advisor made the changes." First of all, that's a big no-no and secondly, I went to all the trouble to make this project all that he wanted it to be and he did not give me the courtesy of at least reading it.  He even asked me a question that I specifically laid out in the second draft.  Unbelievable.  I have cut lots of corners in my lifetime, but then again, I AM NOT A COLLEGE PROFESSOR.  I am not responsible for teaching other people responsibility...at least not yet.  Pretty soon this will all be over.  I will cry no more over sleepless nights, printer problems, trying to get the graphs right, and the stupid freaking stapler in the library that has NEVER worked.   Okay, I feel better now.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yesterday was the last day of classes.  And finals will be over soon.  And next Saturday, I will be graduating.  I just got my regalia today. WOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOHOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's awesome.  It's huge.  It holds the amount of water we are supposed to drink in one day (which is supposed to be half your body weight in ounces).  So actually, I don't have to drink the whole thing every day, I can get by with drinking 59 ounces (so there Jeremy ;)).  This is my second day with it on campus and everywhere I go someone has something funny to say about it: "Hey Mandy, you thirsty?"  "That thing's bigger than you are?"  "Well, that's a bladder buster if I ever saw one." (good one Dr. Forrester).  But I really hope I'm inspiring people to drink drink drink.  The mug has all these interesting facts on it like: 75% of the US population are chronically dehydrated and 37% mistake thirst for hunger pangs.  Wow.  I have been known in the past to drink very little water every day, and I never realized how that affected me!  Drinking water gives you energy and fights fatigue...plus it makes your skin glow :).  So go to WalMart and get one.  I think it was $4.96.  I promise, I'm really going to try and keep this up.  And no, you can't have a sip...I'm measuring.   Okay, when I find the film from Mudball day, I will be sure and share these hilarious pictures.  Unfortunately, as I was cleaning the house, I put the film in some crazy place and probably won't find it again for a while.  Knowing me, it really could be anywhere.  #4  Come Away with Me , Norah Jones (okay, so I'm not exactly sticking to the whole "music from different genres" thing)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Tomorrow morning at 8 AM will be the yearly sporting event called Mudball.  How did I get myself into this?  Well, I'm sort of "involved" with the team captain.  Jeremy tells me this is one thing that you can not miss before leaving Carson-Newman.  So I am going to parade around tomorrow in a volleyball pit of mud with some of my friends, trying desperately to keep a ball in the air while, at the same time, trying  not to fall on my face.  I've seen pictures.  The only thing not covered in mud at the end of the tournament is your eyes.  Jeremy even says that the last time he did this (long before me) he was tan for a week because the mud soaked into his skin.  Maybe this only happens to the white folk, I'm not so sure.  So I'm wondering what this might do to me.  I mean, I'm already brown.  Will I turn another shade of brown? A darker brown?  Anyway.  At 8 in the morning, I'm sure mud isn't exactly warm either.  Right now I'm trying to come up with some homework excuses so I can get out of it (just kidding hunny).  So maybe later you will see some lovely pictures posted on this here blog.  I'll be the brown one.  Wait.  So will everybody else.  #5 is  Rhapsody in Blue   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      There are only four more days of class.  It hasn't really hit home yet that in a couple of weeks, I will no longer be a college student.  But, soon I will be a student again, oh sigh.  I have some time to rest before then.    This day has been so stinkin' long.  That's what happens when you get up at 5:30 AM to be a good sister and take your other sister to get her license.  That place was a mess.  I saw a group of guys at the door and I could smell alcohol on their breath.  They even tried to hit on me.  Hellooo.  Is the ring not visible?  I don't think they really cared.  And do they really think that they are going to get their license back?  They've flooded out too many brain cells.  Speaking of crazy guys, last year a guy asked me for my phone number and I told him I was married.  He said that he just wanted to be friends, and then when I offered him Jeremy's cell #, he didn't want it anymore (haha).  Just friends, hah!  So the place was loaded, all kinds of people wanting their DL...16 year olds....crazy people who'd had theirs revoked...etc.  We were only there for two hours, I was shocked.  But we left and Loree finally had a brand spanking new state of TN driver's license.  So I've invited about 60-65 people to my graduation shin dig.  We'll see how many come.  It's a good thing I've got Sally Anderson's amazing talents on my side.  I did, however, but some of the plates this week for the cake... on my own initiative (I can be creative when I want to...even though this doesn't really constitute creativity...well, I have taken up drawing lately....I'm not too bad). They are blue and white checkered with a sunflower in the middle.  I thought they were really cute.  I got matching napkins too :)    # 6 is  Concierto de Aranjuez  (3rd movement)...one of the most beautiful and most romantic pieces of music ever ever written...hands down.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       As Time Goes By 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Jeremy made my graduation invitations yesterday and I think they are sooo pretty.  We bought the invitations at Office Max and printed them off on the computer....and they really look professional.  The cards have a periwinkle blue border with silver outlined leaves and flowers.  It's good that he's so handy...we saved a bucket of money!  It's almost final!  The picnic is going to be directly after the ceremony at Cherokee lake.  We scoped out a really nice spot and we're going to try to Martha Stewart it up a little bit....flowers...candles...pretty tablecloths....really good marinated chicken....ummm hmmm.  I am so looking forward to this.  So, guess what...I get to conduct a march for graduation: National Emblem.  That'll be fun, but I haven't done this in years!  Dr. Forrester will have to have a few sessions with me.  I'll wait till after our concert, which is tomorrow night (chapel credit you all).  And this is the very last college concert that I will ever have.  I got new shoes for it.  Well, they also go with my graduation dress that I just bought today ;). It's white with tiny black threads outlining flowers, and a satin ribbon around the waist.  I love it.  Well, the important things have been taken care of (party...looking cute..etc.) but there are those tiny little details of making sure I pass my classes.  I really don't think this is going to be a problem.  Then, there's always the little problem of a mysterious fine of some sort that may pop up before I can graduate.    About the project...the final final final...the one that will be bound and put in the library....copy will be turned in by May.  They want me to represent some of my data graphically (no prob) and I have to figure out how to use that organic drawing program.  I will let you know when it is absolutely done.  I really would like to set up a link so you can read it if you're interested.  I'll try to figure out how to do that!  And finally, the # 8 choice of music on my list is:  Under My Skin --Sinatra
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just finished presenting my whopping Psycho----Psychosocial (that is) factors as related to hypertension paper!  I think I did a good job, the only thing is, I went over on my time a little bit....oops.  So, if you are a white male....watch out!  Hypertension could be just around the corner.  Go to JAMA, Vol 290, Issue 16, from October 22/29 2003 and see for yourself.  Okay so here is # 9:   My Immortal  (Evanessence)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Easter was magnificent!  He is risen!  I am redeemed!    Getting some of the best food of the year and getting to eat chocolate were just minor perks.    We saw Jeremy's sister over the break and she's finally showing.  She has a cute little tummy and we can't  wait  till September.  They find out next week if it's a boy or girl. Personally, I want a little girl, but then again, I've always wanted to have a girl first!  I'm too girlie myself.  What would I do with a boy?  I'll be just a thankful for a boy but I will seriously have to learn how to play boy games and such.  Jeremy will definitely have the reigns on that!  Marie!  Thank you for you email and you are most welcome for the package.  I was beginning to wonder whether or not it made it all the way to Denmark :)  I'm going to start a countdown list of Mandy's favorite songs (at this stage of her life).  I will try to include all kinds of genres and give you a news song every time I blog. So here it is:  #10:  With or Without You   Stay tuned for the next greatest hits.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      You have to read this  urlLink article .  It sounds so weird.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The previous quote, as all women everywhere should know, is from  Anne of Avonlea .  Actually, it's when Anne goes to Kingsport Ladies College to teach and she mets Ms. Harris (the grandmother of her star pupil) and her very "high feluting" ways.  So Ms. Harris is an old rich stubborn lady who needs constant attention.  Anne breaks all the "rules" when it comes to dealing with the high class.  Such a funny part!  And if there is any fictional character that I could be, it would be Anne Shirley because as a little girl (just as Seinfeld said about boys and Superman) this was an option.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      "I've had just about enough of your monkey shines! I'm not a raggle taggle gypsie! Take me in, take me in!"  This is probably only funny to me, but whatever.  If you know what this is from I will give you five dollars :)  So, here I am at 2:25 AM in Jeremy's office (well, actually Amy's office down the hall) working away...giving Jeremy moral support to finish his national scholarship essay.  Sigh.  You know, I'm really getting used to staying up all night or only having a few hours of sleep!  This past week, I had three all-nighters and about 10 hours of sleep collectively for the rest.  But, this weekend gave me some time to catch up and after my nap with Phoebe this afternoon...I AM WIDE AWAKE.    So Robin, I have a question for you.  Are you doing any studying over there in France?  Everytime I hear from you you're skiing with Pierre or Javier or hopping over to Germany for a little "get-away", or drinking way too much French wine!  So....Je pense que vous devez obtenir de l'étude faite. Arrête d'embrasser les garçons! Je suis juste kidding et j'espère que tout aille bien. Je vous aime!   P.S. I'm going to go ahead and brag, but I just made more than our rent money this morning playing clarinet in ONE Palm Sunday Service at another church.  This is like 65 dollars an hour!  I hope Philadelphia has more gigs like this.    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I took a personality test and my score was 35, which told me that I was in the middle of the Type A/B personality.  Wow.  I really am different than I used to be!  This is good, because right now I'm writing a paper on a research article called "Psychosocial Factors and Risk of Hypertension" which has evidence to say that some characterisitics of a type A personality increase your odds of hypertension.  You go take the  urlLink test .
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Two years ago today, Jeremy R. Anderson asked me to be his wife.  It was no joke!  It was such a lovely night, too.  We ate take home Macaroni Grill and danced to Sinatra (some of the best romatic music ever). Jeremy was even wearing a tux and had brought me the most beautiful flowers ever. Then he popped the question and I was so overcome with shock (in a good way) that I couln't respond for what felt like a whole minute.  Then I said YES!  After we settled down a second, he then remembered to give me the ring!  It wasn't until about two hours later that I realized it was April 1st, but by this time I was convinced it was real.   We are still happily together with two cats, a Saturn ION, and a kitchen full of Williams-Sonoma.    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am totally finished with Carson-Newman...just thought I'd let you know that pharmacology was a success and if you ever have any drug questions, I'm here for you.  You have a lovely night.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's too bad that I can't go tonight with the others since I have a bunch of pharmacology homework to do.  Well, you can't have it all, now can you. Smart people are not the ones you always see playing around with their yuppie habits, unless they're really really smart and have already made their tenth million by 31 years old.    I have a question.  Does running still count when it was the ice cream parlor that you ran to in order to get an ice cream?  Hey, in my opinion, I was going to get the ice cream whether I drove there or ran there...so the way I see it, running definitely counted. I think I just answered my own question, but you do support me, right? :)    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yes that's right.  Mandy DeVon Anderson is a well-know, often quoted, frequently photographed individual.  I just saw the article about me in the President's Report for 2003-2004.  I'm happy with the way it turned out.  Hey I'm just kidding about all that famous stuff. I'm just plain ole' Mandy. But I am happy that they decided to talk about my scholarship to Spain. It was a great thing for me. If you have the opportunity to travel..don't miss out! You learn so much when you're taken out of your environment not only about different kinds of people, but also about yourself.  Okay, I'll step off my soap box now.  I'm writing a paper on bupropion hydrochloride.  I'll let you know how it turns out;).  On a different not, since this whole job thing is really stressful, I try to remember, "Do not be anxious about anything, but in everything, by prayer and petition, with thanksgiving, present your requests to God." Phil. 4:6  I might have a full time job working for Jeremy's parents while we're up there, which would be great. We'll see what pans out. I'm trying to keep in the forefront of my mind that God already knows the plans He has for me and that these are plans to prosper me and not to harm me.  I'm confident that God wouldn't lead us this far for me not to find a good job up there. This eases my anxiety!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm in Nashville this weekend and I can't decide what I want to do today.  Stephanie's wedding was last night and we got to see Stormie and Michael O. again, which is always nice.  She looked like a princess.  All of her bridesmaids wore hoop dresses and the groomsmen wore tails and had canes(I wore my new Audrey Hepburn dress, just in case you wanted to know.)  It was outdoors in front of a mid 19th century southern plantation home. I love going to weddings because they are so moving.  I dang near cried three times.  It's too bad Jeremy couldn't come with me since there was a large young crowd (Steph's new husband is a West Point grad) and there was lots of dancing. I was asked to dance and Mom agreed that it was harmless, so I did.  When I started talking about my fantastic husband, he asked if he would come after him.  I asked for his last name so that it would be easier for Jeremy to find him ;). But today it feels like all the excitement is over :(.  I think a nice walk in the park might help, don't you?  We have some great leads on some really fabulous apartments.  I simply can't wait to have my own washer and dryer.  I think after trucking my laundry to a facility for five years, I'm going to appreciate doing it in my own home!   Well have a lovely day.  Jeremy and I plan to :).
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Did I mention that in this pharmacology class there are only two students.  Me...AND SARAH.  I'm not even going to go there ;)  Folks it's strawberry season and I really want to go pick some!  I just wish I had all that extra time that you're supposed to have the summer after you graduate...unless you're planning on getting married, which in that case, you barely have time for the ADLs.  But anyway, where was I going with that?...oh, so strawberries.  Next to chocolate, they are the best food in the world to me.  Combining chocolate and strawberries is dynamite, which will melt any girls heart and make you forget all about the fact that the significant other did anything offensive (right Mees?). Speaking of chocolate (again and again and again as a prevalent theme in my blog), all Jeremy has to do is give me candy...candy, candy, candy.  What kitty box didn't you clean?  Huh, you made a mess in the kitchen?  Did you say something about forgetting to pay our bills?  I found out today that chocolate has Phenylethylamine.  And it also has a negligible amount of Tyramine, a sympathomimetic agent.  Cocaine is also a sympathomimetic agent.  Now what does this say?    Vicky, I took the pants back and exchanged the 2 petite to a 2 regular.  I didn't realize how much heels would make a difference!  I love these pants.  Very cute and professional.  Now all I need is a profession.  Stay tuned for graduation pictures.  I have to get the CD from Dad first! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So I'm taking pharmacology because 1. I am a nerd, 2. I think it will help me in the future, 3. It's free, thanks to my on staff husband and 4. I have nothing better to do.  But I'm actually really liking the class!  I'm learning all about different meds and how they actually work in the body...not just that they do this or that, but HOW they do this or that.  Cool.  The book that I'm using in a medical school book, so maybe I'll have a little more knowledge before I get there ;)  We went to the Baptist Hospital ICU and Pharmacy yesterday for a fieldtrip and we saw many of these drugs in action.  I have to say, though, that I've been in too many ICU rooms as it is, and I've seen all this equipment before Heck I've even learned how to push buttons on some of these machines.  The best part of the whole trip was seeing a guy in the ICU who'd just come off the respirator and he was singing with his family.  This, by far, is the greatest reward in the medical field.  Gosh I just love seeing people get better!  I want to be part of this! Where do I sign!?    Philly is getting closer and closer.  I'm nervous about the whole job thing, but I'm not too worried.  God has brought us this far and we're confident that this is where we should be.  Maybe I'll have to work at the MAC make-up counter for a while till the next class of reps in September...but it will all work out, I'm sure.  We're going up to look at apartments next weekend!  I'm excited to have a new place.  We have a magazine that has several nice places and they're not terribly expensive.    So, Vicky, I'm going to try to blog more often just for you :)  Remember that music countdown list?  Well the next one on it is Smetana's Fatherland (first movement).  I just heard it last week and it is LOVELY.  You simply have to look it up and hear it.  This movement portrays a river--and it actually sounds like a river.  I can't believe I've never heard this before.  This is what happens to those who are not fortunate enough to take music history (like my loving hubby).  One last thing.  We went sailing last week (my new favorite hobby). Check us out on the boat by clicking  urlLink here .  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Congratulation Kelly and Daniel!  We had so much fun last night! To all the others (Melissa, Kara, Rachel, Laurie, Emily, Laura, Alyssa) you guys are awesome.  It's too bad we're going to be moving away from CN after graduation :(  You have all just been so wonderful and I am going to miss you dearly.  So, what can you make with an egg roll and some friend doughnuts?  I better not say since other people read my blog :) 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I was freezing all day yesterday and today it's nice and sunny again.  I don't get it.  Now I'm worried about next weekend at the lake for my graduation picnic.  Is it going to be 40 again? Brrr. I hope I can still wear my new dress :).  Now I have to go learn about the vertebrates.    Continuing with the "love song" list: #3 is (and don't laugh it's a great song)  If You're Not the One 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My advisor is really wonderful actually.  She's very caring and willing to give me all the help she can.  I was just in a terrible mood on Friday.  But, the girl, yeah, I still don't really like her too much ;).    It's almost over!  Once my advisor takes her last look in a few minutes, this project will be in the Hussung's mailbox faster than you can say  The Cytotoxicity of Four Boron-Synthesized Carrier Compounds for the Use in Boron Neutron Capture Therapy .  I have my Spanish community service presentation tomorrow, a zoology and seminar final on Wednesday, and then I am completely done.  The word "completely" makes me very happy.   So yesterday, I am ashamed to say, I watched  Maid in Manhattan  four times.  I wasn't paying attention to the movie the whole time, but I had it going while I worked.  Jeremy thinks this is strange that sometimes I like background noise and sometimes I need complete silence.  I know, I don't get it either.  But the movie is so extremely cute.  It's one of the no brainer types, but it still can make you cry!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This blog is to honor Jeremy's (well, mine too) Grandma and Grandpa for all their support and for giving us so much!  Thank you for everything you've sent us. You have made our lives so much less stressful is this (sort of) uncertain time! We love you.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The list:  1.  Pack 2.  Pack 3.  Pack 4.  Pack 5.  Pack 6.  Pack 7.  Pack 8.  Pack 9.  Pack 10. Pack
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It was Jeremy's birthday yesterday and he asked for apple pie.  Hot diggity!  THIS I can make.  I just got this new pie dish from W. Sonoma (we were lucky to get a bunch of wedding stuff from there...the pie plate was a belated gift), and it was great.  So first I went to the market to buy 16 apples.  You have to get the Granny Smith and the Galas, so you have a mixture of sweet and tart in the pie.  For the crust, I have a recipe that Pam gave me years ago.  The crust is really what makes the pie.  As for the rest, I made it up.  A little cinnamon here, a little nutmeg there, some sugar, butter, and whatever else looked good was thrown in the bowl with all of the apples.  Well, let me just tell you that they turned out great (I made two).  I may not be the best at cooking dinner, but dang it I can bake!  We had the newlyweds from downstairs and another really great couple over along with my sis.  If I had a maid who would peel all of my apples for me, I'd make apple pie every week. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I actually drove all by my little self all the way to Philadelphia this past week.  My interview went so well...he already told me they would be contacting me for a second interview with the district manager!  I think it was my new suit.  No, actually, I think it was the fact that my answers were unbelievable good for a person with no sales experience (except for Victoria's Secret...in which my only motivation was to get the discount). I think this new company and I could get along really well.  It's not all in-the-bag yet, though. I've matured to the point where I realize that NOTHING is in the bag till you sign on the dotted line, and then even some things can change. Anyway.  So Jeremy got me this great hotel on Priceline. This place was nicest place I've stayed in since the Honeymoon.  It really was a shame that Jeremy couldn't come (you know ;). My biggest fear while I was up there was how to get from place to place.  This was easily fixed thanks to the help of my sweetie.  He actually faxed directions to the hotel and sometimes to other places (It was pretty funny when he faxed directions about another housing prospect to the one that I was visiting at the time). Ah, they'll get over it.  But the cool thing is, he linked all of them together so I had directions from point A to B and then B to C etc.  It was great.  I never got lost.  Oh, so about the new place! I know you're dying to see it! It's called English Village and it's in Horsham, PA.  I've heard this is a great area to live in.  So go  urlLink HERE  and check it out.  The pool is phenomenal and the clubhouse is better than it looks in the pictures.  Believe me, most of the time this isn't true.  We're getting the 1-bedroom with a den and it has 1 1/2 bathrooms and and a DISHWASHER! Glory!  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Pam told me today that I need to wear a suit for this interview.  What's wrong with a pair of tight pants, see-through blouse and a colored bra? Apparently this isn't appropriate.  So, off we go to the E-town Mall.  I really wanted a suit from  urlLink Victoria's Secret ...but I don't think it'll arrive in time without forking over some decent bucks.  Maybe I'll get that one as a "congratulations to me" gift someday.  Anyway.  So do any of you guys want to help me drive back up to PA? Come on...    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's set for Tuesday at 10AM at Lincare.  Say a prayer for me!  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      That's right.  When I was in Philly this past weekend, he was filming  Shadowboxer  in one of the houses of the development where we were staying.  So, I decided to to sit on the curb and watch a little bit.  There were about 50 people sitting around, doing nothing. All had these little headsets on and frequently yelled "Quiet...rolling".  I wondered as I saw a guy with some duct tape, is this guy the key grip?....he doesn't do very much. They all looked to be in their 20s too, which made me curious as to how they got this job.  Whatever.  As I was about to stand up, Cuba came waltzing toward us wearing a fancy suit, waved to us, and did a little dance right there in the street.  Actually, I would've rather heard him say "Show me the money."  Plus,the thought did cross my mind to blurt out "So how was it working with Tom?"  I restrained myself.    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Here are the pictures that I promised to post!  There are all kind and they're in no particular order. So just go  urlLink here  and enjoy the slideshow!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So a guy from  urlLink Lincare  called me today and wants me to come up for an interview for a sales rep. position. Yeah. Finally something that pays more than peanuts.  I'm waiting around before I call him, since I applied for about 20 jobs yesterday! I want to see who else will call me back. I've already turned down two teaching jobs..with another one still ahead to decide upon.    Vicky and Audrey, I will put two twin beds in my walk-in closet for you.  Just let me know.  Hey Audrey, I'm so proud of you by the way! You're the greatest! You're going to love Carson-Newman. Don't forget that it's this Saturday that you take the ACT. Call me. You can spend the night on Friday. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just don't have the time to tell you all the things that are going on right now in great detail. I'll just have to list them.  1.) The job search is still going on.  I found out that Christian schools don't exactly pay what I think they should.  I've been offered three teaching positions. This is still good, because if worse comes to worse, I can accept.  One administrator said that if he got desperate in the end that he would pay me what I wanted.  We'll see.  I still have some good leads on great sales jobs.  Plus, I applied for some admissions representative jobs at Eastern and the Templeton Honors College.  One in particular is working with people seeking an MBA for Healthcare Administration.  Right up my alley.  2.) We found the greatest apartment!  It's in Hatfield (outside Philly).  Swimming pool...tennis...fitness center...picnic area...free breakfast every morning...two bedrooms...dishwasher...a walk in closet that is the size of our current bedroom...we're so excited.  It looks like this is the top on the list right now.  3.) Smarty Jones...I still think you're great.    4.) Remember the song thing?  Well, here's the next one:  Glorybound  , Martin Sexton. Nate,my good friend from Durham, introduced me to him when he was up here to visit. (Hey Nate, we may be able to come over there and visit either the  19th or the 26th.)  5.) The kitties are still just as cute as ever.  6.) I am totally in love with the new Hershey's kisses with caramel.    7.) I got an A in pharmacology.  8.) I have this new recipe for chocolate muffins that is simply to die for.  There is a secret non-fat ingredient that you mix with a regular package of cake mix.  Please comment if you would like to know what it is :)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      You are not going to believe this.  I was interviewed today...my very first! But the thing is, you'll never guess doing what. Well, being a high school biology and chemistry teacher.  Wow. How crazy is this!?  I'm excited, partly because it was my first real interview, AND MOSTLY BECAUSE I WAS OFFERED THE JOB ON THE SPOT! This is so nuts.  The salary is pretty good and I think I would really enjoy teaching. The school is a private Christian Academy near Philly, and the staff there seems really nice.  Plus, about 10 minutes ago, I received another call from a principal who wants me to come tomorrow for an interview!  It's so funny, though.  He wants me to teach band and Spanish.  I'm so excited!  This time here in Phila. has been great so far.  The apartment hunting has been fun and we've found some GREAT places.  I can't wait to finally have this all in the bag.  God is really blessing us.  I also have some leads on some more pharma company jobs...so lets just see what happens.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Awww...you know I love you too, and I must write you more often! But I did send you a package :).
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Now that the comment button is turned on...will somebody please send me something :)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I think I've applied for every job in Valley Forge, PA.  I've called at least 20 Christian schools hoping that someone may need a Biology or Spanish teacher...and actually, there were some schools interested in me.  I also found out about some new pharm rep jobs available practically in my neighborhood (which is awesome).  It looks promising since these jobs just posted yesterday and I submitted my application for them today.  Seriously.  Somebody has got to love me, right?  I really don't care what I do, as long as we can pay the bills and afford all the stuff we need to afford.  I'm really not looking for a life time career right now...just something to get Jeremy through grad school...then he can make all the money while  I  get to go to school.  I think if you have your MBA, you should be pretty set.  It's a good thing this is an accelerated program!  Life is a dance you learn as you go.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      These heels are killing me....but everything else is going great. Today was my second day shadowing a rep. at another office and we're having a great time together. We went to doctor's offices in central and south Philly today. I didn't know they could look like this. I don't mean to be too critical, but frankly, some of them were a little ghetto. We even went to this one office called "Dr. Housecalls". I had no idea they still did that! I thought this happened&nbsp;like 50 years ago in rural America. Interesting. It's great to see that many of the doctors here are DOs. Most of the offices that we went to today were either primarily DO or they had DOs and MDs.&nbsp; My faith in this worthy sect of medicine has been restored a bit.&nbsp; I really really want to be a DO, but I&nbsp;am so tired of explaining that the profession is like that of&nbsp;an MD and it simply has a different outlook on treatment. Honestly, I think that they practice better medicine, especially if they maintain the mentality that the osteopathic medical school taught them.&nbsp;I see a DO....you should consider looking into it too. You might even see one now and not know it. Trust me, this happens&nbsp;frequently, so don't feel bad if you don't know!   Tomorrow is going to be a busy day since we're having a lunch at a large office. Finally, I get to see giving a presentation in action.   I'm sorry that I just don't have anything fun to say. I was so tired tonight that I declined on going shopping with Jeremy. You now&nbsp;KNOW for sure that I'm exhausted!    Oh, and I do miss the days where it was normal to roll out of bed, brush my teeth, and put my hair in a ponytail on the way out the door :). Ahhh college...you don't know what ya&nbsp;got till it's gone... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So today we were out driving on 309 and we saw this guy who kept stalling his motorcycle as we were coming up behind him.&nbsp; You could tell it was brand new without even noticing that he had a&nbsp;temporary &nbsp;license plate. Thus, it was obvious he was learning.&nbsp; So after a couple of cycles of the traffic light where we were, Jeremy though he should offer a little advice (since he has a motorcycle license).&nbsp; So when the driver steered&nbsp;over&nbsp;to the side a bit, we pulled up and I said out the window, "Hey, I think you need to put it in first...are you pushing the gearshift all the way down? You need to give it a little more gas when you pull out." Well, I hope the guy knew that my husband told me to say those things. He just sort of gave me that, "I can't believe a woman is telling me this look." He cracked a little bit of a smile when I told him how nice his new Harley was.   Did any of you know that Jeremy can drive a motorcycle?&nbsp;Not to&nbsp;stereotype, but he doesn't exactly look like the kind. &nbsp;I experienced it first hand when we were on our honeymoon.&nbsp;It was nice to drive around&nbsp;the streets of&nbsp;Santa Barbara hanging on to this cute guy on a&nbsp;Harley...and he was definitely cute;).&nbsp;On the other hand, even though he would make  me  look good on a motorcycle...I'm not a big fan. They're too dangerous. HOWEVER...I&nbsp;do love those little scooters....you know,&nbsp;something like a Vespa.&nbsp;I want one. They don't go over about 40 and they have great gas mileage.&nbsp;When we were in Spain, they were very popular. I&nbsp;saw both men and women all over the place with them.&nbsp;Jeremy said that someday I can have&nbsp;one.&nbsp;&nbsp;Besides being functional and economical, it's even more enticing since&nbsp;I&nbsp;could wear a skirt and stilettos and still manage to drive the thing.&nbsp;    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am SO joining the Army.&nbsp; Go see  urlLink why .   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I start my job tomorrow with LINCARE. I'm pretty excited about the whole thing, but I think I'll be even more excited when I actually get out there and start the real job.&nbsp; For the next, I don't know, week or so, I have to do the home base training.&nbsp; Next, I'm off to Clearwater, FL to do the corporate training. A whole two weeks down there alone isn't exactly a vacation, so it's not as glamorous as it sounds.&nbsp; Plus it's a million degrees in FL right now.&nbsp; That's why all of the old people come back up north till Octoberish.   &nbsp;   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Very brown. I'm really enjoying the pool here in our cute little apartment complex. I went today to just enjoy the atmosphere and to read my book of the week,  The 7 Habits of Highly Effective People.  I'm not too far into it, since I just started it today, but I definitely think it's going to be a winner.&nbsp; I've learned more in the intro than I've learned in many classes:). Okay, that may be a little of an over-statement, but you get the point.&nbsp; One of the great things about being at the pool (or in PA for that matter) is seeing the diversity.&nbsp; Like today, there was an Asian man teaching his kids the proper stroke techniques...in their own language.&nbsp; It's very refreshing to see so many diverse people in our area.&nbsp; That's one thing I missed in Tennessee. Now I don't stick out so much as the brown girl;). Another thing is that with all of the Spanish I've worked on, whenever I hear another foreign language, for a second I think that I'm supposed to understand it. So inevitable I tune in and try to decipher the words.&nbsp; Folks, there was no deciphering today.&nbsp; It's so wild to hear a language in which I can't even make out one single word. Not one.&nbsp; For most of us, we can understand a few words here and there in the romance languages etc., but the languages on the other side of the world are amazingly unique. I'm in awe that we live on one planet, all under the Creator's design, and we all manage to coexist&nbsp;(usually)&nbsp;in spite of the cultural differences.   Life is great for us right now!&nbsp; I start my job either Thursday or Friday.&nbsp; I'm actually burned out on this vacation thing.&nbsp; I know it sounds&nbsp;completely nuts, and 6 months ago when everything they could throw at me was due in school, I would have died and gone to Heaven to be able to go to the pool and leisurely read. Whatever happened to balance? Or is it just me?... Don't answer that;).&nbsp;   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Now all I need is to somehow make it on the show "What Not to Wear", so I will have 5K to spend on clothes! Seriously, I've been evaluating my wardrobe, and yes, I've been a college student for a while. I've got some cute college stuff, but nothing I want to be seen wearing in doctors' offices. Maybe one of you guys will nominate me as a good candidate...I'll pretend to have no fashion sense. Please.  &nbsp;  Did you know that Kleenex is coming out with a new anti-viral tissue? I find this both fascinating and completely unnecessary at the same time.&nbsp; First of all, I wonder how much money has gone into this? Why not put the money into more aggressive projects focused on the mechanism of viral replication and stopping it? Secondly, when people sneeze, most of them don't have tissues handy. I never do. Plus, they probably don't wash their hands.&nbsp;&nbsp;Also, there's only so much viral nose goo that a&nbsp;tissue can kill. Even more,&nbsp;strains of&nbsp;resistant viruses could emerge from the whole mess.&nbsp; Haven't health professionals learned from using too many antibiotics? Hellooooooooo, they don't work after a while. I do have to say, however, that I am a big fan of hand sanitizer, which used to only be in hospitals.&nbsp; Now, everyone has one of these little plastic bottles.&nbsp; Bath and Body Works is making a  killing  off of their sweet smelling, germ killing soaps and hand gels.&nbsp;Some people don't even flinch to pay $3.50 for 8 oz of mango soap in a cute pump bottle.&nbsp;&nbsp;Hand sanitizer  is  fairly practical, though...gas station bathrooms with no soap,&nbsp; shaking hands with a stranger, and touching dirty doorknobs ring a bell. This is a great product.&nbsp; I don't think the new Kleenex tissue is going to be so&nbsp;great, but I could be wrong.&nbsp; I just don't see&nbsp;it being nearly as convenient and practical as the other santizers.&nbsp; Let's face it, even if you do have a tissue when you sneeze, how much of&nbsp;the "stuff" gets on your hands anyway?&nbsp;....... Exactly.&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;  I would also like to give a shout out to all of my great friends and family down there in Tennessee. I miss you! Hopefully we can come and visit sometime in the fall.  &nbsp;        
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      You know, when I went to Hawaii a few years ago, I had such an easy time sleeping. I woke up at 7AM and was in bed by 10PM most every day that I was there.  The reason for such a lack of jet lag was probably due to the fact that I was already on Hawaii time before I even got there. Think about it. Waking up at 7 over there is like sleeping in till noon...and going to bed at 10 is like staying up till 3. This is what my body (and that of almost every other student) likes. Well, even though I'm not a student at the moment, my internal clock is still way the heck across the Pacific ocean.  I can't seem to break the habit of being a night owl. However, I do get a lot done at night. You know, housewife stuff ;). I pack Jeremy's lunch, wash dishes, go food shopping, work on my scrapbooking, etc. I have a pretty easy life right now. Folks, I have a sneaking suspicion this is all going to change reeeeeeeeeal soon.  Before too long, I will be waking up at the crack of dawn, ready and waiting...wearing a suit and a smile, headed for a local hospital. Ah, sigh, the good life can't last forever:). I want to move to Hawaii.      
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      When you're trying to find a place (like, say, a church), make sure you have randmcnally directions, a contact number, and 20 extra minutes to get there. Just thought I'd let you know.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Jeremy and I went to Barnes and Noble tonight so we both could do a little studying. "Study what, Mandy, aren't you out of college?"--is probably what you're asking.  Well, Mandy needs to learn how to sell, and learn how to do it well.  I spent the evening reading "how to sell" books and taking notes.  There's a lot of common sense to selling, but I needed to be reminded of some things.  For instance, we are always on stage whether it be on the company's time or on our time.  Let me just say that word travels faster than the speed of light sometimes, and if someone sees you doing something, well, not so great outside of work, then the chances of one of your customers hearing about it is likely. Let me leave you with six ways to be more likeable.  1.) Take a good look at what makes someone feel good and identify yourself with it in some way. 2.) Let your human side show--perfectionism doesn't make others around you feel comfortable. 3.) Accentuate similarities. 4.) Be a good receiver. This invites other to feel good about  themselves . 5.) Like them first, and show them that you like them. 6.) Laugh  These ideas are very common sensish, but it never hurts to be reminded!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I guess you all have been wondering about Jeremy and I and our new adventures! I'm really glad to be here and Pam reminded me of something the other day when I told her that we can get to ANY store in 10 minutes. She said, "Welcome to the Northeast", but really I'm thinking "Welcome Back!" I'd forgotten all the pleasures of living up here. Let me tell you about our place.  We were lucky enough to get one of the nicest apartments in the complex.  Actually the apartment we got was used for inspections earlier.  So, when we moved in it was almost perfect.  The carpet looks brand new, all of the walls are freshly painted, and everything was very clean (well, some things were not up to my standards, but then again, who actually cleans in unseen places besides me?) Our location is great too.  We are a two-minute walk from the clubhouse and pool and get this, I can walk to the mall.  Oh my gosh.  Moving in was so easy thanks to Chad and Marsha! They drove all the way up from TN just to help us.  It was great having them here, and once we got all the stuff in the house, we mostly played the rest of the time.  We went to center city Philly, saw fireworks, the Liberty Bell, Town Hall...went to Hershey, to the second biggest U.S. mall, and just had a blast. Did you know that the Declaration of Independence was not signed on July 4th?  The kitties are settling down a bit. They had quite a traumatic trip.  Once we got to the hotel on the way up here, they totally freaked out.  It's like they didn't recognize each other in a strange place! So for the rest of the trip, we had to separate them. (It was so weird.  They were fine together in the same carrier until we separated them and brought them back together in hotel.)  So Fiona rode in the carrier with Chad and Marsha, and little Phoebe rode with me.  We did something kind of dangerous.  Phoebe wasn't in a carrier in my car. But it was okay, and really we didn't have a better option at the time.  She was a good girl, though.  She spent her time rotating from my lap to different seats in the car.  She slept almost the entire way.  Whew.   I have some great news about my job! I had my second interview this week and they sent me for my drug test.  This is a good sign.  The district manager was really nice and she seemed to like me.  Most of my interview consisted of her telling me about the company, how commission works, and what to expect the first year.  Folks, it's almost in-the-bag! BUT, I will let you know when things are for sure.  Oh, and some other great news is that the expected salary is higher than I thought. I'm so lucky to have this.  And yes, when you walk up to our building, we are the apartment on the top floor with the two cats peeking out of the windows :)  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Don't worry you guys, the blog will be up and running shortly.  We get our cable internet tomorrow! Yeah! I have so much to update you on.  We absolutely love it here in PA. Our apartment is awesome.  I let you know all about it soon. :)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      We had a very nice  anniversary  yesterday, thank you all for your nice phone calls to say congratulations....which Jeremy and I thought were kind of funny (since you called at 9 and 10 pm...;). Dinner was spectacular at  Bahama Breeze . It's a restaurant that has bold savory food with lots of color and cool combinations. I had the Jamaican chicken and spicy yams. I can't describe it as well as it tasted, so if you have one nearby, just go there. Trust me. Then at home, Jeremy made crepes with vanilla ice cream and strawberries. Very  romantic . I can't believe we've been  married  for two years. It seems like only yesterday when I imagined what it would be like to be in  love  and to be  loved .  Sometime soon I'll post some wedding photos for those of you who've never seen them!  Have a   love  ly night.     
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    "I have found him whom my soul loves." Song of Solomon 3:4&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Two years later and we're still going strong. Feliz Aniversario!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Life, as I have always known it, is back to the typical schedule of crazy. I really don't know what to do with myself when my life isn't crazy. As I have spoken about in the past, when there is nothing to do, I get a little nuts. I mean, who in there right mind wouldn't love lounging all day by a POOL. See, this is what I mean....I was completely nuts. But now, I'm busy all day, I come home and make dinner, am a mom, am a wife, watch TV, read and sew. Okay, I'm lying about the sewing part. Anyway.... suddenly, my world is sane once again. Mandy has stuff to do! More than that, I make the most out of my down time. You know what I'm talking about, right? When you have an hour to do something, you do it in an hour. If you have a day to do that same something, you take the whole day.  I did have the chance to see  The Village  tonight. Believe me, it is not what you think. It was a very well done movie and you must make the trip out to see it. I practically had to drag Jeremy there, but now he will admit that he was quite impressed. Don't worry, there was nothing demonic or evil in the movie, which is what we're most leary of; however, if you are they type that needs an arm to hold, don't forget to bring a friend. It's really scary in the beginning. Well, I guess it's safe to say that the first 2/3 of the movie is really scary. Adrian Brody does an excellent job as well Joaquin Phoenix. The movie has an excellent supporting cast, including none other than Mr. Shyamalan. I love how he always inserts himself into movies, yet he's never really anyone that important. So if you love suspensful, deep, psychologically developed movies, this one is for you.  My work is going very well. I spent part of the day with one of the VPs, which, trust me, is not typical. My manager told me that some sales reps have worked there a long time and have yet to meet him. He made a trip to my center, and since I was new, he felt the need to give me an orientation. I'm very thankful because he has really jump started the whole process for me. He was also gracious enough to take my manager and I out for lunch at the Olive Garden. The more I learn about LINCARE, the more I am impressed with their progress. He's also a graduate of Gettysburg, right down the road from good ole' Messiah. He had friends who went there. Overall, I had a good time today, but I'm glad it's over. No matter how calm and collected one may be, meeting one of the big dogs...I mean like the boss' boss' boss' boss' boss' boss....is stressful, to say the least.  I just want to say thank you to the Newman family. We had a great time while you were here! So Waunita, when are you coming to visit me? :). I hope you enjoy the video! Isn't my apartment cute? 
       
    
    
</post>


</Blog>