<Blog>


<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Driving around Baltimore, I noticed a lawn sign for  urlLink ReDefeat Bush  on a lawn of a local house.  I don't really get the point.  First of all, the ReDefeat idea seems to cling to the old yarn that Bush lost, stole, or otherwise illegitimately assumed the presidency. This is despite the fact that  urlLink even the media recount  showed Bush would have won.  The only way Gore could have won was if ballots where only the chad was dimpled were counted as votes, or otherwise non-votes were counted as votes.  There is the notorious Palm Beach ballot, but would it really have been fair to count votes that didn't specify a candidate a certain way just because some people felt that the people who voted MIGHT have intended to vote a different way than they actually did.  Then there is the whole popular vote vs. Electoral college thing.  I agree it may be reasonable to eventually abolish the electoral college, but you can't abolish it after the fact.  Gore got into the race knowing that it was under the electoral college system.  Even if you feel that the Supreme Court decision was wrong, 1)a recount probably would have produced the same result and 2)at worst, the election was a draw - with more small things leaning towards Bush than Gore.  Anyway, my point is that it seems reasonable that only a small number of people feel that Bush "stole" the election.  And those people certainly aren't going to vote for him this time. The people in the middle, the swing voters, the people who will decide the election, probably don't feel this way.  And chances are they are a bit suspicious of those on the far ends of either party - which means if you are trying to get them to vote for your candidate, then showing how extreme your views are probably isn't going to help your case.  Granted, redefeatbush.com is a PAC aimed at recruiting swing voters, but to do this they need money from the people at the far left.  But putting up lawn signs that everyone sees might not be the best way to attract swing voters.  Then again, the sign was in Baltimore, which isn't exactly a bastion of Republicanism.  I'm convinced I may be the only registered Republican in Resevoir Hill.  But I'm guessing these signs are nationwide, being seen by undecideds who can't help but wonder if they want to vote for a party that seems more concerned about stewing over wrongs they were convinced occurred four years ago than issues facing people and the country today, especially terrorism.     
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Went to Little Caesar's last night for dinner - I hadn't been to one in years, probably since I was in grade school.  There used to be one near where I grew up in NJ, but it closed down years ago.  I remember thinking the pizza was pretty good back in the day, and cheap.  Well, it's still cheap, but not very good.  Tastes like frozen pizza more than anything.  Next to no toppings - one of the pizzas we got was olive, and there were literally slices that had about 3 olive slices on them.  I think the whole pizza had maybe two olives, tops.  Customer service was pretty bad, interior design circa 1985, ect.  At one point, a guy wanted a couple cups.  The woman tried to charge the guy for them.  When he decides to forget about the cups and leaves, the woman goes "what, did he think we would just give them to him?  I couldn't help but think that a customer-serviced-focused company would.   The funny thing is there website has an article   urlLink bragging about their improvements.  (first article, pdf format).
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink People arrested for prostitution or public lewdness in Dallas, TX   The redhead 7 from the bottom is kind of cute... proof that Mad Anthony needs to get out more.  (hat tip:  urlLink Jessica's Well )
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ( urlLink With apologies to Jeff Goldstein )  coworker:  Do you have a 6 pin to 4 pin firewire cable I could borrow?  me:  I don't know, maybe.  Check my drawers.  me again: HEY!  GET YOUR HANDS OUT OF MY PANTS!
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink With appologies to Jeff Goldstein   (on the way back from lunch)  Coworker:  Wow, we made great time.  And we didn't even hit any red lights.  Me:  That's because you ran that red light back there.  Of course you won't hit any red lights if you drive through them.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      About a week or two ago, I noticed a white Ford Taurus ('92 to '95, if my car memory serves me right) parked on a side street near my apartment with no license plates on it.  Not a big deal, as it's off to the side, and people who never move their cars, or whose cars are incapable of moving under their own power, park there.  A couple days ago, though, I noticed it parked on my street - a very busy, densly populated street, where it has been for the last couple days.  That kind of irks me.  At first, this was only because it was one more car competing for parking, but after some thought I came to realize it's because of more than that.  The first of this is that the owner isn't paying license and registration fees like the rest of us, myself included.  Not a big deal, just a couple hundred dollars a year or so.  But in order to get registration, you need insurance, and I would doubt that someone with no plates on his car would have insurance.  In the city, that's a serious chunk of change.  My insurance bill is around $340 a month.  That's almost as much as my car payments.  It means that I work for about one month every year just to pay the insurance on my car.  And it's not like I'm an awful driver or drive a rimmed out Bentley or something.  I drive an almost-3-year old Chrysler, have no accidents on my record, and one speeding ticket about 4 years ago.  But because I'm 23, and live in the city, I pay enough auto insurance every year to buy myself a plasma TV every year.  A decent one too, not one of those Korean plasmas made by some company you can't pronounce.  And this guy gets to share the same street as me without these expenses, his empty license plate area leering at me like an evil grin as I walk from parking like a block away.  This insurance thing is why I would love to move to a REAL no-fault system, where eveyone pays for their own repairs and injuries.  I worked for an insurance company for two summers while in college, and I saw some rediculous shit.  If you drive, you take a risk, like anything else in life.  If someone hits the brakes a second too late and taps your Toyota, suck it up and pay for it.  I hate seeing my hard earned money go to paying off people who look at collisions as an opportunity instead of an unfortunate accident.  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, now I've got one of them-thar newfangled blogs.  Posting will probably be pretty light the next couple days.  I'm taking the GMAT's on Monday, so I'm trying to force myself to spend a big chunk of my free time studying.  I'm not looking forward to taking them - I've been putting it off for the last six months or so, until I finally realized if I didn't schedule them and force myself to take them I never would.  I scheduled it for summer, under the logic that it would be slow during the summer and I would have less work-related stress.  Of course, that meant that the last couple weeks of work have been way busier than ever.  I'm not sure how I'm going to do.  I usually do well with English, but suck at math.  I've been studing a ton of math (including doing all 700 problems in the "official" GMAT review book, but I still get a lot wrong.  I'm also not sure how much how well I do will matter - I do have good undergrad grades, and also happen to work for the college that I'm applying to.  Even if I get in, I still have to hope my employer doesn't reneg on their promise to let me change shifts so I can go to class.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I learned to drive in New Jersey, a state not necessarily known for it's excellent drivers.  Baltimore City drivers, however, make New Jersey drivers looksane and restrained.  Some tips for driving in Baltimore:  1. Frequently in traffic, there will be places where two lanes of traffic need to merge into one - an exit ramp, a two lane that goes into one, a line of parked cars in the right lane (which we will cover in depth later).  A normal driver in the lane that ends would look to see if there is an opening, and speed up or slow down based on openings.  A Baltimore driver does not feel the need to bother with this - too much work.  Just keep driving and drift into the other lane.  After all, the other drivers aren't going to hit you.  Why should you make any effort to accommodate them?  One acquaintance of mine has dubbed this phenomena the "Maryland merge"  2. Red lights are really just suggestions.  Feel free to ignore them.  Once again, if there is someone in the way, it's in their best interest for them to accommodate you and not hit you.  There is an exception to this rule however - if the intersection you are about to roll has one of Baltimore's notorious red light cameras.  In this case you have to make every possible effort to stop, even if it means coming to a stop in the middle of the intersection and leaving a trail of smoking rubber of a length not commonly found outside of dragstrips.  3. For some odd reason, Baltimore residents will occasionally have accidents.  Some people feel that after an accident, people should restore their vehicles to something resembling factory condition.  This is a waste of money.  Why spend your money on some fancy-pants glass window when the grocery store will give you several free bags with any purchase?  If you are especially spendy, you might want to spring for a trash bag.  The same applies to other  body parts.  Crumple your bumper?  Just take it off.  Break a headlight?  Screw it, you've got another one.    4. Bumper stickers are a legitimate means of debate.  After all, most people get their political opinions from the back of a late-80's Volvo wagon.  An "anyone but Bush" sticker will surely make even the heartiest  urlLink NRO subscriber  vote for Kerry, and a "keep your hands off my body"  will certainly make even the most ardent right-to-lifer start volunteering at Planned Parenthood.  5. Anywhere is a legal place to park, except wherever you are parked right now.  If you are driving down a road with multiple lanes, avoid the right lane, as this will frequently turn into parking spaces.  Avoid the left lane too, if possible, as these are sometimes parking spaces as well - there is a stretch of Falls Road not too far from me where it is legal to park in the left lane on Sundays during certain hours.  However, if you yourself actually try to park somewhere, chances are you will at best get a ticket, and at worse have your car towed, then crushed into tiny pellets by Baltimore's finest.  I once got a ticket for parking in a bus stop, despite the fact that there is no actual way of distinguishing between the bus stop and a legal parking space, and I was well ahead of the concrete apron.  On the other hand, someone once abandoned a Chevy Nova not too far from where I live.  It was clear that the vehicle was abandoned, due to the fact that the driver's seat and B-pillar had been relocated over to the passenger side - it had apparently been T-boned by Bigfoot.  It sat for about a month until an abandoned car sticker was placed on it, and another 2 weeks before it was finally towed.  This was, by the way, on a six-lane road that is technically part of Route 1.  6. Headlights should be used sparingly.  It is not unusual to drive in a blinding rainstorm, where you can barely see a carlength ahead of you, and yet 75% of cars will have their headlights off.  The exception is if you own some sort of fixed-up Japanese rice burner, in which case you must affix at least 6  fog lights and leave them on all the time while bumping Eminem off your 1000-watt system.  7. You should put chrome rims on your car, even if they are worth more than your car.  I've seen chromes on pretty much everything, including minivans, taxicabs, and Kia's.  If you can't afford actual chrome rims, get a set of chrome plated plastic hubcaps.  I once saw a late-90's Ford Escort sporting plastic spinners.  And the car was stopped, and the rims did not in fact keep spinning - possibly because they were made of the same material as soda bottles. 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Slashdot has a post on a student complaining about  urlLink having to install a software CD to connect to his residence hall network . The college I work for is rolling out a similar Cd. I made a couple posts, but considering how far the discussion has gone on, and the attitude of Slashdotters, they aren't going to get any attention.  Slashdot regularly has articles of this type - angry students annoyed about their evil net admins shutting off their access to file sharing, making them patch their computers, ect, and most people there are against it - some have gone as far as calling the CD's spyware.  These people really don't understand how destructive viruses can be, and how few students keep virus definitions and patches up to date. One of our network guys once tracked a Welchia-infected laptop plugged into our network - it had scanned every machine on the network in a matter of minutes. They also don't understand how much bandwidth file sharing takes, or the legal implications to colleges that ignore it and get sued.    I hate making statements like the title of this post, they smack of communism/socialism.  But the fact is, a virus-laden or file-sharing laden network is useless to everyone, and the primary goal of the network is academic - research, email, ect.  Anything else - gaming, file sharing, ect - is OK as long as it doesn't take away from the primary goal of the network - academics.  Some people have asked why colleges don't just shut down infected machines.  Actually, that was what we were doing for the last couple years.  But the problem with that is that it's too late- by then you have at least one trashed machine, and chances are you have many as that machine has infected other machines.  You've also probably wasted a ton of bandwidth.  As far as those who call the CD's spyware, all we check is that you have the latest patches, a functioning and up-to-date copy of antivirus software, and are an authorized network user.  Not exactly blackmailable info.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      coworker: You may want to try having him decrease his internet explorer security level to medium.  me:  And if that doesn't work, try medium-rare.  With a baked potato.  Which reminds me, what's for lunch?
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was watching Aqua Teen Hunger Force off my roomate's RePlay a couple days ago, and they referenced a website during the show - my package came from wegotussomemedicalwaste.com .  Thinking it would be funny to register the domain name, I did a  urlLink whois  and found out it was already registered - to the Turner Broadcasting legal department.  Turns out that they  urlLink actually have a website up .  That's pretty cool - almost as cool as when The Simpsons featured  urlLink whatbadgerseat.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          My inner child is sixteen years old!    Life's not fair! It's never been fair, but while adults might just accept that, I know something's gotta change. And it's gonna change, just as soon as I become an adult and get some power of my own.    urlLink   How Old is Your Inner Child?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The federal government wants to do away with food stamps because of   urlLink the name the stigma contains .   As James Tarantino points out, the stigma is not the name but  urlLink the fact that it's a government handout  (last item- scroll down).  Changing the name is just a way to take a program that some people find questionable, and make it look good.  Of course, this is already going on - here in scenic Maryland, food stamps are known as the  urlLink Independence Card .  Yup, that's right.  The name of a program where  you rely on the government to buy you food  is called the Independence Card.  Talk about doublespeak.  I have a couple friends who have worked at grocery stores, and the stories they have about people using the "independence card" would make your head spin.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Al Gore has decided that anyone who expresses an opnion disagreeing with him, or feels that the media has a liberal bias or has been inaccurate reporting the war,  urlLink is a Nazi brown shirt.   So here's my brown shirt, courtesy of  urlLink here .       Do you notice that everything with Democrats is a conspiracy?  Bill Clinton's impeachment, the Iraqi war, conservative bloggers, BBC reporters - all part of a vast conspiracy.  Not just people having opinions, and seeking out other people with similar opinions.  Because if you have an opinion that's different from Al Gore, then you must be a part of the neocon war machine and not a real person.  Except that the Al Gore of 1992   urlLink had a different view than the Al Gore of today .
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A  urlLink recent article  on Genifer Flower's reaction to Bill Clinton's autobiogaphy refers to her lawyers at Judicial Watch, a " a Washington-based conservative court and government watchdog".  This gives the impression that Judicial Watch is one of those crazy neo-con groups that it still out to get Bill Clinton.  That seems to be stretching it a bit.  Judicial Watch  urlLink describes themselves as nonpartisan .  More importantly, some of their  urlLink current cases  don't exactly fit the Republican adgenda - stuff like  urlLink suing Dick Cheney  for alledgedly making false claims when he was CEO of Halliburton.  I guess one could argue that Judicial Watch is conservative in that they are for small government and judicial restraint.  But chances are most people who read the article will think conservative=republican - and chances are that's what the article's author wanted you to think.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A study by a couple New York resturant and bar groups shows that  urlLink the NY smoking ban hurts their business .  This doesn't surprise me - I am an occasional cigar smoker, and I pretty much only smoke either when I'm at a bar, or at home with a beer in one hand and a cigar in the other.  I think that there are a lot of other people who are "social smokers" who smoke when they go out.  I'm a big fan of personal choice, and I think people should be able to choose if they want to patronize a resturant that allows or does not allow smoking, and the people who own resturants and bars should be able to choose if they want to allow people to smoke in them.  The ban has frequently been cast as a public health benefit to employees of these resturants - but once again they choose to work there knowing there is smoking, and I know a ton of bartenders who smoke themselves and thus really don't mind secondhand smoke.  One really interesting thing from the article I mentioned above - it contrasts with a NY State study that showed increased profits after the smoking ban - but the NY study  included resturants that never allowed smoking in the first place, such as McDonalds and Starbucks .   The way I see it, I would trust the bar trade group's study more - all they want to do is make money, while the state wants to prove that their law helps people, and to control yet another part of our lives. 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Minimum wage laws are always one of those things that it's hard to be against without looking like a jerk.  After all, who can live on $5 an hour?  One simple law and we can in theory make poor, hardworking people better off.  Except that it doesn't work that way.  When you raise the price of a commodity (and one of the few things that Marx was right about is that labor is a commodity), quantity demanded goes down.  So you put a price floor on a unit of labor, and quantity demanded goes down.  Except when quantity demanded of widgets goes down, you have a wharehouse full of widgets.  When quantity demanded of labor goes down, you have unemployed people - the very same unemployed people that minimum wage laws are supposed to help.   urlLink Opinionjournal has a great article  about minimum wage laws.  Some interesting facts: -Only 1.5% of the work force is paid minimum wage or less -More than half of people earning minimum wage are under 25 years old - so they are entry level young workers -More than 60% of workers are hospitality or service workers, who frequently recieve tips in addition to wages -One third of minimum wage earners live with a parent or reletive - so they aren't supporting their families on their minimum wage job, but rather being supported by their family 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Baltimore City just reopened the fountain in Druid Hill Lake Park, not far from my hood.  Went there last night with a friend to take some pictures.  It's pretty dark, so  urlLink this  is the best picture I got.  You can't really make out the fountain (which lights up at night with changing colors - orange in this shot), but it still looks pretty cool.  Taken with a Toshiba PDR-5300 digital camera.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm a big fan of buying stuff cheap, and I've noticed the thing that helps me most with accomplishing this is lazy store employees.  For example, Target is known for marking stuff down in their systems, and stuff that's on sale is well-documented on deal discussion boards like  urlLink fatwallet .  I've bought 5 ipods for $200 back when they were normally $400, a portable DVD player for $150 that I resold for $300, and 2 playstations with lcd screens that I bought for $40, threw in a $10 adapter, and sold for $120 each.  They were all tagged at higher prices.  The playstations were tagged at $110, and the clerks were surprised when they scanned for $37 - they insisted on calling a manager.  The conversation between the manger and the clerk consided of the manager asking "is that the right item?  Is that the price in the system?  Then sell it to him for that price.  My most recent experience - Rite Aid had shampoo that was buy one get one free.  There was a buy one get one free coupon in the paper.  When the clerk tried to ring it up, it wouldn't take.  She called the manger over, who at first said she didn't think it could be done.  I pointed out that the sale thing was store and the coupon was manfacturer.  She then goes "well, I don't care, they pay me for them anyway" and I walked out with $10 worth of shampoo for the sales tax.  People complain about lack of service at stores, but I get most of my benefits out of lazy clerks who just want their paychecks while doing as little work as possible
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      CoWorker:  Why is your phone unavailable?*  Me: What, huh?  Oh Shit.  Oh, wait, it's because I'm signed into the phone over there.  (I work at a helpdesk.  If I'm "unavailable", then when people call the helpdesk, they get a message to hold. Forever.  Plus, my boss gets a report that I haven't been answering the phone, and then she starts to wonder what I do at work.  Besides blog.)
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Spyware supplier WhenU recently  urlLink obtained an injunction against a Utah law that would ban spyware .    I really have mixed feelings on this, because it's a battle of two groups I'm not fond of - spyware perveyors and people who have no idea how to use a computer.  I work at a college helpdesk, and I regularly see computers with tons of popups, multiple "toolbars", ect - we've had students where  urlLink AdAware  has found around 1000 objects.  It has a huge cost in terms of time and user aggrivation.  On the other hand, much of the spyware that gets installed is because of poor user practices - unpatched machines, downloading and installing well-known spyware-laden programs like Kazaa, clicking on any install box that comes up, ect.  I rarely have problems with my home or work PC's, because I'm good about keeping them up to date and because I practice safe surfing.  I worry when the government steps in and takes away any rights, even when those rights annoy people.  What is going to solve spyware is not laws, but educated computer users.  Of course, when the average computer user becomes smart enough avoid spyware, pigs will be all up in the sky.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Interesting article on  urlLink Captain's Quarters  about Jack Ryan, Illinois Senate candidate and former husband of the lovely  urlLink Jerri Ryan , loved by geeks everywhere thanks to her role as 7 of 9 on Star Trek. Apparently, he's quite the fan of sex clubs, and she's not exactly down with it.   It always amazes me when people who have a ton of good reasons not to do stuff - hot-ass wife, political career, ect - do stupid shit to fuck it up.  Then again, if I had good stuff going on, I'd probably find a way to fuck it up too. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Michael Friedman has  urlLink an intersting solution to immigration .  Not sure how well it would work, and I doubt too many government people would get behind it, but profit motives can be powerful incentive, and one that should be used as frequently as possible.  I like immigration - if people are willing to hire immigrants and immigrants are willing to work, it seems good to have them.  But we need to know who we have in this country, especially since there are so many terrorists who would love to get in and fuck us up.  After all, it was weak immigration laws that got the 9.11 hijackers in here and staying in here.   
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My salad blogging won't be as cool as say,  urlLink Michelle's , but I got one of the fire-roasted Chicken Ceasar salads.  Not bad. The chicken was really good, the cheese, dressing, and croutons were decent, and you got a lot of lettuce.  In all, I would say it's better than a McDonald's salad, and nearly as good as a Wendy's salad.   Wendy's has the disadavantage that they always seem to be out of at least one thing every time I go there.  One thing that pisses me off:  if I order a cesar salad, doesn't it seem likely that I want, you know, ceasar dressing?  I mean, if you order a cheeseburger, doesn't that mean you want cheese on it?  If I order a ceasar salad, don't ask me what kind of dressing I want, ok?
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've finally taken the GMAT, something I've been dreading and putting off for the last, oh, 6 months or so.  Every free moment I have either been studying for the GMAT, or feeling guilty that I was doing something other than studying for the GMAT.  Now I'm done with it, and can devote my time to more important pursuits, like working 6 days a week and selling a ton of stuff on eBay  (anyone need five wireless routers or 400 slim-line jewel cases?).   I got a 650, (38 math (55th percentile)/ 41 verbal (94th percentile), so I can't really complain.  Wouldn't mind math being a little higher, but for someone who sucks at math it's pretty decent.  Besides, the school I'm applying to has an average score of ~430, so as long as I don't take a crap on the admission directors desk or send in my application filled entirely in with crayon, I most likely will get in.  Then I'll get to stress over classes, plus I'll have to move to day shift and stress over waking up in the morning.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm not know for my love of members of the Democratic party, and most of the ones who get the limelight seem to be getting more and more caustic.  But since I read his quotes  urlLink On the capture of Saddam  (scroll down to Diplomacy is Critical) compared to certain other  urlLink one-time Democratic presidential contenders , I came to respect him - both for his views and for having the balls to stand up for them in a party that seems to put politics above anything else in the Iraq conflict.  It's a shame that he doesn't get nearly the respect for being a maverick that McCain does.  (While I agree with McCain on certain issues, like his dislike of government pork, I disagree with his namesake finace bill, which I feel hurts free speech).  Anyway, he has  urlLink some more intelligent statements  on Iraq.  (h/t  urlLink PowerLine )
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Wall Street Journal's Opnion Journal has an interesting article on  urlLink income in the U.S. vs Europe. . Some of the interesting conclusions of the Swedish study are that 25% of Americans are considered low income, while applying that same standard to the Swedish (well known for their heavily socialistic government, as well as their fine meatballs) would have 40% as low income.  Americans can also buy more stuff, having a "standard of living which the majority of Euopeans can never come near."  The study also notes that it measures GDP, which doesn't count "output in the black economy, which is significant in Europe's high-tax states."  Interesting... didn't the USSR have the same black-market problem?  This to me illustrates the fallacies of high taxes - sure, you might get a larger %, but it's a larger percent of a smaller chunk.  There is, after all, some wisdom to the Laffer curve and trickle-down.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Looks like I'm going to be co-posting on  urlLink BSOM's  new silly news stories blog,   urlLink NewsAmuse .  At least I will once I find something to post.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink NY Attorney General Eliot Spitzer  is cracking down on companies advertising sales because the companies haven't sold enough items at the higher prices, hence the government feels that they aren't really sales.  Yup, that's right.  The government is going after companies for selling stuff too cheap. Because, you know, we can't have consumers paying low prices for items.  That's bad for consumers.  Yes, I understand that the government feels that the original prices are fake and that the items really aren't on sale.  But shouldn't it be up to consumers to shop around and figure out if something is a good price or not?  Maybe it's just that I consider myself a hardcore shopper - I regularly buy stuff for resale on eBay, after I buy the Sunday paper I rip out the circulars and throw most of the rest away, and I've been known to go to stores just to see if anything's on clearance. But I think it's reasonable for people to do a little research, and not trust the retailer, who obviously has a vested interest, for info.    
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Watching MSNBC while I eat breakfast.  They had a segment on  urlLink phishing  - ie those emails you get written in Pidgin English claiming that they are from PayPal and directing you to a site somewhere in Russia.  They had an interview with a "victim" who said that she felt personally violated because someone had seen her bank account and seen what bills she had paid.  Oh, and they took her money.  I don't know about you, but if someone stole my money, I would be a little more worried about that then about them knowing what my last cell phone bill was.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Goes to  urlLink this article in OpinionJournal" .   Later, as I passed the  local XXX-rated video store,  I saw his truck, and others festooned with flags, parked in front... Each vehicle had flag poles   inserted into every orifice  in its chassis. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink possibly the funniest car review I have ever read , and that includes all of the John Philips articles in Car And Driver.  This almost makes up for his harsh review of the PT Cruiser... almost.  Scroll down and read the article on the Chrysler 300 as well - especially the NYT one with Snoop dee oh double gee...  h/t  urlLink instapundit 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Drove from Baltimore to my parent's house in central NJ today.  I go via Pennsylvania (I-83 to I-81 to I-78).  Depending on traffic, it can take longer than the traditional Maryland/Deleware/NJ turnpike run, but I've grown to like it better.  I started going that way in college, mostly because my Dad liked it and thought I was safer going that way.  However, I also like the fact that it doesn't have a ton of tolls (both in terms of time and money), and I like stopping at out of the way gas stations better than stopping at big ugly rest areas.  The scenery isn't bad either.  I used to visit my parents a lot more, but the last 9 months or so I've been working Saturdays, so the only time I can visit is on holidays.  It's kind of interesting traveling on holidays, because you see plates from all over the country - it makes you realize that Americans really do have strong family ties, and even though they will frequently move cross-country, they also frequently come back to visit and stay in touch with their roots.  I've really grown to like driving as a form of transportation - I've always been a car nut, and never been a mass transit fan, but there's something about rolling through the middle of nowhere in PA at 80 miles an hour, sunroof open, stereo blasting, singing along.  It's my car, it's my life, and I can go where I want when I want.  Even with high gas prices, silly insurance rates, and other high fixed costs, you can still go pretty far pretty cheaply in this country, and I think that's great.  We can leave home for whatever reasons - education, employment, love, whatever - and still be able to visit those we care about.  Lileks had a really good  urlLink fisking of a Gardian article  about a visit to the central U.S. where the writer points out that only 1 in 6 Americans have passports, and Lileks responds that it's because the U.S. is so much bigger, that one can see so much without leaving the country.  I think that's true, and that  that's a great thing about America - there is so much to see, and it's so easy to see it.  People think of mass transit as a great melting pot - rich and poor on the same stinky bus.  But driving is pretty egalitarian too - the guy in the shiny new Maybach and the guy in the beat up K-car share the same road, obey (or not) the same laws, and go to the same place.  If there is traffic, they both get stuck in it.  Yet they also have the freedom to go where they want, to listen to loud music or talk radio or whatever without bothering anyone, to stop when they want and go what they want.  And I think that is a great and underappreciated thing.  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I buy a lot of stuff online.  Partly because there are certain items I don't really like shopping for in person, partly because I work 6 days a week and don't always have time to buy stuff at brick and mortar stores, partly because I spend so much time in front of computers both at work and at home,  and partly because online prices are frequently ver good.  One thing I've noticed companies still love to do is advertise free shipping all over there site, but default to some sort of paid shipping.  Amazon and Buy.com are guilty of this.  I placed an order today with buy.com and used a coupon for $5 off.  As soon as I hit the confirm order button, I realized I had forgotten to pick free shipping.  I couldn't find any way to change my preferences, so I cancelled the order and reordered.  It wouldn't let me use the coupon, saying that I had already used it - which I had, but on an order that was cancelled.  I've emailed Buy.com. and we'll see if they credit me back the $5.  While I am pretty cheap, the cost isn't so much the issue as the principle.  On the internet, there are many companies selling the same things, with only price and customer service distinguishing them.  While I firmly belive people should read the fine print when making purchases and check that everything is correct before hitting OK, I also think that a truly customer-focused company won't advertise free shipping all over their site and then hope that people forget to select it.  There are a few companies online whose customer service impresses me - I recently had a really good experience with Shoebuy.com.  I decided it was time to get a pair of sandles, and I had a 20% off coupon for them (plus they are a generous  urlLink fatcash merchant  and have free shipping on everything.  I got a pair of Birkenstocks (I know, they are for hippies, but they feel so comfortable), but they were too big.  You can automatically request an exchange from their site, and I did this - it's supposed to give you a UPS label as a JPG.  Label didn't show up, no matter how many times I refreshed or did "show image".  Emailed them (on a Friday night, mind you) and had an email with a shipping label in about 45 minutes.  Got the replacement Birkenstocks in about a week.  Granted, companies that sell stuff like shoes HAVE to be more customer focused than book/electronic retailers, because they sell something that people frequently need to try on and thus are reluctant to buy online.  Still, I think there are lessons to be learned from these retailers
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OpinionJournal has a brief mention of  urlLink Formula one racing in Nascar country  that includes the quote  When you're selling tickets or trying to get ratings, your whole life depends on the guy who lives on the south side of St. Louis who's sitting there drinking a beer on a Sunday afternoon," Mr. Wheeler told the Virginian-Pilot. "He's run a backhoe all week. He wants people he can associate with. . . . Guys with big heads and big hands and big feet .  So now Americans aren't just inferior to Europeans for the rest of our cultural gaffes - supporting democracy over tyranny, not traveling to enough foreign countries, not having a socialist government that mandates 2 months of vacation or free health care - but also for prefering NASCAR to Formula 1.  I admit, I don't understand the appeal of NASCAR.  I don't really watch much racing at all, and cars making only right turns for several hours isn't exactly my idea of fun. But except for occasionally making left turns, and having drivers with names that are hard to pronouce, I don't really see anything superior about F1/IRL/et al.  If I'm going to watch any motorsports, give me rally or LeMans style endurance - those are people with true driving skill, and they are exciting and entertaining to watch.  Rally drivers will get all kinds of sideways and do things you didn't know a car could do, and 24-hour racing requires huge amounts of human and mechanical stamina. - plus cars frequently blow up in spectacular ways.  However, I take issue with the Bubba stereotype of the NASCAR fan.  I know a handful of NASCAR fans, and most of them are educated professionals - engineers, accountants, insurance reps, ect.  If  urlLink this chart  is correct, the average NASCAR fan makes more than the average American.  This would seem to suggest that most NASCAR fans are not backhoe driving Bubbas, but it seems people can't resist the urge to paint Americans - especially Americans who live in the South and like racin' - as ignorant.   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Marginal Revolutions  mentioned a couple days ago that there's a  urlLink study showing that Khat (qat)  may increase male fertility.  Khat is a  urlLink natural methamphetamine  that is commonly chewed in African and Middle Eastern countries.  If you've ever read PJ O'Rourke's All The Trouble In The World, he talks about it:   They started chewing it before lunch but the high didn't really kick in until three in the afternoon. Suddenly the drivers would start driving into potholes at full speed.  We called this the "qat hour".   I was curious to try this stuff, but it's apparently been illegal in the U.S. since 1993.  Man, not only is the U.S. taking all the fun out of stuff, but they are making it harder to pop out shorties.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Peter Gordon has an article  looking at how medical care have improved in the last 100 years, looking at the "drug department" items in a 100 year old Sears catalog.  Interestingly, one of the items is  urlLink Vin Vitae , which is made of  urlLink coca leaves and wine  (next to last paragraph).  Cocaine and booze.  Right now it's a party, but 100 years ago it was medical care.  It's amazing how much we have progressed.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      (In between bites of fried dumplings)  Me: I don't know how you can get steamed dumplings instead of fried.  The fried ones have that nice brown color.  CoWorker:  But they aren't really fried.  I think they are just the steamed dumplings that get stuck to the bottom of the pan and soak up all the sweat and stuff  Me: Can you not use the term "soaks up sweat" when refering to the item that I'm eating?
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      John Kerry is  urlLink promising to increase the number of students graduating college .  Interstingly enough, even his campaign says in the article that   "nearly half the hike in graduation rates will come from population increases" .  So basically he can do nothing, and still say that he's keeping his campaign promise.  He also says  We need to move toward the day when four years of college is as universal and affordable as a high school education is today. .  This is, of course, silly.  Unless the nature of jobs changes greatly, there will still be certain jobs out there (ditch digger, fast food server) that don't require much education, and others (plumber, carpenter) where one can be very sucessful without a college education, but rather with on-the-job training or aprenticeships.  The other thing is that college doesn't just exist to teach material - it also serves as a signaling mechanism to employers that a potential employee is willing to put in the time and effort required to graduate from college.   urlLink Megan McCardle has a good discussion of this  (about halfway down).  Right now a high school education is a bare minimum for a job, because most people have one.  If college became as ubiquitous as high school, then anyone wanting to signify that they are harder working than average would need an MBA or pHD.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The ACLU  urlLink protesting the dress code  at a block of Louisville that is shut down at night to become a party spot.  The cloting they are objecting to is sports jerseys, sleeveless shirts and backward baseball caps, and they claim that it descriminates agains the poor and minorities.  This is silly- last time I checked, poor people and minorities don't pop out of the womb wearing a throwback jersey and a backwards baseball cap.  Clothing is an intentional choice, not a racial characteristic.  And I don't see how any rule banning sports jerseys can discriminate against the poor, considering  urlLink how much some sell for .  Shit, I sold my last car for less than many of them cost.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I regualarly surf  urlLink Fatwallet , and sometimes I'll duck into the free stuff forum and sign up for, well, some free stuff.  I've gotten a T-shirt, some golf balls, stickers, coupons for free food, ect.   I had signed up for a free Bavaria Beer T-shirt that was posted there - just got an email from them that "we've been spammed or hacked" - that they expected 200-300 requests, but got 27000.  First 500 to reply to the email would get a t-shirt.  I was too late, despite the fact that I got the email 15 minutes before I clicked the link.  I had a similar experience with Nike two years ago with a free golf ball offer that was supposed to be opened only to people who got mailers - but had a sign up form on the net.  They, too, sent an angry letter out to people who signed up and basically accused them of hacking.  Companies need to realize that once something gets posted on the net, it spreads fast.  Witness chain letters, news on blogs, the "slashdot effect" (websites posted on the popular tech site Slashdot frequenly get so much traffic that the servers crash).  This is the internet, where word of free stuff spreads fast, and when all that someone has to do is fill out a web form, people will, because they are cheap and like free stuff. If you don't want to get pretty much every person with a computer to sing up for your promotion, find a way to restrict people - require a one-time code, first x number, password protect it, ect.  But don't accuse me of hacking because I signed up for something that was publically accessible.  It makes you sound stupid and non-net-savy. Your customers get a bad taste in their mouth when you compare them to criminals for doing something perfectly legal that you should have had the common sense to realize would be done. 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I normally (or would that be iNormally) bring my iPod to work with me - I have an early G4 grey and white on my desk hooked up to an extra 3-piece set of powered Altecs - plug it in and listen to my favorite songs when I'm working late nights.  I do a fair amount of server administration tasks - new accounts, ect - and it's nice to have some background noise.  Forgot it today - had it on yesterday while I was doing laundry and washing dishes and fogot to put it back in my bag, so I decided to try the streaming radio in iTunes.  I'm listening to  urlLink simply radio hip hop  right now.  Sound is pretty good, doesn't have lots of annoying realaudio style "buffering", and a nice selection of songs.  My one pet peeve is I don't see song titles.  Seems to me that one of the benefits of net radio, where you have a video output device in addition to audio, is that you can have song titles. I'm surprised Apple, which usually is good about thinking of stuff, hasn't thought of this, and/or put in an iTunes Music Store tie-in.  It is possible that there is a way to display this and I'm just too dumb to know, but I don't see it.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Look at me.. weee! 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had emailed OpinionJournal about the  urlLink Independance Card .  He mentioned it today - I was hoping I would get a link out of it and didn't, but I did get thanked at the  urlLink bottom .
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've always kind of liked what I've heard of Jadakiss - I thought that "Knock Yourself Out" was pretty cool, and I liked that he discovered Bubba Sparxx, who I thought was a unique and talented rapper.  But I have to say I've lost that respect after hearing his new song  urlLink Why .  It's a series of questions, some humorous, but there are a couple that are nonsensical.  The biggest of these is "why did Bush knock down the towers?" - yup, he's going beyond the traditional claims that Bush either should have known about 9/11, or did know about it and didn't do anything, right into the total moonbattery of saying that he caused it.  Never mind the 19 Al Quaeda members on the planes, never mind the tape of Bin Laden rejoicing over doing it, he thinks that was all Bush.   It also contains the nonsensical questions "why did they let the terminator win the elections?" (umm, maybe because he got more votes than anyone else) and "why didn't they give us a cure for AIDS? (umm, maybe because it's a virus, and there is no cure for a virus).    It seems to be a pattern of those on the far left to bring up claims, with no proof, just random thoughts, and then act as if these are hard proof of some far-out conspiracy.  Sort of, you know, like  urlLink Michael Moore's movie .
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Republican senator Orrin Hatch has introduced the  urlLink INCUCE act  aimed at P2P networks that are supposedly corrupting children to commit the horrible crime of file sharing.  The act is ludacris, and the link gives far more analysis than I ever could.  But it makes me ponder a few things:  -Why is Republican senator co-sponsoring a bill that basically makes him a shill for the entertainment industry?  Most entertainers and industry players are on the left, and much of what they produce is works of art with a decidely liberal slant.  Wouldn't it be in Hatch and other Republican's best interests to have the entertainment industry do as badly as possible?  Why support something that is going to hurt you?  -Shouldn't people, even parents and children, have the ability to make choices for themselves?  Do we really need the government telling them what to do?  What ever happned to individual rights?  -What ever happened to giving businesses the benefit of the doubt, and not assuming that they are all out to corrupt children for their own gain?  I thought Republicans were supposed to be pro-business  -Good job for co-sponsoring a bill with Pat Lehey, the guy that Dick Cheney gave a  urlLink much deserved FU to  last week.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I bought a half-gallon of  urlLink Newman's Own virgin lemon-aided iced tea   yesterday, primarily because it was on sale and I had a coupon that got doubled, thus costing me about a dollar for a half gallon.  Tastes pretty good.  I noticed it's virgin...  does that mean there is an experienced lemonaid out there somewhere?
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Amazon is now featuring  urlLink plogs  - a blog of stuff they think you should buy based on previous purchases.  It's an interesting idea, and I'm always glad when companies come up with ways to market based on stuff I actually want, rather than sending me letters to refinance the house I don't own or spam to enlarge the boobs I don't have.  The success, of course, will depend on how well the items fit the person's purchasing.  I had three recommendations - a wireless bridge (because I bought my RePlay 5060 DVR from them), GMAT prep books (because I bought three GMAT books from them) and a digital camera (because I bought a media reader from them).  The first two make sense (although I already took the GMAT's, so I don't need the books anymore) but the camera seemed odd - if I own a media reader, doesn't that mean that I have a digital camera already?
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      An old college roomate of mine is coming up this weekend for the next couple days, and we'll probably re-create our college days by drinking large amounts of beer.  So if blogging is light, nonexistant, or nonsensical, that's why.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When I was in college, one of my roomate's girlfriend was a huge fan of   urlLink Trader Joe's , the natural/gourmet foods supermarket.  My other roomate and I would make fun of him mercilessly for shopping at such a trendy and pretencious place.  Well, a couple months ago my coworker and soon to be ex-housemate  urlLink BSOM  got me hooked on the Trader's.  I was in Towson going to Target, and he wanted to stop there.  I decided to try a few items from them... and they were good.  I especially like their frozen fried rice in a bag and provolone cheese.  But the most adictive item is their seseme and honey covered cashews.  I think they are actually coated with pure crack, they are so addictive.  I'm usually a cheap, coupon-using shopper, and while I find myself spending more at Trader's than I do  at Giant, it's not all that much more - and the food is way better.  But I can't help feeling like some sort of new age hippy when I shop there.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have Maryland Public Television's show  urlLink MotorWeek  programed on my  urlLink RePlay .  There is something funny about a public television show on cars, considering the general liberal bent of PBS and the general dislike of cars and car enthusists by liberals.  It's not surprising that Motorweek seems to frequently interject their thoughts on the environment, safety, and other things that liberals love but car enthusists could care less about.  This weeks had a piece on  urlLink FlexCar , an hourly car rental service designed for people who need to occasionally use a car.  It's not a bad idea if you live in a dense city - they operate in car-owner hells like Washington DC - where owning a car is difficult.  But it's not for everyone.  However, their news reporter-babe breathlessly stated that "if more of us used car sharing, that would mean fewer cars on the road and less air polution".  Huh?    Unless they have a giant hole in the gas tank spilling gas on the road, cars don't generally pollute when they are parked.  It's not people owning cars that causes pollution, it's when they start them up and drive them places.  Just having people own fewer cars isn't going to reduce pollution - having them drive less will.  And borrowing cars for the owner instead of owning them doesn't mean that people will drive less.  And car sharing isn't going to work for everyone.  I live in the city, but I work odd hours, regularly shop in the suburbs, and I usually work one day a week at a satelite location out in the 'burbs.  I don't see how car sharing would help me, or many other people.  And don't get me started on people like my suburban-NJ parents, where you have to drive pretty far to get anywhere.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If I ever went to court, do you think they would let me swear on the Photoshop bible?
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Slashdot had a link to a BusinessWeek article on  urlLink things that Apple should do to improve sales . The Slashdot article focused primarily on them touting security, but I'm more interested in the others - because I think they are wrong, and that the author doesn't really understand the Mac market.  He starts off saying that Apple should compete more on price, because the desktop computer market is driven by price, not style.  While that is true for a large portion of the market, that doesn't mean that that is the portion of the market that Apple should go after.  Car pricing is competitive too, but nobody is suggesting that Mercedes should price it's products more like Kia.  There is a market for higher-end goods at higher prices.    The fact is that Apple is never going to underprice Dell or Compaq/HP - they aren't going to have 30% of the market, so they aren't going to have the economies of scale that Dell has.  That's why they have to compete on style and quality, not price.  He suggests ditching the all-in-ones, pointing out that iMac sales have been slow - but part of that has to be canabalism from the cheaper eMacs.  When you add the features of the iMac and the cost of a good flat panel, the price is actually pretty reasonable.    He also suggests Apple give a trade-in for PC owners switching.  I've always thought that the Switch ads were not the best of ideas.  I actually own both a PC (a homebuilt AMD Athlon desktop running XP Pro) and a MAC (12" Powerbook, 866). I know several techies who also own both Macs and PC's, and in this era it's not unusual for households to have multiple PC's (one for wifey, one for hubby, one for the kids, a laptop for the road,  ect).  Instead of stressing switching, why not promote swinging - stress how easily PC's and Macs can live on the same network, how compatible file formats are between Mac and PC, and why a Mac might work better in certain situations than a Windows box (photos, video, graphics, kids, laptop, ect).  Instead of trying to convince people to switch to Apple, I think it would be better for them to convince people to add a Mac to their lives.    
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The World Court at the Hauge has demanded that urlLink Israel tear down it's bomber-blocking wall .  The decision will be read by the court's head judge, who is from China.  Not surprising he would come to such a ruling, considering that China knows that  urlLink walls don't do anything for security .  
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I found myself driving down Gittings Ave to Panera Bread for dinner tonight, where I encountered two kids throwing tennis balls at passing cars.  Almost got hit going - sailed over the hood - and on the way back accelerated past them when I saw them lining up to throw.  Beyond the obvious property damage, people tend to react when they see something flying at them, not realizing what it is - and an involuntary reaction isn't really a great thing when you're driving two tons of metal at 30 miles an hour.  However, I wimped out.  I didn't call the cops.   I didn't stop, pull over, and yell at them.  I simply drove on.  And I'm not sure what I should have done.  I don't really feel comfortable calling 911 - with all the crime in Baltimore, kids throwing tennis balls at passing cars seems like it should take a backseat to murder or heart attacks.  Besides, I didn't want to have to wait around or deal with callbacks from the police.  Besides, what would the police have done?  Arrested twelve year olds?  I guess I could have stopped the car, gotten out, and yelled at them.  But I'm not exactly an intimidating figure, considering I'm about as wide as I am tall.  And even if I could physically intimidate them, it would probably get me in trouble.  I can see the headlines...  Crazy tech support guy threatens poor, innocent kids.  Their parents would probably sue me.  Lileks had a  urlLink good BackFence column  (registration required) about him yelling at a kid who was cursing in front of his 4 year old daughter, and the kid totally blowing him off. Anyone who knows me (or reads my posts on  urlLink NewsAmuse ) knows that I don't have a problem with dropping the occasional F-bomb, but I think there is a time and a place for it.  Lileks wanted to box the kids ears, but didn't.  I feel I underreacted.  But I'm not sure what the correct reaction would be.  
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Captain's Quarters  links to an interesting article about the  urlLink length that colleges are going to attract guidance counselors  so they can get them to recommend those colleges to their students.  I'm kind of surprised about this, mostly because I avoided my high school guidance department as much as possible.  I looked at colleges on my own based on books, fairs, and stuff I got in the mail, filled out my forms, and only dealt with them for the obligatory letters and transcripts.  I didn't even report what colleges accepted me, which meant that the graduation program didn't list me as being accepted anywhere - something that my parents were quite irked about.  I have to wonder how effective guidance counselors are - I would think most students have some idea where they want to go, or at least what type of school they want to go to.  It seems to me that it is the most marginal students, the ones who have no clue what they want to do in life and have no desire to try to figure it out themselves, who are going to be most influenced by a guidance counselor.  And if you are a college, is that really the kind of person you want to recruit?  
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The National Review Online has the the transcript of  urlLink John Edwards on the Charlie Rose show on 9/11 .  Edwards mumbles about how we should deal with it via some sort of coalition involving other countries and diplomacy.  He then gets verbally schooled by author (and  urlLink Loyola College alumni  Tom Clancy (who earlier in the show proposed we deal with Afganistan pretty much the way we did).
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Chinese doctor who admits to treating Tiananmen Square protesters sent for "reeducation" .  I always laugh at those who like to use phrases about how "Ashcroft's America" is "crushing dissent" in this country, when you consider how many anti-war protests, websites, editorials, movies, ect. exist in this country.  If anyone tried protesting the way anti-war protesters in this country do in China, or many other countries, they would be stuck to the treads of a tank right now.  Something for anyone who thinks that they know repression to think about
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      (coworker on the phone with his girlfriend)You know, I was playing with my balls last night, and I realized that that lump that's on my one nut is also on my other nut.  Me:  You know, there are some phone conversations that really aren't appropriate for work. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Via slashdot, the NYTimes has an article comparing the server side software of  urlLink the Kerry and Bush websites .  It spends two thirds the article reading all kinds of stuff into the fact that the Bush campaign uses Microsoft IIS while Kerry uses Apache, saying that Bush uses MS because he's pro-business.  Then at the end, it has this quote:   Told that the Democratic National Committee Web site runs on open-source software, Tony Welch, the national committee's press secretary, replied, "Oh, thanks for telling me." Later, after checking with his technical staff, Mr. Welch called back to say that open-source software was "the right technology at the right price."   Which to me sounds like "we don't know what it means, but it sounds good so we're for it".    It also has this great quote about the security of Apache versus IIS on Win2k  But the Microsoft software, he said, "clearly is the least secure of the two Web serving solutions," given its susceptibility to infection by malicious computer worms like Code Red and Nimba.   While I won't argue that Microsoft software has it's security holes, is it really a big deal that it's vulnerable to Code Red, a virus  urlLink that came out in mid-2001  - and yes, there is a patch for it.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Fraters has a great article about light rail  up on their site, with references to Minneapolis and Phoenix's light rail systems, plus multiple Simpson's references.  Baltimore is another city that is convinced of the joys of light rail.  In the five or so years that I've lived in Baltimore, including my freshman year of college when I didn't have a car, I used the Light Rail exactly once.    Usually with mass transit you get the advantage of speed compared to a car - take the Metro in DC, and you zip under the massive traffic jams and horrifically designed streets on the surface.  That helps to make up for the lack of privacy and crush of humanity that you have to deal with.  With light rail, you get the annoyance of standing three inches from someone who hasn't bathed since Bush Senior was president, but you get limited speed advantages, since the light rail goes on surface streets and  actually stops for traffic lights .  About the only advantage with light rail is not having to park when you get to where you are going - but due to the slight number of stations and their locations, chances are you have to drive to the station to park anyway - cutting out another possible advantage, being able to get drunk and not have to take a cab home - since you still have to drive from the station to home.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got a response to the email I sent to buy.com about the  urlLink coupon screwup .  Their answer:    Hello Anthony,  Thank you for contacting Buy.com.  Please note that the coupon cannot be used in this order as no two promotions can be clubbed together. We hope this clarifies any confusion and we apologize for any inconvenience that you have encountered.  We have left a note in your last order(19380822) to provide you $5 discount on your next purchase .So now you will get the $5 discount automatically whenever you will place a new order with us.    I'm not sure how wanting to use a coupon once is considered "clubbing together promotions".  Personally, when I'm "clubbing together" I like to listen to techno music while drinking a red bull and vodka, but I don't think that's what they meant.  However, I do get a $5 discount on my next order, and it sounds like it won't have any restrictions.  Not as good as what I wanted (a $5 credit to my credit card for the coupon which I still feel I should have been able to use), but better than nothing, and not worth continuing the fight.  I still think they shouldn't base their business strategy on hoping customers forget to check their shipping options, though.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink This article on Powerline  tipped me off to John Kerry's  urlLink brilliant plan for using the internet to save the economy .  Powerline pokes fun at his misspeak of "cutting capital gains" (that's called socialism, folks) and paying for it by "accelerating the transition to digital telivision".  I'm not sure how my watching CSI in HDTV produces government revenues (and I dread the coming of HDTV because it means I'll have to shell out the money for a converter, and you know I love buying shit that I don't want because the government makes me if I want to continue watching the TV).  His platform also says that universal broadband could  add $500 billion to the U.S. economy and generate more than 1.2 million jobs. .  How?  The main uses of broadband seem to be to download porn and pirate music faster.  So are Kerry's jobs going to be in the porn industry?  He also wants to make sure that first responders have broadband - so that your firemen can be downloading porn off Kazaa instead of putting out your house fire, I suppose.  He's also going to reward schools that turn out more engineering and science degrees.  Because you know that the kids who got into science or engineering because their school pushed them into it are really going to be the ones motivated to invent the next microchip or lifesaving drug. 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Reading about  urlLink This guy just makes me feel dirty all over , and not in a good way.  He's the sidebar on a Newsweek article about  urlLink married women who cheat on their husbands .    In the article, he says that he's slept with over 40 married women in his career. He also says that he doesn't feel bad about it because their husbands weren't giving them enough attention  (maybe because they were out earning money so that their wives could pay the $150/hour that he feels the need to tell us he charges so that their wives could hire a personal trainer to bone them).  He just seems to ooze sleaze - and at the same time, you read it and realize what a loser he is.  OK, he makes more money than I ever will, gets more action than I ever will, and has the body of a roman god, while I have the body of a sack of jelly donuts.  But he also has the empathy of a bag of donuts with none of the taste.  While I'm kind of a jerk, I'd like to think I'm not that much of a jerk.  Besides, you would think that someone with his money/looks/charm could do better than middle-aged housewives.  Oddly enough, he's also divorced.  I can't imagine why.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As a temporary New Jersey resident for the next couple days, I had the fun of reading  urlLink Fran Wood's Newark Star-Ledger column on the overturn of the assault weapons ban .  I'm too lazy to fisk the entire article, but there are a few stupid things that stand out that I needed to address.  The first is the breathless opening statement:     In case you haven't enough other things on your mind, I just thought I'd let you know that as of Sept. 13, assault weapons could start showing up on the streets again. Legally.    I'm not sure how guns show up on the street.  I mean, I personally would love it if free guns just appeared on the street, but I don't think that's what Ms. Wood meant. I guess she could mean that people can now legally carry assault weapons around with them in New Jersey.  Except they can't, because New Jersey doesn't have a concealed carry law, and I think if you walked down the street carrying an assault weapon, you would probably at some point be stopped by the police.  I suppose she means that criminals, gangbangers, and robbers may now start carrying assault weapons and using them in the commision of crimes.  But it's hard to use a weapon in the commission of a crime and still be legal, and it's hard to imagine that gangbangers and criminals base their gun purchases on federal gun laws.   iting the Second Amendment right to bear arms, they oppose virtually all forms of "gun control" as an infringement on that right.   "The NRA is still living in 1776," says Rep. Bill Pascrell (D-8th). "They oppose any legislation that curtails anything. They did it on the Saturday Night Special. They did it on the child safety lock. They do it on everything."   There is a good reason for this - because the more limits for guns that go into effect, the easier it is to slide down that slope to more regulation.  If it's acceptable to ban so-called assault weapons, why not ban all semi-automatic weapons? If we can ban some cheap pistols (saturday night specials) we might as well ban all of them.  That's why "gun nuts" don't want bans - because they know they will only beget more bans and more infringement on rights, no matter how benign they seem.  And would being back in 1776 be that bad in terms of guns and crime?  I mean, there was a lot less crime back then, and a lot more individual freedom.    Opponents of the ban warn that it would infringe on the rights of sportsmen and hunters -- though the list of banned guns includes no traditional hunting firearms. Instead, the ban prohibits the manufacture, sale and importation of military-style, semi-automatic assault weapons and rapid-fire ammunition magazines that hold more than 10 rounds. It applies to precisely 19 semi-automatic firearms, leaving protected 670 semi- automatic firearms for hunting and recreation.   Except what seperates assult weapons from other weapons is  urlLink primarily cosmetic stuff  like grip type.  They don't fire any faster.  So what is the advantage of banning them.  And while they might not be used much in hunting, they can be used in recreational shooting and collecting. People don't  need  to own a race car or a performance car like a Viper or Corvette, but that doesn't mean we should ban them.      That effectiveness was clear from the outset. After the first year, the National Institute of Justice found that police traces on assault weapons used in crimes had declined by 20percent. Nine years later, that decline has more than doubled.   I wonder if by some odd reason the number of non-assault semi-automatic weapons used increased.  The fact that this statistic is so specific would make me think so.  And if gun control laws worked, wouldn't the amount of assault weapons used have gone to zero?  Oh, wait, I forgot, criminals don't follow gun laws - that's why they are criminals.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've been at my parent's house in New Jersey the last couple days for the 4th of July holiday.  Lots of firecrackers going off, which is amasing since fireworks are highly illegal in New Jersey.  Of course, all the people setting them off will be prosecuted to the fullest extent of the law, right?  Of course not.  Which begs the question: if you are going to have something that is illegal, but pretty much tollerated with a wink and a nod, why make it illegal at all?  All you do is turn law abiding people into criminals and prevent some people from doing something they want to because it's illegal.  There are two reasons to ban fireworks - public safety and annoyance.  On the first, I think people should be responsible enough to decide for themselves if they want to take the risk.  I find fireworks going off at 4 in the morn rather annoying, but there are usually zoning/noise ordinances to deal with that.'  Of course, this wink and nod illegallity exists in a ton of places - underage drinking, drugs, guns, and speeding.  All areas I wish there was a little more public freedom and a lot less half-assed government control.  Half-assed policing of things lots of people engage in means that a few people get punished for things that most people do.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Marginal Revolutions  has  urlLink this article about a polio outbreak in Nigeria  that's killing kids.  The local Muslim religious leaders have refused polio vacines, claiming that they spread AIDS and HIV and are a western plot to steralize the Muslims.  Now that children are dying, they are accepting vacines from Indonesia because it's a Muslim country.  The article includes this quote:    the wise men of those regions of Nigeria had decided to see sense a long time ago, polio would most probably not exist in Nigeria today. Why didnt they ask for batches from muslim countries a year ago? Why did they wait so long?   Forget asking why they didn't ask for batches from Muslim countries, why would they rather have children -their children, Muslim children that they claim to care about so much - die rather than accept U.S/Western vaccines?  How can you claim to be a religious leader and put propaganda above saving the lives of your own people?  Similar stories have happened before with Muslim religious leaders, with vaccines and other circumstances.  After the huge earthquake in Iran, the local Mullahs  urlLink refused any money or search and rescue teams that were offered from Israel .  My theory on why these leaders won't allow Western help is that any good behavior on the part of Americans/the west/Jews weakens the "us against them" mentality that their propaganda thrives on.  It's hard to preach that all the Jews are out to get you when they are digging you out of collapsed buildings, it's hard to preach against American imperialism when American drugs are keeping your kids from dying.  So in order to keep their propaganda alive, and thus their power, they let their own people die.  That sickens me.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A very well written article on Edwards and his legal backrground  urlLink is up at OpinionJournal . He says a lot of the stuff I said in  urlLink this post  but does it a whole lot better than I ever could. 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I mentioned the song by rapper Jadkiss a couple weeks ago  urlLink in this blog post .  Now he is saying that his line asking  "why did Bush knock down the towers"  urlLink iis a metaphor .  Sort of like how the title of my post "why did Jadakiss become such a crappy rapper" was a metaphor - in other words, not at all.  He claims that the line means that Bush should have stopped it.  But he doesn't say how. Apparently being the President of the United States gives you superpowers to see into the future.  Of course, when Bush tries to do stuff to prevent future Towers (PATRIOT act, increased security, Afganistan, Iraq) that's wrong too.  He also says he's for a higher minimum wage and more jobs. Too bad that most economists feel that  urlLink  a higher minimum wage means  fewer  jobs .  (An interesting alternative view to this is that  urlLink employment won't change, but jobs will get less pleasant  as employers cut perks to save money and demand higher productivity from their higher-paid employees. 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I got my  urlLink giant box deeply-discounted of cigars  today.  While unpacking them, I noticed that all of them say that they contain/produce material that is known in the State of California to cause cancer.  This might be nerve-racking, except for a few things, the first being that I live in Maryland.  More significantly, this isn't the first cancer-causing-in-cali product I've seen. So what is this other dangerous product? My  urlLink digital camera .  Apparently, the charging cable contains lead, and the owner's manual reads like the directions on something you would clean the bathroom with - wash hands after use, don't give it to children, ect.  It's a strange world where a digital camera and tobacco are equally as dangerous.  Then again, anything can be dangerous.  Life is about making decisions about how to manage risk.  Sure, driving is dangerous, and so is taking showers (spoken by a guy who fell in the shower last year and walked around with a giant bump on his head for a month), but we decide that being able to get to work and not smelling like we're French are worth it, so we take those risks.  But apparently the residents of the left coast can't be trusted to make their own decisions without the government giving them some extra information that they probably already knew, or didn't care about.  (BTW, about the cigars - so far the only one I've tried is the  urlLink John T's The Crowdpleaser .  Not bad - slow-burning, mild, not overly flavored, and unusually moist, as a reult of being packaged in Tubos.  Not sure how crowd pleasing the scent really is, though.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This  urlLink WaPo chat session  has gotten a lot of play in the blogosphere for mentioning that the press now considers it open season on the lovely Bush twins. Several people in the chat session also complain that if the Bush twins want to show their support of the war, they should sign up for the military.   What nobody in the chat session seems to mention (and what I didn't know about until reading  urlLink this VodkaPundit post  is that Barbara Bush is going to be going to Africa to work with AIDS patients after the election is over (also mentioned in a few articles like  urlLink this one . That seems like a very selfless thing to do, and way more than the average just-out-of collge rich American girl (or American in general) would be willing to do.   It also seems pretty reasonable that having someone as high profile as the President's daughters might be a bit of a security risk for the military, and that the Bush daughters might want to help their father with their campaign, since he is kinda running for President right now. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I enjoy an occasional cigar - maybe 2-3 a week - usually either when I'm out at a bar or sitting on my deck at night enjoying a beer while watching Baltimore City police helicopters circling above.  I'm also cheap.  I've bought from  urlLink cigars international  and been happy with the service.   I recently discovered that they also run a cigar auction site called  urlLink CigarBid . They have good prices, and they will hold your items for a week to combine lots to save on shipping.  I figured I might as well buy a bunch at one time to save on shipping, so I put bids on a bunch of auctions.  I ended up winning a total of 165 cigars for $44 pluss $11 shipping.  They are:  Title: Professor Sila Churchill - 5-Pack Price: $6.00  Title: Maxim's de Paris Imperial - 5-Pack Price: $6.00  Title: Dominican Cherry Treasures - Box of 25 Price: $1.00  Title: John T's The Crowd Pleaser Tubos Pipe Tobacco Cigars - Cherry Cream (20) Price: $10.00  Title: Vega Fina Natural Elegante (60) Price: $10.00  Title: Antonio y Cleopatra Tubos Maduro (15) Price: $5.00  Title: Middleton's Black & Mild Untipped (25) Price: $3.00  Title: Colita Cigarillo Vanilla - Tin of 10 Price: $3.00  OK, most of them aren't the greatest (even the auction listing described the Cherry Treasures as "stinky" (and I've bought them before, for 10x the price, and they are), but for everyday smokeables they are pretty good, and I've had the Maxims before and they are really good. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Atomizer at Fraters Libertas wonders  urlLink why anyone would wait in line overnight to be the first to get into a new Ikea .  I have two words for him - free shit.  Last May, Ikea opened a store in College Park, Maryland. They had a number of giveaways at all their area stores, including in White Marsh.  The first 100 people through the door got a free Poang leather chair worth $200.  I got there around 10pm the night before and was one of the first people there.  I called my friend  urlLink BSOM , finally got him to come around 12pm.  It was pretty fun - we actually bumped into some people that BSOM knew and hung out with them.    While you could get to White Marsh as late as 4am and still get a chair, there were people there who had gone to the College Park store at 10pm the night before and there were already over a hundred people there.  College Park also had other giveaways, including a ton of furniture for the first person willing to camp out in the parking lot for a couple days.  They also gave away gift cards if it was your birthday and had contests, big sales, ect.  So the reason that people will wait outside all night outside an Ikea opening is because Ikea makes it worthwhile for them to.  It's pretty brilliant - they get a ton of publicity in exchange for giving away some furniture, and they build goodwill among those customers who got free stuff - I'm typing this while watching my TV sitting on it's Ikea TV stand, with my feet resting on the corner of my Ikea bed.  BTW, pics of the chair are  urlLink here . 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      coworker:  What's the number for the reception desk?  I can never remember it.  me: I don't know, hold on let me look it up. I can never remember it either.  Mostly because I never have a reason to call them.  Although I get plenty of calls from them:  Anthony, you have a package to pick up.  Anthony, is the email down? Anthony, we're hot and we would never go out with you.  me: OK, they never say the last one.  But I bet they are thinking it....
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink funny 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink OxBlog  links to this  urlLink USA Today  story about how Iraqis are starting to obey traffic laws and traffic police of the new interim government.  Dave at OxBlog sees it as a good trend.  Having read PJ O'Rourke's columns for the Atlantic, which talk about driving in the Arab world, this may be even more meaningful.   urlLink like this article from Egypt    When I could bear to peek, I saw traffic copsnot in ones or twos but in committees, set up at intersections and acting with the efficiency and decisiveness usual to committees. And I saw a driving school. What could the instruction be like? "No, no, Anwar, faster through the stop sign, and make your left from the far-right lane." Surely John Kifner, Chris Matthews, and NBC News are kidding when they use "Arab street" as a metaphor for anything in the Middle East. Or, considering the history of the Middle East, maybe they aren't.   In his column from Iraq, he talks about distribution of food,  urlLink  discussing how Iraqis would fight with each other over food that the U.S. was distributing , even when there clearly was enough to go around.  If the new Iraqi police can bring order to this, I think it's a pretty good sign that Iraq is improving, and I think it bodes well for the future of Iraq.  Maybe I'm reading too much into this, but establishing order in a country with that little order is impressive.  
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      U.S. hater and French president Jacques Chirac is yelling at the U.S. for  urlLink expecting to get paid for the drugs they invented .   The WTO has ruled that countries can ignore the patents that apply to everything else that is traded in the world.  U.S. companies are trying to make agreements with countries that both protect their intellectual property and allow them to get discounted AIDS drugs - you know, voluntary agreements where everyone wins, the kind of deals that happen every day in every capitalist economy.  The profit motive is what gets innovative drugs invented - because companies can make money creating them, they do, and the money that they make supports all the research and development for the drugs that never make it to market. Remove the profit incentive, and you remove those drugs getting made.  It's interesting that the U.S. is the source of all those effective drugs.  If the French want the world to have great new drugs for free, why don't they invent them themselves instead of legalizing the theft of them from other countries?  Maybe it's because the French system of 2 months of vacation, restrictions on the number of hours that employees can work, and massive welfare system doesn't produce the same innovations that good old U.S. capitalism does. As far as I know, the French economic system produces mostly stinky cheese and cars that fall apart after 20,000 miles (and I speak from experience - my parents once owned a Renault).
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink City Journal  contributor James Glassman has urlLink an interesting article on modern kids , saying that they are in many ways more conservative than their parents.  I'm not sure I really count as a young person anymore, although I was not too long ago, and I'm not sure about his analysis - the college kids I know still do a ton of binge drinking.  But there are some interesting stats, one of the most interesting being that half of college students now consider themselves conservative, twice as many as in the 70's.  I wonder if part of this has less to do with cultural shifts and more to do with the fact that people are going to college in larger numbers to study useful stuff like accounting and computer science, and actually hope to get good jobs instead of becoming poor grad students.  But it is something to think about...
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Chez president slams F 9/11 .  He calls it weak, and similar to communist propaganda.  And Kerry thinks all the foreign leaders support him....  Why do I get the feeling that Moore would not find his film being compared to communist propaganda to be a bad thing?
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink NRO's The Corner  links to a  urlLink Time survey  that shows 35% of people thinking Edward's lawyer experience is a plus, while only 28% think it's a negative.  That kind of surprises me.  Part of that reason is having read  urlLink this excellent Mark Steyn article  on Edwards (via  urlLink PowerLine ).  I have a big problem with medical malpractice lawsuits like those Edwards won.  Sure, if a doctor does something overtly negligent (shows up at the operating room drunk, prescribes a drug someone has a documented allergy to, ect) they should be sued.  But it frequently seems that people believe that surgery is foolproof, that everything will go fine as long as the doctor doesn't screw up, and I don't think it's that simple.  Medicine is inherently risky, and we've gotten to the point where we can save people who we couldn't a few decades ago.  If we punish doctors for negative results of surgeries that are inherently risky, we discourage those surgeries from ever happening - and some people who would have lived die, and we are all worse off.  I'm especially sensitive to the risky surgery argument because I had open heart surgery when I was 4. Open heart surgery on a four year old isn't exactly a cakewalk, and I'm lucky that everything went well.  But I think too many malpractice lawsuits discourages risky but possibly life saving surgery.  The second reason for my general dislike of trial lawyers is that I had a family member who was in 8th grade when he was hit by a car while riding his bike.  The people who hit the 8th grader sued the kid's parent's for being negligent in, well, letting their kid get hit by them.  This dragged on for years before the kid's parents homeowners insurance company settled.  There is something disturbing about a system where years and dollars can be spent suing a kid on a bike for being hit by a car.  I also worked for two summers in college for a large insurance company. Some of the lawsuits we saw were justified - cases where the driver was drunk or overtly negligent.  But some were ludicrous (ie drunk guy crossing 6 lane highway at 3 in the morning gets hit by multiple cars.  First 2 cars drive away, third car stops.  Because they couldn't find the first 2 drivers, the family sued the 3rd guy - the one who was honest enough to stop).  I'm not saying that all trial lawyers are bad - I think that we need some, and I think they provide a balance against overt recklessness by companies and individuals.  I also think that lawsuits can be a better way of solving some problems than laws.  But Edwards is a guy who sues doctors for making decisions that were perfectly rational, then complains about the high cost of health care, and that makes me, well, sick.  
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Via  urlLink Captain's Quarters , I found this article on  urlLink Women joining the new Iraqi police .  From the article:   Whipping out her handgun and slamming a magazine into the grip, 20-year-old Hadeel Alwan can't wait to start catching criminals.  "My biggest wish is to destroy terrorism," said Alwan, one of the youngest of Iraq (news - web sites)'s new women police recruits.    Hmm.. hates terrorists, loves guns, and probably has a cool accent.  My kind of girl. 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      With  urlLink Lilek's constant griping about DirectTV  I'd like to point out that cable isn't much better.    It should have been fairly simple - my roomate moved out, and so he had to get his cable cancelled and service started in my name.  While I was at it, my landlord wanted to get the cable rewired in black, and installed properly.  I live in a  urlLink hundred-something year old brownstone  with windows over all the doors inside.  When the last cable guy was there, he wired between the doorframe and window with white cable.  Personally, I could care less, but my landlord actually has taste, unlike me, a guy who uses one of those tables from Staples as a desk.  I mentioned this to the cable people, they said OK.  Cable guy gets there at 3:30, says no, spends half an hour talking to his boss, followed by his boss's boss.  They say it would cost $75 to remove the old cable and $25 to put new cable.  He offers to run it over the doors for free.  Between hooking it up, running the line, ect, it takes a couple hours.  Gets my floormate's working, can't get mine working.  Tries swapping cable boxes.  Realizes there is no signal from the cable, and reruns all the cable from the living room to my room.  Plugs in the cable box.  By now, it's around 8pm.  He finally calls into the cable company to give them the cable box serials.  One isn't in the system, so he has to swap that out again.  Finally leaves, 4 hours later.  Five minutes after he rolls out, my landlord lets me know that the bottom floor doesn't have cable.  I curse, call the number the cable guy gave me, get a voice answering in Spanish.  He puts me on hold, and about a minute later my cell drops out.  Call back, finally get someone in English, give him the info, he tells me he'll call back.  Almost two hours later, there's a knock at my door.  Cable guy actually came back at like 11pm.  He goes out back, hooks the other tap off the pole back up, and all is well.  Except I still have to get my reciever, RePlay, TV, and cable box to play nice together.  So far I can get sound and video, but I can't change the channel, and I can't program the RePlay.  I'm hoping it's a simple matter of switching cables, but at that time last night I didn't want to deal with it.  Unfortunatly, the roomate whose moving out is the AV expert, so I can't even easily ask him for help.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      MSN's brilliant screaming front page headline of the day, accompanied on the main page by a picture of a hottie running-  urlLink Can too much exersize make you sick? 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      MSNBC is now running  urlLink HardBlogger , featuring blogging of the conventions.  It's interesting to see blogs getting that much mainstream attention, although we'll see how it pans out.  The first link is to this article by  urlLink Joe Trippani , who sees the election coming down to three groups of people he said don't traditionally vote.  The first of these are Howard Stern listeners, who he sees as a large block of voters who rely on Howard Stern to tell them how to vote.  That's a pretty scary though.  Howard Stern is a great source for lesbian strippers, but the thought of people depending on him for political advice frightens me.  He also sees get-out-the vote websites like  urlLink VoterVirgin  as a big determining factor.  I've never heard of VirginVoter before, so it doesn't strike me as hugely sucessful, but what do I know?  VoterVirgin in theory is nonpartisian, so shouldn't it's voters be evenly split?  Then again, it works with WorkingAssets, which works with groups like the NAACP, so it would seem to lean Democrat - in which case it may be more that Joe Trip is  hoping  it will have an impact than that it actually does.  His third force is blogs, and that's the one I find the hardest to swallow.  Blogs are great for getting news out, getting different reaction to news, and mobilizing the faithful to do more.  For people who haven't voted or aren't interested in politics, they don't seem as useful.  Blogs appeal to people who have strong opinions on politics, and thus are already likely to vote.  He does list all the bloggers that will be at the Democratic National Convention - KOS, Wonkette, et al.  Maybe they would have more appeal if they had a more diverse crowd of blogger there - in other words, if they hadn't kicked out  urlLink the conservative and moderate bloggers . But I think if you read KOS/Wonkette/et al, chances are you are already voting and voting for Kerry, and would have even if you had never read their blog.  
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      One of my housemates is moving out, and he had the cable and DSL in his name. He has to cancel it, and I have to get it connected.  I had taken today off anyway to burn off some time, so now I'm waiting for the cable guy, who is supposed to be here between one and five.  Comcast even called me to tell me that, despite having already told me that over the phone when I called them the first time.  If they are going to call, couldn't they give a more specific time?  Anyway, I had to unhook all the old cable boxes to give them back.  Mine was plugged into my  urlLink TV stand , which meant I had to unplug it.  Of course, the stand gives a tiny opening in the back - it's covered with those thin wood panels, which is pointless since they cover the back. It literally took me about a half hour to find the power plug for the cable box in the mess of wires.  Which brings me to the title of this post.  Someone somewhere got the idea of putting a white stripe on the side of the power cord, presumably so you could distinguish it from all the other power cords.  It was apparently such a good idea that now EVERY power cord has one.  Out of the 6 things I had plugged in, five had the stripe, making it near impossible to figure out which plug is which.  And it's 3pm and the cable people still aren't here.  Grr. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink BSOM  forwarded me a link to  urlLink this article about the "Pants on Fire" tour  sponsored by stoner ice cream company founder Ben of Ben and Jerry's fame.  I love how this is what passes for political debate by the left in this country - calling the president a liar and building a giant effigy with burning pants.  And people say that O'Reilly screams too much (he does, but that's not the point).  At least when Rush and O'Reilly scream, they are screaming about actual issues, not just making blanket statements.  Blanket statements about Bush lieing that are, of course,  urlLink lies .  And as  urlLink this great article  points out, the left seems to be split on how to cast Bush- brilliant liar, able to pull the wool over the eyes of John Kerry to convince him to vote for the war in Iraq, but at the same time too stupid.  The B&J Bush doll does this, combining the liar aspect with silly facial expressions.  So which is it, ice cream man?  Is he a brilliant liar or an idiot?  I will confess that Ben and Jerry make good ice cream, although being a cheapass I only buy it when it's on sale and I have a coupon.  But their politcs have always made me shudder. I remember reading  urlLink this book  years ago, and I thought it is was funny that one of the things they were so proud of as their examples of public service was they ran a drive to get every school in Vermont signed up for the free federal school lunch program.  Yup, they didn't actually donate money to feed kids, but instead donated money to get the government to feed kids using taxpayer money - money from working-class taxpayers, as opposed to rich business owners who started sucessful ice-cream companies.  Of course, the school breakfast/lunch program is a brilliant pork program.  Pay farmers way too much for crops, then give it to poor people.  This way, you satisfy two special interest groups and make it that much harder to get rid of the program, as public-choice theory would dictate.  Anyway, I do give mad props to the Bush PR guys for their response to this:  The president welcomes the fact that we live in a democracy and that people in this country are free to make their own opinions known," .  At least someone still engages in civilized discourse in this country.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink   free enneagram test   I was actually tied between 4 and 6, but 6 sounded more like me - if only because it had George Bush 1 and Richard Nixon as similar people.   The title of the post is, by the way, a  urlLink Futurama reference .
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Democratic National Convention is  urlLink going to be pretty safe .  They are taking the protesters, shoving them in an area surrounded with 8 foot fences covered with plastic sheeting placed under an abandoned railroad trestle.  Meanwhile, the Republican convention  urlLink can't even get a metal barrier and bulky bags searched .  I'm not going to chalk this up to a vast left-wing conspiracy.  The steps that the Boston people are taking seem a bit excessive, but given a choice between security and protesters, I tend to side with security.  The conventions are big, juicy targets for terrorists, and it's important to protect them from attack.    I know some will see that view as violating free speech - but they probably think screaming fire in a crowded theator should be protected too.  I know it's not up to the government to judge the value of speech, but how much impact do protesters really have?  Does anyone really look at a bunch of college dropouts and aging hippies holding giant paper-mache puppets and think that they are making coherent policy arguments.  Do they look at them and think they want to place America's future in their dirty, pot-soiled hands?    I'm still not sure what the free speech rights the NY judge is protecting -since when did it mean you could carry a backpack unsearched?  After all, you can't on a plane, why should you at a political convention?  And if metal barricades are so bad, why was it OK to put the  urlLink Protest Warriors  behind them (I think it's about halfway through the film, in the NY section).
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      the  urlLink Pundit-R .  No word if it has any blogger-specific features such as coffee cup holder, flameproofing, or a giant siren that goes off whenever Kerry flip-flops on something.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I work at a college, and one of the perks was that we've had an on-campus Taco Bell Express for several years.  Being both fat and cheap, I was a huge fan.  There are few other resturants in the world - especially in the closed world of a college campus - where one can get $3 worth of food and feel so full that you felt sick.  Taco Bell was that kind of place.     Sadly, the on-campus Taco Bell is no more. It's being replaced by something called "salsa Rico" -which is apparently  urlLink an in-house brand owned by Sudexho. .  They are on a bunch of Sudexho-fed campuses.  Looking at price lists on  urlLink Other college's websites , the prices are  WAY  higher than taco bell - and they don't even make plain beef tacos.  I'm a big fan of capitalism, and I guess all is fair, but it's sad to see a company that has an exclusive contract with a college take steps to limit choices and raise prices, considering how popular Taco Bell was with the students.  Looks like I will probably be brown-bagging my lunch once the school year starts.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Towards the bottom    This is another thing Ive learned about the installation business: the people who pretend to listen to your problems are playing Minesweeper on their computers. They send all the installers out cold, with general hints: customer having problem with signal. Its like writing patient ill on every hospital admission form. Eh, why get specific. The doctor will figure it out.    I work in phone tech support, although for computers at a college, not for a satellite TV, and I take offense at his suggestion that people who do phone support sit around playing minesweeper.  In fact, we actually sit around playing  urlLink Zuma .  However, screwups happen on both sides... I've put in work orders, only to have techs ask me questions that were answerd in the body of the work order.  And we frequently have customers who aren't exactly sure what they want 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      coworker: We have 3 computers for the "new media" lab for communications that need to be installed.  I guess we should do that  me: Why don't we open an old media lab?  It can just have pen and papers in it, maybe a printing press and an abacus
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oddly enough, I've gotten a couple hits from people searching for  Anthony is an asshole .  Turns out that I am  urlLink the second search result for Anthony is an Asshole  on Google.  I don't know why anyone would search for such a generic term as "Anthony is an asshole" on google.  When you consider the number of Anthony's in the world, and assume that even a small percent are in fact assholes, it seems unlikely that your search would produce the specific asshole Anthony you are looking before.  Besides, assholedom is kind of in the eye of the beholder, so you have to assume that whoever wrote the webpage you are hitting has the same standards for assholeness that you do.  I ask your help, oh faithful blog reader (both of you).  Consider doing a  urlLink googlebomb  to right this wrong.  Link to  urlLink this post  with the text "Anthony is not an asshole".    
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Instapundit links to this  urlLink L.A. Times editorial about the potential evils of blogging .   Gee, an old media organ that has been  urlLink heavily discredited in the blogopshere  complaining about bloggers.  This is the modern equivilant of buggy whip manufacturers complaining about how cars suck.  The crowning paragraph is this one:   However, bloggers, with few exceptions, don't add reporting to the personal views they post online, and they see journalism as bound by norms and standards that they reject. That encourages these common attributes of the blogosphere: vulgarity, scorching insults, bitter denunciations, one-sided arguments, erroneous assertions and the array of qualities that might be expected from a blustering know-it-all in a bar.    Hmm, vulgarity, scorching insults, and being a know-it-all?  Sounds like a  urlLink Maureen Dowd column .  Most bloggers I read link heavily to both other blogs and to mainstream newspapers and magazines - and critique each other pretty heavily.  And many of them do their own  urlLink reporting  as well.  It also includes this sentance:  There is already talk of bloggers who would consider publishing items for cash and commercial blogs that tout products.  .    Great job, Alex Jones.  Way to show the blogosphere how to, to paraphrase your earlier statement,  "subscribe to norms and standards that members of the blogosphere reject" - by making an unsubstantied claim with nothing to back it up.  News flash - most bloggers have very strong opinions on things and are more than willing to share those opinions. They don't need someone to pay them to express those opnions (although they do appriciate it when you click on their google ads). Furthermore, because they have strong feelings on issues, they aren't likely to change their minds based on cash.  Most readers know that the writing of bloggers is just opinions, and usually let other bloggers know, either through comments, emails, or their own blogs, when they disagree.  The success of blogs is because people read them KNOWING they are getting someone's views.    
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      MSNBC has an article on the new  urlLink iPod fourth generation .  There is a big picture  urlLink here .  The big change is moving the buttons onto the scroll wheel.  This is like the first/second generation iPods, which had them to the side of the scroll wheel.  I have a second-generation iPod 10 gig, and I like the placement of the buttons, which are easy to change when I have it in my pocket. I was surprised to see the placement on the third-gen, and this seems like a good move.   I only bought my iPod because I got a good deal on it - Target was clearancing them out at 50% off when the 3rd gens came out - and was originally going to sell it on eBay.  I decided to keep it, and use it all the time now - I plug it into my Mac at work and listen to music, and use it around the house while I'm washing dishes, doing laundry, ect.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dean Esmay has a good sum-up of  urlLink young conservatives  prompted by the  urlLink New York Times article on the future of conservatism .  The NYTimes article is kind of funny in that he treats conservatism like it's some alien being that they have never heard of.  My perception of some of the rifts it finds (like the anti-war crowd) seems kind of overblown.  Sure, the hard-core libertarians of  urlLink Reason  and  urlLink Mises  fit the bill, but I think most conservatives place a high value on the security of the U.S. and feel that the Iraq war was a justified and neceassary step in protecting our country.  I don't think that the social conservative split is going to be as big a deal as the Times likes to think either.  I think most young people, including conservatives, are more tolerant of people, even if they don't agree with it.  That means that issues like gay marriage and abortion are not going to be big issues in the future, as people will continue to be against these things but will see less of a role in government in discouraging them.    I think that the Blogosphere is a pretty good picture of the thoughts of, well, people who think alot, and most of the conservative blogs I read - which are some of the most popular - tend to be that way - conservative on economics and security issues, more liberal on social issues. 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was watching the Dennis miller show this morning off my RePlay (it's kind of a Sunday morning tradition at Casa de Mad Anthony) and one of the Varsity Panel members was  urlLink Darcy Olsen  of the Goldwater Institute.  Cute and conservative - she might bump the  urlLink Iraqi policewoman  out of my heart.
     
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Every now and then I read something on a tech site or a tech magazine that just makes me go huh?  One of them is in  urlLink This MacCentral column on the RealNetworks/iPod hack .  For those who haven't heard about it, Real Networks, possibly the worst software company in the world, has introduced a way of playing it's DRM (digital rights management copy protection)-enabled songs on the iPod.  So far they haven't demoed it, so it's hard to tell what it does.  Apple. however, is claiming that Real reverse-engineered it's iTunes/Fairplay DRM software in violation of the Digital Millenium Copywrite Act (DMCA).  Now the DMCA act has some stupid provisions, and it isn't a great law.  But it is the law governing copywrite, and Apple's job as a profit-earning publically held company is to earn as much as possible for it's shareholders, and it has to do that by protecting it's technology, and in that case it protects it's profit by invoking the DMCA.  Anyway, the money quote from the article:  Now, I've always found RealPlayer to be an unsatisfying piece of software, and over the years, I've had oodles of trouble with Microsoft's Windows Media Player. Whereas Apple's QuickTime media player has always performed quite nicely on my Macs, and Windows-using friends have generally applauded how it works on their machines. But even QT-hating Win-users don't advocate suing Apple for developing a client that runs on their machines.   That analogy makes no sense.  Windows and MacOS are operating systems.  They are designed to run programs from multiple vendors - an operating sytem that you can't run programs on would be useless.  Companies go out of their way to convince companies to develop software for their OS's by producing developer kits and sharing information with developers. In some cases, companies that make operating systems make applications that run on other systems - not only Apple with QuickTime and iTunes, but also Microsoft with Office for Mac and the oddly named Windows Media Player for Mac.    What Real Networks is accused of is way different than developing software - they are acussed of illegally reverse-engineering Apple's hardware and software to do things it wasn't intended to do.  If they did this remains to be seen, and it's an interesting legal question if it should be illegal, but it's way different than developing an application for a specific platform. 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm in New Jersey right now... I decided to drive up and visit the 'rents.  I had taken today off to use up some vacation days so I don't lose time, and I just found out yesterday that I don't need to come in on Saturday - the satellite campus I usually work at is going to be closed because there's nothing going on.    It's not the greatest time to visit the family - my parents are actually going away on a trip tomorrow - but I wasn't sure how many chances I will get to visit them in the near future with the start of the school year (which is nuts when you work at a college, and will probably be more nuts this year than in the past), working Saturdays, and starting grad school.  I also just kind of wanted to get away... it's been kind of stressful lately.  I like my job for the most part, but my social life isn't as active as I would like it to be.  Also, I don't really like change and uncertainty, and there has been a lot of that - I'm not sure what's happening with work, if I will be changing shifts or what.  I'm also not sure how much longer my weekend overtime will keep on, and I'll miss the money if that ends.  One of my roomates also just moved out.  Not a huge deal, but it's change, and I'm not a huge fan of change...  I like routine, and I like knowing what the future will be like, and I don't right now,  Anyway, it's nice to have a change of scenery sometimes, be somewhere familiar.  I'm probably making too big a deal of all this... I've got a lot of good things going on, and chances are everything will work out fine, but until everything falls back into place it's kind of a pain.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           You're Chile!      You're really skinny, and kind of bumpy in frame, but you're not as  rough a person as you used to be. &nbsp;You like long, long, long walks on the beach and  avoiding having your rights violated, just like anybody else does. &nbsp;You're even  willing to stand up to those with more power and influence than you, trying to bring them  to justice. &nbsp;Fight the man!   Take the  urlLink Country Quiz  at the   urlLink Blue Pyramid         Fight the man?  I don't want to fight the man, I want to  BE  the man. And I'm anything but skinny... when I sit around the house, I sit  around  the house.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pejmanesque has  urlLink this article on mob-connected dem donor Steve Bing .  Ignoring the political implications, it has this sentence:  Bing is perhaps best known for sparking a tabloid frenzy when he publicly expressed doubt that he was the father of actress Elizabeth Hurley's baby. (A paternity test proved he was indeed the father.)    Shoot, if  urlLink she was my baby momma  I'd be proud of it.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SCSU Scholars links to this  urlLink article on small airports closing becuase no airline wants to fly from them .    Interestingly, many of them got or are trying to get federal subsidies.  Yup, the federal government wants to use your tax money to fly small planes to crappy old airports (they are all turbo-prop -only airports, probably because they are too small and the runways too short to support jets) that not enough people want to go to to make it worth flying planes to.  I know a few of the areas mentioned in PA, mostly because I drive that way to visit my parents.  For example, Reading PA is on the list.  Reading is probably less than an hour away from the  urlLink Harrisburg Airport , which actually has real airlines, and is probably less than two hours from BWI and Newark.  Why would they need their own airport, and why should the federal government pay for them to have it?  The article has this quote:  "It's a matter of economics," says Joyce Opp, Lancaster airport's finance director. "There have been countless studies that show that communities that have air service fare better economically."   I wonder if Joyce and the study are confusing cause and effect.  Maybe it's that places that have businesses and tourist attractions that people want to fly to, and people who can afford to fly, are better off to begin with, and that's why they have air service. 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      USA Today has an article in yesterday's paper about  urlLink TIVO and it's competitors .  It talks about Tivo and it's competitors - cable and satellite/DSS providers that are including their own DVR's in their cable or satellite boxes, as well as PC companies that are including it in Windows Media Center PC's and DVD-R settop boxes.  The article doesn't mention Tivo's only competitor in traditional DVR boxes, however -  urlLink RePlay TV .  They have been around since 1997, have a pretty strong cult following, and make what I think is a really good product.  They had commercial skip on some of their DVR's until the MPAA made them pull it.  They also had home networking and ethernet connectivity on their units way before Tivo.  As I said, I own a RePlay - a 5060 - and I love it.  Not to sound cliched, but it's changed the way I watch TV.  I bought it over Tivo for a couple reasons - native ethernet connectivity, which Tivo didn't have when I bought it (I don't have a phone line), commercial skip, and a really good price ($50 rebate plus $50 gift card from Amazon).   It could be that the author looked at RePlay and didn't think it was worth a mention.  Still, when you are writing an article on a company's competitor, shouldn't you mention the company that has been competing directly pretty much since day one?  Especially when you mention fringe products like Media Center PC's, which haven't exactly been rousing sucesses?  It makes you think about the mainstream media, and why people are turning away from it.  Unlike some things, I don't think this is any bias, but it strikes me as really sloppy reporting to ignore a major aspect to a story, and is probably the reason that people are turning away from newspapers.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got a letter from the John Kerry/Democratic National committee today.  It starts out in the second paragraph that they "know how hard you have already worked to prepare our Party for victory in 2004".   WTF?  I've never given to any political campaigns (yet - I keep saying I'll kick in a few bucks for Bush eventually) and I'm a registered Republican.  And I write a blog with a giant "days until the election Bush/Cheney" counter on the side, but I can't expect the DNC to know that.  The funny thing is this is the second Democrat fundraising letter I've gotten.  The first was a far more left-wing one - I think it was written by Barbara Boxer - and it was filled with some pretty strong "Bush is the worst president ever and is destroying America" drivel.  If you are a die-hard dem, it may be exactly what you want to hear, but if you are a die-hard Republican it makes you dislike them more, and I can't imagine swing voters like it either.  The DNC letter is pretty calm - it's got the usual stuff about evil HMO's, destroying ANWAR, and defending civil liberties, but that's to be expected, and it's politics.  I did get one letter from the Republicans a while ago, none since.    I can't help wonder how I got on the DNC's list - it seems like they would get it from voter rolls, and a guy who is a registered Republican in a city that's 90% democrat doesn't seem like a candidate for donating.   I've always disliked untargeted marketing.  It always strikes me as odd that companies supposedly know everything about everyone, but their marketing is always untargeted - ie all the credit card ads I get in the mail stress low interest rates and balance transfers, even though I have never carried a balance.  You think with all the info out there, the Dems could at least figure out who their party faithful is - and if they aren't sure who is who, they might want to send out a middle-of-the road, swing-voter-oriented plea to those who they aren't sure, and keep the party faithful stuff for the people who definitly are party faithful.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got a new keyboard and mouse today.  Ordered them from different places - the keyboard is  urlLink an Eluminix knockoff from CompGeeks  and the mouse is a  urlLink Kensington Gamer mouse from woot.com .  I'm loving the mouse - huge, grippy, accurate, nice scroll wheel.  I was using a wireless before and it had a lot of communication issues.  $15 for a wired mouse seems high to a guy who usually buys whatever's free after rebate, but this one's worth it.  They keyboard is decent - it's brighter than I thought it would be based on the reviews on fatwallet, but it's smaller than a normal keyboard, so I'm still having issues hitting the right keys, as they aren't always where I expect them to be.  I'm wondering if buying decent peripherals was a bad move.  I go through a lot of keyboards and mice - partly because I use them alot and want one that feels right, but also because I they get dirty, crumby, and coffee stained from the fact that I almost always eat breakfast in front of my PC and frequently eat dinner there as well.  
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The National Review has an interesting collection of  urlLink Quotes from Moore at the DNC  where he has all kinds of fun things to say about Republicans.  He says that "The hate, they eat for breakfast."  I'm a registered Republican, and I have to say I've never eaten hate for breakfast.  Usually, I have toast and lots of coffee.    He goes on to say that Republicans "up at six in the morning trying to figure out which minority group they're going to screw today".  I don't usually get up until 10am.  Guess I'll have to turn in my "vast member of the right wing conspiracy" registration card.   Well, that and I don't think of myself as hateful (except against terrorists. Hate them).  The thing is that the democratic party, especially Moore and his ilk, seem to think that anyone who thinks the U.S. should let people keep more of the money they earn, or should defend itself against those who want to destroy it's way of life, are evil.  Maybe I read the wrong blogs (in addition to eating the wrong breakfast and not getting up on time), but I don't really see conservatives calling the liberals hateful - in fact, some are pledging  urlLink way more  in terms of niceness.  I don't think that Democrats or Liberals are evil or hateful for the most part.  They are for the most part misguided.  They don't see terrorism for the threat that it is.  They want people to be better off, but they don't grasp that people are better served by the free market rather than by government programs.  They want people to make more money, but they don't realize that the minimum wage will hurt, not help that.  They want better healthcare, but they don't understand that (additional) socialization of healthcare will make most people worse off.  They honestly feel like they are doing good, even when what they are doing is destructive.  Sure, there are some Republicans out there who are jerks, but I don't think most are.  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Mickey Kaus has his  urlLink four steps for a Kerry election win  (scroll down to Monday July 26, his site doesn't appear to have permalinks).     Number 2 is interesting:   2. Return to 'Return to Normalcy': Peggy Noonan's insight, which is that Americans crave a respite from Bush's frenetic history-making, doesn't mean we can go back to happier pre-9/11 days. Everyone knows we can't. But we can take a break from the abnormal, over-leverage- and over-heated presidential decision making process that led us into Iraq and to the brink of a violent, generations-long global "clash of civilizations." At this point, Kerry's over-deliberativeness may be just what's called for.   When I talk to people who are against the Iraq war, or the Patriot act, or other anti-terrorism Bush policies, I frequently feel a hugely insurmountable obstacle between their views and mine - I think that we are engaged in a struggle for the very continuation of our way of life, and they don't.    When you believe that civilization is in danger, you tend to be willing to sacrifice a few civil liberties and take action against countries that you feel are significant threats, even without absolutely perfect intelligence or approval of every country in the world.  You realize that the struggle you are engaged in is different from previous struggles, and it means acting differently than your country has acted in the past.  It also means that sometimes you will take action that may not seem as wise as it did earlier - but it's done with knowledge that the costs of not acting may be higher than the costs of acting too early or too much.  I firmly believe that Islamofacist terrorism is a huge threat to our civilization. I think that there are small but very powerful groups of Muslims who want to make the entire world follow Sharia law, and want to kill anyone who doesn't.  I believe that these people will do whatever possible to destroy our way of life, and that we need to do whatever is necessary to stop that from happening.  Bush didn't start this battle.  He simply responded to it because 9/11 was the first time that many people, myself included, realized that this struggle existed.  However, this struggle has been going on for years - on U.S. soil since at least '93, and throughout the world earlier.  The clash of civilizations that Kaus alludes to isn't something Bush invented, it's simply something that he realized was reality and responded to as best he could.  The fact is that the terrorists, the Islamofacists, aren't going to take a break.  If we relax our defenses and become less proactive in fighting terrorism here and abroad, they will seize those opportunities and hit us harder.  When someone's coming at me with a gun, the last thing I want is someone whose own supporters describe as exhibiting "over-deliberativeness".
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Eugeune Volokh is  urlLink not happy about spam blocking that involves whitelists  that he is not a member of.  I had a similar experience with an ebay buyer a few months ago who I sold a wireless router to.  He had a whitelist-type spam blocking setup where you had to click on a link in his email or reply to his email to go through - except I couldn't get the link to show up and the emails bounced back.  I think he finally emailed me.  I think spamblocking by IP addesses of known spammers, keyword filters, ect, can be good as long as it doesn't result in too many false positive (ie legitimite emails not getting through) Whitelists seem to complicated for anyone who ever has to get emails from someone they don't know (business owners, ebay buyers and sellers, people in jobs who  ever  have to deal with outside vendors/customers/users/ect).  Personally, I don't care about spam that much - a few clicks and it's gone.  I understand the huge costs to networks (but they still bear much of these costs with whitelists - they still get the emails, and in systems like the one I tangled with, store that email for some length of time), but as a user, it's not a huge deal to me.  
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I got my acceptance letter for the part time MBA program. Originally when I opened the packet, the letter was stuck to the side of the envelope, so I saw a course catalog and some insurance info, but no acceptance letter, which puzzled me.  But I found the letter, and so I know that it's all good... mostly.  I currently work nights.  The plan I had orignally worked out with my employer (which also happens to be where I'm taking classes- I work for a college) was to switch with another coworker (who was hired after me and thus technically gets the bitch shift, but I liked working nights and figured I would stay doing it as long as I could).  They changed his duties though, and he no longer does phone support - so I have no clue what is going to happen, and I can't even be sure they will let me take classes.  Why can't my life be simple - or at least simpler?
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I saw this on Drudge this morning, but apparently the page is down now - but there is still googlecache.  Planned Parenthood is/was selling  urlLink I had an abortion  T-shirts.  Which makes me say WTF?  I think abortion is morally wrong, except in cases where the woman's life is in danger, incest, rape, ect.  But at the same time, I think groups that want to make it illegal are taking the wrong route.  I think convinicing women not to have abortions and providing alternatives is a better solution - basically, focusing on demand instead of supply.  Given how long Rowe v Wade has stood, it's unlikely it's going away.  I understand the pro-life positon - when you think something is immoral, that it's murder, you are going to be against it.  But I don't understand why so many pro-choice people seem to see abortion not as a necessary evil, or something morally neutral, but instead as something fundamentally good, something there should be more of, like abortions were cute fuzzy puppies or Krispy Kreme donuts or something.  Every tiny limit that many see as reasonable (partial-birth bans, not having the government pay for abortions, not providing funding for abortions to China, with there one-child policy) is seen as a repeal of Roe v Wade.  The China issue is funny, since most chinese families are aborting their first child if it's a girl because they prefer boys - way to go, woman's rights.  The other think that strikes me as odd about Planned Parenthood is that their name and mission should be to AVOID abortions - it should never go that far.  If you need to have an abortion, you aren't planning very well.  If Planned Parenthood focused more on birth control, safe sex, ect, fewer people would need to have abortions in the first place. Even if you see nothing morally wrong with abortion, it seems like women are better off not having them - it seems like the pill or a condom are less risky than ANY "medical procedure".  My theory is that most people are somewhere in the middle on abortion- they don't have a problem with some limits, but don't want a total, or even nearly total ban.  It seems like both sides keep pushing at the extremes.  I understand why the religious pro-lifers are pushing against it, but I don't understand why the pro-choicers seem to see abortion as such a good thing, and don't seem to be making much of an effort to make them as rare as possible - such as Planned Parenthood actually living up to their name and making them rarer.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't watch a lot of news-based programs on TV.  I used to be glued to FOX news, and I used to be a huge O'Reilly fan.  I kind of grew out of it.  O'Reilly is entertaining, but he tends to bend facts to suit him and be mean to his guests, and I kind of got tired of it.  I also bought a  urlLink RePlay TV , and thus my days of flipping through channels for something to watch and settling on FOX News are over - if I want to watch something, I usually have about 20 hours of Law and Order reruns waiting for me.  I've also tended to get more of my news from the internet, and most of my analysis from blogs.  There is one exception - a news analysis show that I make a point of recording - the Dennis Miller Show on CNBC.  It's funny, I like Dennis' politics - hard on terrorism, softer on social issues - and it frequently has guests who are bloggers or writers for online magazines (Cathy Siepp, Hugh Hewitt, writers from NRO, Manhattan institute, the weekly standard, ect).  Every now and then, though, I will hear someone say something that is totally incorrect, and I wish the show was like a blog, where when someone makes a wrong statement, you can email them, or post in the comments with a link.  One I remember from a while ago was someone describing the no-fly list as "obviously it's a list of people who are not permitted to fly".  But it's not - it's a list of people  urlLink subject to additional scruitiny before flying .  Another one was on Thursday's show, where Bill Press was on the Varsity Panel.  He said that the 9/11 report reflected badly on Bush because "he got this memo on August 6 that the terrorists were going to crash planes into buildings in New York and didn't do anything to it". This was unrebutted by Miller, who made a comment about Clinton not doing anything either.  But it seems like a pretty glaring error since the memo  urlLink said nothing of that sort .  It did say in two places that New York was a potential target, and it also talks about a plot to hijack airliners  in 1998 . That plot was to release hostages, which is a very different thing than what actually happened.  During a hijacking, people act exactly how the pilots on 9/11 act - like the target is the plane, not that the plane is a weapon.  Yes, there is stuff about planes and buildings, but nothing about flying the former into the latter.  How was Bush supposed to connect a 3 year old plot and some people in NY taking pictures (which turned out to be  urlLink Yemini Tourists )to what actually happened.  Anyway, that's what I like about blogs - it's easy to point out and refute lies or truth-twisting - something that is much harder in movies and TV.  Sure, I can yell at the TV, but then my roomates start giving me dirty looks...
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      USA Today has an interesting article about  urlLink the eDonkey file sharing program . It talks about how the  urlLink INDUCE  act, which tries to make P2P companies criminally liable for materials on their network and for abetting copyright violations, would affect it.  Unlike Kazzaa, eDonkey is headquartered in the U.S., so it's basically screwed if INDUCE passes.  The article doesn't mention that there is a very popular open-source version of eDonkey called  urlLink eMule . Unlike eDonkey, eMule is open-source, so there's no company to sue, and it's way harder to go after than a company like eDonkey.    I don't generally agree that open-source is inherently better than closed-source programing, but there are some things, like p2p, where the lack of central control or profit gives an advantage.  Even if they kill the Donkey, I doubt they will kill the mule.  
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      (while helping one of my roomates move out)  roomate:  that's going to have to go to  me: what is it?  roomate  it's a photo enlarger  me:  does it enlarge other stuff too?  (begins humping the photo enlarger) roomate:  well, I guess I'll never be using that again...
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      AllahPundit links yesterday to an article by Rick Perlstein of the Village Voice, and  urlLink he asks for responses .  His contention is that Bush fans like Bush only becaus they think he is inherently good, and that such a view is unamerican because the constitution doesn't believe in the inherent goodness of people.  I think that Perlstein has his cause and effects reversed.  Perlstein seems to think that conservatives support Bush's policies because they like him.  I think that conservatives like Bush as a person because he's someone who agrees with most of their views.   Sure, there are some conservatives who will formost argue that Bush is a great guy, but chances are they think he's a great guy because they think he is pursuing policies that make the country safer and more prosperous.  It seems odd to me that it's Un-American to think that Bush is a nice guy, but if you think he's totally evil, that's perfectly normal.  Comparing Bush to Hitler, calling him stupid or a monkey or making fun of his mispronunciations is par for the course, but thinking he's a nice guy makes you Hitler too.  I would like to think that the reason that liberals dislike Bush is because they disagree with his policies based on reasoning and analysis, and not just because they don't like the guy's accent or where he comes from or who his dad is, but I don't think that's always the case, and it seems odd to critize Republicans for something I think the liberals are far more guilty of.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Unconventional Wisdom  links to  urlLink this article on the possibility of the Amish becoming a large voting block. .  The article is interesting, but even more interesting is this money quote from a Democratic spokesman:   If I know Republicans and their grass-roots operations, they'll spend most of their time trying to phone bank the Amish," said Kerry spokesman Mark Nevins.   I'm going to give Mark Nevins the benfit of the doubt and assume he's intellegent enought to realize that the Amish don't use phones. So I'm guessing what he is saying is that the Republicans are too dumb to figure that out.  Gee, thanks Mark.  Very nuanced.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Via  urlLink Dave Barry's Blog  comes  urlLink this article blasting the Axe deotorant campaign .  OK, so I find the little armpit with feet a little creepy.  But I think it's hard to deny that women generally like men with good grooming habits, and would probably not want to date a guy who didn't bathe on a regular basis, unless the woman is  French. And I don't think it's any secret that men like to look at attractive women, and I don't think that makes them evil sexist pigs.  But does any stupid ad really call for this characterization of a product?   The ads are for a deodorant called "Axe," which is some sort of mass-produced cheap-ass Wal-Mart gag-reflex men's body spray that doubtlessly smells like a rank synthetic admixture of pine cones and road tar and Raid Ant & Roach Death, the scent of which will likely remind you of something your drunk mulleted cousin might've worn to the Spokane Auto Show back in 1984. Mmm, carcinogens.    Would it have killed the author to buy the product instead of assuming what it smells like?  But god forbid, he would have to go to a Wal-Mart to buy it, and who knows what kind of great unwashed (or maybe great washed, if she's offended by the idea that women like guys who don't smell like a locker room floor after the big game) he might encounter.  And what's wrong with mass-produced deotorant?  Should I be buying my deotorant in small batches from the local perfumery instead of buying whatever happens to be on-sale-with-coupon this week?  And of course, anyone who lives in Spokane, and not a real city like NY or LA must be dumb, especially if they would enjoy going to an auto show.  I mean, auto shows are filled with vile, pollution belching SUV's.  A cultured person would never go to an auto show, they would go to an opera or something.  And they evidently wouldn't put on deotorant first.  Then there is this line:   offering up their sex to a giant hairy armpit as though it was a fat Republican senator and they were a cheap hooker.    Because only Republicans are fat and visit hookers.  They probably use deotorant too, those materialistic bastards.    And then there is this:    every ad for the Gillette Mach 3 razor, for example, features roaring fighter jets and a skanky-hot girlfriend who slithers over to her hunky bulbous dork of a man just after he finishes shaving, and she strokes his smooth rugged manly GQ skin and coos and melts and shoots him a naughty glance that says she would like to be immediately stripped naked and bent over the bathroom sink and made mad grunting 1.7-minute love to before the second-half kickoff. You know, just like real life.    Because, you know, girls don't like guys who work out, which is why my giant hairy beer belly gets so many chicks.  Also, girls love it when you don't shave, or when you shave badly.  So  urlLink Michael Moore  must be getting mad play.  Also, girls are never sexually agressive, or initiate sex, and no guy would want them to.  Plus, no guy who would want a clean shave could possibly last for more than one minute and 42 seconds.  At least not in the world of Mark Moreford, San Francisco Gate columnist.   The end of the story is possibily the craziest thing I've ever read outside of IndyMedia:   We say sure, here, just take a significant hunk of my brain, scrape it over the invidious Madison Avenue cheese grater, pulverize it and liquefy it and inject it with a thousand visual toxins and a million corporate logos and countless inane slogans and then reconstitute it and shove it back into my head.   And I'll just sit here and pretend like nothing happened, like everything's fine and that this endless barrage of surreal silly disgusting marketing swill isn't slowly leeching all the truth and beauty out of the sacred vaults of time and love and meaning. This is what we say. Well, some of us.    Because women don't really don't like guys who smell good, and guys would not enjoy looking at beautiful women, if it wasn't for the Axe ads.  People don't buy products because they actually improve their lives, make them more enjoyable, and fulfill needs.  We're all just following our advertising overlords, who aren't trying to make profits by selling people products that they want and can use, but rather trying to spread horrible myths like women would rather date a guy with the faint smell of deotorant rather than the strong odor of B.O.   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Michelle Malkin, who evidently is  urlLink less conservative than I am  has a  urlLink Media Diversity Test  aimed at pointing out how liberal the media generally is.  urlLink Dean Esmay shares his results .  So how do I stack up?  1. I have never voted for a Democrat in my life.  -Yes, at least nationally.  I may have voted for some local ones in local elections back in NJ   2. I think my taxes are too high.  -yes   3. I supported Bill Clinton's impeachment.  -yes   4. I voted for President Bush in 2000.  -yes   5. I am a gun owner.  -not yet, but I may be someday, and I fully support the rights of people to own them.   6. I support school voucher programs.  -yes   7. I oppose condom distribution in public schools.  -no - I really don't have a problem with it, as long as schools are honest in pointing out that they aren't perfect - they do break, ect.   8. I oppose bilingual education.  -yes   9. I oppose gay marriage.  -no.  I really don't care either way.  I don't think that not letting gays marry is the modern equivilant of slavery or Jim Crow laws, like some on the left would like you to belive, but I also don't think that letting it happen is going to cause man-dog marriages to become legal.  I  DO , however, oppose having gay marriage thrust upon us by the courts, (or for that matter, banned by the Federal government).  I think it should be decided by the states through ballot referendums.  This gives rights to make decisions on it to the states, and if you don't like it you can always move to another state.   10. I want Social Security privatized.  -yes   11. I believe racial profiling at airports is common sense.  -not exactly.  There has been buzz that the FAA and other groups want to LIMIT the number of Arabs who can be searched, and that strikes me as stupid.  But there are Muslims who aren't Arabs (and Arabs who aren't Muslims), so there is still the possibility that Islamofacists can use people of other races.   12. I shop at Wal-Mart.  -Not really.  I haven't been there in years.  I have nothing against it, but I like the clearance deals I find at Target, I think they have better selection and quality than Wal Mart, and their locations are more convinient to me.    13. I enjoy talk radio.  -Not really.  Like my complaints about  urlLink opinion TV programing , I would rather get my news and commentary online.  I think it's easier to select what interests me and easier to disprove or prove statements.  I also like listening to music, and will usually listen to CD's in the car and MP3's at work or home.    14. I am annoyed when news editors substitute the phrase "undocumented person" for "illegal alien."  -not really.  It is kind of silly when you think about it, but it's not at the top of my list.   15. I do not believe the phrase "a chink in the armor" is offensive.  -Yes, I don't.   16. I eat meat.  -hell yes.   17. I believe O.J. Simpson was guilty.  -yup   18. I cheered when I learned that Saddam Hussein had been captured.  -yes.   19. I cry when I hear "Proud To Be an American" by Lee Greenwood.  -yes.  It is a touching song.   20. I don't believe The New York Times.  -Yes.   Hers scoring system was 5 points per yes, which would give me a 60%, although you probably could add a couple points in for all the maybes and sortas.   Of course I'm not a minority, so this may be meaningless.  But I think it makes me a conservative, but also somewhat middle of the road, which I think describes my views - fiscally conservative, hard-line on defense, more liberal/libertarian on social issues.  
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Instapundit links to  urlLink this justoneminute entry  about Kerry and his version of playing nice, which includes  urlLink blasting Bush for waiting too long to leave the classroom. .  Kerry says he would have left immediatly.  I think the most interesting thing is the link to  urlLink George Stephanopoulos' views on the subject .  He raises good points, namely that 1)no other president has ever been seen in front of live TV cameras reacting to such devestating news  2)Clinton's reaction to Somolia was similar, but was behind closed doors and 3)it's easy to say in hindsight what one would do differently, it's harder to actually do that in that situation.  Obviously Stephanopoulos is no Bush apologist, and I think his comments are right on the money.  If Kerry were honest with himself and the american people, he would have said that he doesn't know how he would have reacted - that he likes to think that he would have leaped out of the classroom and taken action, but that it's much easier to second guess than to actually be in a position.  I'm not sure what Kerry would have done after leaving the room. I'm not sure anyone could have done anything, especially considering that  nobody knew what the hell was going on. .  I think Bush's reaction also gives some pause to the "Bush knew" moonbat wing - if he expected it to happen, he would have had a planned reaction.  
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well known linker  urlLink InstaPundit  (aka Glenn Reynolds) is taking heat from  urlLink certain   urlLink left wing bloggers  for having the nerve to wear a pro-gun shirt.  The shirt parodies the left's views on diversity by showing a bunch of guns and the words  celebrate diversity .  A pretty straightforward pun on the varity of guns out there.  But apparently, since a different version of the shirt has colors on it, and colors are popular in Africa, Glenn must be advocating using guns to kill black people, and thus should be fired.  The funny things is that reading the comments on  urlLink steve's blog  you would think Glenn Reynolds was somewhere to the right of the Christian coalition, when he's pretty middle of the road.  He's come in against  urlLink Ashcroft's war on porn ,  urlLink Bush's KASS council on bioethics  and the  urlLink Federal Marriage Ammendment , among other things.  But if you like guns and dislike affirmative action, and are willing to poke fun at the latter with the former, you are automatically a racist.  Despite Steve's claims that he doesn't want Glenn fired, I can't think of any reason to write to UTenn.  And when liberals are so concerned about diversity, why do they want to eliminate what is probably one of the few conservative voices in a university?  I also think that it was funny that Steve and/or his commentors complained about Glenn running a blog during work hours.  Never mind that he's a professor and thus doesn't HAVE any specific work hours beyond class and whatever office hours he is required to have.  As a professor, he's probably juged mostly on what he publishes, not clocking in and out.  And as an employee of a college, I have to say that professors are given wide latitude for what they can do with college property.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm not the world's most religious person, although I do believe in God - if only because I can't believe that something as beautiful/perfect as the world could be created by accident or random activity.  But sometimes something happens that makes me wonder if someone's watching out for me.  I was making a right out of the parking lot at work tonight, and I notice the light turn amber and two cars speed through.  I remember thinking "hmm, I should probably make sure nothing is coming before I turn after the light turns green".  When I glanced left before turning, I see a white early-90's Chrysler New Yorker fly towards the intersection and thru the red light.  I'm not the world's most careful driver, and I think if I hadn't had that though, they would probably be picking out pieces of the driver's side door out of my ribcage.  Makes me wonder if I'm here for some bigger reason I don't know about, and gives me a little hope for the future.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Powerline had had great coverage of Kerry's eating issues, including his  urlLink slumming at Wendy's, then eating shrimp vindaloo at the Yatch Club  and his tendancy to  urlLink say he is going to local resturants, then not showing up. .  I think that it is interesting to compare this to  urlLink Bush's unannouced visit in New Mexico.   Instead of saying he's going to go to places he doesn't, Bush goes to local eateries without announcing it, actually buys food from them, and encouraged the reporters there to buy food too.  Bush seems to be a much more likable, down to earth guy, despite the liberals who try to paint him as evil Hitler - and I think that that is going to resonate with the swing voters that both candidates are going after.  In the small world catagory, I've actually eaten at the Alexis Diner mentioned in the first article - the Newburg, NY resturant that Kerry said he was stopping at, then skipped.  I used to go there with my parents during the fall - we would tour local wineries, and stop for apples.  He missed a good cheesesteak.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When I first saw  urlLink this article on the woman in Florida fired for eating Pork at a Muslim company , I thought "just another example of people trying to impose their religion on other people".  When I thought about it some more, I'm not so sure.  After all, it's not like her religion  required  her to eat pork.  She's not being stopped from expressing her religion, she's being stopped from doing something that she wants to do that happens to be against another religion.   As much as I love meat, it doesn't seem that oppressive to not be able to eat pork at work.  After all, there are plenty of things that I would like to be able to do at work but can't - light up a big fat cigar, come to work wearing shorts and birkenstocks, drink a pint of guiness with dinner.  None of these relate to my religion in any way, but they are part of the job, they are things I knew when I started working here, and I accept that because I like having a job so I can have a roof over my head and food on my plate.  The impression I get from the article is that she took the job knowing that they had a no-porkin' policy, that she was warned about it, and still kept doing it.  If she didn't want to workin in a no-porkin' zone, she shouldn't have taken the job.  She wanted to have it both ways - get whatever benefits and higher pay the job offered over others, but not follow it's policies.  I can see how not being allowed to do something your religion requires is discriminatory, but I don't see how not being allowed to do something your religion allows is discriminatory, even if it's restricted based on someone else's religion.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My cell phone rang around 15 minutes ago.  202 number, which I think is D.C.  Don't know anyone in DC, but I answered it anyway.  Guy on the phone says "someone from this number called me".  Nope "I just got home and checked my caller ID and someone from this number called me"  Told him I didn't call anyone from this number, and he hung up.  WTF?  I don't make a lot of phone calls, and I checked the recent calls on my cell, nothing.  I'm wondering if a)somewhere somone made a mistake and someone else's number shows up as mine in caller ID. b)some telemarketer spoofed my number on the caller ID so it wouldn't show up as them or c)someone cloned my cell phone.  Guess I should keep a close eye on my phone bill....
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My politcal compass results have been posted at the  urlLink Blogosphere Political Compass Project .  I was kind of surprised to notice that my results put me to the right (and slightly more libertarian) than well-known coservative hottie  urlLink Michelle Malkin .  I'm at 7.4 conservative, -05 libertarian, she's at 6.8,0.  I realize that the conservative label is  urlLink more economic than anything else  and that I'm very conservative from an econ perspective, more liberal socially.  I only picked Michelle because she's a conservative blogger I read regularly, so I was familiar with her positions.  It is really interesting to see where bloggers rank, so I encourge any blogger who hasn't done it to  urlLink submit their results  (scroll down for instructions).  The more data, the more interesting comparisions you can make.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       CoWorker: : Can I borrow a screwdriver?   Mad Anthony :  I don't know.  I've got some vodka, but I may be fresh out of orange juice.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      via  urlLink NewFeed , I found this  urlLink silly article about how it takes a village to make a millionaire.   The article starts out by asking some poor kids if they think they will ever be millionaires.  They say yes, and the aricle goes on to dash their dreams by saying that they won't be because America isn't wealthy enough, because too many kids inherited their wealth, and finds a couple rich people to say it's true.  The study is by  urlLink United for a Fair Economy  which is filled with articles on how people with money don't deserve it and shouldn't get to keep it.  The article has a quote from  urlLink Google  founder Eric Schmidt, who says  Lots of people who are smart and work hard and play by the rules don't have a fraction of what I have," Eric Schmidt, the CEO of Google, told Forbes Magazine in 2001. "I realize I don't have my wealth because I am so brilliant."   Eric, you discredit yourself.  Sure, lots of people work hard and are smart, but you came up with products that made the world a better place, made it easier to find information, and made people's lives easier.  You also found an advertising model to support it that was better tageted and less intrusive than any other.  You made internet surfing and information hunting better, and the market rewarded you for it.  Be proud of that.  The article also says he doesn't deserve it all because the government funds internet research.  They also fund the arts, but I don't see anyone saying that that's why 50 cent is rich.  It says that 1/3 of the people on the Forbes 400 were born on the list. OK, but how long will they stay there?  Inheriting wealth is easy, but keeping it is harder.  Do you think Paris Hilton will do as good a job running Hilton Hotels as her father did?  It then follows with this confusing statement:  . Another quarter inherited a small business, oil lands, or perhaps had well-to-do parents able to provide an expensive education and family friends helpful in a business career.   If I understand their math, that's 33% plus 25%, which is 58%.  If that means 43% of people got to be  among the richest 400 people in the country  on their own, that's damn impressive.  Note the inequality of their statements.  Inheriting an oil field is a gift not many people get, but a decent college education is in reach for the entire middle class.  As far as a small business, you don't get on the Forbes 400 running the neighborhood hardware store.  These people may have inherited a small business, but they turned it into a huge one by providing stuff that people in the village wanted to buy.  In that vein, the article also includes this quote:  For example, prosperous parents give their children a head start by buying homes in a good school district, financing college, and contributing to the purchase of a child's first house or condominium.   Much of those things sound like middle-class things to do, not just things the rich do.  As far as college, there are so many college-backed scholarships, other scholarships, federal loans, government-subsidized state colleges, and other ways of getting money that it's hard to imagine that anyone who has half a brain and wants to go to college can't.   Helping your kids make a down payment on a house is nice, and it might make your kid a little more comfortable, but it's not going to make him rich.  It ads that the rich benefit from government in terms of  , may benefit from the free-enterprise system, financial markets, democracy, law and order, a public school system, libraries, museums, and other aspects of modern society.  and thus should embrace income-reallocating taxes.  Nice how it manages to list most of the things that conservatives and even libertarians think government should do - enforce laws.  I can't imagine that too many large business owners did it because there were museums.  But it skips the things that conservatives and business owners complain about - a tax system that isn't always understandable or fair, regulations that make it difficult to run a business, and government programs that take their hard earned money and give it to the politcally well connected.  UEF's website has lots more stuff that looks like future MadAnthony fodder, but I don't think I can read the words "income inequality" again without screaming.   urlLink SCSU Scholars  has a good look at the income inequality arguement.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>