<Blog>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The moonlight streamed through the window, it wasn't summer, but the weather was mild enough to leave the shutters open all night. Sitting in the alcove by the window Rahna watched Aidan sleep. She had not meant for any of this to happen. Marriage! She almost snorted at the thought but clamped her jaw shut, not wanted to disturb her husband of several hours. Pulling the blanket around her she became aware of new sensations in her body, enjoyable changes.  She smiled, but the expression was slightly bitter. All she had wanted was a quick roll in the sack with him, but he had never even tried to take advantage of her injured little girl act. She scowled at him, she could still leave. She had received what she wanted, she could feel the change coursing through her body. There was nothing to stop her, "I can leave," she whispered to herself.  And yet -- she couldn't. She had sworn to stay with him, to cleave to him, to be his and he hers. Never mind that it had been sworn in the name of a god she would never acknowledge. She had said those words, she had promised.  With a slight shiver she turned away from him, fixing her attention instead on the land. There was a full moon, weddings always occurred during the three days when the moon was full, and the light was almost as bright as day. It was a cold light, unforgiving, and even from this height in the keep she could see the harshness of the land below. The courtyard was normally kept in impeccable condition, but after the celebrations it was strewn both with rubbish and food as well as with people.  Placing her palms flat on the stone walls Rahna closed her eyes, her attention fixed on the land. It pulled on her. She was almost ready, almost. She could feel herself become who she truly was again. Her head arched backwards as she flowed to her feet. Whole again. The figure of Rahna was gone, replaced by the guardian. She had maintained the more human form, and as she examined her long pale fingers she turned back, away from the window. She took one step towards Aidan. Her golden eyes glowed suddenly, he had stabbed her. Tried to kill her. Her lips curled back, revealing sharp white teeth that resembled animal fangs more than anything than belonged in a human's mouth.  In an instant she stilled herself. He had tried, but he had failed. She was alive, she was strong again, and now she had the advantage over him. With a flick of her silver hair she placed a hand on the wall and sank into the stone.  So much had gone on since she had last been able to be herself. Could so much damage have been done in only four months? Without thought she began the repairs that were part and parcel of her duty, any flaws in the stonework of the keep were to be fixed. Not only in the keep itself, but the stone walls in the fields needed constant attention, sheep and cattle brushing and bumping against them dislodged them, knocked them over time. She stopped suddenly, and almost with regret left the keep to its own devices. If the Lord of Tiercyl wanted her dead, then he obviously did not need her assistance in maintaining the keep's structure, nor the fertility of his land.  Doubts began to assail her, could she really abandon her duty like that? Retreat as the other guardians had done? Sink into the stone with no intention of waking ever again? If she had been corporeal she would have shaken her head in denial. She was Guardian of Tiercyl! The guardian of the land. The humans thought she had been summoned in order to defend the people, the right of the lord to govern, but that was not completely true. More than checking acts of aggression her role was to look after the land. That was her true duty, her very being was caught up with the land. The grass, the stone, the earth, she could feel them all as though they were part of her.  She flew through the land, taking on physical form again far from the keep, flames and wings danced around her, but only for an instant before she took on her more usual form. She sat, silver hair blowing gently in the wind, her legs curled up under her as she considered what she was to do.  She would not let herself be used by Aidan, she would leave the keep alone. But she could not punish the people, the rest of the land for his mistake. She would not abandon them to the same lawlessness that infected the rest of humanity. Without the guardians the human desire for power and wealth resulted in too much bloodshed. Even in Tiercyl there was a standing army, but it was tiny in comparison to most of the other lord's armies, she knew this. And she knew that she was the reason. No other lord would risk the wrath of a Guardian by invading. That made Aidan's actions all the more puzzling to her. Why had he risked so much? What wrong had she ever done him?  She turned her mind back to the question of what she was to do now. It would be no great burden for her to continue to lead a life as Rahna. Over the past few hundred years she had always kept a human side. The family of healers that all the Tiercyl inhabitants knew of were merely a succession of her taking on different human forms. She wasn't sure why she had first begun it, mere curiosity she had told herself, but she knew that it was more than that. It was loneliness. There were no other active Guardians that she could feel. Her borders were silent and empty, and she would not risk leaving her home to travel and find others. The danger was great, and she did not want to find out that she was totally alone.  So she had decided to try and put up with human company. At first she had attempted to talk to them as herself, but they had too much fear. They were unwilling to see her as anything but a brute force, and felt threatened when she conversed with intelligence. That was the reason she had adopted a simple, almost monosyllabic, vocabulary when dealing with humans. If they thought they were smarter than her then her other strengths seemed somehow lessened.  She knew it had been luck that she had had Rahna available to use in order to gain Aidan's attention. The Guardian raised a hand, moving the dress to reveal the faint scar between her breasts. It was almost invisible, but she could feel the raised skin with her fingertips.  That knife had hurt her more than anything she had experienced in centuries. Like blood spilling onto the ground it had burned at her flesh, but she had been unable to wrap herself away from the agony, and it had seared her to the bone. When the blade fell from her body she had been left a choice. Remain as Guardian, but weak and impotent, to slowly regain her strength and former power. Or, and this was the choice she had taken, abandon that side of her and become totally human, but with the opportunity to regain all that she had lost. The risk had been there, Aidan might not have been attracted to Rahna, and if he had never lain with her then she would have been condemned to life, and death, as a human.  Rising to her feet glanced at the sky. The moon was beginning to lose its hold as the sun began to light up the east. She cocked her head, concentrating, Aidan was still asleep. She had time to return to him as though she was nothing more that Rahna, or she could return in this form and take her revenge.  Uncertain as to what her decision would be she sank back into the land, returning to the keep.  
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is it then?" The voice roused Aidan from his memories. He grinned at Oscar, Captain of the Guard and Aidan's oldest friend. He swept his eyes over the hall; everywhere flowers and banners competed for attention with the bright dresses of the women and the embroidered coats of the men. Their chatter and laughter filled the air, but Aidan was not interested in any of them. His eyes had fallen on Rahna, she was seated on the opposite side of the hall, surrounded by people. Yet as she gazed off into the distance Aidan got the impression that she wasn't happy. As that thought made him frown she seemed to feel his eyes and turned her head, her face brightening with a smile as she saw him watching her.  "Who would have thought it? Lord Aidan Tiercyl marrying a goatherder."  Aidan ignored Oscar's teasing, it wasn't the first time this had been mentioned between them, and part of him couldn't really belive that he was marrying her. His eyes remained on her, but her attention had been distracted by a well-wisher, she didn’t see him smile. She was so beautiful, and more than lived up to her name, Rahna, the graceful one.  	 "Do you love her?" Again Oscar disturbed Aidan's thoughts, but on this occasion the serious tone in the Guard’s voice made Aidan answer. "I asked her that question myself, did she love me." He paused, remembering. They had been in the forest, she seated side-saddle in front of him on the horse, leaning against his shoulder for support and balance. She couldn't ride, had never had the chance despite her love of the animals themselves. She had remained silent after the question, for so long that he didn't think she would answer. Eventaully she had opened her mouth, and as had happened before and since, surprised him with her honesty.  "She told me she didn't know. That she had never felt for another man what she felt for me." Aidan told Oscar quietly. She had kissed him then, her mouth so soft and gentle, and told him that she didn't know what love was.  “But I know that I am yours, for as long as you want me.”  He didn't tell Oscar that, he was still trying to figure out exactly what she had meant by that.  "But do you love her?" Oscar insisted, and this time Aidan looked him in the face as he shrugged.  "I don't know, I think so. I've never wanted anyone more... And at the same time-" He stopped suddenly, unwilling to tell his best friend that he knew he could have had her; if he had pushed her at all she would have been willing to lie with him. He didn't know why he hadn't even tried, hadn’t forced the issue, the gods knew he wanted her. Part of the reason, he thought, was because he found her so different from the other women he had been with. She was open and honest, never trying to change him like the noblewomen he knew, or seduce him like many of the servants. His forehead creased as these thoughts raced through his head. "I don't know if I love her," he repeated, "but I want her to be my wife." "Well that is a good thing," the teasing note had returned to Oscar's voice, "Because here comes the priest now.  Aidan glanced up and saw Rahna getting to her feet. He swallowed, and watching him Oscar shook his head. “Cold feet?” Aidan ignored him, of course he had doubts. He had only known Rahna a few short months. Did he really know her? Did she know him? And that was without even considering the fact that she was, as Oscar had pointed out, a commoner, a goat herder. Still, as his eyes followed her, he turned to the Guard; “Not at all.”  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It was mid-morning, the sun was shining through the tiny slit that passed for a window. The sick-room was on the ground floor, the stone floor covered with straw not rugs and used so infrequently that it was dusty, which added to the darkness. Aidan still needed the light from the lamp to enable him to read. Catching movement from the bed out of the corner of his eye he left the book down on the floor.  The girl opened her eyes and looked around at her surroundings. She caught sight of Aidan and lowered her head, pulling the blankets closer to her body.  "My Lord Tiercyl?"  Aidan smiled at her. Once he had been disturbed by the fact that everyone always knew who he was. That had been years ago, now he took it almost for granted. "You are fine, everything is alright," he reassured her. "You are in the keep. Do you remember what happened?"  "The horse- How long have I been here?"  "A few days, but don't worry, you are going to-"  "A few days! But the goats, they need takin' care of-"  "I said don't worry Rahna. I've had one of the men out to take care of your animals."  He thought he saw uncertainty flicker in her eyes as she glanced in his direction, but her gaze moved away from him so quickly he couldn't be sure.  "You know my name?"  "I do. You are the old healer's granddaughter."  She didn't respond to that, but raised a hand to her forehead. Touching the dark purple bruise that was half hidden by her dark hair, her voice was hesitant as she remembered. "Your horse, the new hunter. He kicked me, but not here." She sounded a little bewildered, and he didn’t blame her for that. It must have been confusing for her waking up in a strange room. "No," Aidan agreed with her, "You hit your head when you fell. You do have a rather large bruise on your hip as well."  She blushed slightly as she lifted the covers to take a look.   "How did you know that the horse was new?" Aidan didn't really care, he just wanted to keep her talking. She had a wonderful voice, soft and gentle and so low he had to pay close attention to catch everything she said.   Instead of answering, however, she dropped her head again, a faint flush visible under her sun-darkened skin. After a moment of silence she realised he was still waiting for an answer. Her blue eyes darted about the room before she replied.  "I always- that is, I like to watch you with your horses." Her voice grew even fainter. "You always seem to understand them so well. It's almost like you can make them dance."  Aidan smile deepened, despite her injuries he found her entrancing, and she flushed again. About to make some reassuring comment their conversation was disturbed by a faint knock at the door before it swung open to admit a servant 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Aidan waited in the entrance hall, pacing backwards and forwards, impatience marking his appearance. Part of him knew the reason for his sudden black mood, but he didn't want to think about what had just happened in his room. It was as though he hadn't been thinking properly for the past week. What difference did it make to him if the priest thought the Guardian was a device of evil? She had never done anything but protect the land, protect his people as he was sworn to do.  He snatched the crop out of the servant's hands, and mounted the hunter. "Where are the hounds?" He asked.  "Milord?"  "The bloody dogs! Do you expect me to give hunt by myself."  "There was no.. I will see to it."  Aidan scowled, more at himself than anything else. He hadn't asked for the hounds after all, only for the horse. Still taking a hunter out, obviously he would be hunting. They hardly expected him to use his own nose to find the game.  He pulled on the reins, turning the horse's head, forcing the prancing animal to circle. The gelding jerked his head, eager to be off, full of energy. His hooves danced across the courtyard and Aidan was content to let him move. It gave him something to do, avoiding the people who had arrived for the market.  He tapped lightly with his heel, and was pleased by the animal’s immediate response. The brown horse was somewhat nondescript in appearance, but anyone who was a judge of horseflesh could see the depth of chest, the easy and smooth leg action. Stamina, speed and a willing heart, those were the qualities Aidan looked for in a horse. He still had to test just how willing this one's heart was, see how brave the gelding was when confronted with jumps and ditches in the forest.  The animal circled again, pulling at the reins. Irritated now Aidan pulled sharply on the reins, and the horse snorted, backing up and lashing out with his off hind leg. The action was merely a way of showing his displeasure, not a malicous act from the horse; the result was violence nonetheless.  Aidan twisted in the saddle, he had felt the horse connect with something. Cursing he jumped from the saddle, a girl lay sprawled face down in the dirt, mud beginning to soak into her skirt. As he turned her over, gently, the crowd began to gather around him.   "Any of you know who she is?"  Most remained silent at the question, but one came forward.  "Milord," he took his cap off his head. "She is the healer's granddaughter. Rahna I think is her name."  "The healer? The old healer? Didn't she...?"  "Pass on my lord, she did at that. The girl was learning from her, has taken her place this past year."  Aidan looked down at the young woman in his arms. He brushed the hair away from her face, revealing a large bruise was now visible on her forehead. He didn't think that was from the horse, more likely she had been kicked and knocked her head as she fell. She stirred slightly, not waking but the movement gave him hope that she wasn’t badly injured. "I'll take her up to the keep." Aidan decided. Maybe one good act could erase his earlier actions. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Both stared at the handle that now emerged from the dress between the guardian's breasts. Then their eyes met, and her's were no longer wild as Aidan remembered, instead they seemed hurt, puzzled. They remained motionless, his hands still wrapped around the knife's hilt, the tiniest trickle of blood began to seep out of her wound, soaking into the pale fabric.  The guardian gave the briefest of coughs, and a drop of blood made it past her lips, darkening them before slowly flowing down her white skin and dropping from her chin onto Aidan's hand. "Why?" she asked softly  Aidan couldn't answer, he stepped away and as his hands left the knife the guardian swayed slightly, and, having lost her support, fell to the ground. For the space of a breath she lay crumpled at his feet, then as Aidan stared she seemed to fade away. The only remaining trace was the knife he had stabbed her with. It lay gleaming on the stone floor, not a single drop of blood marred its surface.   After staring at the knife on the stone floor Aidan shook himself, he was not going to let this bother him. The Guardian had no right to life, she-  it  was an abomination.  "A beast of hell, spawn of demons and evil. Nothing good can come from such a monster."  Somehow it had seemed reasonable when the priest in his white cloak had spoken with him. Now he could think of all the good that had come from the Guardian, even his very life. Were it not for her he would have died a long time ago.  The lord of Tiercyl reached down and picked up the knife, carefully he placed it in the drawer and locked it away safely. Recriminations ran through his head, thoughts that he tried to ignore.  He wrenched open the heavy oak door and stalked out into the hallway, almost knocking down one of the servants who was busy cleaning.  "Get my rooms cleaned." He snapped at her, not even waiting to see her quick courtsey. Seeing another he ordered a horse to be made ready, "the new hunter" he called as the boy ran to do his bidding. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Aidan paced the floor, eyes closed as he went over what he had just read. He ran a hand through his hair, trying to remember the exact details. After a few minutes he collapsed onto the chair, and putting his feet on the table took the book onto his lap. He reread the instructions again, then lifted the blade that lay alongside his chair. He stared at the blade, its bright surface reflecting the lamps that lit the room, the heavy shutters were closed, keeping the daylight out.  Biting his lip uncertainly he flicked through a couple of delicate pages, then with a sigh tossed the book back onto the table, knocking a glass to the floor. It landed on one of the rugs, a soft landing so it did not smash. He ignored it, the room was in a mess anyway, one more item littering the floor wouldn't make a difference.   With a scowl he ran a finger over the blade's edge and then gritting his teeth made the shallow cut. Carefully he held the knife so the drops of blood ran along its length, but did not fall to the ground. Then he waited for it to dry in.   Finally he dabbed at the redbrown stain with a finger, it was dry. He got to his feet and, kicking the rugs back to reveal the stone underneath, paced out the dimensions of the casting. Luckily there was no need for a physical marker, he had no doubt but that she would spot it if there had been.  Taking a deep breath he cast away his misgivings and began the incantation. It was a remarkably straight forward spell, with little in the way of double-meanings, still he was careful to ensure that every single word was pronounced correctly, and that he did not speak too fast.  When he got to the end, he looked around, expecting to see some results. Nothing. Slowly he turned, examining the room. Not even the wall hangings were out of place.  If the beast does not appear to heed your call  he recalled the note at the end of the page  then you must command it to take on it's true form.   The moment he did so she appeared in front of him. Her long hair swayed as she stepped towards him, her wild eyes glowing golden. "Lord Tiercyl?" Aidan swallowed, trying to ignore the little voice that asked what exactly he was doing. He stepped forward to meet the guardian and, taking a deep breath, drove the knife deep into her chest. 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Finally she took on a visible form and calmly surveyed the chamber. The lord of Teircyl and his wife were on one side of the room, facing the strangers. The familar one held a blade across the throat of the heir.   The faces paled as the guardian began her advance, all wings and flame, she knew what humans feared. Some cowered before her, but she had barely lifted her now clawed foot when the lord called out, begging her not to move.  "My son."  She paused, and the beast that had threatened the invaders now became almost human in appearance. Long, straight hair and skin so pale, but her eyes, glowing golden, gave her away.   "Give me the seal." Obedient to the man who held his son's life in his hands Lord Tiercyl ripped the seal in question from around his neck and threw it towards the stranger.  As it was snatched out of the air with a smile the guardian finally recognised the invader.  "You are the lord's father-brother," her low voice made the invader smile. "His uncle, you remember me then my Guardian?" His knuckles turned white as he gripped the seal in his hands. "The one who posesses the Seal, who posesses the Keep. To them alone shall the guardian listen," he declaimed, then glanced at the child in his arms. "Guardian, kill the child."  After a second's pause, head cocked quizzically to one side, the guardian stepped forward. She could feel the fight in the courtyard continuing, every drop of blood that soaked the ground and dirt sent pain flaring through her. Yet her appearance remained serene as she reached the child.  The heir was young, the guardian was unsure of his exact age, but not more than a few years... perhaps 4. His dark eyes were wide and fearful, his face pale. He tried to back away, but arms held him firmly as the guardian reached out towards him. One touch and she could kill. Behind her she heard the lord and lady protest, begging for their son's life.  She stretched out an arm, as it drew closer to the boy it became claw-like. Her talons touched the boy's hair. Behind her the mother cried out "Aidan!" The boy whimpered as she brushed the top of his head, almost gently, tears streamed down his face. Then with a sudden savageness she plunged her claws into the skin.  The man screamed in pain as his hands left the boy, attempted to pull her claws out of his flesh. The blood gushed out of his chest, scalding the guardian wherever it touched her but she smiled. The violence was not necessary, she could have killed him with the barest of touches. As the child ran to his mother the other two strangers drew their swords. The guardian seemed to lean towards them slightly and her free hand reached out, almost caressing them. They were both dead before they hit the ground.  Transforming back into the winged beast the guardian lifted the still struggling man into the air,  "You mistranslated." She growled softly in his ear, then vanished.  She reappeared high above the courtyard, still holding onto the invader. For an instant she hovered, watching the soldiers struggling below. One or two caught sight of her. Finally she allowed herself to feel the pain caused by the shedding of so much blood. She screamed. The noise made everyone look up in horror. Then she released her hold on the bloody mess and the body of the intruder fell towards the ground.  It landed with a sickening thud. The men below seemed frozen. The guardian screamed again and flapped her wings to gain even more height, then folded them close to her body, her sudden descent spurred them into action. As they realised their danger the men fled in fear as the guardian plummeted towards them. 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Slowly the guardian stirred herself. The hoofbeats drumming across the land had attracted her attention. Although the soldiers did not seem worried she watched as the strangers drew nearer to the keep. Unseen, unfelt, she moved closer to them. In the courtyard they were greeted, laughing with the inhabitants of the keep as they dismounted.  Less wary now that they were being escorted through the building she began to withdraw. Then she paused. There was something familiar about one of the men.   He strode confidently at the head of a small band; the others had been left lounging in the courtyard. It was not his appearance that drew the guardian back, but his voice, it tickled her memory. Humans changed so much over time. Often the passing of a few short years would make any human unrecognisable. But his voice... the way he spoke.   As she tried to remember, to discover why it was so familiar to her, she was distracted by shouts from the courtyard. Her attention flickered back to them but it was only the soldiers. The serving girls had come out to see the new arrivals, and now each group was trying to impress the other.   The guardian turned back to follow the strangely familiar voice. The group had been shown into a side chamber off the great hall, where the lord of the keep waited for them.   Still unseen, she flowed through the keep, back to the strangers. As she reached them, a scream pierced the air. She halted. Trying to identify the sound, was it fear, pain or merely excitement? After a moment she continued towards the noise. As she entered the small room she felt blood spurt onto her ground. As the drops sank into the ground outside in the courtyard the guardian flinched, unprepared for the shots of pain.   Hesitation struck again, a beat passed before she decided to ignore the blood, to ignore the pain instead answered the fear from inside the keep. 
     
    
</post>



</Blog>