<Blog>


<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      hehe..no i'm not pregnant. NO! notchet! 2 more years..3 tops. heehee. anyhoo, like we've always been saying, it's fish, plants & now DOGS for us. welcome WINSTON, our english bulldog =)     
      
</post>

<date>29,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Message: LAYER 0NE:  -- Name: AngelicaJaide -- Birth date: December 4, 1980 -- Birthplace: Vancouver, BC Canada -- Current Location: San Diego, CA -- Eye Color: Dark Brown -- Hair Color: Black with reddish brown chunks -- Height: 5'2" -- Righty or Lefty: Righty bebeh -- Zodiac Sign: Saggitarius..  LAYER TWO:  -- The shoes you wore today: my black duffs -- Your weakness: VJ -- Your fears: losing the people i love the most -- Your perfect pizza: don't like pizza..i'll take the crust though =) -- Goal you'd like to achieve: plenty! travel the world, have a baby..so much more =)  LAYER THREE:  -- Your most overused phrase(s): that's greaaaaaaat *sarcasm*, back off, getchor own sammich *from the ever so famous canadian commercial*, whaddawhoddawhaddawha? -- Your thoughts first waking up: get vj's heavy leg off me -- Your best physical feature: smile..iono..i'm guessing.. -- Your bedtime: anytime btwn 10pm-12am -- Your most missed memory: the memz with my papa & the times i spent in vancouver with my famz   LAYER FOUR:  -- In love?: you betcha!  LAYER FIVE:  -- Smoke: are you insane?  -- Cuss: only when i'm really pissed & most of the time it's in tagalog -- Sing: Yes ma'am -- Take a shower everyday: of course! -- Have a crush: yeppers! his name is ben. ben bostrom. *rawr* (i know i'm married, but vj gives him the thumbs up! lol) -- Do you think you've been in love: umm hmm...& i still am...to my wonderful hubby -- Want to go to college: already did =) -- Like(d) high school: yep, although some memories i would rather forget..hahah -- Want to get married: already married! -- Believe in yourself: you betcha -- Get motion sickness: err, not really -- Think you're attractive: ehhh -- Think you're a health freak: i'm in the middle -- Get along with your parent(s): yes ma'am -- Like thunderstorms: yes =) especially when vj's there to hold me when i get too freaked out -- Play an instrument: used to play the piano  LAYER SIX:  In the past month...  -- drank alcohol: whaddayah think -- Smoked: hell no -- Done a drug: does tylenol count?  -- Gone to the mall?: hi, my name is aj & i'm a shop-a-holic -- Eaten an entire box of oreos: ew. -- Eaten sushi: oh hell yeah -- Been on stage: Nope, not this month -- Gone skating: notchet!   LAYER SEVEN:  Ever...  -- Played a game that required removal of  clothing: puahahha. *sigh* HS & college days.. -- Been trashed or extremely intoxicated: hahah umm the day before our second wedding..yep.. -- been caught "doing something": naughty? uh, no. i don't think.. -- Been called a tease: haha yep. i'm not damnit! -- Gotten beaten up: say whu? uh no.  -- Shoplifted: does taking extra napkins @ the restaurant count? -- Changed who you were to fit in: nope.  LAYER EIGHT:  -- Age you hope to be married: married at 21 -- Numbers and Names of Children: going for 3..no names decided yet -- Describe your Dream Wedding: i already had two beautiful ones. why ask for more? -- How do you want to die: peacefully & definitely not violently -- Where do you want to go to college: already graduated =) -- What do you want to be when you grow up: i'm already a web developer  LAYER NINE:  --drugs taken illegally: wasn't this asked already?  --people I could trust with my life: mama, hubby, heidi, big bro --CDs that I own: yikes..too many --tattoos: None yet..gonna get one soon.. --things in my past that i regret: why regret. learn from it & move on..everything happens for a reason =)  
      
</post>

<date>28,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      i hate the fact that i can't seem to express myself clearly. i hate the fact that when i'm upset & i'm trying to explain why i am, it comes out all wrong. i hate the fact that people will say stupid shit as a form of defense & i hate the fact that i get shit for what i feel. it's how i feel damnit, accept it. does anyone else out there feel the same way? who knows.   at this point, i'm just ready to isolate myself from the world because no one tries to understand who i am. they just make their pathetic assumptions. do i know who i am? yes & quite frankly, i don't give a rats ass if someone i don't know doesn't understand me, or thinks shit of me. what kills is when the people that i care about (or who i think care about me) don't even try to understand me. it's like, they've set these invisible expectations of who i am or who i should be. & if i don't meet any of them (or dare i say exceed), i'm not up to par.     sometimes i just imagine myself driving away from everything. every single friggin' thing. everything that i know, everything that i think i know, everything that i could come to know. from my family, to my friends, to society...just everything. i feel as if i should just hop on the next breeze & go. disappear. vanish.  but of course, it's not that easy....  sometimes, i wish it were....  
      
</post>

<date>27,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      well, ok it's actually my second. hehe. except THIS year, we're the one's making the thanksgiving feast. the LA famz are heading down, so the hubbs & i have been cooking all morning. no turkey (grocery stores on strike, ran out of turkeys, not a big fan anyway), but we do have a huge roast, mash potatoes (hope they like my version!), scalloped potatoes, steamed veggies & more =). should've picked up a pumpkin pie last night, but forgot. no biggie =). they've got white chocolate macadamia  & gingerbread cookies on the way. not your typical all american thanksgiving, but it's being with the family eating happily that makes it great.   what do i have to be thankful for this year? PLENTY.  1. another wonderful year spent with the hubbs. going on our 2nd year of marriage this coming march =).  2. my mama & tita.  3. my health 4. my friends 5. last but DEFINITELY not least, GOD. He is so good to me; so good to me & VJ. We are so lucky to have a loving & wonderful Lord.  I am so thankful for a lot of things, so much that I can't even name. To all those celebrating thanksgiving, may you all have a safe & wonderful day. *peace*
      
</post>

<date>26,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      1. puddle of mudd - come clean (their 1st album) 2. sarah mclachlan - afterglow 3. default - elocation 4. trapt - self titled (yes, it's kinda old)  so far that's all i can think of at the moment. i'm getting sick of hip hop, rap & r&b. i mean, some of the old songs out there i still love (jodeci's diary of a mad band album still rocks) & some new jams i like, but a lot of it is starting to sound the same. bleh. 
      
</post>

<date>25,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      ok, so me & the hubbs are looking for a male english bulldog puppy. we figure instead of having kids, we'll stick to plants, fish & dogs. heheh. THEN, when we're ready, we'll have a baby. hopefully in 2 years. if anyone knows of any sellers in & around san diego county, LET US KNOW!!! thanks =)
      
</post>

<date>25,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      ok i'm making my own up. sue me.     1. name three things in your fridge:  -ice tea -bottled water -champagne  2. name three things in your car:   -sweater -stress cow (all that traffic, yah know) -stock shift knob   3. name three things you wish you were doing right now:  -at home sleeping -at home watching dvd's with hubbs -snowboarding    yep i'm THAT unentertained.
      
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      handsome boy. he's just THE BEST. 
      
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      what's the deal?! yesterday, veej & i walked around the mall & alas, there was THE store. hehe. Hollister Co. i walked in, found a GRIP (no joke) of stuff that i wanted, got lost (damn store...so dark, so maze-like) and ended up having to leave empty handed. (good girl!) HOWEVER, as we found ourselves in suncoast, i found something i hadn't seen in AGES. kuya arnel, you have to remember this. TOTORO!!!!!!! heheh. yep, the kid in me came out & bought the dvd. it's hilarious. even veej thought it was funny (so i'm really not that crazy..haha).   anyhoo, found a few cell phones that i wanted to get. i swear, i'm having such a tough time deciding. at&t, verizon OR tmobile. urgh. veej & i currently have nextel & we've been off our year contract for a while now. and now that they have this thing where you can switch cell providers without having to switch numbers, we're all over it (like icing on a cake. hahahah. how corney). ugh...someone help me decide!! i like at&t cuz they've been around for a long time & people say they have the best service; best area, best plans; best phones. blablabla. but verizon seems just as good; great phones & great plans. tmobile, i'm a lil' sketchy, but the only reason why i'm thinking of them is because vj is gonna get a plan with them AND they offer unlimited mobile to mobile. *sigh*. such a predicament.   so i think i may be going with at&t, but if verizon can give me an even better deal, i'll go with them. but if all else fails, looks like it's gonna be tmobile!  on another note, it's sunday & the sun is shining so beautifully. (damn, i wanna go riding so bad) that's what i love about california. it's always sunny. i miss the cold weather; the rain & snow *sigh* but no worries. in a few weeks, we'll be up at big bear boarding...woo. yeah baby. 
      
</post>

<date>22,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      FRUSTRATED! ohmy. so we went to watch it tonight & it left me irritated. for those of you who have not seen it and would LIKE to see it, STOP READING NOW!  as i was saying, the matrix 3 wasn't as good as the first, nor was it better than the second. one thing i must admit though, it did not leave me hanging, which is a good thing. however, it just dragged on and on and friggin' on. get to the point. the storyline was alright, neo turned out to be the ONE. it wasn't a happily ever after for neo and trinity though, so that kind of sucked. but oh well. smith pissed me off. he was just toooooooo creepy looking. kinda like that guy from charlie's angels, the one who was also in that creepy movie willard. anyhoo....  i am not a reliable movie critic, so don't not see this movie. great effects, just toooooo long a movie.
      
</post>

<date>21,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      ben won! ben won! ben won! hehehe. he has now added the 2003 Supermoto Champion to his title. woo! the hubbs & regret even more that we didn't go. could've gone to the after party! ack. ohwell...next time...=)
      
</post>

<date>20,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      daaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaamnit all. we're missing the races in vegas. i feel like kicking myself right now. ugh. bleeeehhhhhhhh sooo frustrated. hahaha. wish i was there. then i could get my helmet signed AND a shirt AND (i'm really infatuated with the guy) my stomach. hahahahhaha. ya'll think i'm crazy. how can i not be?? check out his website:    urlLink ben bostrom        *rawr* *drool*   
      
</post>

<date>20,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      *meow*
      
</post>

<date>19,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I will NEVER understand the concept of why a husband will tell their wives "WHY CAN'T I HAVE A LIFE OF MY OWN??". seriously. It's quite the pathetic statement.  First off, understand that you MARRIED your wife & if you're really all gung ho about marriage, then you would understand that MARRIAGE is a life between TWO people and that whatever goes on in one's life, goes on in the other. Marriage is a union; TWO people becoming ONE. So, why are men so stupid when they say shit like that? I will never understand. I mean, ok, guys have their lil' manly man things as women have their girley girl things. But, does that really mean having a life of your own? It really irritates the hell out of me when I hear people going through shit like this. Let's just put it this way, why the hell did you get married when you want a life of your own? You shoulda just stayed a bachelor since that's how you want to live. Such a pity. 
      
</post>

<date>19,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      thursday. woo! happy day. today is my friday since i took the day off tomorrow. hmm, am i gonna see ben bostrom race in vegas this weekend? who knows. i would really really love to, but there are a few other duties we have to take care of.  mmmmmm. ben bostrom. *rawr*. hahahhahaha. yeah yeah, i'm married (& HAPPILY @ that) but even the hubbs acknowledges him as my "BF" hahahah. he was the one who started calling him that. hahahahah. what a goofball.   anyhoooooooo...i've been feeling pretty frustrated lately. a lot of stuff going on in my mind. homesick like a mofo, dying for snow, dying to go snowboarding, dying to see my family, just missing out. i was so used to being there, enjoying everything with them; the holidays, the first snowfall, karaoke nights, sushi every week, just EVERYTHING. i hate being so far away from them. i almost feel like i'm not part of the family anymore cuz i'm missing out on a lot. ehhh, ok not to that extreme, but close enough. and i've been irritated with certain daily duties, but ehh..it's a phase. i'll get over it. i gotta stop letting things like that get to me. bleh.  on a brighter note, thanksgiving is just around the corner. there's a fund raiser by a local radio station that's going to feed the hungry. $39 feeds 20 people. i think that's GREAT =).  i'm planning to donate, but i'm also hoping that a few of us will head down to the shelter to help out. it'll be quite the experience. we take things for granted all too often, and something like that, like my coworker said, is a definite eye opener. there are so many out there that are less fortunate than us & yet here we are complaining about what we don't have & blablabla. which remnds me of something the hubb told me a few weeks ago. during the wild fires, a homeless man won a great deal of money at one of the casinos. what did he do? he donated $25000 to help out the victims. he said the reason why he did it was because he wanted to help out all the san diegans who helped him when he was out on the streets. it just amazes me how people who are less fortunate tend to be the most generous. i don't know.  for me, i believe that being rich means you don't have to have an abundance of materialistic things. for me, being rich means not lacking anything in love, in life & in GOD.   sooooooooo, with that being said...happy thursday all. have a good day =) 
      
</post>

<date>19,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Soooooooo, my REAL website has been updated. hehe. goofy lookin' pic on the intro page. hehe.  Any updates? Well, let's see. Dying to go home to Vancouver to see the famz; our family Christmas party coming up on the 20th, but can't go due to other things going on. bleh. Then there's another christmas party in LA and I really really don't want to go. *crosses fingers* Yeah, don't want to see certain people & oh yeah, what's that? I don't get any respect from them anyway! Ehhh. 
      
</post>

<date>18,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Day two on this site...  Any new updates? Ha, not really. Been on this cooking binge. Not really eating, but just COOKING. I like to cook,  it's the clean up that's a butt. heheh. What can you do...  Uploaded the pics from our mini vacation to Vancouver for our 2nd Wedding Celebration. The one link is only of our NIGHT before the wedding. Yeah, we all got drunk...hmmm...good times though =)   urlLink Purple Onion   Oh yeah, THANKS REL & Kuya Rodel for hookin' it up...brings back good memz of clubbin' in my sweats..hahah BLEH...  
      
</post>

<date>17,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok, so I kinda got bored at work. Hmmm. Oh well...read on & if you want, copy & paste it & send it to all your friends. hahaha   I AM: "an-GEL-ica" NOT "an-ge-LEEEEK-a" I WANT: the new STi & a house I HAVE: 3 moles on my face I WISH: the troops back east were now home with their families I HATE: being so far away from home home (Vancouver) I MISS: my family in Vancouver... I FEAR: dying alone I HEAR: the printers going off I SEARCH: the web for a "Canadian Girls Kick Ass" tshirt I WONDER: what time I'll be off work today I REGRET: not spending more time with my dad before he died I LOVE: God, my family, my hubby & my friends I have yet to meet: more professional motorcycle riders...& BEN BOSTROM *rawr* again.. I ACHE: well i don't ache to, but I wanna go home... I AM NOT: going to give up on anything i aspire to have/want I DANCE: like there's no one watching I SING: when i wanna, but i haven't in a while.. I CRY: when i'm hurt, frustrated & when i'm homesick... I WIN: in Mario Party 4 I LOSE: in Backyard Football I NEED: coffee I SHOULD: stop shopping..but i won't. lol.   Would You Ever~ 1. Eat a bug? yeah...by friggin' accident. ew.  2. Bungee jump? hell yah...eventually 3. Kiss someone of the same sex? on the cheek yes, on the lips no... 4. Have sex w/someone of the same sex? what the...unless vj is wearing a dress, umm hell no... 5. Walk on hot coals? wha??  6. Go out w/someone based on looks? heheh uh...yeah..i did...& i ended up marrying him. lol. well, of course looks come first then personality..so yeah...hehe 7. Be a vegetarian? kindasorta. i can do without steak & pork...not chicken though. and veggies are a MUST.  8. Sing karaoke? hell yah. 4 hour karaoke...kuya rodel can vouch for that..lol...what were we thinking?!?! 9. Get drunk off your ass? hahhahahaha yup! right before our wedding reception in vancouver... 10. Shoplift? does sampling the candy thing count?? hahahah... 11. Run a red light? hell no.  12. Star in a porn video? hahahhahahhahah NO WAY! 13. Be on Survivor? nah.  14. Wear makeup in public? yuppers!. 15. NOT wear makeup in public? yep!  16. Cheat on a test? hahahha yeah. under my kilt in HS...heehee.. 17. Kick a baby? what the hell? 18. Date someone more than ten years older than  you? hahah no. & before i was married, i wouldn't have ruled that out either...lol.. 19. Stay up all through the night?  oh yah. back in hs & college..studying like there's no tomorrow...now? hardly ever...vj & i are "old" & married..hahah 20. Drink straight espresso? i don't remember. probably...
      
</post>

<date>17,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      i hate drama & i dislike the people that choose to have their lives revolve around it. it makes me sick to my stomach when i think about how some people just live in it, day in and day out. don't you LONG for a breath of fresh air?!?!??! ugh. yesterday i encountered someone who lived in that world. such a pity. whatever. live your life however you want. just don't mess up mine or my husbands. 
      
</post>

<date>17,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Soo, this is IT, huh?? I know I know, I have my own personal website (www.adeezines.com)..why don't I just use THAT? Well, I'm at work most of the time & I don't have the time to update it at home. Why not link it? Blah...I can do that later...heh.   
      
</post>

<date>29,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      at work, thinking about the past few days & the events that have happened throughout 2003. i can defintely say it's been an incredible year.  i don't want to sound as if i'm bragging, but from getting my dream car, to a new house, man oh man...there's a few off my goals list. i know that even though these things are material, i never would've  been able to obtain/accomplish  these things, (or doing anything for that matter) without GOD. i gotta say guys, GOD is GREAT. keep Him in your life, keep Him near you & you will NEVER go wrong.   on another note, my best friend is coming down!! woooo!!!
      
</post>

<date>26,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok, so I'm missing out on what's supposed to be the BEST shopping day ever. lol. Ah well, it's too CROWDED & crazy anyway..hehe  So, Wednesday we started moving & yesterday we cleaned out the apartment. VJ & I got to sleep in our house on the 24th but only in the living room AND on the futon. BUT, last night we got to sleep in our bedroom with the bed!! PRETTY COOL. I still can't believe it. Anyhoo, we're both tired from the past two days & we're deinfitely ready to just sleep, but there's still a lot of work to be done. Cleaning, unpacking & arranging..oh & PAINTING! We're gonna be painting the inside all weekend. Kinda exciting yet I know we're gonna be DRAINED. Ah well, I think we're buying one of those paint brush thingys VJ saw on an infomercial. hahahah. WTH!? Apparently it's supposed to do one room & 5 mins or something. heheh. We'll see...  Anyway, THANK YOU ALL to those who called & greeted us Merry Christmas. We're so sorry we weren't able to call or even email you guys cuz we lost our net & phone connection when we moved. I still have access here @ work, but we won't be reconnected until next Wednesday. Hope all of you are well & safe & we wish you ALL the best in the New Year. Love you guys!!! 
      
</post>

<date>24,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      You are now looking at two VERY proud HOMEOWNERS!!!!!!!! VJ & I have just closed escrow & are now proud owners of our VERY FIRST HOME!!!!! WOOOOOOO! Man, just the excitement of being a homeowner & not a renter anymore, is a great feeling. Overwhelming, but great nonetheless. We're moving TODAY & will be in our new home for Christmas =) To our family & friends, we will be sending you all information regarding our NEW addresses & telephone numbers. COME VISIT US!!!!!!!
      
</post>

<date>23,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      totally works. can't be mad when i'm smiling; smiling when i'm mad eases the tension. hehe. another great word of advice from a big brother?? you betcha =) thanks again kuya. 
      
</post>

<date>21,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       GREAT MOVIE . nuff said.    with other events, i'm growing rather impatient. i'm sick of run-arounds & bs. if you say one thing is gonna happen, make damn sure that it will. ugh. we're getting sick of it. 
      
</post>

<date>21,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       boarding withdrawals. ugh.     prospective ride:     am i gonna be a kawa girl?? maybe.
      
</post>

<date>20,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      i feel sick. i had some pizza & now i think i'm gonna hurl. why did i eat it? iono. i guess cuz hubbs asked to order & outta hunger i said yes. hahaha. sad. urgh. now my stomach feels queezy.   anyhoo, we bought our major appliances today =) we're hoping that everything goes well tomorrow and we get our "GIFT"!! it's exciting, stressing and overwhelming at the same time! what's next? a baby. =) when we're ready!!!!!!!!!!!!
      
</post>

<date>20,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      have you ever wanted something SOOO bad & would desperately do things to get it? yah, i did all i could yesterday to get our "GIFT", but it'll have to wait til MONDAY. ack. blargh. ugh. bleh. ok, i'm up way too early & it's a saturday. hubbs has duty. i miss him already. hahaha. ok, i'm gonna try to fall asleep again. heh. i want our "GIFT"!!!!!!!!!!! you'll all see what i'm talking about soon =)
      
</post>

<date>19,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      To my Ate Anne & Kuya Neil, CONGRATULATIONS on your ENGAGEMENT!!!!! VJ & I are SOOOO happy for you guys!! Soon, you'll be part of the married club =) WOOO!! Wherever you decide you want to have your wedding, we're there! (MAUI! MAUI! MAUI!). LOVE YOU GUYS!!
      
</post>

<date>17,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      a big pain in the ASS. HUGE. MASSIVE. for some, it worked, but for me, I got the short end of the stick. So to drop all that & have no more hassles (3 hour hold times on the phone, frustrating conversations & explanations, etc) I got a new number. Message me or email me to get the info. Barkada, I posted it on the family site, so you can pull it from there. AT&T still gets a thumbs up for being curteous & polite *knocks on wood* on the phone despite my ranting & raving due to 3-4 hour hold times. hehe. 
      
</post>

<date>15,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Soooooooo, hubbs & I went to the show yesterday. Had a BLAAAAAAST. Got good deals on a lot of stuff & most importantly, got to see the new line of MC's. I LOVE how the new R6 looks, but once I actually got to sit on it & experience the "feel' of it, I didn't really like it. Unless I've gotten weaker within the past few weeks, that bike felt like a damn brick. But, it could've been that since it was at it's normal height & not lowered like my bike, it was harder to handle. Less leverage? Who knows. Anyway, since I'm on my quest to sell my R6 *sniff* because we're trying to buy a new house (I prefer a house over a bike), I've since been looking at 250's. Hubby's scared for my life because he thinks I'm too small to be riding an R6. I think I'm just fine with it. BUUUUUUT, I checked out the new Ninja's & they're not too shabby. I wouldn't mind getting me one of those & since I'm not going to be doing any track days in the near future, a 250 would be GREAT =) Anyhoo, the "highlight" of yesterday was that I got a pic with Eric (no, not BEN..his BROTHER) Bostrom =) wooo! heehee.    
      
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      so i read my comments from my previous post about SECRETS. i couldn't help but LMAO when i read my kuya's comments...SUPER  BIATCH. hahahahhaha. i kinda like that. lol.
      
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      sometimes i sit and wonder what the deal is with couples & keeping secrets from each other.  it's really pathetic if you ask me. i hate it especially when married couples go through shit like that. it's like, what the hell? you're effin' married damnit. what kind of couple are you if you have to keep secrets from each other. it's like that other thing i brought up before. who the hell is a husband to say that he wants his own life when he's effin' married? i swear, the stupidity of these people. it's like, dude, why the eff did you propose?? dipshit.  & how on earth can you say that you have nothing to hide, when you're doing all the things to make the other person feel like you are hiding something? that's effin' stupid. you're giving them a reason to not trust you, asshole. ugh. i hate it when i hear about people going through this. it's not fair to anyone!
      
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      to all those who called, text, emailed, posted on boards, left a message, etc etc... to wish me a HAPPY BIRTHDAY... THANK YOU!!!!!!!! it meant SOO much to hear from all of you =) i love & miss you guys so much!!  thank you especially to VJ for the great bday gift (can't go wrong with a shopping spree!) & the wonderful dinner & movie. you say it's not much, but it meant the whole world to me because it came from you. love you.  
      
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      woke up. worked. went home. took a nap. ate dinner. played monopoly with the husbie. downloaded the trapt album (which i paid for by the way) from musicmatch.com. pretty cool program. only $9.99 for the whole album. i like it. worth it. plus it's not illegal =). tomorrow's another day. woo!
      
</post>

<date>30,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Our puppy is getting bigger each day. He was born on December 10th (he's a saggitarius like his mommy!) & is about 8 weeks old. He's a HAM. A handful, but a clever one too. No matter how hard we try to put a barrier around him, he gets out. Anyhoo, here's a few new pics of him:         yeah, he likes to sleep A LOT..kinda like us..hehehe..
      
</post>

<date>26,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      TGIF!!!!!!!! Week went by so fast, can't believe that it's going to be February ALREADY! Can't wait til next week! Headed up to Washington for Judy's 18th birthday  urlLink (www.jcbg.net)  & for some serious boarding time. WOOO!
      
</post>

<date>26,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      so, thanks to my cousins JAS & Rodel who got me hooked on this one song when i was little..i find out now that there's a REMAKE by forte & glenn medeiros....hahah..whoa!! it's pretty dope tooo!!  (now that i look over the lyrics, *getting mushy* this is dedicated to my HUBBY!! my wonderful wonderful VJ. love you babe!)   If I had to live my life without you near me  The days would all be empty  The nights would seem so long  With you I see forever oh so clearly  I might have been in love before  But it never felt this strong   Our dreams are young  And we both know they'll take us  Where we want to go   Hold me now  Touch me now  I don't want to live without you   Nothing's gonna change my love for you  You ought know by now how much I love you  One thing you can be sure of  I'll never ask for more than your love   Nothing's gonna change my love for you  You ought know by now how much I love you  The world may change my whole life through  But nothing's gonna change my love for you   If the road ahead is not so easy,  Our love will lead the way for us  Like a guiding star  I'll be there for you if you should need me  You don't have to change a thing  I love you just the way you are  So come with me and share the view  I'll help you see forever too    ahh the memories... 
      
</post>

<date>24,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      his name is  DUKE  & he's a 7 week old german shepherd puppy =) we just got him today, along with the necessities. he's definitely a handful, but he's our "baby". heehee. no REAL babies for us, YET!!! anyway, here's a few pics of the lil' booger:     
      
</post>

<date>23,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      darling nikki by the foo fighters. damn their music rocks.
      
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      good movie but not the greatest. let's put it this way, my mom & my aunt thought it was weird & vowed not to watch something like that ever again. hahaha. i, on the other hand, expected more suspense & more of a storyline. instead it got a few seat jumps & a blank stare. ashton kutcher, although i'm not a huge fan, didn't do too bad. he was pretty good @ being serious considering he's known for his goofy obnoxious side.   is it worth seeing? on dvd yes. theatre no. save your $$ for something else. perhaps mindhunters.
      
</post>

<date>20,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      i am NOW a verizon wireless customer. damn att. now i gotta cancel THAT service. blarrrrrrgh.
      
</post>

<date>19,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      i am so sick of AT&T Wireless. damnit all. watch out, new number on the way again. sorry guys. 
      
</post>

<date>19,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      day off. woo! didn't do much cept for buy our hood fan for our kitchen. it's coming along GREAT =) hubby is doing an awesome job. we'll show pics as soon as they're done.   tomorrow's another day. my mom & tita's stay is getting shorter & shorter. sucks. they're quite entertaining with their antics. they've done so much for us; they've helped us out with everything. sometimes i wish that i paid more attention to how they worked around the house when i used to live back home. get a few pointers here & there, but i guess it all really comes with experience. they've taught us a lot these past few weeks.   anyhoo, saw some of the cousins yesterday. came by to say hello (hello! washingtonians!) & to take a look at the house. it's not all done yet, sorry!! anyhoo, it felt nice to see our godson & his mama. we miss you jas, aj & al!  okie dokie, til the next entry...no big updates....oh yeah, my website hasn't been touched in AGES, i know, but i'll be fixing it soon...hopefully...   
      
</post>

<date>18,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hit up LA this weekend. saw my side of the famz, good times, good laughs..omg they're so loud! haha. our family is always loud, but it's the GOOD loud. full of shouts of laughter. after, hubbs & i did some shopping & met up with good friends, had some good eats (thanks pauline for the hookup! i think i need to see the fetish product line!!) & good laughs. trying to meet up & see our Godson & his mom later tonight..vj misses the lil' guy. can't wait til we head up to washington. dyiiiiiiiing to get new boarding pants & dyiiiiiiiiing to get on the powder. make my own tracks again! all day boarding? 8 hours or more? you bet.   holiday tomorrow. resting much? haha...probably not. ah well.
      
</post>

<date>16,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        You have a dominant kiss- you take charge and make sure your partner can feel it! Done artfully, it can be very satisfactory if he/she is into you playing the dominant role MEORW!    urlLink   What kind of kiss are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    hahaha. *rawr* 
      
</post>

<date>14,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      so, I FINALLY got my bike back. it looks sooooooo dope. i almost don't want to sell it. i tried riding it, but i was a bit wobbly since i haven't been riding in a LONG time. vj's still convinced i should get a 250 & i pretty much agree since A) i don't ride my bike as much B) it's a waste of power  (not riding a 600 to it's full capacity is definitely a waste) C) he thinks i'm too little for it. C, i don't fully agree cuz i think i can handle it, but oh well. I LOVE MY BIKE!!!! grrr.
      
</post>

<date>14,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      blargh. my comments through blogspeak aren't working. so i've changed it using haloscan. blaaaah.   btw, GO & WATCH something's gotta give (jack nicholson & diane keaton)...great movie. 
      
</post>

<date>13,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      worth seeing or not? well, hubbs & i got free tickets to a pre-screening of the movie last night. all in all, it was ALRIGHT. we were actually IN the movie as extras, but only if you look hard enough, will you be able to see us. in this other scene you can see vj running through the crowd. pretty funny. actually we were the only ones in the theatre laughing our asses off. haha. anyway, movie was like i said, ALRIGHT. a bit too overdramatic in some scenes, and yes, definitely a movie you should wait for to come out on dvd.   anyway, after the movie our friend gets the worst news. his bike (a honda rc51) got stolen; along with another guy's chromed out suzuki. what's weird about our friend's bike, is that when arrived at the theatre, we saw it parked. and it's not like it was in an isolated area either. it was right between two cars in a  regular parking spot. we felt so bad for him. apparently this year (or last-2003) was the last year for the RC51's. ugh. anyway, we gave him a ride home. poor thing.  thank you so much to SEAN who not only hooked us up with the torque tickets, but also gave us pre-screenings to MIRACLE, a hockey movie and the BUTTERFLY EFFECT with ashton kutcher. woo!  i'm still coughing like there's no tomorrow. damnit. 
      
</post>

<date>09,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      leading a double life, eh? rather pathetic if you ask me. why the hell don't you just grow up & face up to your real responsibilites?
      
</post>

<date>08,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      my voice has flown the coop. vanished. kaput. adios. sayonara. you get the picture. i squeak when i talk. lovely.   so, yes i have changed my cell number AGAIN. why? because my old number sucked. anytime someone would call, it would say it's not in service, when it very well WAS. people had to call literally 10 times just to get through to me. it continued for a good while until i said screw it, gimme a new phone AND a new number. FREE. and they did. i have been so patient with everything. from port failures, to jacked up numbers, to ugly phones, just too much. but why do i put up with it? they're good.   anyway, the house is coming along. sorry guys, still no pics. we have the before pictures, but we're not gonna post em until we have the AFTER ones (sorry Jas!). all we need to do is paint the master bedroom & the master bathroom and complete the kitchen and we're done. cleaning things here & there, but yeah, basically we're finito. lowes, home depot, walmart & of course IKEA, have definitely become the hot spots these past few weeks. almost done!   it feels good to be able to say, we OWN a home. i love it.
      
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      OMG. again. yep. familia/friends..i'll be emailing you the new number. at least this time, i have a good phone. 
      
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      to our perfect home =) on monday my mom, tita, vj & i headed to ikea to finalize the plans for our kitchen. gosh, i can't even begin to say how unbelievably THANKFUL i am to my mommy. she BOUGHT us our kitchen. OMG. it wasn't as expensive as the other places (home depot & lowes-thank GOD), but it was still a HUGE gift from her. she said it's our bday & christmas gift. heehee. since they got here, they've been buying things for us left & right. & it's like STOP! of course we can't be more grateful, but they're here to VISIT not to spend. they're soooo sweet.   anyway, the kitchen being delivered on friday. can't wait!
      
</post>

<date>04,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      our betta's died. =( i guess the moving was too much for them. saaaaad *sniff*. wrecks was the one we had the longest (a year), then came red, pink, pinky & then goku. pink commited suicide by jumping out of the tank & into vj's shoe (lol), red fought too much, goku got sick & then wrecks & pinky got stressed out during the move. poor things. oh well. 
      
</post>

<date>02,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      first off, THANK YOU so much to my bro vincent & his gf minette for coming down to help us paint. secondly, i can never be more grateful to my mama & tita for helping us with cleaning & painting & JUST EVERYTHING. those two are wonderwomen, crazy sisters who are always there when i need them. i love you mama & tita!!!  soooo, today was filled with an obscene amount of painting & cabinet ripping. the guys handled that while the women painted & cooked (thank you tita). VERY VERY TIRING. it's coming together slowly; all we need is our brand spankin' new kitchen. *sigh*.   ooooooooookie, thank you all again!
      
</post>

<date>02,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      i want our brand spanking new kitchen put in asap. ugh.   yes, today i am feeling very impatient. and now, i'm starting to get a cough. blargh.
      
</post>

<date>02,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      so, family is supposed to stick together through thick & thin, right?? well well well. my family is WONDERFUL, no doubt, except for ONE. i'm so tempted to name her on here, but i won't. let's just say she's the oldest, she has a younger sister AND two younger brothers. her mom is a bitch & her poor dad (who is my relative) is stuck. so, this girl, goes around telling her mom that i taught her how to shoplift. WTF!??! shoplift?! are you effin' INSANE? my ass is too scared to do that crap, let alone shortchange a cashier!! i admit it!!! for fack's sakes, don't be spreading rumours about me especially since youre a lying, cheating (yes, your man V should know that you cheated on him with FRANCIS who btw, is our RELATIVE..you sicko...AND you're NOW cheating on him with NORMAN) bitch who has nothing better to do than to hate on me. i may be stooping to your level by writing this in here, but bitch BACK THE FUCK OFF. what the hell is your problem?? don't even be spreading rumours about our other relatives, cuz i know that you are. you need to stop. BOTH you AND your sorry ass mother need to stop. don't get mad at the rest of the family or blame anything on the family when its you guys who fuck everything up. tell your mom to stop blaming other people for YOUR mistakes. trust me, it's all gonna come back  to bite you guys in the ass. 
      
</post>

<date>01,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      happy new year everyone!!! vj & i wish you all the best in the new year!!!   yay! my mama & tita are here!!
      
</post>

<date>29,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      okie dokie, guess i should update this...hmmm...  well, the past few days have been pretty crazy. with month's end & trying to close out client loans, my ass has been busy with work. on friday, we had a going away party @ gordon biersch & omg, i have not drunk so much in so long. err, let me rephrase that. i have been told i am a lightweight & by the looks of how much i drink (2 shots of tequila = buzzin hard, 1 honkin' swirl from on the border = drunk as an effin' skunk, 1 beer, 2 shots, 1 martini = goner, etc etc) i can only take so much. anyway, we had a blast but it was sad to see a good friend leave. after that, hubbs drove me & my drunk butt around town cuz we didn't feel like going home. he laughed at my comments about basically everything & was so patient when i insisted that i was a fatty back in the day. i dunno, don't ask. heheh. i was drunk remember!??!   saturday headed out to the beach for another going away party & then headed up to LA for a bike night @ camachos. ended up winning 2 new pairs of motorcycle gloves & 2 mc stunt dvd's, along with a free shirt that hubbs caught. it was pretty cool seeing all these bikes, but i dunno, it seemed too ghetto & too "biker boys-ish" for us, so we bounced. met up with a few friends & had a few drinks. headed to the inlaws for an early morning wake up.   sunday-today, headed back with both puppies duke & poncho in tow. straight to hooters to watch the season start of the world superbike races. absolutely awesome. i love watching mc races & pretty soon (i'm hoping), my ass will be on a track practicing. not plannin' on making racing a big part of my life, but enough so i get my license & some discounts & enough to get some adrenalin rushes during the snowboarding off season.   now we're home & we've just cleaned out the backyard & most of the house. we're POOPED! this week is gonna be a long one!
      
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      har har...messin' around again...  
      
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ok, this whole storm watch thing for san diego is a joke. it's funny cuz here i am, born & raised in vancouver, hometown to rain, snow, sleet, hail, etc etc & i'm listening to people freak out about some showers. yes there were some moments where it just poured like a mofo, but a storm!?  i understand the whole flooding & landslide thing, cuz yes that is a very serious issue. but when all hell breaks loose because of rain? wow. it's pretty funny. you haven't seen anything until you live up north. hehehe.   anyhoo, this weekend was pretty cool. saturday was filled with CLEANING! cleaned the house & kitchen, hubbs cleaned out most of the garage & mowed the lawn (with duke barking & chasing the mower..haha) & then came the down pour. darnit. so, i decided to dye my hair back to it's natural colour & man i'm HAPPY. no more streaks! no more roots! just jet black =). hit up the gulls game shortly after (thank you sean for the socalriders sweatshirt & the free sample shoes!! yah baby!) & unfortunately they lost. grr. watched the 50cc races which wasn't exactly that entertaining. i mean, it was funny but it could've lasted longer. but yeah...  yesterday we did JACKSHIAT. we were slammed with rain so we stayed in & played with duke. gave him a bath, threw him on the couch with us & watched daredevil. i still think ben affleck wasn't the best lead for that movie. so yep, we were chillin' on the couch the entire day yesterday. it was the best. hehe.   blaaaaaaaaah, now we're back to work & i find out that where i'm at is prone to flooding. aah. i shoulda taken hubby's truck. 
      
</post>

<date>21,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      i've been doing a lot of thinking about where i stand in my life & where i want to go. i've accomplished a lot of goals, gratuated college, married my dream man, bought my dream car, bought a house, got a dog & so forth. but sometimes, i still feel like there's something missing. like, i feel as if i should be closer to home. when i went back to visit a few months ago, i realized i have missed out on so much. i feel guilty.   vj's duty here in san diego is almost up & we're both trying to figure out what to do. we definitely have agreed that we don't want him back on a ship. most importantly, we don't want him on a ship that goes on 8-9 month deployments. for me, i would give anything to move back to the pacific northwest. i would love to be so much closer to home to be able to see my family, to be able to celebrate birthday's, christmas, various other holidays, & even just to go over for dinner. i also wouldn't mind moving to las vegas, which is another location we're considering moving too. it'd be cool. we've already looked at houses & the community where we'd hope to move to would only be 15 mins away from the strip. the weather extremes would be a challenge but i ask myself, what challenge have i come across that i haven't successfully overcome? so as cliched as it sounds, i say bring it on. oh & the best part about vegas, it's approx. 30 mins away from the sierra mountains, which means  SNOWBOARDING!!! .   we've got some time to think about things still, but as it stands, my heart is set on 2 places. the pacific northwest or las vegas. 
      
</post>

<date>20,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      it's finally FRIDAY!!! despite the fact that this week was short due to the president's day holiday, it still felt just as long as a regular week. slammed @ work. insanity. anyhoo, tonight, hubbs & i might check out 50 first dates. i heard it was really good, but i also am still dying to see miracle. hockey movie, go figure =) heehee. speaking of hockey, we're plannin' on hittin up a gulls game tomorrow night & right after, there's gonna be a 50cc race on the ice! heehee. that's gonna be one dope sight. grown men on mini bikes racing around on ICE. hehehe. anyhoo, our baby is getting bigger everyday. we weighed him in at 16lbs on tuesday. he gained 10lbs since we first got him. he's gonna be a big boy! oooooookie, my ass has to get back to work....
      
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      friday = vegas, blueman group, drunk hubby & friends, 3am strip walkin saturday = strip walkin, 45 min drive to BFE - pahrump, nv, sweet date with the hubbs,  sunday = track day in pahrump,  45 min drive BACK to civilization - las vegas, nv, late night chillin' with ice cream & cookies monday = visit the famz, CHUBBY BEBEH! lauren angelica..heehee, 4 hour drive BACK to LA, pick up our bebeh, duke big doggie! 2 hour drive home tuesday = ass back to work...tired *yawn*  thanks babe for such a great weekend! i can't wait til you get your race license! me next! me next! heehee... 
      
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      to all of you!!!! Hope you all have a great weekend =) I'm off to Vegas! Yah baby!
      
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      i feel so faaaaaaaaaaat. i'm a fatty. hahah. ew.
      
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      quick description: i'm asian, which basically entails: short, black hair, small eyes...nuff said  Best Date:  he drove 2 hours to get me, took me to the mall cuz he knew i liked to shop, he took me to the movies to watch what i wanted & we ended it with a long conversation on the porch @ 4am which he topped off with the most amazing kiss. =)  My personality: enthusiastic, corney, bubbly, occasionaly anal retentive (hahaha) & passionate & compassionate, i shop in spurts, & umm yah.  What Others Notice: you tell me =)  Lived: born & raised in vancouver, bc but now living in san diego, california =)  Organizations: nasioc  iclub clubwrx socalriders  Pet Peeves:  fake people ignorant asses constant negativity  Humor:  uh, what's it like? different.  Whats on my mind:  i wanna go home cuz i'm tired, but i don't wanna go home cuz i gotta clean the house. haha. damn. oh yeah, i'm on my shopping spurt, so i wanna shop like there's no tomorrow.
      
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      so, if any of you haven't noticed, i took down my website. why? cuz it was gettin' old. nothing was being updated, mainly because i've been SO busy & cuz well, lack of motivation. so now, i'm trying to come up with layouts for my new site, but nothing's working! blaaaaah.   anyway, hit up the socalriders bike night last night @ the doubletree. good food, good company, nice bike vids. scary how some of these people perform their stunts. eegaah. thanks sean for the tickets to the prescreening of hidalgo =). gotta love free shizz!   i'm tired as hell. i've been hittin' the off button on the alarm for the past few days & i've been waking up to hubby's alarm. despite my extra half hour, i still manage to be sleepy during the day & i still come home & hit the sack for an hour to 2 hour nap. ehhh.  
      
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      one of the pics we (err, eric)  took of us while we visited bainbridge island...   
      
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ok, so it began & it ended. our not so long enough trip back to the pacnorthwest! we had a blast & it had been a while since we went back. humm, let's see...   wed  left san diego around 4, arrived in seattle around 7; met up with eric & ate at bush gardens (no karaoke for me, thank you!); watched mystic rising play..damn they're good; had a few drinks & headed up to vancouver;   thurs  arrived around 1am, friends & kuya came over (thanks for the timmy ho's jolico & gian!); no sleep til 5am; woke up around 11 to get ready for boarding @ cypress; breakfast/lunch at moms-can't beat longonisa & eggs! breakfast of champions i tell you; boarding for a good 5 hours-had originally planned on boarding the entire day, but we decided that we had other things to do & dinner to eat; great conditions on the mountain; only a handful of people; makin' donuts in the park avenue in the parking lot (crazy hubby!); dinner with the famz; practice at our place; no sleep til 4am;   fri late wake up; hospital to visit my uncle ( RIP Jacinto De Grano =/ ); lunch @ daimasu-ordered what seemed like everything on the menu; headed back down to seattle; crazy shoppin' @ aeropostale; dinner @ ivars..mmm gooood;  hook up with the famz; sleepin' in mukilteo (muh-kill-tay-yo!); no sleep til 4am;   sat  late wake up again; headed to the base to help out; headed down to seattle to check out ducati seattle; scored a shirt & a toy model bike for the hubbs; headed back to get ready & bounced to marysville to get the famz; back to the base for the bash; last minute practices; unorganized emcees! john & i had no practice-hahaha; more than words  & don't change revamp performance-awesome!; dope performances by the entourage; partyin' til midnight; back to mukilteo then back to marysville for late night chillin'; no sleep til 5am; back to mukilteo;    sun  late wake up; downtown seattle to bainbridge island; saw eric again & his dope place-right on the waterfront!; ferry ride back; quick dinner with the guys @ ivars; back to sea-tac; 720 flight didn't leave til an hour later; late arrival in san diego; late sleep....  and now my ass is home & back to work...pictures of our lil' trip will be posted soon =)  weekend went by too fast! can't wait til we head back to vancouver...dunno exactly when, but we're looking to next month to celebrate our 2 year anni in whistler! yah baby...  
      
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      7 more hours til our butts are on the plane. i can't waaaaaaaaaiiiiiiit!!! horry sit! all packed & ready to go baby.  anyhoo,for anyone that's interested in sending me text  send em to AJ80@vtext.com   urlLink Send me a TEXT! 
      
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      one more day (well, day & a half) & vj & i will be on our way to Washington State =) wooooo! & then a few hours after that, we'll be headed up to VANCOUVER!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! yah baby!! & of course, as mentioned below, we'll be snowboarding!!!!!!!!!!!! woooooooooooooooooo! so *ahem*, i'm excited. every time we head up north, i get happy =) mainly because we'll be in my neck of the woods and cuz my family is there! yay =)   anyhoo, i just found out  our cutie patootie Godson has his first tooth coming in. go Logan!
      
</post>

<date>02,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        happy 18th birthday to my beautimous neice JUDITH CHRISTA BIHIS GUTIERREZ!!  you're so grown up now!!!   wow, it's FEBRUARY already! time flies. next month, vj & i will be celebrating our two year wedding anniversary. whoa. time REALLY flies. we're debating on eating lobsters all weekend in mexico, or snowboarding like mad in whistler. hmm, what do you guys think i'm gonna choose? duh.  SNOWBOARDING . seriously, i've become obsessed with the sport. yah so?!?!??! heh.
      
</post>

<date>02,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      sooooo, this weekend was the superbowl. interesting, although i did fall asleep during part of it. ah well. we got a new chihuahua puppy this weekend, a christmas gift from my mom in law. sooo cute!! i named him poncho the moment i saw him. duke isn't really taking to him very much, he's already tried to bite him. pretty funny cuz they're the same age, but they're sooo different in size. duke's gotten so huge since we got him...i miss him!!! we left the two babies in LA cuz we're headed out to washington & vegas for the next two weekends & we can't take em. can't wait though!!! boarding the thursday we're there..wooooo...definitely gonna release some tension. make my own tracks? possibly. depends on whether or not some areas have been touched. bleh. sooooooo yeah, vegas the next weekend. blue man group, track day, extra day off (woo! presidents day!)...yah baby. got a call yesterday from my kuya..i've got lead?!?! are you sure i can handle that? lol...okie dokie =) i'm down!
      
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      well this weekend was pretty dope. hit up mexico to celebrate a few of our friend's birthday. the weather was AWESOME. sooo beautiful & warm! kicked it at the beach for a while, did a bit of sun tanning and sun "BLOCKING" (avoiding the sun). i hadn't been to mexico since i was 8 so i was pretty excited. it's definitely a different lifestyle down there. a lot of stuff we normally couldn't do in the US could be done there. ie: a pick up carrying a bunch ppl in the back with alcohol, shooting fireworks at cop cars & riding around on the back of a jet ski while being towed to the beach & the best one, DRIVING ON the beach & parking there while surfing. yep, you got it. our friend lives a block away from the beach & he literally took his bronco down this extremely steep & rocky hill to get to the sand & drove it around as if it were his playground. it was awesome. kinda scary, but still awesome. anyway, when we first scoped out the waves we noticed this other truck stuck in the sand. we passed it, went back up the hill & when we came back IT WAS ON IT'S SIDE. no joke. it blocked our passage to the beach for a good 30 mins. but thanks to the great mexican tow truck drivers (man, those guys can DRIVE) we got back down to the beach. we chilled there for a good 3 hours & headed back for some grub on the grill. lots of craziness, lots of alcohol, lots of laughs.  it was a GREAT weekend! thanks kevin for being a great host =)
      
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        HAPPY TWO YEAR WEDDING ANNIVERSARY TO THE MOST WONDERFUL MAN ALIVE!   I love you babe! 
      
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      friday-hit up the dog beach @ coronado w/ hubbs, duke & poncho. pretty cool place. duke refused to go into the water & poncho just waddled around. the other dogs showed up a while after & duke barked like a mofo. he's not used to being around other puppies/dogs (besides poncho), so he goes a bit crazy. ay. anyhoo, after the beach we watched starsky & hutch. crazy ass funny movie. go watch it!! saturday/sunday-cleaned the house, steam cleaned the carpets, cleaned all the bedrooms, cleaned out the garage & bought us a new toy. hehehe. for those of you that'll be comin' over will know. lol.   & now it's back to the daily grind. urgh. gonna hit up the doggie beach again. yay! let's just hope duke doesn't go bonkers again. hehe
      
</post>

<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ok, here's a pic...mebbe it's a bit too short? nah! it's just hair! it'll grow back =)    
      
</post>

<date>09,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      yep, i went & got my hair chopped off =) it now sits on my shoulders, well just barely touches. hehehe i'll post pics up soon, but if anyone is really that interested, my cut is very similar to that of amy smart, the girl on the cover of this month's lucky magazine (that's what i used as my example)
      
</post>

<date>09,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hmm well let's see. weekend consisted of cleaning, more cleaning, "teaching" the pups to swim in our pool, organizing the kitchen, cleaning the garage, walking the pups, & watching the passion of the christ.   what to say about the movie? absolutely moving. i have definitely changed my outlook on life & i must admit, i've changed my outlook on my faith & my belief. the intensity of the movie woke me up & shook me around a bit & it made me realize that despite the fact that we as a whole did not witness the sacrifice our saviour made for us, it DID happen. i mean, i knew it happened, i grew up knowing it happened, i grew up knowing about the sacrifice, but i didn't quite understand or even appreciate the intensity. i cried during & after the movie & even when i was at home. so for any of you who are skeptical to watch this spectacular film, please don't be. i urge you to go & watch it. but please don't go in there expecting action, bombs dropping or any of that hollywood crap. instead, go in there with an open mind & an open heart.   anyway, that's basically all we did this past weekend. the pups are so cute. they can swim! duke kinda learned by accident, i think. i guess he jumped onto the tarp which was covering part of the pool & in he went. he swam out though & he doesn't seem to mind it. poncho on the other hand, learned by force. hehe. vj just plopped him in & let him swim. i think he liked it cuz he wasn't crying or anything. soooooo yeah, our life basically consists of organizing & cleaning the house & coming up with new ways to improve it to make it more VJ & AJ like. lol. we're thinking of painting our garage a whole whack of different colours to make it more interesting. possibly match our bikes & our cars. hahahah.   okie dokie, gotta get back to work. duke's got a dr. appt today along with obedience class! yay! he's got sit, down & come pretty good, and now we're working on the ROLL OVER! lol.  
      
</post>

<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      and i can't stress how happy i am that it is. this week went by fast, but just like the past few weeks, i've been busy!!!! nothing much really to update except my joy that it's friday. hahah. duke & poncho are definitely keeping us busy. on tuesday, hubbs & i had a puppy training class for duke. they gave us pointers about how to potty train & discipline duke, but he's ok with the potty thing. he pretty much knows where to go *knocks on wood* & right now, he knows how to sit & lay down. the two boys crack me up though. poncho seems to have this napoleon complex. he'll bite & growl @ duke & duke will sit on him to hush him up. hehehe. crazy ass dogs.   anyway, this weekend we're pretty much wingin' it. shoot, i think we do that just about every weekend. can't wait til april b/c we're heading to fontana for the ama races & we'll be heading to vegas roughly 2 weeks after for another track day in pahrump-a-dump.   ok, gotta get my ass back to work. *snarf* 
      
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      he makes my heart SMILE. no one else has EVER been able to do that. 
      
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      well, it's sunday evening & the weekend is just about over. what'd we do? uh, nothing besides clean & organize. friday we watched the girl next door at the drive in. dude, that was dope. we haven't done that in a long while & it was good to just go out & lounge in our car with a movie. movie was pretty good, funny & very ummm, sexual. heehee. s'all good, we're married! lmao.   anyhoo, saturday we cleaned & cleaned; the house, the cars, the dogs, everything. sunday, chilled, more cleaning, and more chillin'. dude, this weekend was filled with nothing but chillin' & cleanin..it's all good =) dinner..mmm..fajitas & the fixin's (me no eat tortillas...mine was a nekkid fajita), fresh salsa, black beans, veggies, mmmmmmmmm bomb. i love to cook! i think hubby does too, but he'd rather eat than cook. hehe. how's the south beach thing going? pretty good. i'm still not really into it just yet, still reading (yeah, i'm taking my time, plus i'm trying to clean out all the fruit so i don't get tempted for the two weeks of phase one). i'm pretty cool with the no carbs thing, but i admit, i've been tempted to indulge myself with a peanut butter & jam sammich. heehee.   anyhoo, i guess that's about all for now. i'm lookin' forward (well not really) to another hectic weekend. gotta close all my loans!
      
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      yesterday one of our boys, DUKE, graduated from puppy obedience school =) he's a bit stubborn still but he was able to complete all the testing. he seemed to love the lil' tube thing he had to go through, so much so that he went in a few times. heehee. our lil' ham hock =).   anyhoo, so as i said in my previous entry, i'm somewhat on the south beach diet (i'm not gonna be on it completely until i'm done reading the book). yesterday killed me. i cut out a lot of the stuff i normally eat ESPECIALLY the coffee. i switched to decaf & i got headaches!! i also felt extremely tired & cranky. today wasn't so bad, but i'm still pretty tired. anyhoo, hubbs is now gonna start doing the diet with me becuase i'm really concerned about his health. his family has a history of heart problems & i want him to start changing his eating habits. he's willing to do it, i just gotta cook the food. no probs there =).   okie dokie, guess that's all for now. since i booked our flight back home, i've been thinking of things that i want to do. 1. walk around stanley park (vj wants to ride a bike..uh, we'll see). 2. go to victoria 3. see the family 4. eat at all my favourite restaurants & umm yeah, PARTY!   i'm ready to go home now. hehe  
      
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ok, so i haven't written in this thing for a while, sue me. i've been busy! lol. from cleaning the house, to parties, to track days, to overtime @ work, my bootay hasn't been able to keep up with this. anyhoo, what's been going on? well, besides the aforementioned, i've been TIRED. exhausted with everything, the daily grind & the trips, u name it. but it's all good =) i'm happy & excited to head back home!   hmm, what else? well i've just started reading the south beach diet & yes, i'm gonna start doing it. i'm not fully engaged in the diet just yet because i haven't finished reading the book, however i am starting to cut out a lot of things that i'm not supposed to eat. yes, i have to completely cut out carbs for two weeks & no fruit (sucks ass) but then i get to bring it all back (slowly & attentively) after that. now, before any of you guys start yelling at me telling me i'm crazy, let me tell u some of the reasons WHY i'm on this diet. 1. my mom has diabetes & it's hereditary. this diet helps u learn, control & manage your sugars, fats & carbs. it basically does a 180 to your system. 2. i want to drop a FEW pounds. 3. i want to start eating healthy again (since i got married, despite the fact that i've maintained most of my healthy eating, i started to dabble with bad foods). 4. i want to remain healthy as i grow old & by starting these better eating habits NOW, i'll live a longer happier life =) heehee. but yeah, in all seriousness, i'm not doing it to just lose weight, i'm doing it to get off the path that might lead me to diabetes.   so yeah. i'm drinking decaf coffee & i'm getting a headache. it's cool, i gotta get off my caffeine dependancy anyway.   eeeeeeeeeeeks, i can't wait to head home to vancouver!!!!!!! i'm excited!!!!!! yay!
      
</post>

<date>07,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      3 personality traits of yours  1) determined  2) friendly  3) compassionate   3 of your chillin' spots  1) bedroom  2) living room  3) computer room    3 of your best girls   1) heidi  2) lori  3) jackie    3 of your best guys  1) my hubbs  2) my kuya rodel  3) ben bostrom..lol  3 songs you like  1) darlin' nikki by foo fighters  2) control by puddle of mudd  3) cold hard bitch by jet   3 places you've worked before  1) superstore (hated it)  2) intuit  3) eaton's (whoa old!)    3 of your online buddies   1) heidi  2) jas  3) umm, a lot of my cousins..   3 brands you dislike or would not wear  1) fubu  2) sean john  3) phat farm   3 brands you wear  1) abercrombie  2) hollister  3) american eagle   3 feelings you are feeling  1) i wanna go home  2) tired  3) fed up  3 things you are looking forward to   1) my trip back home to vancouver in june  2) my trip to vegas in april AND may  3) going home to bed..  3 drinks  1) water  2) ice tea  3) diet pepsi, although it kills my stomach..urgh   3 schools you've attended  1) langara  2) bcit  3) mti   3 things you did this weekend  1) cleaned the house  2) watched the friggin' lilo & stitch marathong (hubbs was working)  3) went to the AMA races in fontana..ben bostrom..*rawr*   3 things you are doing right now  1) working on closing 4 loans  2) working on opening 7 loans  3) wondering what or where i'm gonna eat  3 wishes you have for the near future  1) buy another house  2) get another subu, this time the STi  3) have a baby...umm yeah..lol
      
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      we're headed home june 10th-16th! wooohoo!! 
      
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      #98 Honda Racer, Jake Zemke!     
      
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Despite the fact that this weekend is not over, a whole lot of shizzo went on. Friday night, went out with the coworkers for a goodbye ol' boss, hello new boss party. Had a blast! Drank only THREE drinks but damn, that was good enough to get me drunk. Uh, Stoli Vanilla & diet Coke, bloody mary & a red headed slut shot..mmmm. bomb. Anyhoo, because I was wayyyy too drunk to head home (shutup, i know i'm a lightweight), the girls & I headed over to Roy's to sober up. Got the hookups for some bomb ass grub! Thanks Sandy & Evan! Anyhoo, ended up home later that night & knocked out. Sorry hubby!  Saturday was filled with pretty much nothing. Cleaned a bit & then just played with the doggies. Hubby had duty so we weren't able to go out that night, no biggie.   Sunday-today; BOMB! Headed up to Fontana to watch the MC races. mmmm, Ben Bostrom. Unfortunately, I wasn't able to get a picture with him because he was in his gear & was gettin' ready to race, but I did get a pic with Jake Zemke (#98 Honda rider). He was pretty cool, nice & all & he's half flip! heehee. Hubbs got a few good pics of the race while I tried to avoid the sun (I forgot my sunblock! argh!) & a few of "my man", Ben. He didn't make the podium, but he did make #5. S'all good! Anyhoo, pics of Fontana will be posted soon. 
      
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      april fool's. i'm not prego, YET! heehee. to all those who emailed, sorry guys! lol..    HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO MY MOMMA! LOVE YOU MA!   
      
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      there's a lot of stuff running through my mind about what lies ahead for us. we have choices & options, but it's definitely very very overwhelming & scary when it comes to thinking about whether or not we've made the right decision. are we willing to give up some of the stuff we've worked so hard for? at the present time, no. there's other options that won't necessarily cause us to do the aforementioned. but who knows. one thing is set in my mind. whatever happens happens. it's an experience. it'll be a part of life that will help us grow & be strong. no matter how you look at it, there's a reason behind it & as long as we continue to put our faith in God, we'll be just fine.   sooooooooooo, with other news & totally & utterly not related to the above....   I'm gonna be a mommy =)
      
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      yep, i'm sick. i've been sick since saturday & it hit me really bad on monday. got off work at noon on monday with plans to meet up with my cousins & to take out my kuya, but the moment i got home, i knocked out & slept til 4pm. by that time, i had developed a fever, got the chills, aches & pains & nausea. didn't get out of bed often, only to get water or to go banjo. tuesday called in sick, felt like craaaaaaaaaap and slept almost the entire day. wednesday (today), called in sick again cuz i was really dizzy, felt more nauseated, more chills & more aches. went to the doctor & i'm now on meds. bleh. i'm feeling a tad bit better, more dizzy than normal, but so far my aches have dissipated. i owe my wonderful dr. hubby a huge thank you cuz he's taken care of my sick ass so lovingly. heehee. he checked on me constantly, made sure i took my tylenol, made me drink my fluids and made me eat even when i wasn't hungry. he went out & got me my fruits & OJ (despite the fact that i hate oj, but i made him buy me some cuz i needed the extra vitamin c) & he even punas (kinda like a sponge bath, but no sponge, just a cold towel with water & a bit of rubbing alcohol) me to cool my body off. the worst part of my fever finally broke tuesday morning, but i was still somewhat feverish the rest of the day. i'm back to work tomorrow (phew!) and hopefully i'll be feeling 100% then too. i hate being sick & i especially hate going to the dr. i'll only go if i really need to, otherwise just point me to the nearest drugstore for some OTC meds. anyway, that's basically all that's been happening in my world. sorry kuya rodel for not taking you out as much while you were here. glad you had fun eating lots though, since that's all that we really did anyway. heehe. see you in a few weeks!
      
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      well, let's just say this weekend started off AND ended off with FOOD. friday, after my eye doctor apt (he's a new dr. & he rocks!) the guys & i headed out to TODAI for all you can eat seafood. can i just say one thing?  HEAVEN! . i avoided the sushi, had my share of sashimi, but went bonkers on the crab legs. OMG, that was grubbin. starbizzle to hit the sweet spot, then off to a friend's house to watch the pacman fight again. saturday cleaned a bit, hit up IKEA & had a carne asada & pollo adobado bbq feast. omg. we still have a grip of carne asada left, num. sunday, had some dim sum, hit up the swapmeet, got some new games for the xbox & gamecube & then grubbed @ the butcher store restaurant (apparently, it's the home of the best prime rib in america). holy crap the prime rib. i kid you not, it was the size of my plate which was about 20 inches. *shudders* i didn't have much of it (honestly, i'm not a fan of prime rib; waaaay too much fat) but what i did have was pretty good. i think i could feel a heart attack coming on or something. egah. this weekend was somewhat tiring & now i've gotta find a dress for the upcoming wedding memorial weekend. *sigh*. i think i'm getting sick too =( my throat is killing me, i've got the chills (which i had yesterday) & i've got a slight headache. bleh. 
      
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      it's a pocketbike...heehee..my dorky yet handsome hubby was messin' around with joey's pocketbike yesterday...we dared him to rock his full leathers & ride around the neighborhood...he did. heehee..      he's the biggest goofball & i love him =)
      
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      yesterday the guys along with hubbs & i hit up the hustler bar and grill in downtown. no, it's NOT a strip club nor is it anything kinky, rather it's a nice restaurant with good food & hustler inspired. met up with jay's cousins for some good grub & good times. now, i don't know what the heck happened to me last night, whether it be something i ate or something i did, but after dinner i got extremely achey & nauseas. i still don't think it was anything that i ate cuz the guys had the exact same thing, nor do i think it was the glass of chardonnay. anyhoo, after dinner i started getting this burning feeling, then aches & pains & then once we were in the car on the way home, i started feeling nauseas. i almost yacked in my own car, how attractive, eh? hubbs was ready to pullover. as much as i tried to hold it down, i couldn't and the moment we stepped into the house, i bolted to the banjo & drove the porcelain bus. eww. *shudders*. i still feel kinda gross, achey & such, but not as bad as last night.   anyhoo, that was my wonderful night. today my big bruder (my cousin who's practically my big bro) is coming down for a visit. yesterday hubbs & i decided that we may hit up fatburger in pacific beach today for dinner (woo! i never used to like burgers, but since my south beach diet i've started to develop a liking for it). mebbe show him around san diego. ehhh. i still gotta shop for a dress for this wedding we're headed to memorial weekend. aye.   urg. i just found out that hoobastank is gonna be @ soma on the 11th of june, which sucks cuz we're not gonna be able to go. blah. we'll be in vancouver (woohoo!!) though, so it makes up for it. hahaha  oh yeah!! one more thing! my cousins, kuya rodel (big bruder) & jasmine went to on air with ryan seacrest yesterday & were on TV for a good 3 minutes. it turns out they were sitting behind someone who was getting interviewed & i got em on DVR. lol..funny.
      
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      weekend was a BLAST! been a while since we've had one of those. arrived in vegas friday evening & headed over to the strip. fatburger for dinner, contact lens killing my left eye, yard long margaritas, sephora stop over, hubbs & his $50 increase, and more walking! i love walking the strip..great exercise & good sights. saturday track day; hubbs made his goal of completing a lap in under 2 mins..good for you babe! rested, dinner @ the outback, more walkin' on the strip, hubbs & his friends had a bachelor party so pauline & i just did our girl thing; more sephora shoppin', walkin' & talkin' til 430am til the guys were done watching nekkid girls (lmao); again "don't tell me to go to the car if it's not there!!!" hehehehe; slept til noonish & left for home on sunday afternoon; hit up the outlets @ stateline & got myself some pretty darn good deals; can't wait to go again! this weekend is most likely gonna be a chill & clean the house weekend. joey's gonna be leaving on sunday so there might be a going away party thingy..who knows; can't wait til june! 
      
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hubbs & I are going to Miss Saigon, JUNE 9th =) yah baby!
      
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ok, first of all i gotta say a BIG, HUGE, GINORMOUS,  THANK YOU  to my friend, April for sending an awesome gift from England! she got VJ & i this lil' walking, barking & flipping BULLDOG named WINSTON!!!!! for those of you who don't know, before we got duke & poncho, vj & i had our heart set on getting an english bulldog which we would name winston. however, things didn't work out & we weren't able to get him. anyway april who, for being pregnant still has her memory in tact, (wow lady!) remembered & got us the lil' toy! it was soooo sweet of her! it totally made me & vj smile. happy happy! it meant a lot =) so again, thank you april!!!   anyhoo, yesterday i hooked up with a few friends who i haven't seen in a while & went out for japanese. it felt nice to see them again, since it'd been so long!! i made a huge mistake with my order though. i am never ever ever gonna order the broiled fish from bento & noodles cuz that was just wrong. normally, when ppl hear broiled fish, you'd picture a filet that's been broiled/grilled. umm no. instead, i get this oily, mayo & cheese filled foil square box looking thing with pieces of fish floating around in it. kinda like oysters rockefeller. anyhoo, i picked out the fish, drained it as much as i could & ate it. everything else, the sashimi & salad were good, but of course no rice. sooo yeah.   hit up bed bath & beyond after & then headed home to show off the new "doggie" to the two pupps. duke freaked out the moment it started flipping backwards; barked at it, ran circles around it & hid under my leg. poncho on the other had, seemed less enthralled. he just kinda looked at as if it was some freak dog or something & sat up with joey as it roamed the floor. he really didn't care too much for it. hehehe.   anyway, let me just straight out SAY THIS. what a friggin' travesty. american idol is sucking arse. i'm sorry, but out of the two, fantasia should've gotten booted off instead of la toya & really jasmine should've been the one on the bottom two and not those two. urgh. kinda makes me not want to watch anymore. it sucks. oh well. it's america's choice, right? la toya's probably gonna get a record deal anyway & surpass the others.   on a brighter note, today is my friday! yay!! vegas tomorrow!!
      
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      *sigh* i dig this song.  i'm not a perfect person. there are many things i wish i didnt do but i continue learning. i never meant to do those things to you. and so i have to say before i go, that i just want you to know  i've found a reason for me, to change who i used to be a reason to start over new, and the reason is you  i'm sorry that i hurt you, its something i must live with everyday and all the pain i put you through, i wish that i could take it all away and be the one who catches all your tears, thats why i need you to hear  i'm not a perfect person, i never meant to do those things to you and so i have to say before i go that i just want you to know  i've found a reason for me, to change who i used to be a reason to start over new, and the reason is you i've found a reason to show a side of me you didnt know a reason for all that i do, and the reason is you
      
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      the series finale for friends came out on dvd yesterday. right after work i hit up best buy & got the last one! $6.99 man, can't beat that. i also picked up blink 182, incubus & hoobastank's albums. pretty good lp's considering i've only listened to a few songs.   i've been thinking about a lot of things lately. mainly what's going to happen in the next year or so. there's a good possibility we may be moving to a different country & it's not that it scares me, because i'm all for living in a different country (umm yeah, i moved to here from Canada), but because we just bought a house & all these other things, we don't want to give them up. i doubt we'll have to, i mean there is such a thing as rental property, but i dunno. things are up in the air & we gotta make our decisions soon. no worries, things will work out, things happen for a reason & no matter what, we've got our faith & love in God.   anyhoo, i definitely cannot wait til this friday and til next month. even next week! family visiting, mini vacations, week vacation...yay =) now if i could just get through the rest of this day without yawning, i'll be good =)
      
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hungry. i want a big fat piece of meat & veggies. lol. i got this from one of my coworkers. made me laugh so hard...darn yankees!   A Canadian is having his breakfast (coffee, croissants, bread, butter  and jam) when an American man, chewing gum, sits down next to  him.   The Canadian ignores the American who, nevertheless, starts  a conversation.   American: "You Canadian folk eat the whole bread?"   Canadian (in a bad mood): "Of course."   American: (after blowing a huge bubble)"We don't. In America,  we only eat what's inside. The crusts we collect in a container,  recycle it, transform them into croissants and sell them to  Canada." The American has a smirk on his face.   The Canadian listens in silence.   The American persists: "Do you eat jam with the bread??"   Canadian: "Of Course."   American: (cracking his gum between his teeth and chuckling). "We don't. In America we eat fresh fruit for breakfast, then  we put all the peels, seeds,and left overs in containers,  recycle them, transform them into jam and sell the jam to  Canada."   The Canadian then asks: "Do you have sex in America?"   American: "Why of course we do", the American says with a big smirk.   Canadian: "And what do you do with the condoms once you've  used them?"  American: "We throw them away, of course."   Canadian: "We don't. In Canada, we put them in a container, recycle them, melt them down into chewing gum and sell them  to America."  
      
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      i'm in a happy mood today. i dunno why, maybe because i just ate a big carne asada breakfast burrito (w/no tortilla of course); no cheese, no guac (darnit, i'm allergic to guac..& it's so good!). yumm. now i'm full. *burp*  weekend was bomb. headed up to LA on friday for sissy inlaw's bday. haffy berday drunkard ate ness. sold my bike on saturday to some dude in long beach. i almost cried. haha. grubbin' at black angus for dinner for mom's day; new york steak & a ton of veggies ALL GONE. i cleared my plate, literally. mmmm. visited gramma & then headed home. sunday grocery shopped & watched van helsing later that night. pretty good movie. a movie to definitely get on dvd.   speaking of dvd's, i'm gonna go & purchase the series finale of friends today. i swear, that was the FUNNIEST episode i've EVER seen. i literally laughed so hard i couldn't breathe. the cab scene rocked. hahah.   anyhoo, this week is gonna be somewhat of a short one. took friday off so we could head out to vegas early for yet another track day. man, i wonder if the heat is gonna be really bad. hmmm. buffet dinners, shopping galore, starbucks stop overs, fatburger grub (i've never had a fatburger before cuz i really don't like burgers, but since this diet of mine, imma try it protein style) & much more.   can't wait til my big bruder comes down for a visit! my baby bruder might come too (daps, come visit!) and my closest cousin's, jas & her son are coming back down to live in cali =)  family reunion!!! i miss those boneheads. *sigh*. can't wait til june! vancouver baby...another big family "reunion"! yay!
      
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      today started off rather slow. irritabilty has crept up on me & i'm ready to go home. some people just don't know how or when to shut up. i swear, it's like they've got ADD or something. ugh. work has more or less become less challenging thus making me feel like i don't want to be here. there's a good possibility that i'm pmsing, so this down in the dumps mood will probably subside in a few hours. hahaha. i think i need a starbucks iced no sugar vanilla nonfat latte...  anyway, i came across this lil' survey...i'll do it.  : ***10 IMPORTANT THINGS INSIDE YOUR BAG: 01. wallet 02. cell 03. car keys 04. gloss 05. mirror 06. gum 07. tweezer 08. moisturizer 09. bobby pins 10. south beach food guide book  ***9 THINGS YOU WEAR EVERYDAY: 01. thong 02. bra 03. top 04. glasses (to drive) 05. gloss 06. wedding rings 07. earrings 08. hair tie 09. watch  ***8 OF YOUR FAVORITE FOOD/DRINK: 01. sushi 02. fish 03. hot sauce 04. sugar free jello 05. chicken 06. tofu 07. water 08. coffee  ***7 OF YOUR CLOSEST FRIENDS: 01. hubby 02. heidi 03. lori 04. jas 05. jackie 06. pauline 07. april   ***6 OF YOUR FAVE MOVIES: 01. ocean's eleven 02. the recruit 03. godfather trilogy (well, part one really, the other two weren't that great) 04. italian job 05. all of the star trek next generation movies 06. van wilder  ***5 THINGS IN YOUR ROOM: 01. bed 02. big tv 03. alarm clock 04. night stand 05. laundry hamper  ***4 THINGS YOU ATE/DRANK TODAY: 01. water 02. ham omelet 03. nuts 04. spicy chicharon  ***3 THINGS (NOT PERSONS)YOU COULDN'T LIVE  WITHOUT: 01. hubby 02. money 03. food  ***2 BOOKS/MAGS YOU RECENTLY READ: 01. south beach diet 02. mario puzo's the scicilian  ***1 PERSON YOU CAN'T FORGET: 01. the man i'm married to
      
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ok, don't think we're insane, but yesterday we bought a new bike. LMAO. no no no, we DID NOT spend a grip on it & NO NO NO, it's not a fancy schmancy one. it's a '90 VTR 250 & we only got it for $300. yes, $300. it's in great shape, just needs a simple tune up, it's super light & it's CHEAP!!!! those bikes are very rare & actually go for higher (around $1000) but the guy wanted to get rid of it & hubbs snatched it up right away. so, we headed out to aliso viejo to pick up our new toy. heehee.   on another note, i'm on a shopping frenzy. big time. i think it's cuz work is somewhat stressin' me out, so of course to relieve stress i shop. hahaha. *sigh*  to all those celebrating, happy CINCO DE MAYO!!!! 
      
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      holy cow, this weekend was HOTTER than HOT. omg. it felt good but i was so paranoid that i would tan so i gooped up the sunblock like you wouldn't believe.   friday, hit up hooters for some good grub. the south beach diet rocks & with that being said, if anyone else is on it go eat the philly cheesesteak sammich with NO BREAD & veggies on the side. yummmmmm. saturday hit up the swapmeet (damn i love that place - i don't care what you all say!) & nearly burned to death cuz my butt forgot to goop the block. an ice cold starbucks rocks when you're dying of heat. hit up the drive in again later that night (that place rocks too! can't beat $10 for two movies!!!) & watched kill bill vol.2 (very good movie, completed the first quite nicely) & dawn of the dead (yeah, i screamed so loud that the car next to us started giggling; i'm a chicken, shoot me). sunday did some light shopping & cleaned the house & dogs. those two lil' boogers know how to tear up the backyard. gaaaaaaaaah.   back to work..ready for the daily grind. can't wait til next week! vegas again baby! this time we're gonna hit the strip & shop! yeah baby =)
      
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      well, yesterday i said bye bye to my honda vtr 250. veej sold it & made 100% profit. lol. it's not a big deal that we sold it, i'm not riding as much anyway. anyhoo, we made it up to la jolla to drop off the bike then headed over to UTC to get some grub. watched a bit of jr. hockey @ icetown in the mall then headed back home.   watching lil' kids play hockey puts a big smile in my face. you never know, any one of them could become the next gretzky, linden or bertuzzi (hopefully minus the psycho temper). i definitely want our kids (given that they want too also) to play hockey & be as active in extra curricular activities as possible (idle minds are a dangerous thing, so they say). as toddlers, we'll arm them with pocketbikes (possibly a mini chopper depending on their preference), rollerblades, ice skates, paintbrushes, tons & tons of books & of course, a computer. they've gotta have some type of computer nerdness in them considering mommy & daddy are. lol.  anyhoo...oh yeah. if anyone is interested, i'm selling my Sony CyberShot DSC-P71 for $150 obo. It's still in good condition, takes good pictures, but I just wanted a smaller camera. It will include the batteries, the charget, an EXTRA set of batteries, an adaptor & a memory stick. anyway, email me @ gel@adeezines.com for more info.   peace  ps: CANADA DAY is coming up this thursday (july 1st for all you yankees out there). imma rock my canucks jersey & possibly, a maple leaf on my cheek? lol
      
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      so this entire weekend was filled with EATING & MORE EATING. friday, dropped off the PT Cruiser rental car (my Subie was in the shop cuz the computer got sent to Subaru USA to get reprogrammed) & picked up my baby & then headed to Costco to shop for VJ's bbq bday thing on Saturday. got home, famz arrived & prepped & cleaned the house while hubbs took the adults to viejas. saturday, dragged my neice & my bro inlaw's gf to run errands with me lol. hit up the commissary for more grocery shopping, picked up the lumpia, pancit & cake & then headed back to start the feast. rode around the neighborhood on the pocketbikes (vj LOVES his!), watched a few movies, played video games & then slept til noon. sunday, headed out to rosarito for some good eats, walked around a bit & then said our goodbyes to the inlaws as they headed back to west covina. weekend went by pretty fast, too fast as usual. looking forward to this weekend, it's our Godson's 1st bday! still can't believe he's gonna be one! anyhoo, have a good week all!
      
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        hahahaha
      
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      as you all know, yesterday was VJ's birthday & as some of you MAY have known i got VJ a pocketbike. hehe. for two & a half months, i've kept his gift a secret. from constantly saying NO to his "baaaaaaabe, can i have a pocketbike??" to literally dragging him away from the pocketbike stands @ the swapmeet, to even saying, NO! we don't have money for it! i stood "tall" & kept my foot down; little did he know he had one coming. hehe. thanks to john & kristie & jay for keeping the bike & helping me bring it home. and, thanks to all of YOU who knew about it & didn't let the secret slip! heehee.   anyway, after i picked up the bike i rushed home & got it ready for it's new owner. i tied balloons & stuck ribbons on it & placed it right smack in the middle of the livingroom so when he walked in, he would see it. when he got home, i hid & watched as he slowly walked towards the livingroom checking out the flying balloons. he stood there, jaw dropped, staring at his new found toy. i came out wth a big smile saying, surprise! happy birthday! hehehe. all he could say was "na-uh!!" me: yah-huh! & yah, that kept going for a bit. yep, he was definitely shocked & surprised & very happy that he got his toy that i kept saying no to. lol. i then explained to him how i kept it a secret, who helped out & he still couldn't believe that i got one for him. he had no idea whatsoever that he was getting one (good job aj!) & he was really shocked that everyone kept the secret for so long. a few of our friends on socalriders.com knew & yesterday morning, they kept asking him what he got. heheh he still had no idea. yessssss.   anyhoo, after that we went to peohe's in coronado for dinner & then headed out to dave & busters to catch up with al, jas & the gang. played ddr & just about died cuz i wasn't wearing the right shoes (jumpin around in pointy heels is NOT, i repeat, NOT a good idea). we are now determined to get the dance pad & the game for our playstation 2 so we could use it as a workout. HAHAH. i think we're waaaaaay behind the times, but ohwell. lol.  anyhoo, yesterday was cool & i'm really glad that my hubby liked his gift. plans for the weekend? bday bbq @ the house with some family & friends, then possibly mexico on sunday. can't wait!      what was left of VJ's bday cake @ the boathouse restaurant in vancouver
      
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ok so i've been debating, researching & comparing various digital cameras this past week & a half & i've finally made my descision. basically i wanted a new SMALL camera that takes great pictures & is at 5mp. my sony cybershot was messing up & it's too bulky for my purse. anyhoo, i've decided (& pretty much purchased) to get the canon S500. now that that's all done, i've just gotta deal with the waiting for my new toy to arrive. LOL. patience!    anyhoo, as the below entry states, it is hubby's bday today! he's a whopping 26 years old! heehee. plans for tonight include: dinner & then...surprise! lol..can't say much cuz he doesn't even know what's going on & he might read this. haha. hope he likes it!
      
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      well, today's the BIG DAY for my hubby! it's his 26th birthday!!!!  HAPPY BIRTHDAY VICTORJAY!!   love you babe.
      
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        hubbs & i goofin' off...     mommy & tita's version of the karate kid...
      
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      once again, the weekend has come & gone way too fast. in a nutshell, dinner @ black angus for bro inlaw's bday, movies after, saturday swapmeet, new puppy! (chow chow mix) which they named kobe, shopping & home. yep, you read it right, we got a new puppy. it's actually a shared puppy since it's staying in LA (it's mainly vince's) but we get to take the lil' boy to our place for a week at a time. yay! he's the cutest lil' thing, kinda pudgy, very calm & mild mannered & very very loving. it loves to be held, it loves to sleep (it's still a pup pup) & it loves to eat. heheh. from the two days i got to spend with it, i assume he knows to go potty outside (unless he can't hold it anymore..he's a puppy!) cuz whenever he does, he cries. he's soooo cute! i would love to just have him as my own cuz he's easy to take care of; he doesn't go all over the place like duke did when he was a pup & he's CALM! he loves to be babied (which i love doing) so, i'm ready to just umm, keep him. hahahha. i know i know, i can't cuz he's my bro's, but oh well. so yah, that's basically all that happened this weekend. can't wait til next weekend cuz it's vj's bday & we're having a mini bbq party @ the house & kobe's coming down! heehee. i really hope vj likes his gift....*crosses fingers*
      
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, the trip back home has come & gone & unfortunately, its gone by too fast. We had without a doubt, a BLAST. It was nothing less than awesome! From seeing family & friends, to non stop eating, the trip back made me realize one very important thing. APPRECIATION. Never did I realize how much love I had (well still do!) for Vancouver, nor did I ever realize the beauty of it until I left. I knew it was a great city, but I didnt come to appreciate it until now. 2  years after the fact, I realize it now. Better late than never, right? Anyhoo, basically this is how our week went:   Thursday: left San Diego & arrived in Vancouver around 920. Picked up the last minute rent a car & started our venture around town. Met with Kuya Rodel & hit up one of my old Chinese food joints for some late night grub; Gourmet Castle on Hastings & Renfrew has BOMB ass food. YUMMY.  Friday: slept in til 930, then hit up an all you can eat Chinese buffet @ lunch for my God-Brothers HS grad party. Saw some faces I hadnt seen in a while & some new lil ones that had just joined our huge family. After, shopped a bit & then hit up one of my friends going away party.   Saturday: woke up somewhat buttcrack early & headed out to shop & pick up the food for the evening get together. Saturday was the day we had my dads 10 year death anniversary prayer dinner. Saw the faces of a lot of people I hadnt seen in SO LONG!! It felt really good seeing everyone again, not the entire gang unfortunately but it was good seeing the ones that were there. After, hit up Luces & ran into a few old friends. Again, thank you Relly for getting us on the guest list & thank you Eric for getting us past the damn list line! Hehe.   Sunday: Hit up Metrotown for some more shopping & then went to the Boat House restaurant in Horseshoe Bay for VJs early birthday dinner, c/o mommy. GOOD GRUB! BEAUTIFUL SCENERY! Cant get enough of it, I tell you. After, a quick visit to the hospital to see my cousin & then off to the Riverboat style Casino in New Westminster. Got some late night grub & a movie to end off the night.  Monday: Ventured east of Vancouver to Minter Gardens to take in more of the beautiful sights of British Columbia. Despite the lack of Sun, the garden was still a fabulous sight. Hit up one of my old favourite restaurants (White Spot) for some good ol fashion triple o burgers. YUMMM! After, headed back west to Vancouver & then went to my cousin Johnnys HS graduation. *sniff* Im so proud!! He graduated from my alma matter, Saint Thomas Aquinas High School & man, that ceremony brought about many fond memories =). Anyhoo, had some grub with the family & then headed out for drinks @ Earls on top. WOO! Cant beat $2.50 margaritas!!!   Tuesday: hit up downtown for some more shopping & then headed over to my cousins for our (kuya ben, ate beth, max, mine & vjs) going away dinner with the family. Food was SOO grub; Kuya Rodel you make some bomb ass dishes! Thank you! After, said my goodbye to Gian & Jeff & then what do you know? We head out for some more late night grub! Kuya & Veej grabbed a honkin pizza & I got one of my faves, a donair. YUMMY! Cheap too! Headed back to watch Gothika (I knocked out) & stayed out til 5am. Goodlawrd.   Wednesday: woke up buttcrack early (as with everyday we were in town) & got our stuff packed up. We bought A LOT! So much that I had to borrow a suitcase from my mom! LOL! Hey man, cant beat cheap & cant beat low exchange rates! Grubbed on some good seafood & said our last goodbyes. Headed to Richmond to kill the remainder of our time in Vancouver & got reacquainted with one of my favourite asian malls, Parker Place. I swear, I couldve spent HOURS (literally hours) on end in there buying stuff, but unfortunately we didnt have the time to drop a dime (good for my wallet, I guess???). DARNIT! Bought some last minute gifts & then headed to the airport to discover that we couldve spent an hour or so at Parker Place but I read our itinerary wrong! DARNIT AGAIN! Anyway, boarded the plane & started our (sad) venture back to San Diego. We arrived in Portland & got delayed two hours, so I walked around the terminal gift shops (tax free!) for some last minute gifts for myself. Hehe. Finally arrived in San Diego @ 1am & headed home.  Our fun filled vacation has come to an end & despite the 2 days of rain, the time spent there was absolutely wonderful. I will always love being there, either Vancouver or Washington State and I can honestly say that I would give up the sun & beach life in an instant to be back in the breathtakingly beautiful Pacific Northwest.   *pictures up shortly* 
      
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      yep, 8 more hours til we're on the plane & headed home =) yay! yipee! an advanced THANKS to my kuya rodel for picking our asses up @ the airport. heh. uh, sushi? OK! just no rice for me, thanks.   well, last night we watched miss saigon & well, it was nothing short of fantabulous. despite the fact that we were somewhat higher up (les miserables; we're front row for that sucker) it was an awesome show. i didn't cry (whoa, surprised) but at the end, when they were showing off all the actors & everyone was doing the standing ovation, i felt a bit teary but none were shed. anyhoo, miss saigon-A DEFINITE MUST SEE.  ok, so back to umm TODAY. heh, yeah we're leaving. uh, what else do i say? besides the fact that i'm ecstatic to see my family & friends, happy that i'll be grubbin' on REAL home cooked meals (my cooking will never be as good as my mama & tita's!) & stoked (for lack of a better, non 80's slang, word) to be back home, i don't really have much else to say. hahahah. even though we haven't taken our trip back yet, we're already making plans to hit up whistler in january for a week of some serious boarding. we're also looking to maui in december for my cousin's wedding & sister's grad vacation & italy in march or april for our long overdue REAL honeymoon. very excited! from now until those dates, i can't take anymore vacations. hahahah. DAMN!   ok, to my vancouverites, i'll be seeing you shortly! 
      
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      miss saigon today & one more day til we leave for (my) HOME SWEET HOME! yeah baby. at the present time, i am excited however i don't think i'll be REALLY excited until we're on the plane. heheh. anyhoo, last night i packed to my heart's content. no, i'm not taking my entire closet because we ARE only there for a week AND hubbs & i are taking only ONE honkin' suitcase. (better hope i have plenty of room for the stuff i plan to buy). anyhoo, i'm pretty much ready to go! just waiting for hubby to add the rest of his stuff & we're set. tonight we're headed to miss saigon & i'm DEFINITELY excited. i haven't seen it yet so you can just imagine how i'm feeling. hehehe.   anyhoo, i noticed that i have failed to mention my complete disappointment with the results of the stanley cup. WTH!?!??! once again, those darn yankees (heheh JK) have taken the cup "home" while our canuck (canadian, not the team) butts are once again to hang our heads in shame. goodlawrd. i was rather frustrated when i saw the game and quite frankly i still am. darnitalltoheck. anyhoo, like they (always) say...there's ALWAYS next year (this time the canucks BETTER take it home & i mean the team).   okie dokie smokey. i think i'm done for now. tah tah!
      
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      i'm sick & tired of dealing with bullshit mindgames. you got a problem, tell me. otherwise, suck it up & shut the hell up. i'm sick & tired of dealing with inconsiderate jerks who care only for themselves. i'm sick & tired of dealing with people who like to twist words around and who are so manipulative that they actually come to believe that they're right when they're actually wrong. i'm sick & tired of dealing with people who have no regard for others; people who are just so disgustingly self-involved. i'm sick & tired of attention whores; the world doesn't involve around your ass, thanks.   sorry for my bout of negativity. sometimes you just gotta vent. 
      
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2 more days til we leave for vancouver, 1 more day til miss saigon =). weekend went by too fast; i'm still tired. didn't really do much, just hit up the swapmeet to buy a few things & then shopped on sunday while hubby fixed a few things around the house. anyhoo, came across something interesting & it really does make sense. 5 things to do to live a happy life:   1.  Free your heart from hatred - Forgive. 2. Free your mind from worries -  Most never happen. 3. Live simply and appreciate what you have. 4.  Give more. 5. Expect less  have a good day all =)
      
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      the best commercials i've heard SO FAR are the Bud Light, Real Men of Genius commercials. omg. i literally fall off my chair & laugh my ass off. hehe. 
      
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      A BIG Congratulations goes out to my cousins Ate Mae, Kuya Mel & Rachel Mae on their new addition to the Calinisan-Cruz family; Brandon Michael! Congrats you guys! Can't wait to see you next week! Love you!
      
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      it's friday! it's friday! it's memorial day long weekend! woo! well, as you can tell i'm feeling MUCH better however, i'm still not at my 100%. s'ok, i will be soon enough =). went shopping yesterday to find a 'fit for the wedding we're attending. yah, couldn't really find anything so i just bought a silky top & i'm gonna rock some black pants with it. no biggie. played double dash with the hubbs til late last night; man that game's funny. anyhoo, dunno how long we'll be in LA for, if we're there til Sunday we may hit up a few bbq's our friends are having. head back down & again, start into the workweek. but, we're one week closer to watching miss saigon & of course, one week closer to leaving for vancouver! yah baby!
      
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      well this weekend was pretty dope =) warm warm weather, both in LA & San Diego but it felt good. friday hit up bike nite. won a few prizes from the raffle but unfortunately didn't win any of the track days. boo. saturday headed up to LA, then to huntington beach for Ted & Lamy's wedding. it was so beautiful! i cried when they said their vows (since we got married, i've never been able to keep a dry eye @ weddings..heehee). the reception was wonderful, open bar (yay!), decorations were lovely, the food, the never ending wine (which i gotta buy, that was some bomb wine!); just the entire night was great =). hubbs got a bit tipsy (it was pretty evident on the dance floor..heehee), went a bit crazy with the "free wine" & umm, we pretty much ended up in the parking lot til 430am. lol. sunday rested for most of the day then hooked up with miguel & melissa, reggie & pauline & jaycee for some good grub @ buca di beppo. had our round of mini golf @ camelot then hit up the AMC to watch the day after tomorrow. it was an OK movie, great effects just not so great a plot. it definitely makes you think twice about global warming & how we can prevent it though. anyhoo, sunday rested up then headed back down to San Diego before the serious traffic hit. oh yeah, i got my SSX3 game for my gamecube! woohoo! this week, got the office dinner & then next week it's miss saigon & then off to vancouver!!!!!!! yay!!!!!!!
      
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      i guess i kinda needed to change this huh? well, i'm done posting on here. please just visit  urlLink http://adeezines.com . THANKS!  
      
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ok i need to vent. i know i shouldn't let this shit get to me and it's not like i really do, but when i see it & hear it almost everyday, i can't help but get somewhat TIRED of it. so what is it per say taht i'm getting irked by? ok, i absolutely HATE IT when people say that they don't like something and they haven't even tried it yet. come on! that's absolutely pathetic. how can you honestly say that you don't like something unless you've tried it? seriously. i understand if you've already tried it. i'm not gonna force my opionions of something on you if you don't like it. it irritates the crap out of me everytime i hear that ish. oh & another thing? i hate it when people smell their food right before they eat it. i can understand smelling a pot of food or a plate of food, but actually picking it up & holding it up to your nose? cheezeandcrackers, people! urgh. oh even better? when i'm eating something (i love different types of foods) and someone comes over & says "ew what's that? that look's nasty/gross". fuck off. i'm eating. how damn rude is that? seriously. grrrr. ignorance sucks ass.
      
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      of course this weekend went by way too fast, so there's not much of a surprise there. friday hubbs & i chilled @ home then headed over to the nex for some "shopping". tried to make our way to border's bookstore downtown but parking was a brat so we ended up heading to in & out for some easy (but bomb) grub.   saturday headed up to la for our Godson's 1st bday party. hopped around in the moonbounce, watched lil' babies run around, grubbed on bomb food & chatted it up with the "outsiders" (lmao).   sunday headed out to the block @ orange for some shopping (no luck, damnit) & then tried to watch the angels/dogers game with no luck; sold out event. grr. headed out to knotts for some fireworks, grubbed on caramel apples & funnell cake then headed out to a's house to set off our store bought fireworks. grabbed a late night showing of spiderman 2 (pretty good, cept i think cuz i was tired, i didn't enjoy it as much) & headed home for some z's.   monday afternoon headed back home, did some shopping, cleaned & then attempted to put together my model R1. damn screws. i think cuz i was so burnt out i couldn't really keep my eyes open thus making the whole task of screwing small screws a very daunting one.   on another note, i've got my mind set on redesigning (& actually going throug with it) my website. i've decided to just make it simple yet effective. i'll have it up & running soon AND with pictures from my new camera. lol. yeah baby. 
      
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      holy muthereffer. one more hour to go then i'm outta here. well, almost. i'm bored out of my mind even though i'm working. goodgawd. came across this, thought it was interesting. decided i may as well do it since i'm just SO BUSY here.    1. Grab the nearest book to you, turn to page 18, line 7. Read what it says: wire procedures for consumer loan funding. err yah. 2. Stretch out your left hand as far as you can. What do you touch first? my lil' glass jar of binder clips 3. What was the last thing you watched on tv? mtv morning music videos. 4. Without looking, guess what time it is: 140pm  5. Look at the clock. What time is the actual time? 144pm-close enough 6. With the exception of the computer, what do you hear? my radio tuned to 94.9 (sd's rock station) 7. When did you last step outside? when i got to work. damn. 8. Before you came to this website, what were you looking at? nothing really. just something to satisfy my boredom. so far it's worked.  9. What are you wearing? khaki capris, green shirt, denim jacket & white with green chunk shoes from zara 10. Did you dream last night? errr.... 11. When did you last laugh? last night with hubby. he cracks me up real good sometimes.  12. What are on the walls in the room you are in? motorcycle posters. mmmm, ben bostrom. *rawr* 13. See anything weird lately? i live in san diego. there's plenty of weird but not enough to  make me say hmmm... 14. What do you think of this quiz? beats staring at my computer.  15. What was the last film you saw? harry potter & the prisoner of azkaban & part of garfield 16. If you became a multi-millionaire overnight, what would you buy first? a house in vancouver...wait, no my STi. then a house in vancouver. then another motorcycle. yeah, that's it... 17. Tell me something about you that I don't know: i just inhaled an apple 18. If you could change one thing about the world, regardless of guilt or politics, what would you do? hard to say... 19. Do you like to dance? you betcha 20. George W. Bush: um no... 21. Imagine your first child is a girl: if i said her name, someone may steal it! just know that it's two names with the initials d.a d. d. 22. Imagine your first child is a boy: again, if i said his name, someone may steal it. but so far, we only have ONE name picked out & we're still looking for his second one. so uh, his initials? a.d.d. lol.... 23. Would you ever consider living abroad? consider it? it's been done.
      
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      friday. long weekend. can't muthereffin' wait. this week was a drag. lots to do, lots on my mind. just lots.   yesterday was CANADA DAY & i rocked my canucks jersey @ work. i honest to God was gonna paint a maple leaf on my cheek, but i thought that my yankee coworkers would freak out. whatever. oh & i'm on a hunt for team canada's soccer jersey. anyone have any ideas where i can score one for cheap?   anyhoo hubby & i were gonna go to the san diego county fair (aka del mar fair) yesterday  but instead vouched for dinner & two movies @ the drive in. have i mentioned that that place rocks? it's even better in the titan; all that room. anyhoo, we watched harry potter (not hairy partner, veej) & the prisoner of azkaban & garfield. harry potter plain ROCKED. literally. i don't care if i'm 20 something yrs old, that movie was good & yes, some parts did actually scare me. i'm a chicken sometimes, sue me. anyhoo, shortly after, garfield came on & we originally planned on watching the whole thing, but it got late & i was starting to fall asleep so we headed home after 40 mins. pretty funny movie though.   this weekend seems pretty busy. tomorrow is our Godson's 1st birthday party so we'll be headed up to HELL-EH for that. (hopin' we'll head back sunday night to avoid the crazy traffic on monday). lookin' forward to good grub & "good" alcohol. lol. nice one, p. hopefully i'll be getting my pocketbike beforehand & then after, who knows. as for the 4th of july, dunno just yet. we're pretty much just gonna go with the flow like we always do with everything else. whatever happens happens. i get to bust out my new camera & go ape with it. i'll post those candids as soon as i can (i know i've said that a billion times; sue my ass..i'm busy!).  anyhoo, that's about it for now. to all you yankee's out there, happy fourth of july!
      
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        HAPPY CANADA DAY!!!   Have a great & safe Canada Day, all!! I'll be enjoying the homeland's day here in San Diego by rockin' my Canucks Jersey & waiving around the flag. lol...
      
</post>



</Blog>