<Blog>

<date>24,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      "Whats on your mind"????...... Toby Toby Toby toby Toby Toby Toby Toby toby Toby Toby Toby Toby toby Toby Toby Toby Toby toby Toby Toby Toby Toby toby Toby Toby Toby Toby toby Toby Toby Toby Toby toby Toby Toby Toby Toby toby Toby Toby Toby Toby toby Toby ..........get the idea!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      in school...o the fun!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      hey...well x-mas is over...mine was pretty good this year- got most of the stuff i wanted. i kinda want 2 put a lot more in this thing- but then i kinda dont want everyone 2 know whats spinning around in my head. wld probably scare them- scares me somtimes and other times it really should but i doesnt...i'll leave that as i can tell by the black expression on ur face. january soon...my b-day :D...the ripe old age of 16....kinda looking forward 2 it i spose- i mean its my b-day- but at the same time im thinking- shit im 16- felt like yesterday i was 14- kinda wakes u up. x-mas is over- i giot the christmas feeling.... a day late on boxing day..ah well...got some brilliant cds - iron maiden- dance of death, HIM- love metal and REM greatest hits...anywayz cya cant b arsed 2 rite any more- i think this is the longest blog i have written- should c my diary goes on for ages!lol- get cramp after a while- however this isnt my diary. cya...actually i am basically speaking 2 my self cos i dont think anyone can remeber the address  and if they can they cant spell it right they put tease instead of teese- a little bit of random information for u there   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      well...im back and writtin on this thing again 4 some unbeknown reason- feel like shit 2 day...i wld explain but i really cant b arse and even if i cld i dont want 2 - keep 4 getting its x-ams which dsnt help ...anywayz i said that i wasnt even gona put this much on this blog thing- ive given 2 much away- o and hi 2 any1 who reads this......basically no1- may some caretaker all alone.......with his mince pie- lol
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      well...im writing in this thing for some reason- 2 day im really happy- everything is going gr8 4 once in my life- got these excellent pressies from sandie and alex- thsi really cool light plastic spikey thing- and this stocking form alex that has all these thorntans chocol8s in :D everything is going gr8 with Toby ..yey- i dint know who the fuck  will read this- probably cat- aww bless her- sitting by her self reading this all alone-lol hahaha.....only joking- awww its christmas time- kind ahyper today havent got a damn clue why- anywayz enought crap from me- cya
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      ~ill~ kinda better than friday and sat- kinda sad as well- dunno y- im blaming the weather and the end of my cold. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      yey fire- spose i cld link that 2 my final piece  Your element is Fire. Wild and free. Your emotions lead you everywhere. You are a very passionate person, though sometimes forceful and destructive you have a goal in life, even if that goal is just to make it another day. Fire consumes and purifys, it also protects. There is always caution with fire because once it is started on something there is no telling how much it can destroy. Fire people have the same tendency when mad you could be a candle burning but if someone tips you over...    urlLink   What's your element     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla     
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      ello.. well i dont really write on these things and i only plan 2 say a little...just 2 keep it..so......erm......... isnt this fun...... in ict  zzzzzzzzz so sleepy i might fall off my chair..........havent seen toby 2day (properly) :( didnt c him at break....its been 2 weeks and a day :D .. i have no idea actually why the fuck i am writting on this thing- no1 will read it... just some poor lonely soul by themselves...all alone......ah well... ill gt over it!... i mean its not as if im gonna write this thing like a diary cos ..well im not gona tell the world and all its friends wot is going on in my head... thats just stupid, and it can get messy and end up hurting ppl  cos on the net u cant tell the tone of ppls voice so im not going 2 say anything incriminating,so life....yer....isnt it fun ~sarcasm seeping out~ . im in one of those moods 2 day and was yesterday where if i dont really like u then beware, i was quite bitchy 2 this girl (not naming names cos i cant b fucked) , just in a kinda twisting ur words mood  anywayz beter go and do some work, may post l8r..or mayb not- i think i will just stick with a diary that only i can read (its in a safe in my room)...literally in a safe thing, meant 2 b a makeup thing but anyways) and then i can put what i want with out every1 knowing....and now 4 ~drum role please~ ~joes (any holes a goal) owen's bit~  I dont think Im Petay Pan, I am Petay Pan!!! Chamone motherfucker!!!!!!!!!! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      not got a lo2 say really- nat when...if u read this-lol soz about the cd i feel well guilty- erm....actually i dont have naythign 2 say...oh yer was my b-day!!!!! shows how brilliant my memory is! cya
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      well hello again- fancy seein u here-i am righting on this thing again- well erm...played football yesterday after school- yes i know football and katrina uaully dont go in the same sentence but it was really good fun- i was kinda persuaded by everyone- 4 once i actually felt wanted by ppl- cld really say no and i was a bit reluctant at first but i liked it- although on the way home all these ppl were staring at me cos i was in my shorts with my black and white stripey knee high socks that i brought- i mean these ppl really need 2 get out!- b-day next week- not over excited but i think thats just cos i hav alot on my mind at the mo- stuff which i really wish wasnt on my mind-grrrrrr- anywayz enough from me- cya
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      well hello again my fellow chums and vampires...... well not a lot 2 say again erally- although i keep finding cuts on my hand and bruses than i dont know how they got there- it is really starting 2 bug me- i mean ill look at my hand then there be another red line on my hand- grrrr-  anywayz- my obesession with dice...ah... i have added 2 my collection recently with dice hair tie things and a dice belly bar, so that means i have....(like u actually care...im just talkin gout of my arse as per usual) dice: ( i cant b arsed 2 right dice b4 each one) bracelet,a silver necklace, black dice necklace, hair tie thingies, key ring, nails, no they're not fake i put spots on my black cherry nails-lol- a dice pen- i need more thigns though, i have spoty socks which cld b dice- god listen 2 me- tlkin about fuckin socks on this blog thing- makes me sound so exciting!-lol- was was tlkin about something that happened ages ago(wld oput it... but... well i dont want 2) the other day that was soooooo long ago- but it just goes 2 show that u can leave soemthign behind and when u least expect it it pops up and surprises u- these blogs r getting longer- my birthday soon- 12days 2 b exact- hav not got a clue what im gonna do4 it- so if u read this and hav any gd ideas let me know please- Vampires- yet another opf my obsessions and when i say vampires i dont mean like buffy or angel - kinda pics and films- i need thigns with vampires on it aswell! New years resolutions- well i kinda have one- 2 loose some weight on this diet thing- nothing likem atkins- my own one and its worked before so im on it again- dont mind being on a diet actually- dsnt really bother me- i dont eat loads..actually i think i hardly eat chocol8! o yer and haz has sais that my new yrs res should b not 2 say sorry after thigns i say- i uu know me then u will know what i mean!- anyways thats a big enough injection  of my life- hope u enjoyes the trip!mind your step as you leave the vampire train and beware of the ticket lady- she hasnt 'fed' for a while...mwhaha..lol..ok i can c by the worried look on ur face i have confused and scared you !bye- oh yer and 4 once im happy- that is the most u r getthing out of me emotion wise.....unitl next time
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hello- well that should b hi 2 nat and i think cat cos u r the only ppl that know the address- and not cos im a bitch and hav said no 2 ppl when they hav asked just ...well they havent asked...lol-well dont really ah a lot 2 say really just a genral little tppey thingie magig! u c i was going 2 put a pic of dita on here however i dunno how 2 get the HTML 4 the pic- shows how much i know!-lol anywayz cya
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hi- this is mainly in reply 2  a post on toby's blog he put as follws:  "yep for those of u who do not no i am indeed single again after i had a operation and could not leave the house and was always feeling ill and loosin my balance my GF desides shes not seeing enough of me (i can go out and fuckin see her i just had a fucking op) and dumps me so that made me feel worse."  this has fuckin pissed me off now- i ended it with him cos i harly saw him- i was fuckin fed up of thinkin 2 my self "havent seen toby 4 a week" and it was nothin 2 2 with his fuckin operation- it was the fact he had made no effort at all 2 say- "hey ive got not cred or what ever"- didnt c him 4 nearly the whole of the x-mas holidays and everyttime emily or haz wld ask if i was seing toby i wld feel like shit cos i hadnt seen him 4 a week or more (and this is b4 the operation) i got treated tlike shit - and evern if he didnt meant  2 i felt like it - he soooooooooo does not understand at all- and he still blissfully thinks that its cos i didnt c his after his op...................hadnt been right 4 ages- 2 fuckin long was doin my head in........and the stupid thing is i thought this might actually make him sit up and think "shit - what hav i been doin- mayb i should make more of an effort" but instead he just kinda accepted it and sat there in silence- didnt even hav any questions 2 ask like ppl do when they break up from some1 - and as 4 gettin over me- well he said he loved me but i doubt that very much-   god ive wote loads- on stuff i said i wld not talk about on here- ah well i needed 2 get it out of my system- i still cant belive he thinks i eneded it cos i didnt c enough of him after his op- god!!!!!!!!!!! anywayz thats enough from me - hope u enjoyed the rant-lol cya 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ello- jst looked at those weight things when u put in ur height and it tells u what weight u r mean t 2 b between and appearently im not technically over weight- i think they need 2 update their sytem- well ive been doin my sit ups and eating less- i just want 2 b fuckin thin- fed up or being lardy!-grrrrrrrrrrrrrrr- and while we r on the subject of things that hav not gon that brilliantly boyfriends- either i hav the worst taste in guys or im doing somthignworinfg cos i have been treatred badly too many times 4 it to just b the guy- anywayz enough of- ! grrrr- yer grrrr ~badger badger abdger badger badger badger badger- - damn song is in my head!- cya l8r and nat u do not need 2 loose weight- if u want 2 then u can obviously- but u r beautiful the way u r and u r sooooooooooo not fat!- ello 2 nay1 who reads this!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hi.....well not a lot 2 say although i have started my situps again- done 250 2day- will try and do that 2 moro but maybe get it up to 500, that is the only form of exercise (even though its really toning up) that i cn actually get motivated 2 do- need 2 loose some....well alot of weight and hopefully that will heplp me loose a bit- anywayz cya 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      well just 2 let u know me an toby r no more- not really a lot 2 say- just thought i wld let any1 who reads this know- bye
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      fuckety fuck fuck fuck.......................................................................... y? i ask myself..............wld explain but i dunno who reads this and also i dont really want some random person who i dont like readin this................grrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr - bollocks............................................................ a really incitefull blog there
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      im writin in this Haz-lol so sleepy......didnt get 2 sleep till 12 last night and 3am the night b4 that-lol- in a dreamy kinda mood now- not in a "tryin 2 keep my eyes open even though they hurt like hell cos im tired" kinda mood-lol..........closes eyes and imagines self asleep in the arms of......ahem....... anyways- had forum after school 4 3 hours didnt think it was gona go on 4 that long.but we got everything sorted for the performace on monday- get 2 miss ict- not like i actually do any work in that at all.last sex and the city 2 night :( ah well-lol na its a brill program- god how sad im tlkin about bloody tv programs- god we hav so little time left in school- is bloody scary- and kinda cool at the same time- i like the idea of the free time off but not seein my m8s everyday- i mean obviously ur gona c them out side of school and that but i mean just seein them cos not everyone can make it out. thats one thign i will miss in the hols. will definally hav 2 organise some outtings 4 us-lol we hav thourpe park in the picture at the mo 4 one of them-lol- arhg fuckin exams.....god i need my sleep now......zzzz..... wld inform u of other stuff about ym self but im not 2 sure who reads this thing..... zzzzzzz....anywayz c u all- heloo 2 anyone and everyone who takes the time out of their meaning for lives to have a glimpse of my not so meaning full life-lol- that wasnt meant 2 sound depressin or angsty whether it did or not- anywayz cya- luvs u all my m8s- lol- god that dsnt sound like me at all.........................so this is what sleep deprevasion does 2 u- wish i liked coffee - then i cls stay awake :D - god im stil bloody rambling and i said goodbye ages ago.....la la la ..... oh yer was gona scan my pic of brody on here but...well i kinda 4 got- did it in pse the other lesson - i think it looks like her but not like the pic exactlly - only took me about 10 mins so that might b why- i might spend longer on it i dunno- drama ia going really well- 2 day mr davy was helpin us with the play cos we got outa pse :D - we do fuck al work in there anywayz - my character is like some physco- but not as in agressive and in ur face- kinda silence staring at haz's character (kiszarren) dunno if i hav spelt that right haz- art bloddy hell- the suject thign taht we hav 2 choose from r not that brill- they cld b way better- they r ..... landscape, cubism, camoflague, fashion,asia and difference- there is one more but i cant think- gona do differences cos i can do what i want basically- might involved vampires :D anywayz of 2 watch SATC (sex and the city) cya all Kat :D
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ello- im feeling really happy 2day- wld say y but im not gona go in2 it-lol - in 1 sense i hav a lot 2 say but then i another i dont-weddin on sat- that'll be fun, slight hint of sarcasm there by any chance-lol - felt like summer again 2day...god im in one of the rambling "comes out with any kinda shit" mood- well jsut kinda writin on this thign 4 the sake of it- la la la cant b arsed 2 right...anywayz c u all went i c u- who ever reads this blog-lol not really an incite 2 my life! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ello Yay- just got my prom dress – god how I laughed- I tried on about 12 in total and there were 4 contenders. The first lot I tried on were 16 and they just did not fit so she said to try 14’s- these fitted better but still they didn’t fit enough to compliment, so she said to try a 12- at first I was gona say no cos I thought no way in hell. Ive got no chance, but I thought well might as well give it a try- what hav I got 2 loose. So I tried on this dress and well…what can I say…fitted like a dream :D cld not belive it- I tried on others and they fitted and looked brill- but I felt more comfortable in the one I have got- the price was good as well only £70 to hire and £6 for this necklace- it is like a burgundy red but I cant really describe it- will have 2 be a surprise-lol- there was a serious over load of compliments though- in a nice way though- not in a “im tryin 2 selll u this dress way” in a nice way- shes makes u feel like u can wear anything – yes I know that sounds sooo bloody cheesy- ah still can not believe what size it is though (by the way I went to cinderellas in felpham, have cards if u want 1-lol is really good :D )  Anywayz just kinda telling u about that…u probably got bored when I startyed saying about the prom dress –like the first few lines so im sorry 4 that-lol Drama play is going really well at the mo- has come a long way and we have only just started- got some decent cds as well- muse is mind blowing- purely beautiful-I love the piano- and system of a down- their rare tracks is very very good- download metro- and that is an order if u haven’t heard it- go on- got to ur download thing- tupe in system of a down yes that’s it- and type in metro- and wala!- anywayz im off 2 finish some drama c/w and talk on msn- keeps mooing at me (that’s what it does when some one sayd something) is very weird with system of a down in your ears with the mooing !-lo anywayz hope u r ok if u read this…who ever that may b-lol cya 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      well im sittin in ict - bored out of my fuckin head as usual- with joe pushing random buttons on the keyboard...... i 32re2al25l2585825825285282[poijjjjjjjjjjjjjj  c what i mean cant b arsed 2 type- just a blodg 2 say im still alive cya- and nat u will look brill in ur prom dress and no1 will laugh! cya kat
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I am the me I want 2 b now, the me I was a while b4 has surfaced again and I am happy 4 it  Well hello there everyone, - now 2 explain wot I said above- this might sound a bit dawsons ceakish and shit but ah well- now im not sayin some blabby rubbish l;ike” ive found the real me” or wot ever just I hav noticed that I have bee me or wot ever but not wot I was like a couple of years agao. Now I don’t know if everyone or just a few of u hav this kinda of idea in ur head- wot I mean is u hav a time whe u were little more confident, and little more chatty and a little more happier and that. Or some thing along those lines. Now im not  going down a self pity road or anything- this is actually meant 2 sound really positve- but anywayz 2 actaully get to the point with out this infantile rambling which is common of me in speech and when I bloody writin/typin wot ever. But I do remember in yr 9 just sittin in southfields against that building this (toilets I think) and just sittin chattin 2 joe (hope u don’t mind me sayin this joe), just a couple of mates just getting on well and chattin about absolutely everything. And just the general feel of that time (as in like the beginning of yr 9….bloody life story this is….send u all2sleep-lol), but yer I actually felt confident (may hav something 2 do with me being thinner and actually havin ppl like me which I wont go in2 cos they might not want it 2 b known..lol)- but anyways now I actually feel really bloody happy- I actually feel confident and not like a complete and utter fuckin idiot…just a bit of a twat who does speak shit (not 2 b confused with spreading shit I just mean as in ramblings) am v happy with simon :) and most things in my life seem 2 b goin pretty gd (with the exception of the weight lose thing- a minor obsticle which willb conquered if I put a lil more effort in- wil up date u on the situation-lol) ah- that feels better….any1 still there….ah we…lol Now 2 talk about yesterday DRAMA I woke up yesterday like it was Christmas- it didn’t even feel like Christmas on feckin x-mas day…but anywayz it was like x-mas cos I was just thinknin about the day- I wasn’t nervous at all- all through the day and even b4 the performance- I don’t get nervous-hehe-lol  WELL DONE 2 EVERY1: SANDY, HAZ, TARA,CAT.G AND SAM who all performed amazingly. Every1 done really well :) I think actual performance went really well- there a few cock ups but not on our part- there was meant 2 b a black out at the end of scene 1 but there wasn’t so we just kinda sat there (I think every1 had frozen) ansd then sandie just went in2 here joke and that went ok- there was meant 2 b a blackout at the end of taras death, but there wasn’t- and I don’t really know  if mrs a actually knew cos in the technical rehersal she didn’t do the lights and the point of the tech was just that-lol. Theaudiecen seem 2 like it as I hav had really positive feed back not just above my self but I mean about the play itself cos every1 did fab. Somje bits were funny in my head. At one point where I grabbed cat g (Irina) cos she was goin 4 sam (zulieka) she was struggleing so much (which she was supposed2) that iu actually pivoted round in a circle still holding on 2 her. And wen I was “sleepin” that was good cos I was just thinking 2 myself “its nearly over and I haven’t got hardly anymore lines 2 say –yay – (cos most of my lines were in scene 2 (which is actually scene three- I will explain in a mo) lil at the end and the rest kinda meaduium 2 small ish at the beginging- but then that was the build up of the character- she didn’t say a like at the end cos that was scene 1, and tehn she said more in scene 1 cos that was scene 2, and she said loads in scene 2 cos that was scene 3 cos it did an overlap thing- hence why we repeated the same bit at the beggingin again- some ppl got it som ppl didn’t- gemma (both Goodyear and bridger) thought that she had been reincarnated and came back from the dead which I liked and cld give an edgey feel 2 the play- rich actually got it which I was kinda impressed with- the rent didn’t get it and neither did ryan (my lil bro) my rents were really supportive and they sed that I did well evern tho they were obviously kinda bioust . although I wasn’t expectin the audience 2 laugh when I went 4 cat (Irina) the second time kinda sneakily- was kinda good tho cos I suppose wh  u look at it was kinda of a lil comedy moment cos she doesn’t really im goin 4 her and sanide (mariana) and sam (zulieka) havin 2 restrin me yuet again cos im like a bloodty physco- but an educated one- kinda scared my self a lil at one pint cos about 2 mins b4 the audience came in a went brhind the curtain and punched the clothes on the rail thing and shouted (quietly so no1 eklse cld hear) u fuckin whore and just general rage words or wtoever and then came out comempletely pissed off as the character which was cool- but the thing that I was sayin about scarin me was when I was staindin looking at haz (Cyzarine) with a knife in my hand I was actually picturing her screamin in pain as I kinda stabbed her with a knife and blood goin everywhere- which Is only gd in the scense of getting inside the characters head and that. Btw haz I dotn want 2 do that 2 u btw, don’t b scared-lol- mwhahaha….lol – my mum said that she was cared of me cos when I looking at haz at the bit that I just said she was thinking “oh god Ive had that look a few times” lol- oopppsss probably will think of some other moment in it that made me laugh (not while I was doin it just in my head) 	The tattoos were fukin amazing even if I do say so myself- a giant thank-u 2 chrsi 4 stayin after school and doin them 4 me- every1 else was impressed with them- was funny cos after the performance I got changed in2 my clothes 2 go down the pub with simon, gemma and rich. Thing is I had a strap top on- so all my tats were on full display- I like the attention tho-lol- I actually like the tats- I like the skulls or the way they looked- so I walked down hill raod and these boy racers were kinda just gawping out of their car and some lil kinda were lokin at me a lil weird- and then I was waiting at the end of hill road 4 about 15 mins cos simon went home after the performance and I was gona meet him- but ppl weer drivin past looking at the and that kinda double takin me-lol but I did hav a jacket tho which I put on when I met up with them cos I thought-“ well u hav starlinh on ur arm and a fukin ss mark and all u need is some drunk guy comin over and thinking they r real- Ignoring the smudgmarks and startin a fight- or just getting un wanted negative attention- the tats took about 2 hours 2 do- simon lent me some facepaints which chris worked wonders with- gona by him  some chol8 2 say thanks- under the condtition that he shares it with stefie cos she stayed behind with chris just 2 tag along- but that was cool- she kept chris entertained…not in that way u dirty ppl-lol :P but she halped do the epaulette on my arm and she did the spiders web on sams neck which looked really good- 	Speakin of stefie- we hav this thing with a Rastafarian goat – a whote goat with a rasta hat in with a spliff, some big fuck off 1980s black rimmed  blues brothers sun glasses, a gold tooth and a big grin in his face…on a beach- and I am surprised that I canot fina a pic of a goat  on a beach let alone with all of the description above-bloody internet 	Went 2 the poub with simon like I sed b4 and was kind weird cos I knew most of the other corwd , (but we didn’t sit with them) cos of their lil brothers, like adam gs brother, Lloyds, damiens, joe mate “matan”-lol – adam ls sister and these other ppl- had this guy just come and sit in riches seat cos he was up with bar with simon getting the drinks in and I thought gemma or leane knew him but the just kinda laughed at him and I cld c they didn’t- and he said 2 me about three tiems with long pauses “should I go” and I said sorry cos he kinda said it really quietly- but he was just sittin starring at me- he wasn’t scary or freakin me out- and simon lloked a bit protactive over it-lol- but then he just got up when richj came over and asked him if he cld hav his seat back, then he moved round 2 simons next 2 me and then rich said his m8 was sittin there and then he wondered off (he was realy drunk btw if u haven’t already worked that out) and he went and was just kinda talking 2 any1- 	God I hav written shit loads- I hav verbal diorea (can spell it 2 save my life) im still on a hi from last night cos of the play J dunno if we will performe it again- I think som ppl will want 2 and others not-  well that was quite a big update- erm…………….  Hope u r all ok  love u all my lil chicken nuggets :D KAT :D   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ello- i ned my bed now.......................its 1.30 in the bloody mornin and im up tryin2  find feckin opics 4 art.zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz shaun of the dead was brill 2 night was only 6 of us (me, simon, haz, alex and louise) but was still cool- saldy shelley cldnt go :( had 2 wait 2 get the rain back 4 about half an hour but that was ok cos we jsut tlked- every1 seemed 2 like simon - yay-lol- might hav 2 rent shaun o fhte dead when it coems otu on dvd.was gona say somit else but i duno wtf it was....o i dunno- just my blog is gona b short- like my memory- sleep in round hazs 2moz...well 2 night really (cos its mornin) zzzzzzz and dont i bloody know it- ah the bags wil show 2moz- feckin art......grrrrr......drama is comoni along- will exlplain mroe wheni hav the time and can b arsed...and now is not 1 of the those times- one thing  i hav noticed about this blog is that i write mroe now- not necessarily a gd thing tho cos it is usually and assaltment of ramblings and pointless stuff..ah but thats me.........anywayz off 2find more vampries pics.......zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz cya all zzzzzz 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      written on the friday (9th) but i havent got round 2 postin it till 2night-lol(*)ive been watchin ur worl from afar, ive been tryin 2 b where u r (*)…ah I love that song- gd old aqualung..and 4 once that wasn’t a sarcastic comment Ello  my lil chicken nuggets….have been needin 2 say that 2 som1-lol- usually I write on this thing 2 just kinda say that im still alive and that-lol- but 4 once I actually want 2 write on it- anotha thing that is different is that I hav been busy over the easter- nt been up 2 a gr8 deal just drama rehersals which r goin really well I think. I think that with a few more rehersals- as in like a few hours we can get it perfect- its is basically up 2 perfromance level now anywayz- got all the props and that organised- well kinda- 2 the level of sayin we need this and that- broght this cheap top (£2)…bargin-lol well it was a shitty top that I cld basically hack apart for my characters top, tis a bugger cos it gotta b kinda low 2 show off my tats- and I hav 2 find som hena so if u read this and u know where 2 get some (and its not 2 expensive) then tell me please… I think just tld about 3 ppl-lol mayb 4 I dunno who reads- this- I always manage 2 put that in my blogs.lol- I say lol 2 muc as well ~tempted 2 put lol here) I don’t actually laugh out loud …anywayz..yer drama, tis goin well got rehersals next week tues and thurs – been working up at the roundstone aswell- has been kinda fun-  only been working from 12 til 3 but it is still money 2 wards irelnad and wor ever- the ppl there r really nice- ollie who works there behind the bar asked me am I in colloege and I was like no im doin my gcses- and he looked shock and said that he thought that I wsa older than him- or at least the same age as him. Hes 19! I was like na- Im just 16-im like the youngest there cos every1 else is 18 or over-not cos u hav 2 b just cos …well they r- but every1 is pretty cool- its such and change tho- I hav 2 b nice really nice 2 ppl- u know plolite cos they r the customer and that but it’s a change cos im all nice at work and not I a patronisin way or anything- just genuenly nice and then I hav 2 go 2 drama and b a bitch basically- from smiling all the feckin time 2 scoulin all the feckin time-lol- I kept walkin round the restaurant and I wld get this lil smile on my face, I think a some point si may hav kinda spoken out loud or moved my lips 2 what I was thinking but I don’t thihnk any1 was looking-but anwayz part of the money isgoin 2 wards my phone bill- even tho I get my 250 txts a month free I know I hav gone over that- been txtin a certain som1 (u know who it is) but ah well- if I didn’t hav contract I wld still b txtin as much as I hav-lol 	SHAUN OF THE DEAD IS OUT2DAY ! YAY- me bein  the usuall idiot must hav read the certificate (although I swear it said 18 when I checked at school…but anywayz) I thought it said 18, but now it says 15 and it does on the advert as well- tryon 2 get every1 2gether- was on the phone 2 alex 4 about an hour just tlkin and tehn 2 shelley and louise- but by the time I had got off the phone 2 alex it was kinda 2 la8 2 ring nat- so If u reading this nat I will txt u pr ring u on sat (10th) 2day will b on thurs like I said- meetin at the sation at 6 2get the 6.15 train- will tell u more wen I txt u- bee the lil organiser 2 night- although thinking about it that’s my lil job- orgainisin the cinema outings-lol ill out that on my cv-lol-I don’t mind- kinda likeit in my own little sad way- lol- there I got again with the lol- dunno if It irritates ppl- but I suspect there r things that irritate ppl more about me then just put lol after ever bloody sentence 	Not a lot else 2 say really…erm………….yep……………………………..still here……………………………………………………………………. Oh yer im stealin wat joe does-lol Currently feelin: happy J som ppl will know y lol Currently listening 2: system of a down- metro- is a kick as song- if u haven’t heard of it then go and down load it- that’s an order- tis no off any off their albums so go and download it I tell u O and by the way ..not that it really has any relevance and that- but I posted my manson pic on 2 the manson usa site  a few weeks ago- and I had a look at it the other nite- and its on there – yay! Kinda postin it anywhere and everywhere- probably cops it is the best pic ive ever drawn and If u haven’t noticed im kinda pround of it- and 2 joe if u do actually read this- I didn’t trace it- if I did ii wldnt b like the way I am with it- I don’t want 2 sound big headed or anything…erm…lol Honestly I don’t mean 2 if I do sound a bit. 	Art is pissin me off at the mo- haven’t got a lot done= not cos i hav been a lazy fec or anything, just cos I hav been tryin 2 find vampire pics- should hav learnty the last time that it was a giant pain in the arse tryin 2 find pics and thatwas a only a few 4 my last final piece. And tryin 2 find an artist who paints differences- as in a women and a man- or black and white- opposites really- but 4 the art exam question purposes it is differces- tis a bloody pain- got a lot 2 do over the weekend- just wana get a load outa the way so thayt I can get on with the plainin for my final piece. Anywayz that enough from me- Cya all wen I c u  Kat :D  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      y'ello eveyone- hopr u r all gd well this is just kinda of an up date -was gona right on here the other night but i really cant b arsed- 4 once i am actually quite busy- i have a job - yay!- at long bloody last may b the thought in ur head right now- tis near and the pay is gd- drama is comin along well- on the 23rd- jsut c me if u wana c it- was speak 2 my lil chick-a-dee hair boffin chum (haz 2 everyone) about performin it again cos we hav put so much effort in2 it and we basically only get 2 perform it 2 about 50 ppl or  however many turn up and we can fit in2 the studio- but ibviosly got 2 speak 2 everyone else- got rehersals next week. at the mo i am feelin very happy :D lol- haz and cat will know y. i am happy with the situation and things r cool- wont go in2 much detail so ill keep it vague. art is beign a bugger- got a lot 2 do- am more worried bout art than drama-i think i know wot im doin 4 my final piece- jsut need that umpf thatbi got with the last piece and it is 40% of the final marks so ti has 2 b good- is gona hav vampires in it big yay! scoll ends soon , then exams and tehn freedom- pure bliss- doin wot u want, when u want and not havin 2 worry buot some shitty work that u've got 2 do bythe followin tuersday or sommit- ~thinks~ i swear there was sommit that ii was gona say on this- bugger- i hav 4gotton, yet again. tis a bloody pain in the arse - keep 4gettin stuff- wen the 'rents go away i will hav 2 leave some keys at cats or somit cos i am so gona 4 get them- althoughi havent told them this cos i dont think they will let me stay alone... it is such a nice night 2 night and it was so peaceful adn calmin down the beach earlier- nearly 4got that work was at 5.30 not 6- lol - was a bugger cps that meant i had 2 get back earlier- oh yer-~remebers~  the piercin i hav been wantin 2 get 4 ages i am now not sure of- tis pissin me off- got 2 e0mail them 2 ask if i can take it out - and the scarin i really didnt think of- i need 2 give it some thought of- basically i need 2 b 100% cos once its done its done and if im not completely sure then i wont get it- wld b a kick arse piercin if i did get i though- me and alex r gona get our piercins done in the summer- (will hav money then) yay!- well actually payin 4 holiday and spendin money i mgith not but ah well- live b life and live it 2 the full.  I SAW DITA YAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAY wldhav missed it if it werent 4 simon txtin me about ti- i literally jumped outta my bed and turned on the tv- ws only 2 mins tho :'( but then it was 2 brilliant mins- havent heard her speak 4 that long b4- she was lookin her usual standard of classy-ness- she never fails 2 look her best- i recorded it ...and then watched it about 5 more times after....lol- yer i know it sounds sad but ppl do not really how damn cool she is and she is a v pretty laydee-check out her web site -but just bear in mind that she is a fetish model so if u r around the family or not prepared 2 c a bitta flesh then u might not wana click on the site www.dita.net   think this is the most i have written on here- ah well- btw i am on certain quests, need 2 find stuff and that 1. 2 find a horro film that will scare me shitless...so far the quest has been unsucessful and with some films very diappointing ~remembers more stuff~ shaun of the dead is a fuckin 18 - i mean 4 fucks sake- has pissed me right off- u c i cld blag my way in2 the cinema as i hav been told by my m8- but the problme is not everyone who i want 2/wants 2 go will get in2 an 18 cos chi ask 4 id and that- tis a bugger- looks such a brill film- mith hav 2 just snaeek in -lol 2. quest number 2 is fairly recent but i am lookin 4 the most sourest thing i can find- there r these coke bottles that r pretty sour - and r the most sourest thingni can find- lemons i can take and now hardly hav the sour effect on me- i do realise 2 anyone  how whas read this far i am speakin such a lload shit- but if u r bored then this will help.... i hope..if not teh  sorry!- so if u find anythign really sour then tell me or sommit cos i nedd it-lol- am lovin comedy at the mo- need 2 rent the league of gentle men or sommit- ~shes my wife now dave~ lol- papa lazarous..dont u jsut love him had forum last week if i didnt say b4- gar ~meow~ has will b the only 1 who gets that-lol actually thinkin about it i wish ppl cld make comments on thsi  so then i cld c who actaully takes the time 2 read it-  ok brace ur selfs-kat bein emotional, with a side order of cheese jsut wana say how much i love all my m8s and i wldnt b me with out them-summer will b brill- relaxin in a filed, on a picnic blanket- as shelley said with lloyd playin his guitar under a tree-lol-  im glad haz and cat hav made up- and i h8 2 c my m8s unhappy-it hurts me 2 c gd m8s unhappy-i am aware that sounds cheest but it tis true-  hello 2 anyone who reads this babble btw 2 change the time 2 what it is then click on the lil arrow 2 change it-lol speak 2 u another time in the world of me kat
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      yay, first english exam is over, at long last, the summer is nearly here, thats all- will write more soon (didnt realise u styill read this thing joe, didnt mean 2change the font of my whole blog...ooops-lol) c u all! Kat
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well hello there, fancy seein u here-lol      &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  God im writhing on this again, iys getting&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   addictive, like flippin facewhore.-lol, I mean its not  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   like a chat room or anything liket hat, its only got a&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   message thing 4 god sake yet I always seem 2 b on it tho,&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  Im blamin msn I tell u cos its STILL not working which is irritating me 2 the bone but ah well, shit happens and life goes on,      &nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   Twas weird cos I was just thinking about stuff alst night at work (I&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; kinda go in2 my own world, like in the car with my music on I just kinda   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; drift and think about everything and that) but I was kinda thinking &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; how u know u wish 4 stuff , and I don’t mean like 2 win the &nbsp;&nbsp; lottery and kinda stuff like that,just kinda little things, or how u   &nbsp; wld kinda imagine something happening, but when I was thinking about stuff it the weird thing is som of the stuff which I hav imagining happening and kinda wishesd 4 (not as in like “I wish”….just kinda “that wld b nice/ I wish that cld happen” just kinda in my head sorta stuff) but anywayz back 2 the point, but som of the stuff has come true. I wld say wot but im not gona mwhahahahaha-lol but its just kinda weord that it has…….aht eh ramblings of a stressed student……lol      Tis nice and sunny outside but a bit wondy, I kida said I wish it was nice but save the really nice hot weather 4 when our exams finish….and the next day it wasn’t as hot….anwyaz now 2 move on cos I can c by the look in ur face that u r a lil freaked out and now precieve me as a little weird cos of this wish theory of mine, ( u c I kinda think that if u wish 4 something 4 urself like ur own success in somthign I might “come true” cos u push ur self harder and that….but the things I kinda “wished4” I cannot control my self” ah anywayz…..      english 2 moz....argh! now that is bloody scary, altho the gd thing is 2 think about after 2moro i wont hav 2 know all the stuff i do, as in all the knowledge that ive crammed in my head abotu the poems and of mice and men i can kinda just let go and concentrate on sci adn the other cultures poems and that       oooooooooo. soz got a bit carried away with the&nbsp; O's there, but nat has inspired. this mornin i said i liked her new audrey hepburn bag and i said i wanted a dita one, and i said i might hav 2 put her picture on a transfer and by a nice bag, and tehn she said abotu cusions with transfers....and i was like BED SPREAD/ DUVET COVER! which i really wana do now. it wld hav 2 b with her blue background , altho i wldnt b able 2 sleep cos i wld jsut b lookin at it all teh time, and i wld hav like a dita collection.simons got a really nice poster of her which wld look gr8 as a duvet cover. i wish there was a shop that did dita stuff, there porbbably is and i dont know about it, grrrrr.SO IF ANY1 KNOWS ABOUT A SHOP WHICH DOES ANYTHIGN DITA THEN PLEASE PLEASE TELL ME! THANKS ah end of caps-lol       well the randomness is now at an end as i cant think wot 2 write........c u all l8r (gd luck in ur eng exams 2 moz)       Kat
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well hello there, fancy seein u here-lol      &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  God im writhing on this again, iys getting&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   addictive, like flippin facewhore.-lol, I mean its not  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   like a chat room or anything liket hat, its only got a&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   message thing 4 god sake yet I always seem 2 b on it tho,&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  Im blamin msn I tell u cos its STILL not working which is irritating me 2 the bone but ah well, shit happens and life goes on,      &nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   Twas weird cos I was just thinking about stuff alst night at work (I&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; kinda go in2 my own world, like in the car with my music on I just kinda   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; drift and think about everything and that) but I was kinda thinking &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; how u know u wish 4 stuff , and I don’t mean like 2 win the &nbsp;&nbsp; lottery and kinda stuff like that,just kinda little things, or how u   &nbsp; wld kinda imagine something happening, but when I was thinking about stuff it the weird thing is som of the stuff which I hav imagining happening and kinda wishesd 4 (not as in like “I wish”….just kinda “that wld b nice/ I wish that cld happen” just kinda in my head sorta stuff) but anywayz back 2 the point, but som of the stuff has come true. I wld say wot but im not gona mwhahahahaha-lol but its just kinda weord that it has…….aht eh ramblings of a stressed student……lol      Tis nice and sunny outside but a bit wondy, I kida said I wish it was nice but save the really nice hot weather 4 when our exams finish….and the next day it wasn’t as hot….anwyaz now 2 move on cos I can c by the look in ur face that u r a lil freaked out and now precieve me as a little weird cos of this wish theory of mine, ( u c I kinda think that if u wish 4 something 4 urself like ur own success in somthign I might “come true” cos u push ur self harder and that….but the things I kinda “wished4” I cannot control my self” ah anywayz…..      english 2 moz....argh! now that is bloody scary, altho the gd thing is 2 think about after 2moro i wont hav 2 know all the stuff i do, as in all the knowledge that ive crammed in my head abotu the poems and of mice and men i can kinda just let go and concentrate on sci adn the other cultures poems and that       oooooooooo. soz got a bit carried away with the&nbsp; O's there, but nat has inspired. this mornin i said i liked her new audrey hepburn bag and i said i wanted a dita one, and i said i might hav 2 put her picture on a transfer and by a nice bag, and tehn she said abotu cusions with transfers....and i was like BED SPREAD/ DUVET COVER! which i really wana do now. it wld hav 2 b with her blue background , altho i wldnt b able 2 sleep cos i wld jsut b lookin at it all teh time, and i wld hav like a dita collection.simons got a really nice poster of her which wld look gr8 as a duvet cover. i wish there was a shop that did dita stuff, there porbbably is and i dont know about it, grrrrr.SO IF ANY1 KNOWS ABOUT A SHOP WHICH DOES ANYTHIGN DITA THEN PLEASE PLEASE TELL ME! THANKS ah end of caps-lol       well the randomness is now at an end as i cant think wot 2 write........c u all l8r (gd luck in ur eng exams 2 moz)       Kat
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ello every1 just note and kinda of a forward appology, or an appology in advance, 4 if i am kinda blunt and a bit sharp, tis these bloody exams, but then out of every1 i shld b the least stressed cos i hav the least exams 2 do,(cos art + drama etc r outa the way) so erm soz if im a bit of a bitch or a grrrr kinda person-lol had german exam 2 day- oh the excitment, wasnt 2 bad altho there was on q on teh listening where the only thought in my head was "i havent got a clue with the fuck hes just said", was gona put taht down but i thoguyt the exam board wldnt take 2 kindly 2 that...na i wasnt really-lol- anywyaz this b only a short lil message, again there si somethign in my head that i was gona write but 4 the life of me i cant think wot the hell it si- ah well, wldf just ramble 4 a bit and go in2 som random discussion...with myself! about nothing, or just so random that only certain ppl wld under stand, me and nat only know2 well with our weird lil convos on the way home-lol (i hear the voicees 2 ...no seriously)lol anywayz cya all soon Kat (or Kita as haz has named me!)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Life is worth living,so live it 2 the full.                  Ello there was something was gona                                                             write on this but I cant remember now damn emmory-lol- ah well           Went 2 c van helsing on tues night with every1, although our cinema ppl r decreasing, or well just ppl cldnt go, or had seen it b4 and that. Im gona get every1 4 “the day after 2 moro”, that’s looking like its gona b a brill film. Van helsing tho. It wasn’t wot I thought it was gona b. I mean it had vampires in it which was gr8 cos as u know i love my vampires but the actual plot and ending kinda sucked….lol….excuse the pun there that actually wasn’t perposly done even if u don’t belive me-lol. But ah well, was a night out with every1…and simon…yay!just 2 kinda scim the topic cos I don’t really talk about personal stuff on here cos I am still none the wiser who reads thihs- think it is only haz and nat actually, just so I know and outa intrest if ur readon ths cld u just  post a comment, as in like “hi I read it” don’t hav 2 put a name if u don’t wana., but anyayz wot I was tryin 2 say was that em and simon r gr8. he such a gr8 person, no other person I hav been out with is a patch on him. So yay 4 me-lol STILL haven’t got my damn prom photos developed.bugger! got my free photo and I think it looks really gd, every1 looks amazing.tis goin up on my wall…with my other 70 pics-lol.shit that’s a point got find some space 4 my prom photos. 	The pics on the left are fromt his site where u can make ur own lil charactrer in the style of south park. Ill find out wot it is cos I wana make another 1-lol-  	Damn exams,cant wait till the 16th of june, will b my first day of freedom (my last exam is on the 15th…and its maths…the exam ive already got wot I needed / wanted-lol.  The weather is brill at the mo, kinda got a lil burnt and it was only a little really, I have gone brown now although there is still a lil redness, more pinkyness on the top of my back- If I didn’t sayb4 then wen u cam over haz 2 do som revision the other day it was cool, was nice  Chattin about stuff and that, will hav 2 do ti again I hope every1 is happy (apart from the whole exam thing) I and if ur nto the u know where  I am, and I mean that! Well I b off now, probably think of wotr  I was gona say on ehre as soon as  I come off the net-lol-there s a word  4 that …but I cant remember ….no  seriously I cant-lol  If I don’t c u b4 ur next exam  then gd luck :D Luv u all my chums ….ahem….lol Kat! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
             Well hello there every1         written on 18th (tues)     Tis a time and a place for&nbsp;      everything...      my time is now         Well hello there every1- now I cam actually b arsed 2 write on this thing…and the sun is shinning outside-lol-(I write this on word and post it l8r)     So at the mo I just got back from an ecitin 2 lesson day at school- god im lovin these days- turn up 4 2 lessonis 2 do a bita revision (which I am in dire need of) and then stroll home and sit in my garden in the sun doi &nbsp;  some revision…well I try…damn music is so relaxin I can c myself fallin asleep….just listinin 2 lemon jelly (tis a band  /group…nto 2 sure actually wot they r, who they r but they r v good indeed, proper relaxin summer music. They r pretty random.not as random as aphex twin (inthink that is wot thry r called) simon had it on the other day, sounds like a cartoon character thing. Like music from a ps2 game or sommit.lol     DITA! :D      &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;        Anywayz on2 the big story or THE PR  OM. Well there isn’t a big story really- I wldnt say no major cock ups or fallins out, so it wldnt hav made a gd eastenders episode ( there is such thing as a good east enders episode I hear u cry-lol) every1 did look amazing. Natalie looked soooooooo beautiful,(and I am havin no word from u (nat) asyin that u didn’t…cos u did :FACT :P lol. Cat looked amazing, merel looked like a little princess, alex looked so vampy and truly astounded my, shelley looked so pretty in her dress, I love the colour so much, loiuse looked realy pretty and every1 else looked amazing. Even the guys looked pretty gd, joe and his tied back hair looking very swarve.lol- adam (g) looked pretty dapper as well. There was something goin on with dan tho. I mean everytime &nbsp;  I saw him he was dancing with a different girl!lol     The limo was really cool- nat and shelley came 2 mine , and we started the evening with some wine, I only had three glasses, but in the space of about 40 mins-lol, was such a nice evening as well. Claire said 2 grab som cds….so I did, about 10 just kinda random and I cam out with this bag and was like, well u asked me 2 grab some- was good tho- we eneded up stopping as mcdonalds tho, not 2 get some food, cos we needed the toilet, no theres me louise, Claire and chloe walkin through mcdonalds in our prom dress with every1 staring and that headin 4 the loo. Then on the way back clair said is that ur garter, pointing 2 the floor, and it must hav fallen down, so I kinda just put it back on…in the middle of the car par… not very classy or lady like but at that point I didn’t really care.ah well, we ended up turning up 2 the prom with muse playin and there were som many ppl &nbsp;  out side waitin 2 go in and ppl who had come 2 c the ppl goin in. buts anywayz there was some dancing, and chattin and just kinda messin about. And then it was all over. Ont the way back in the limo we had chop suey and me and alex kinda singin cos we knew all the words. I do feel it was a bit expensive 4 wot it was. Mean the place looked great and that, but it only lasted 3 ½ hours, half an hour of that ppl were outside. M not sayin I regretted goin or anything like that cos I loved the dressin up and all that and the excitement of the day and building up 2 it just well…was a bit expensive, but anywayz i had a good time     ive put all my pics in my wall, there r about 70 of them-lol - showed simon yesterday and he jsut went &quot;wO&quot;lol might out all my prom ones up wen i get them developed.      well thats enough of me-talk 2 every1 soon :D     &nbsp;      
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      elo every1- ill start off by sayin gd luck in ur exams this is just a lil test 2 c if the new comments things that i found works...mayb som1 was listenin 2 me.......~shakes head~ na!-lol anywayz will write in here wehni can b arsed 2 and update on the prom and other stuff and taht cya all
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       tis not the end nor the beginning of the end tis merley the beginning    well ello there- this is jusdt a shiort bog 2 say ui am still alive- well tis the end of school now- was kinda...well really out of order just kinda senin out letter in the last half hour of the day sayin that that day (thurs) was our last day- feckin school- i am gona miss ppl- even tho i am gona get 2 c them again - its just i wont b in lessons with tehm and that- and its the ppl that ur m8s with- u know just kinda hav a laugh with cos ur in teh sasme class but u dont reallykinda know-those r teh ppl that im gona miss- well anwyayz- ona  lighter note- went 2 c simons show- was amazing and he was excelent :D went with haz and we had a cool time- wld puot more but i really cant b arsed 2 write in this thing at the mo- ooo yeee i hav the net back as if u havent guessed- however msn is being a complete pain in the arse and not lettin me sign in - grrrrr- anywayz- cya all soon kat
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      .........saw a sheep in a film bein blow up by a rocket launcer..was quite funny really!...........even tho i ike sheep.....................................
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      well im not gona write loads cos well im shit but anywayz- jsut got back form teh meal and was v funny- with the lovely prawn (who bites and its leg moved apparently, according 2 haz-lol) twas an excellent nite and if u r reading this and went thankyee 4 comin- it cldnt hav been as gd if u werent there (nat, stefie,sandie,vic,me of corse, haz, alex,louise and shelley) twas a cosy little crowd. haz tho i didnt get a cheeky pic of us 2 pre bushin it-lol- thats a date 4 the future!hehe there was this prawn and we kinda made faces and stuff with it (yes childish i know) vic kinda put it in a napkin and put it in her bag- they were gona chuck it outa the train window- ut haz just left it on the seat-awww- poo lonely burty-lol-alex was gona eat teh eye but well she kinda felt a bit ill so shes didnt. i think a gd night had by all -cant weight 2 get the pics developed and put them on my wall- where i duno cos it is kinda full up getin my tongue done on thurs woooooooooooooo-cant weight- im likea little kid- im well excited- tis like its my b-day! andmy art showin (gcse art thing_ is the same day so yay 4 that as well- me im all gd- everyhting is goin gr8n (makes a change) thankyee nat 4 ur letter thingie and i love the border haz i hope u will like ur fairy-will probably finish it 2moz (sunday) any1 else who reads this i hope ur well (in no order) thankyee sandie 4 comin 2 night thankyee vic 4 comin 2night thankyee nat 4 comin 2night thankyee haz 4 comin 2night (who else read this...lol) anywayz- im off 2 recover from my beely buster thankyee haz 4 bookin it (dnt worry boutt aht stressy women) and thankyee nat 4 the brains nite nite Kat
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Grrr, well I just hav 2 vent my anger here even if no1 realy understands wot the hell im goin on about- dita von teese was in the sun on Friday whioch I was quite happy 2 c cos she is not really in everyday publications and there is not a lota stuff with her on around (that I know of) but she  was in the news of the world 2day  so yay, but they got her age wrong on the Friday and 2day (sun) on fri they said she was 29 and 2day they said she was 31- shes 32 (I think-I may b the 1 in the wrong) and it said that she has a “secret past as a hard-core porn star”- well its no secret as here site gift shop shows, just u don’t ealk around saying that u hav been in pron!-lol Ah rant over- just had 2 get that straight! Hope ur al ok, tis weird not having anything 2 worry about- although I know im gona hav 2 hav som little projects type thing cos ill go mental if im not doing anything  with my brain!-lol Had forum yesterday and it went really well- was nice ocs we went out 4 a meal afterwards instead of vouchers- went 2 the gribble!-lol what kidna of a name is that sounds like a troll…and speakin of troll. Lindasay the most creepiest man..yes I said man ( I know who names their son Lindsay!) well everything that he seemed 2 say was just wrong, he always seems 2 lower the tone in a really dirty old man way!-twas nice on the way back cos me and simon was just sitting in the back and that- wsa a really ncie day actually- haz with her “bag inside a bag”-lol- tis the 8th wonder of the world! At 1 point it sounded as if som1 had been stabbed in the kitchen- was kind of a shout and a weird noise-lol I don’t realy like  put 2 much about em and simon but ill just say this- I am v hapy at the mo and I cant believe we hav been goin out 10 weeks, sometimes that sounds long (4me) and others it doesn’t at all. Tis all gd tho Hope the weather gets better- tis meant 2 b hot and sunny cos its gota b good 4 goin down the beach!-lol There is so something that I was gona put on here btu I really cant remember – flipin memory-grrrrrrrrr Tis Ireland soon –yay! Go on the 17th so its less than a month!get my tongue done soon as well-next week somtime so yay 4 that Well that’s all I can think 2 oput on this thing- cya all soon Kat 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       ah tis the end of an era and the beginning of somthing new, tis the summer of love :D- im a happy bunny  Elo there Well I kinda hav 2 pounce on the chance wheni  actually want 2 write on here.  Well we had forum 2 day with : THE TROLL MAN! – keep sayin that 2 cristina, he does look like a troll tho im telling u. was funny tho cos me and simon were walkin back 2 getther and tehn 4 some reason we were dancing in the street, kinda doin tebh tango thing down the street and then he was tryin 2 teach me salsa but he cldtnt remember it-lol Was fun round nats- thankyee nat 4 the cheese,crackers and the cherries-lol- was some nice cheese Erm….gr8- now I wana write on here I cant think of what 2 say! The meal will b cool, every1 who is invited can go, and hopefully charlotte can leave early and come. The dress code is “spanky” as quoted from harriet…although haz if u r 2 spanky that bush might look a little 2 appealin-;) lol, oh and also minxy, sexy classy laydees-lol I just hav 2 say 1 thing tho. Vic- WOW! Ur r so slim and curvy and I hadn’t noticed b4, so yee vic-lol I really cant belive I hav just done my gcses- shit!- tis kinda of a realisation- akltho with all this free time I am feelin really tired around 8, I mean I keep wakin up around 8.30 anywayz, need 2 do some exercise- I wana by som weights- take full advantage of tehj exercise…well really toning and that that I like cos I wldnt mind joioning a gym just costs money and that- I mgith- I dunno-anyayz anough of the futile ramblings-lol I need 2 just focus on things, like nats fairy drawin-still need 2 find a pic- I will nat- just gota fin the perfect 1-tis my way of repaying u 4 always walkin me 2 the corner even tho u didn’t hav 2-lol Loosin track of days at the mo as well- tis cos I havtn got 2 write in a shitty txt book the day and that NO MORE MATHS.YAY!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! NO MORE SCIENCE.YAY!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! WOOOOOOOOOOOHOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO Miss brophy, the blind mans trophy-lol-hes funny simon (sladen) So yee that is me at the mo- ah…o and I think I may hav hayfever cos I feel kinda fluy and that and my eyes r itchy and nose a bit cold-ish- grrr-lol Will speak 2 u all soon me chums Till next time in another edition of……………………… Cya Kat  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      elo there...fancy seing u here Yay!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! My exams r over and that’s it 34 the summer- now im free whooooooooooooooo-lol Well anywayz-lol Im writin on this cos well haz kinda ordered 2…and she wants me in abush so I gota keep her happy ;) lol shes  dirty bugger but u gota love her-lol Dunno wot Im gona write on ehre, just a bamble or futile ramblings and a mixture of other stuff-lol Finally i hav msn back. YAY! god that sounds really sad but u know i havent had it 4 a while and my phone bill i think is  sufferening for it-lol-so i finally got it back and so i went on fw (facewhore) jsut 2 hav a quick look at my profile and found that i had -840 points :S ....when i had about +1000 so therefore making me a "tramp" on it istead of a blinging pimp...altho now it has sorted it sefl out and is back 2 normal....god how sad- im writing about fw on this thing- my blog has reached an all time low on teh content-lol  " Boring and repetetive" 				The sun 			 		"the worst in blog history" 							The daily Mirror   Doin forum at the mo which is niocs cos I haven’t don’t it since B4 my drama exam which feels like ages ago. and carols leavin L so tis nice 2 do it again, will b werid in a ncie way 2 do a forum with simon J-lol  C now I am lost wot 2 say- 4 once I don’t really ahv anything 2 say….. So…..erm…… Well now I hav the summer free I can finally start work on nats fairy which I am drwwing/kinda painting her, gota find a pic first though so if u hav a gd 1 cld u send ti 2 me please Been invited 2 go and c slipknot and slayer in October so yay!-lol- wasn kinda surprised that joe asked me really The meal should b gd next sat,goin 2  smith and western I think 4 about 7 so that should b a good night then the following Tuesday im goin 2 c simons film which will b really cool, chance 2 get all dressed up on both occasions Vics sleepover was really brill on sat night, didn’t get 2 sleep til bout 4 in themorin and woke up around 8 or somit, was v funee tho and it was an alround gd night as vics sleep overs always r  So yay everything is v gd at the moment, with life, simon and everything So ill b seein u all soon Cya Kat   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      well hello!  just a short blog- had a brill day shopping with the ever so lovely nat.brought som funky trousers which i will probably live in now 4 the next 2 weeks-lol ooo and a top, was getin slighty pissed off cos they didnt hav anythign gd in miss selfridges, but the goodness began after a trip 2 top shop (cos they didnt hav my shirt in h&m, only had ity in red and i wanted it in black) ah well- u win som u loose some! ireland in t minus 47 hrs-lol cya all soon :D
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ouch...ouch...ouch.....damn rock city, swear its got more space on it- just waitin 4 the bruises 2 com out on my leg- ouch...ouch...ouch-lol....that is all....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Wot i wld say2jamie oliver after callin mark lemar a cock sucker: "C .U. N.ext T.uesday!" Well (mayb2 joes delight) im writin on my blog  Well has been quite a gd week- my tongue is completely healed now, well at least that’s wot it feels like, alcohol was no problem on my tongue- I was a bit weary on firi (last week, the day after I got my tongue pierced) so I just stuck 2 J2o-lol but then on Sunday down the pub….erm….again-lol…but that was with the rents and their friends-lol-god I sound lik a alki but anywayz I found out (grrr) that alcohol did not sting my tongue 1 bit, fizzy drinks made my tongue more tingley-lol- but anywayz, erm…wot else….o yer and on sat (how cld I 4get) sloept over simons :D…mmmm…-lol…..i wont go in2 detail,don’t think he wld b 2 happy me displayin the ins and outs in the net-lol-  the week kinda blurs from mon 2 wed……erm…..-lol Went round nats on the friday 4 a lil movie session, “cor blimey govner”-lol and then work…o the fun- wasn’t 2 bad tho, then went over marks with simon 4 a drinkin session, was only me simon, mark and mel, but she had work so she went 2 bed, ws a gd night all round really-lol- although in the morning I kinda felt the worst of the teckilla, vodka and orange mix and the various other drinks I had.i felt ike I kinda messed up the day cos I was being sick (not manky pukey stuff, just the alcohol, pure just liquid) cos we  were gona go in2 worthin- I was gona c if they had my shoes in my size and buy sandi a card and that, but I had 2 ring my mum cos I knoew that I wldnt make it 2 the station and back with out being ill- mark and simon were v understanding tho- felt a lil like a little kid tho- just like I cldnt handle my drink but they were really cool about it-J - felt bad as well cos he brought me som water whilst I was in the toilet and I was like please shut the door cos I didn’t want him 2 c me all looking proper ruff, my makeup wasn’t smudged and ii ddint hav like sick down me or anything, just I felt so ill, last time I was that bad was went I had food poisonin, the thought did cross my mingd if I had given my self a lil food poisoning the ngith b4 wen I cooked a chicken stir fry- but I don’t think I did, sjut didn’t drink any water the night b4. and I did feel kinda bad as well cos any physical contact made me feel more ill- so I cldnt even give simon a kiss let alone and hug  wen he went :’( my brother bless him tho, wen I got home I just wen straight upstairs2 the bathroom, just made it home in time-lol, 5 more minutes and it wldnt hav been a pretty site- not something I wanted simon 2 c, even tho he was so sweet and said that  I “ still looked beautiful when u were feelin shit”- soz if I seem a bit wrapped up in simon, but its hard not 2 b- 2 sum it up I am a v lucky laydee at the mo 2 hav brill m8s who r there 4 me wen I need them , and I hope that they feel that I am there 4 them wen they need me, or just 4 a bit of a laugh, how ever close a m8 they/u wld considere me, and 2 hav a  gr8 bf and just generally b v happy which makes a v nice change, of course there r a few little bugger in the pipe line (ie my weight) btu I gona kick that seriously in the arse- tis all my own doin, so I gota deal with it, and solve the little equation,…..argh! maths…noooooooooooooooooooooooooooo! But anywayz wot I was sayin b4 about my bro, I got in and as I sed I went upstairs and I asked my mum if she cld get me som water please btu she need the toilet so my bor said he wld get it, so im up stair, being il (lovely image hey!) and he brings me a pint of water so I take a little swig…..and its damn salt water….the water I use 4 my tongue..and im tryin 2 explain whilst being ill and he like all sweet and that and worried cos I found it funny , cos im triny 2 say its salt water and that and hes like im sorry im sorry –lol- twas funny- kinda had 2 b there- but tehn he did get me som water, no added salt-lol- b7t then he was really sweet cos he made me beans on toast :D  yum!- at this point I was doubting if I wld b ok 2 go 2 sandies sleepover- I really r5eally wanted 2 but I just had 2 getall the rubbish out from my body- even tho I literally had nothing in me at all, and I mean nothing-but luckily I was ok after a lil hang over sleep and I cld so soa big yay! Although I had 2 make her card cos I hadn’t been able 2 get 1 cos of b4- but yay! Was a really really gd night- really glad I went- big thank u 2 sandie 4 invitin me and 2 simon (sladen) 4 the lovely hospitality-lol and sandie mum and dad-lol- didn’t leave till about 2.30-lol- watched som films, ate som…..ok altoa food….ehem-lol….lukily I cld tho, on guilt, makes a change-lol-overall a really cool- ngiht- havtn been 2 sandies b4- nearly cldnt find it tho Btw joe soz I cldnt com2 ur party- althi I don’t think its really that much of a loss- although I think I wld hav been on orange juice 4 the night-lol- just don’t say the “T” word around me (tecila) but anywayz, enough of my sad little antics-  Not been up 2 a lot 2 day at all, just helped my dad build som draws- really exciting I know-  Cant belive a week 2day I wld hav spent my first night in Ireland!- tis mental There was som stuff that I was gona write on here- somit about “wot if” as in- “wot if I didn’t do that” kinda thing- wld everything else still hav happened= kinda like r things just meant 2 b or do we create our own fate (really don’t mean this 2 turn in 2 SATC carrie bradshaw moment)-lol but anywayz- my mind is fresh blank Hope every1 is ok- Cya all soon I hope Kat   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        my tongue comes complete with hole and a metal bar    Elo- well the deed is done- there now is a hiole in my tongue-mwhahahaha I had it pirced at “punctured” in Brighton, quite a nice place really, simon new the guy tim who worked in there and the girl who did my piercing seemed really friendly.basically it was  a kinda dentists style chair in a room up stairs (don’t mean 4 this 2 make the place sound seedy or tacky ocs it was far from it) and there was a window  so u cld kinda look outa that. She said take  a seat and the rest and then she put 5 dota on my tongue 2 c how far 4ward or how far back I wanted it, I chose the 3rd dot, in the middle, im not 2 sure if I shld hav had the 2nd  one (from the fron of the tongue up wards, 5 bein the furthest back) but that might b just cos wit is swelled up now.2much tlkin-lol. Anywayz I asked if they numb it and she said no- so I kinda had little thoughts goin through my head of  “that’s quite a big  bita flesh 4 a metal rod 2 but put through with no anesthetic”…well somit 2 mumb it by, although with my belly button they didn’t numb it and that’s gona really hurt, bugger! Nto kinda doubts just kinda realisein wots gona happen-lol- So she put the clamp on which didn’t hurt at all,even tho I was told that that hurts more than the piercing tis self-lol, and then it came……… She put the needle or wotever through my tongue. I was gona look but she said “close ur eyes” so I kinda did cos at that point I was just kinda following instructions cos I was kidna in vunerable position. So I didn’t c it being pirced-think tho It wasbetter that I didn’t c it. It did hurt, but it was  a standable pain. I felt it pierce tyeh top of the tongue but I cldnt feel it go through really, kinda don’t remember the pain anymore. Was completely fine when she had put the bar through. Just had som water and spat it out in the sink and she just went “wooo” and I was like o sorry, cos I thought she wasn’t expectin me 2 spit in her sink even tho she said feel free if u wana spit the water out. But it was only cos she said that the tongue piercing usually affects ur spittin, and I just spat normally, not like a bit of a knob cheese-lol I was lispin through out the rest of the shpoppin trip (didn’t egt it pierced straight away, got it done around 3 I think and we  got the 5.20 train from brighton SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY 2 nat, she will know y and I kinda feel a bit shitty about it so im not gona out it on here soz again nat my tongue is aching like hell now, just had som soup.cant eat youghurts 2 save my life, think I pulled a muscle when i got it pierced cos u hav 2 stick ur tongue out and when I got it done  the only pain straight after it was pierced was my left side of my leck, under my jaw. Speakin like a complete twat at the mo. Was speakina bit 2 much I think round brighton. Has only been since I hav been home that it has start 2 feel enlarged. It doesn’t feel weird in tongue either, feels kinda natural-lol- although went I was first pierced I kinda flet like somthign had invaded my space in my mouth, byut all was cool-lol- altogether I had a pretty cool day shoppin, with simon, alex and nat. I thought that we weren’t gona make it 2 the art th8ing and miss it cos by the time we got 2 the school ti was about 6.25/6.30, but I went in and asked and they said na I cld just walk around and they think its on till 7, so I shouwed simon my art book and my final pieces.My final pieces r a ll on the wall, including my 1 with the mud rock, which I thought wld rip down cos of the weight of it on the paper, but luckily it hasn’t…yet-lol Gota dice necklace 4 a £1 – bargin!-lol  	I think nat is glad with her purchases from the vintage shope and that other “magical” shop.  Damn it, I wish they had x-men or thundercats dvds ,but more likely videos, gona go 4 a search I think on the net thank yee joe 4 the cd btw, hope every1 else is well, and sorry 2 b rambling on about my tongue but it makes a change I that I actually ahv somt 2 write about cya all soon I hope now Im off 2 recover, 2moro its gona swell up like a bitch…the things we do aye!-lol Kat 
       
    
    
</post>


</Blog>