<Blog>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   so my "companion" really likes the Red Sox because he is from Vermont and that is the closest sports team to those hinder regions. this reminds of of football season when i kept making fun of him because he was a patriot's fan. i mean, it is really pathetic when six states have to share a football team. why don't those pilgrim descendants get with the program?   so we are going to drive from philly to baltimore to see the red sox play the orioles in a couple weeks, on the same day that is incidentally my ex-boyfriends birthday. i have no idea why i should care about that, it's just plain wrong. i am only interested in seeing andy pettitte, or in a distant second- kyle farnsworth, but baseball games are fun period. i also thought carl pavano was cute for a split second, but then i reverted back to pettitte. my three obssessions are:  1. andy pettitte 2. foundation (origins or christian dior) 3. exfoliant (neutrogena deep clean)  this is a pretty constant list, though items 2 and 3 fluctuate, but 1 never does, really. 

						
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   i just had lunch and i am still hungry. i want a fruit salad.... 

						
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   free coffee ususally tastes pretty bad. expensive coffee is okay. i need a caffeine boost. tired here. so i am trying to study for the lsat and it is going okay, except i am now officially convinced i am retarded, despite all my protestations to the contrary. if i am not retarted, then at the very least, i find irrelevent pieces of information relevent.   The results of  urlLink America's Favorite Cities Survey :  Being that I live in Philadelphia, I find these results abhorrent. Who is making this list? I have been to San Francisco, lived in New York for a year, and I don't agree with this at all. Let's just say I am a typical Philadelphian, but not according to this survey.  

						
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   how many mirrors in one room is too much? i have six in my bedroom, and they are various sizes and shapes. i hope this is not too much, but the sick thing is, i am always tempted to get more! i have serious problems.  i think the fact that i didn't have breakfast this morning is contributing to my monday morning depression. i must have low seratonin. ok, i am now eating a plain bagel with veggie cream cheese from Cosi. I don't particularly like Cosi breakfast, but it's really close to where I work, so sometimes it's a default choice.  i am thinking of investing in Dove Soap, or whichever company owns it- Proctor and Gamble or something. ok i just looked it up- dove is Unilever, and neutrogena is Johnson&Johnson. i wish i had gone to school to become a cosmetic chemist.   do you know anyone who pronounnces "espresso" as "expresso?" how embarrassing.   

						
</post>

<date>19,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   i want to get more exposure for my blog. someone who knows something about computers, please help me!!! i feel sad that no one is reading this except for two people. it's a very serious situation that needs medical attention. i don't know if i feel like margaritas again tonight. i can be quite a habitual person. if i know the margaritas or the tiramisu, or the plum tea, or the green-tea latte is excellent, why do i need to to branch out? 

						
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I want to get an anklet because not that many women wear them, so when you do, you stand out. I told my boyfriend that wearing jewelry below the knee was sort of riduculous, but then again, who am I to judge where someone wants to wear jewelry?   This gets me thinking about NFL players, especially the Eagles players, who spend large portions of their disposable income on diamond earrings and furs. I mean, Freddy Mitchell probably owns more fur coats than J-Lo. Scary. I guess part of the NFL American Dream is to be able to wear all the dead animals you want. What will happen if man-made diamonds become accepted as authentic. Then DeBeers will lose their power and then, there will be- equality, happiness and bling-bling for everyone. Or I can just pretend my CZ bracelet from Claire's is real.  I love the "Idiot's Guide" book series, and I was reading the one called "Understanding Men and Women," and it said that women expect gifts of QUALITY and that it reflects your perception of her. Therefore, if you give her a tacky gift, it means that you think she is tacky. I hope any man reading this is taking notes.  feeling sad today:  The first song of his happiness, and the song woke  His heart to the darkness and into the sadness of joy. - Galway Kinnell  

						
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So, my boyfriend informed me that according to the US census in 1999, asians make up 3.6 percent of the population, and jews make up only 2 percent of the population, a statistic to which I was incredulous, especially, the jewish statistic. I stated that that only meant there were less jewish men for me to choose from, to which he replied: "fewer." I argued that because I do not know the specific number of jewish men available to me (because of people being born and dying making it an constant variable) that less would be appropriate. after all, we all learned to use "less" when referring to grains of sand or other unquantifiable entities. but he argues that to make a choice requires there to be a specific number or something to that effect. but he is dead wrong! sorry marshall. 

						
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   so i heard on the news that using anti-bacterial hand soap doesn't decrease your chance of getting sick, any more than washing your hands with regular soap. personally, i like the hand sanitizer gels with their slightly nauseating alchohol scent, covered up with the scent of fake apples. So far, luckily, this winter I haven't been sick at all really, with the exception of a mild case of conjunctivitis.  so I hope all of my two readers (including myself) like my design of this page. I was going for the Houston Astros theme, with the red and black, but somehow this design ends up looking like a hurricane flag, or a Dentyne wrapper gone wrong. but, i have to stop fooling around with the page, because no matter what I do, I am never satisfied with it.  I love thursdays because I am all about anticipation. by the time it gets to friday, it's anticlimactic for me. no one understands me when i tell them this, but for me it's true. i love thursdays. 

						
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I was going to give my boyfriend the book "Money" by Martin Amis because I enjoyed it a lot and I thought he might like it. So I went to get it from my shelf and I realized it is too much of a treasure to give up. It's poetic, it's beautiful, it's philosophical, all at the same time.   so my sister starts her first job as a nurse in a couple of weeks. nursing is something I personally would never be able to do. it is sorta difficult for me to take care of a cat, let alone a human being.   I'm already thinking about what I want to accomplish this weekend. I move the stuff on my walls somewhat frequently, so I need the plaster that comes in a tube so I can fill some of it in. My bedroom walls are white, so it shouldn't be too much of a problem. Also, I need to study, big time. Time is running out, or as the poet says, there is a "Deprivation of time." 

						
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   comments are what make these sites fun. i hope to have many stupid discussions based on my blog postings from now on. even if they are between me and one person. so nicole is not allowing anyone to bring guests to her wedding, which means my boyfriend can't come. if my boyfriend can't chauffeur me there, how the heck am I supposed to get there. I am not driving to New Jersey if I can help it. oh, to have a chauffeur at your beckon call is one of life's great pleasures, other than verbally and mentally attacking people on their blogs under the guise of pseudonyms.  if i ever get married, the bridesmaid's dresses are going to be off the rack from target if i remember how terrible it feels now to spend all my disposable income on a pink vera wang bridesmaid's dress. there are much better things to put that money to use to, namely, books, skincare products and three way mirrors.  

						
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The Ides of March is so cool. Technically, it should be March 16, considering there are 31 days in March, but I'll stop nitpicking. Julius Caesar was a cool play, but Macbeth was even cooler, and both involve stabbing the monarch to death. It was this day in 44 B.C. that 60 conspirators led by Marcus Junius Brutus and Gaius Cassius Longinus attached Gaius Julius Caesar in the Roman Senate. I think Macbeth might be my favorite Shakespeare play. I love the three portentous witches, the indelible blood spot, and the ambiguity of the line Macbeth says after he hears Lady Macbeth committed suicide: "She should have died hereafter," which has varying interpretations.  

						
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I am trying to figure out how to alter this site so that it is possible to post comments on my entries. As it stands, I can't get any feedback, which is quite disturbing. I need reassurance, good or bad. Any attention is better than no attention at all. I also need to figure out a way to put a site tracker on this site. Site trackers rock! 

						
</post>

<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I have grown to love home depot which is a frightening development in the life of someone only 24 years old. I am not that much into interior decorating, but I do believe that a home environment should be beautiful and functional. I am not that big a fan of IKEA, but I did get a mattress pad there and it is mightly comfortable. There were three tiers of mattress pads there-one for 50 dollars, one for 100, and one for 150. They were sold out of the 150 one, which I wanted to get because I am not going to scrimp on my sleeping comfort, so I settled for the mid tier one. It's working out okay, but I wonder what I am missing if I got the top of the line mattress pad. Oh well, moot point now. 

						
</post>

<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   How can I get this site to be more aesthetically pleasing? This split-pea soup green color background is neither appetizing nor pretty. I have to decided to change my favorite color from pink to green because geniuses are supposed to like the color green. Hence, that is why I have decided to make my blog template "split-pea." Pink is a pretty silly color to admit to being your favorite, although when I wear bright pink I feel more playful and it brightens up my face. Green does impart an interesting feeling though. It's serene and versatile. I like the color green of Clinique products, with the faint white swirls reminiscent of green marble, if there were such a thing.   So, tonight, there is going to be- MARGARITAS. I hate Tequila on its own, but somehow, add some Margarita mix and the world is a better place. I prefer the frozen variety, but I'll take regular ones too. I love Blue Raspberry margaritas, and in a distant second, Strawberry. Copabanana's on South Street and University City have excellent Margaritas. I also like the ones from Roy's Hawaiian Cuisuine, though theirs are 9 dollars a pop.  

						
</post>

<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I am really wanting to get lasik surgery, because I have a mild infection from contact lense abuse. Good vision is very underrated. If I were a Cro-Magnum woman I would be dead already because my Cro-Magnum husband wouldn't be very happy with the slipshod way I was handling the housechores, which really wouldn't be my fault. It would be because I couldn't see very well.   Speaking of Cro-Magnum woman, I told my friend that Molly Sims is pretty, but she occasionally looks like Cro-Magnum woman, and I think he just thinks I am jealous of all insanely attractive women, which I admit, but it doesn't alter the fact that her forehead occasionally resembles Cro-Magnum woman, or a woman from another era of prehistoric man, maybe Home Erectus or Australopithecus. 

						
</post>

<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I love Queen, in all their melodramatic hypersensitive glory. My favorite Queen songs are "We are the Champions" and "Bohemian Rhapsody." One person says I should listen to the rest of the albums, but I only like these two songs. Occasionally, I will give in and listen to "Under Pressure."   On the agenda for tonight- Home Depot! I have to look for flooring, preferably the fake wood kind, but not the too-fake looking ones.   

						
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Teresa's beauty, so divine She outshines belles from across time. Ne'er Spartan Helen could compare; Nor fair Psyche, I would not dare To put them in a common light. Her beaming face could cut the night And guide an errant ship to shore Like beauty never has before. Her beauty, stunning, burning bright, Consumes me like no other sight, Yet it does not compare one bit To her intelligence and wit.   

						
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Love for her blazes; I cannot escape her eyes. They are shining stars Which vaunt radiant genius And fascinating passion.  

						
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I am glad I switched to blogger because I think I will be getting much more traffic on my blog this way. I was using xanga, and hardly anyone was getting to that site. What a waste of blogging energy. What's the point if no one is reading it, right? Hopefully this new site will lead to more viewers which will lead to the overall well being of Teresa Cho. Funny, I have no problem referring to myself in third person when I am writing, but I find it very draining to do it when I am speaking. Interesting. 

						
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Now that I have bangs and don't like the length of my hair, i have been wearing it up, and i am getting checked out a lot. mike doesn't like my hair up as much as he likes it down, but i think most other guys prefer my hair up and away from my face.   tonight i get to see bok dung, my cat! my sister is taking care of her, so I don't get to see her very often, and i miss her. she is so cute. 

						
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I have learned this the hard way. I have to start studying like crazy or else my whole future will be resigned to low wages and no respect. So, hopefully, now that this site comes up when you search my name, I will gain a readership who will check in now and then to see what I am up to these days. Boy, these sites make you very egotisitcal, to think that you are link number one when you type in your name, even without quotation marks surrounding them.   Something to chew the fat on: would you rather be incredibly hot,  incredibly intelligent or both? 

						
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I forgot to mention that Andy Pettitte is going to be back tonight from being on the DL for fifteen days. He is pitching against the Pirates tonight, who I undestand have been hitting the ball very well these first few weeks of the season.  

						
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Today we get lunch at The Palm. I have never been there, and I understand it's a chain restaurant, but a fairly nice one. Another restaurant I like in the area is Roy's Hawaiin Cuisine. So I am officially addicted to eyeshadow. It is a much better addiction for your health and financial well being than smoking, which I quit several years ago. I will never touch a cigarette again, if I have any willpower at all. And I do. Lots of it. At least when it comes to matters like smoking.  

						
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I finally got my wish in that this site now appears when I search myself on yahoo. It doesn't come up when I search myself on google yet, but the worst is behind me. I can't wait to see Troy, another historical drama. It looks like it has really spectacular battle scenes, and they don't look digitally done.  I also want to go to the Phillies game on May 2nd because they are giving out free pink phillies caps for mothers day appreciation. i can be such a sucker for promotionals, or actually, I am just plain frugal. 

						
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I saw The Alamo last week, which was good. I like historical dramas, especially ones that end tragically, because it makes them truly gut wrenching, which I enjoy. I learned a good deal about the circumstances surrounding The Alamo situation, which is a plus, to be entertained and informed I mean. After seeing that, I had the itch to see Glory again, which is one of my favorite movies. I love how the title of the movie is not without its ironies, the closeness you feel to the characters, their desire to prove themselves in the only way that would matter, by dying. Matthew Broderick is not a manly man, so that makes his bravery even more poignant. I especially like the soldier's head getting blown off at the Battle of Antitiem. 

						
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   i don't mind you coming here and wasting all my time 'cause when you're standing oh so near i kinda lose my mind it's not the perfume that you wear it's not the ribbons in your hair  

						
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I wish I were a genius so I could get a 180 on the LSAT, or at least a 178, like Elle Woods.  Here's what Mike says about my not being able to get a 180:  "You are too smart to get a 180.  To get a 180 you would have to have a very narrow sort of intelligence -- be only analytical --  that would make you a good constitutional law attorney or a good legal theorist but not very smart in other ways."  Thanks Mike, but what if I want to give up my dreams up being a divorce attorney and instead pursue Constitutional Law? Yeah right. 

						
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   here is an interesting article on  urlLink stolen cars . so i need to get round-up weed killer today at target. the weeds are going beserk. they are on plant steroids or something. seriously, our driveway is turning into the amazon rainforest these weeds are so large and scary. these aren't your garden variety dandelions.  my new favorite store is urban outfitters, and my new favorite color is green! i used to think blue was my favorite clothing color, but i like emerald green. actually, i look good in all colors, except earth tones like mustard yellow. 

						
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   i dont normally think of myself as being a very jealous or suspicious person, just competitive. i think they are not entirely unrelated, but they aren't the same thing either.  i need to buy some sunblock, because i am already starting to get too tan. i won't resort to carrying around an umbrella a la michael jackson, but i don't like myself too tan. 

						
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   so i said i was going to lay off the caffeine, but i am not able to do it. i rationalize my lack of will power by saying that i will be less productive at work, so it's okay to feed the addiction.  if i read another annoying person's blog, I am going to go ballistic.  

						
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   i want the christina aguilera cd. i haven't gotten around to it yet, even though it came out last year.   my hair grows really fast. i got bangs about three weeks ago, and they are already growing out, big time.   

						
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   i've been very productive today at work. yay, i am very proud of myself. so it looks like i will not be going to princeton reunions, but i may be going to vermont for memorial day weekend.   the day i give money to princeton is the day i am a decamillionaire. 

						
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   i need to put some pictures on here or something. but i don't have that much html expertise, so this may not happen.  so mike and i saw troy this weekend, which wasn't a bad movie, but i am now very convinced that brad pitt cannot act at all. on the bright side, the movie did inspire mike to work out more because of Hector's impressive arm muscles. btw, the woman who played helen was very attractive, but if i am just as attractive, does that make me the most beautiful woman in the world? or just in philadelphia? 

						
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   i get to eat at  urlLink buddakan . i am so exicted. i don't know if i spelled that correctly, buddakan?   i read in an article that  urlLink vibrant eyeshadow  shades like teal look good on asian people. so try jpeg and digital by smashbox if you fit this description!  

						
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   my neck hurts. i think it has to do with the way my computer screen is facing at my desk.   i don't know how long i can keep up the bare bones living. i mean, i don't even have a cell phone! 

						
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So two things that were weird happened in the elevator today. On the way to lunch, mike and I were in an elevator with a guy who joined in on our conversation and inquired as to whether it was supposed to rain later. Then, on the way back from lunch, when we were discussing lsat test centers that were still available, a different guy who was in the elevator with us looked emotionally invested in what we were talking about.  Is this weird? 

						
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Because I really like the book "The Millionaire Next Door," I went to scope out Thomas Stanley's newer book, "The Millionaire Mind." Stanley gives all these statistics such as the fact that very few millionaires had SAT scores above 1400. Probably because the smarter you are, the more likely you are socially retarted. Being intelligent is also inversely proportional to having common sense, many a time.   I am worried about Bok Dung, our cat, because she has been hiding under the bed a lot, and I understand that when cats don't feel well, they hide.  So for Mother's Day I gave my mom skincare products, because she really likes and appreciates them, and mike thinks that it is a very impersonal gift.  We went to see Van Helsing yesterday, and it was surprisingly good. Frankenstein was more verbose than usual, but his humanitarianism and philosphical nature were impressive. I like when Kate Beckinsale's character asks Frankenstein, "What do you want?" and he simply replies: "I want to exist." Very deep. 

						
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Here are Mike's thoughts on  urlLink The Millionaire Next Door , one of my favorite books. It's not perfect, but it exemplifies the fact that just because someone drives a Volvo or Saab or what have you, doesn't mean he or she is rich, necessarily. It could just mean they care about impressing people. This doesn't mean that you can't be rich and drive a nice car.  He apparently doesn't share this opinion:     Okay, I really liked the book and I am glad you gave it to me; I think I am a better person for reading it.  What I did   not like, however, was that nearly all their examples of professional (doctors, lawyers, etc.) were UAWs and nearly all their PAW examples were people who were entrepeneurs who did not have to dress up for their jobs.  Essentially, the book ignores professionals who have accumulated wealth (of which there are many, including attorneys for whom we work) and other lines of work (like executives) where one must live a certain "business lifestyle" to be successful.  There is an overiding message in the work that if one buys nice things, one can never become wealthy.  Although there is some lip service given to the fact many professionals do have to wear a suit and drive a nice car in order to be successful, this is never really explored, and I think this is negligent on their part because there are many people who buy nice things who accumulate wealth.  One of the last chapters does give numbers that show being a professional is more profitable than being an entrepeneur, but the tone of the authors is anti-professional and pro-entrepeneur; so much so that at one point they felt the need to put a note saying that parents should not tell their children to drop out of college because so many of their examples of successful people were college drop-outs or people who had never attended college.           Had there been more statistical analysis -- or anything other than anecdotal examples -- to back up their conclusions, I would not be ciritical of the work, but what about the professionals who have been successful at accumulating wealth?   There are few examples (the Dr. North/Dr. South comparison is the only real one, and I do not think the PAW, Dr. North, represents professionals who are urban and cannot live a "country doctor" low cost lifestyle).  And what about Average Accumulators of Wealth?  They are outright ignored, even though these people succeed at accumulating wealth and buying moderate amounts of expensive things.  It is certainly interesting to learn about the extremes of wealth accumulations, but if there is an "average" wealth accumulating lifestyle, I would love to learn about and not just be left with the impression that it is impossible to accumulate wealth if you are not a pure PAW.         The reason I say this is an "ideological" work is that it excludes examples of PAW's who are professionals and executives but includes many, many examples of UAW's who are professionals and executives.  Furthermore, their only examples of people who accumulate wealth are extremely frugal, and there are many people who have accumualted wealth who are not as frugal as the examples.  This would make any reader  who is not a professional or an executive feel positive about their chances of accumulating wealth, but by using such selective examples they attack an entire segment of the population who are high earners without using data or other hard research to back up their depictions of professionals and executives as UAWs.  I agree there are many high earners in these occupations who do spend a lot, but what about the others?  I know they exist.  If I were a college dropout I would not care, but as a future professional I would like to know about ways they can accumulate wealth and be successful in their line of work, or at least see real data on overall wealth accumulation.  From the examples cited in the work, it appears it is impossible to accumulate wealth if you have to wear a suit to work.  

						
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I can't believe it's May 3rd already. This is really depressing. Sometimes I really wish things were different from the way they are, and I am trying to change them one step at a time. I'm hungry, I need breakfast, then maybe I'll feel better. 

						
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   i was thinking of getting mike a bottle of jean paul gautlier's "le male summer fragrance," but there were some deterrents. The main problem the bottle is HUGE! 4.2 ounces. I mean, I don't want to encourage him to douse himself like mr. way to much cologne wearer. another problem is that the bottle which is shaped like a man's torso is too "gaiye." i can't encourage that kind of behavior.   

						
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   so, i was watching the nba draft with mike, and jameer nelson, who is from philadelphia, didn't get picked till number 20. And the cameras kept panning over to him every time they called out picks and he wasn't being chosen. Seriously, from pick 11 to 20 they showed him, looking really sad with his son. When he was passed over one time he shook his head! I was upset that they were making him look really pathetic and you could read the disappointment all over his face. why does the media like to humiliate people? also, they were playing the song "I want you to want me" when they put the camera on him!  friday! i want to get chicken wings at 'mad for mex' and a strawberry frozen margarita. 

						
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So when I took the LSAT last Monday, I saw this girl I sort of know through my sister, and that was pretty weird because she sat right in front of me during the test. Then afterward, I went to the mall to blow off some steam (females go to the mall, men get drunk, or something like that) and low and behold, not only was SHE there, but another girl I recognized from the test center. I think we were all mutually embarrassed because of our shameless predilection for power shopping to chase away the blues. or rather, i power window shop, because i am a combination of both cheap and broke.  mike and i saw the stepford wives, and i haven't seen the original or read the book, but because there are so many cultural references to "stepford wives," i wanted to see what all of the fuss was about. i thought the message of "perfection is imperfect" was a little oversimplified, and hence not very satisfying. what was satisfying, however, was Glenn Close going ballistic at the end. she is always very convincing when she goes psycho. 

						
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   nicole is registered at macy's for her wedding. you can also register at target and walmart. i was saying to my sister and mike that i wouldn't want anything that was permanently going to be in my house from target, much less walmart.  i should feel relieved that the lsat is over, but i am not because i don't know what my score is, and i won't for another four weeks. this sucks. i feel like i can't relax, when really, that is exactly what i should be doing. 

						
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   my free advice to young women everywhere- do not become involved with the following people:  1. selfish bastards who need Levitra or Cialis  any questions? 

						
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   so i took the lsat on monday and i think i did okay, but i really can't tell because the curve changes substantially depending on how others do on the test. i guess i will find out soon enough.  i was intereted in "the millionaire woman next door," by stanley danko, but it was horrible! i was flipping through it and it is basically useless. why is it that book sequels, like movie sequels, are worthless?  btw, i majored in english and i hate to read. weird. 

						
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Did anyone read this thing about the  urlLink hottest girls at princeton ? the funny part is that i am better looking than every single one of these girls. hands down, no contest. 

						
</post>


</Blog>