<Blog>


<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Crimplesnoff will be leaving BlogSpot in favor of an adfree server before the weekend is over. More details as they are worked out.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Gmail is astounding. Today I sent a few emails and saw the magic of "conversation view", as Gmail calls it. Instead of storing each email separately, the Gmail user sees emails in context with their replies. This is especially good for referring to a conversation you forgot about.  The interface is sleek and Google-style cool/functional. Instead of loading new pages all over the place like most web email, Gmail shows a small "Loading" in the corner of the screen, and even on my slow dialup, loads quickly.  Problem is, all this coolness is made possible by JavaScript. Browsers without it, like the one on my T-Mobile Sidekick, can't use Gmail. One flaw in a great design so far.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I mentioned on my old xanga a few days ago  urlLink these  little cutout, foldup arcade games.  Today I found loads more of the same sort of thing, including:    urlLink "Make Your Own Mac"  Those of you who like Macs or iPods, have fun making these fake ones     urlLink Papercraft  This site is half in Japanese, but if you click on the "Remote CTL" button on the left-hand side, you can choose from many different cutout thingys.   Have fun!
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yes! I got two Gmail accounts from blogs. I may give away an invitation or two here when I have them.  It is most certainly the best webmail ever. Not just because of the gig of space, either. The interface is clean and fast and useful, and overall the service is amazing. Yay Gmail!
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      New site feed links are now in the sidebar for anyone who wants them.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I had a  urlLink xanga  but it wasn't right for me. I'd rather post fun stuff that interests me (what I did on xanga anyway) than write a journal (yuck.)  If you're wondering about "crimplesnoff", let me fill you in. The word is meaningless, but fun and random, hopefully in the spirit of the blog itself.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      A true Google mirror... image, that is. www.alltooflat.com/geeky/elgoog/  The rest of All Too Flat is also quite good. 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Daily, I and my younger brother Alex each select a word, his from the  "New Dictionary of American Slang" and mine from a real dictionary.  Real Word of the Day: taradiddle- (n.) a minor falsehood  Slang Word of the Day: snurge- (v.) to avoid work, esp. by sneaking away 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink cockeyed.com  is simply one of the best websites in existence. Go read it. I'd start with the pranks or "How Much is Inside". Trust me, you will get hooked.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I have an invitation to Gmail, and I'm giving it away to the person who can (drumroll please) give the best (i.e. funniest) definition of the word "Crimplesnoff". I may get more, in which case I plan to give second and third place invites.  Nine points for your idea funniness, and a bonus point for linking to Crimplesnoff on your webpage or blog. In the event of a tie, I'll think of some sort of tiebreaker.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      UtterlyBoring has a contest going on: http://utterlyboring.com/archives/2004/06/23/gmail_invite_jeopardy_contest.php Good luck!
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Crimplesnoff will complete the move promised, but possibly after the weekend is through. I am finding a server, but the process is long. The only free domain names I can find are ".co.nr"... so I'm debating that too.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Another recommended site. Homestarrunner.com is my new favorite. Everybody! Everybody!
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The funniest entry to my Gmail contest was submitted by dalinbe19 with:  "Crimplesnoff (v.): to coerce or trick others into thinking something is desirable when it is in fact repulsive. ex. "If you ever want to get married, you'll have to crimplesnoff the bimbo.""  Thanks to all entrants!
     
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Lately I've been thinking about ways to make Google recognize  Crimplesnoff for more searches. I won't stoop to the level of adding  useless keywords to this blog. I could offer FREE LAPTOPS, iPODs or a  chance to win A MILLION DOLLARS or other CASH AND PRIZES. Nah, publicity  stunts don't suit me or the ULTRA morals and standards of this blog. 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Get nostalgic! You don't need to play text adventures to enjoy classic  computer games: little games from the 90s don't take up memory and are  often inspired. The-underdogs.org has SimTower, an incredible old Maxis  game, and many others, free. 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       "Now is the time for action... We recognize the font may be appropriate in a few specific instances, {but} our position is that the only effective means of ending the epidemic of abuse is to completely ban Comic Sans."   Rock on! The folks at  urlLink BanComicSans.com  know what they're talking about. That ugly font has spread like runny mustard on a clean plate. I ask all readers to take a stand! Over at the site, they've got some great propaganda to pin up or stick up. Join the revolution. Or rather the antirevolution. 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Little changes in the web world:  new!  urlLink h*r  strong bad email:  urlLink "crying" . Strong Bad makes Homestar cry.  semi-new!  urlLink angry alien productions :  urlLink Alien  in 30 seconds, with bunnies. (really The Shining is the best bunny reenactment.)
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       "Time is an illusion. Lunchtime doubly so."   - Ford Prefect,  The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy , by Douglas Adams   So better grab your PB&J lunch break while you can ;)   But this is, actually, a book rec, in disguise as a clever reply to Carson's post, which made me think of it. If ANYONE reading this has not read the all of the above-mentioned book/trilogy/series, or any of it, OR -insert scandalized gasp of horror here- perchance has not heard of Douglas Adams at ALL - GET THEE TO&nbsp;A BOOKSTORE!! Especially if you're a Discworld fan. Douglas Adams is a lot like Terry Pratchett plus spaceships, more random humor &amp; wackiness, and minus magic, giant Moving turtles, and any semblance of a plotline whatsoever. XD Put it this way: if you're reading this blog, you ought to also be reading Douglas Adams. There is no other way.   And for all you fanfiction geeks out there: Douglas Adams is, IMO, the creator of the world's longest, best, and FUNNIEST PWP - in the PG-13, ff.net,  original  sense of the acronym. So go read it!! NOW! 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      A double decker peanut butter and jelly sandwich is one of life's great  pleasures. Well made, it is a good breakfast or lunch, with milk it is  heavenly. A good sandwich is made with extra crunchy PB and strawberry  preserves (raspberry is also good) on thick wheat bread. Go take a lunch  break. It's good for your soul. 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Bah. To rebut the rebuttal (I'm not a debater, I just argue ^^):  1. :P Gmail rox meh sox. Especially the labels. The labels are even better than the conversation system. I compulsively label EVERYTHING that comes through my inbox. So there.  2. But I do occasionally electrocute him through the modem ;)  3. Yes.  4. IMHO = In My Humble Opinion - except i should really take out the H. *snicker* WIKTT = don't ask, don't tell ;) Unless you already ship that pairing, you probably don't want to know.  5. Yes, and yes. Hence the "victorious chai latte" thing in my siggy -&nbsp;I once tried to explain my SN to someone who couldn't understand randomness, and had to use "Java" as a sort-of-but-not-really synonym for "Jaza," which sounds much cooler. He then said, "Oh, so it's sorta like a chai latte?" -_- Go figure. But it was funny, so there you are.  6. See #4 B. 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Like any good extemp speaker, I'll break it into points.  1. Yes, Cathy got a Gmail invite before I offered them to you. Hey, what  do you expect?  2. Cathy only dangles me from windows every once in a while.  3. That quote is mine and is from an IM conversation.  4. I don't know what any of those acronyms mean.  5. Cathy explained to me that Nike is 'victorious' in Greek. I'm almost  sure she made Jaza up.  6. I'm as confused about the driftwood thing as you are.  There you go, readers. I'm pleased to welcome fellow asylum escapee  Cathy to Crimplesnoff. 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Hi! This is your friendly neighborhood geek speaking. To thank Carson for giving me a gmail invite awhile back (& he's not kidding about the wonders of conversation organizing ^^), I snuck into his hotel room in SC &amp; dangled him out the window until he let me join the blog. HOORAY!!!   Just kidding, haha ha ha. . . yeah. Actually, I'm here because     "i have noticed that we have many of the same tendencies toward insanity. i also wish to retry the failed blog experiment. so my offer is for a membership (ie password) to Crimplesnoff, my blog."   Thank you, Carson  . The "failed blog experiment" refers to a politicaly-oriented blog called The Angry Democrat, which ran for a VERY short while last year. My condolences to anyone who happened to read it.     Anyway,  I  think I'm here because - IMHO - the blog could use a bit more from the non-slashdot side of web-culture geekiness. *snickers behind her hand at Carson's reaction to some of her online obsessions* Is there a WIKTT member in the house? *dies laughing* ANYWAY - this was one hell of an odd intro post, but here I am:    Keeper of Driftwood "Ships" Stalker of&nbsp;Carson (*snicker*) Theatre Geek Extraordinaire&nbsp; - JazaNike - ...the victorious chai latte ;)   
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      For those curious about the move I mentioned, it will not happen... at  least not soon. I'm fairly happy with BlogSpot for now. If this blog  grows to the point of needing adfree hosting and image serving I'll  move. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Google finally lists me first for a search for "Crimplesnoff", not  UtterlyBoring.com's mention of my winning its gmail contest! Hurray! 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It's late and I need sleep, but instead I'm blogging. Will this affect  quality? You decide.  Never buy the dark blues in Monopoly. Seriously, they are nothing but an  expense for people who don't have 3000 dollars SPARE. You WILL NOT make  back your investment because  1. Low probability of landing on them to get the monopoly.  2. High cost of houses/hotels  3.  Low probability of somebody landing on your properties.  Don't fall into the trap, my friends. Until next time, play for the gold  properties and eat your spinach. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      To my loyal fans, both of you, (insert rim shot here) I'm sorry for my blog gap. I was vacationing in the mountains and even my trusty T-Mobile Sidekick refused to connect.   Some little updates for you, because I care:  1. There's a new Strong Bad Email on homestarrunner.com. It's called 'pom pom'.  2. Seth Mc(or Mac?)Farlane, creator of Family Guy, will be introducing his favorite episodes all this week on Adult Swim.  3. The PS2 game "Frequency" is worth buying. This game is very cool.  That's it, neighbors! Get off my lawn!
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Some elements of all road trips are similar and should be noted. Now, as  I'm on one (not driving, don't worry) I feel I ought to note them here  before I stop caring about it.  1. Food. The chain "Country Kitchen" is one I would not eat at, ever,  save those frequent road trip visits. The reason? It exists in a  parallel universe accessible only to road travelers. Similarly, "real"  restaurants like the ones you eat at back home and when you get where  you're going, are excluded from this universe. Probably to give Country  Kitchen more business.  2. Shops. On road trips, and only on road trips, signs like "Used  Usables" pop up everywhere. "Amish Furnishings and Canned Goods" exists  in the same parallel universe as Country Kitchen.  3. Broad generalizations. On all road trips, bloggers have the urge to  make hugely broad generalizations.  Now excuse me please while I figure out how to get 134 Mason jars of  peaches and an oak table from the Amish market in my trunk. 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It's around 1:30 and I just got back from a returns party for Claire McCaskill (claireonline.com), a Democratic contender for Missouri governor. Tonight we watched the results come in and found out that she beat incumbent Bob Holden in the Democratic primaries.  I hadn't been to one of these things before. They are definitely interesting. If you're interested in the results, that is. We watched Holden concede on a big screen that had been playing results from the local news all night, and then Claire stepped up and talked about beating the Republicans in November. Very cool.  If you have the chance to do something like this, I recommend it. Get involved in politics in your area. And hey, if you live in Missouri, please send some money  urlLink Claire's way.  Blunt, her Republican opponent, is very well funded and had little primary trouble.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      For those of you who have a website of some sort,  urlLink RE_INVIGORATE's data archiving service  is an incredible free service for tracking website statistics invisibly. Go check it out! 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today, make it a priority to listen to some songs you've never heard on  CDs you've owned for years: underrated songs, the B side songs of old  records. Today, pull out a CD you bought for two songs and listen to  them all. You will be pleasantly surprised at your discoveries. Maybe  you'll even find a few new favorites. Today, grab a snack and press  "shuffle". 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I love my iPod, no question about it. It comes with me everywhere, and I  strongly feel that the iPod is the greatest technology ever used to  store music. I bought mine a month ago- 15 gigs for $299. Within the  last week, Apple dropped prices and upgraded the product. Now a 4th gen  20 gig model is $299. Meep. In a year or two I'll buy whatever new  flavor they've got. Then I'll be atop the curve... for a week or two.  Now playing on my (slightly) outdated iPod: Supertramp, "Breakfast in  America". Classic rock with great lyrics and construction... not to  mention the British accent. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Before I begin, let me put your fears to rest. I am not going to ruin  air navigation with my Sidekick's wireless signal. I've got the wireless  off. This entry will submit once I turn wireless on again in the  airport.  (insert Monty Pythonesque "Get on with it!" here)  The nerve of some people is incredible. The woman in front of me  reclined her seat on takeoff, thereby forcibly placing my tray in a  groove in my knee. This I tolerate. Maybe she has no idea of the  discomfort she is placing upon me. I begin to feel angry when the same  woman requests in that snooty 'I am better than you and I know it' voice  that I refrain from pushing her seat. Before I could look up from trying  in vain to remove an object from the bag she resticted my access to, she  turned around.  I feel better now. Maybe my next post will be less..... um... hateful.  For now, merry Christmas and a happy new year. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Expect light blogging and partly cloudy skies as I fly back to my  Midwestern home from South Carolina. (You can make up your own South  joke. Don't expect me to do everything for you.)  Until next time, laugh at parts of the movie that aren't funny. Loudly. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>