<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Was feeling very bored today, so decided to change the template of my blog.  Feel free to tell me how the blog is looking now?   UPDATE >>> On Public (read makuchacku's) request, I am back to a similar template to the old one.  
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I was just surfing the Internet and I did a search for Ankit Malik (my name!) and it showed up a few links I already knew but..  There was a new link too which surprised me! It was a link to fedoranews.org  For those who came in late, Fedora is a Linux distribution which is extremely popular. Its like the Windoze of the Linux world( though some won't agree) [without the bugs of course!]  The article was about FC3, the next release of Fedora series. And they mentioned my name in that  urlLink  article.         "The Fedora Core 3 outlook    Now's the time to think about Fedora Core 3 ................(it goes on)        Ankit Malik  started a   Fedora Core 3 Wishlist   thread, which grew relatively large........................ "              
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
             What is it about Yahoo! ?      They are giving out 100 MB to new Y! customers but not to the old ones.    This is so sickening. I am still waiting for my 100 MB .  
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       A special thanks goes to Ms. Heather for weeding out the various grammatical errors/ typos/ incorrect phrases that plague my blog.         
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
              Software Freedom Day is coming soon. And I am afraid the Indian  representation is way less. We need more volunteers to spread GNU amoong India: where one-sixth of the world population resides   So let us all join for the cause of FOSS (Free and Open Software for the unintiated). Buzz me @ ankitmalik@gmail.com if you are interested.   For those who aren't aware: here is what SFD is all about:     "On August 28, 2004, we will celebrate the first annual Software  Freedom Day. On that day, we will make the world aware of the virtues  of Free and Open Source Software (FOSS), and encourage its widespread  use. We will set up stations in public places to give away  informational fliers and CDs with selected FOSS, including TheOpenCD   and a Linux Live CD.This is a global grassroots marketing campaign in  which we are inviting volunteers from around the world to participate."        To catch up with it log on to  urlLink http://softwarefreedomday.org    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Eeks! Why do  people keep talking about Linux? It must be so technical! And definitely it must be awful to look at. My Win...oze XP looks much better than this!   If these are your thoughts: then FOLKS I have three words for you: YOU ARE WRONG!  Don't believe me or what??? See for yourself  urlLink here    (This link take you to my Linux Screenshot Gallery) 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       A Slap on the face of M$ Windows    Check it out @   urlLink http://algolog.tripod.com/linux/slap.htm      
    
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Have been trying out different distros these days.    First it was Lycoris: poor ! Then it was SuSe - the installer didnt start up !!! Also couldnt find any statement to tell it to start  YaST 9the SuSe installer) with VESA on the SUSE Support Site.      Then came Knoppix 3.4  : Gosh ! it has improved so much. It's much slicker and much faster than before! And it took exactly 10 minutes  to install on my Celeron 851 MhZ/128 MB Ram  Plus the fact that its based on Debian makes it easier to add more packages. All I need to do is    apt-get install kdegames  and all my games are there ! People say Debian is for advanced users but it's my first experience and I find it much easier   than RPMs.  And the SPEED -  it rocks on Knoppix! My KDE on Fedora was a crawl! Knoppix + KDE is much,  much faster.   BTW, If anyone's looking for Knoppix in India: mail me @ ankitmalik@gmail.com     Check out  urlLink www.knopper.com  for more info.   
    
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      Get Firefox ! Man it surely rocks    Have been using it since months!    And i now wonder how i used to survive with Internet Explorer!!!!    Its better than IE for sure.    Want more reasons before you try it out?   urlLink Click Here     
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey Everybody!  For all those wanting to shift to Linux but wan' a peek of it before doing so; visit my Photo-Gallery Linux @ Work   urlLink Click Here  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Want a GMAIL Account but don't know where to look for:   There are options galore albeit @ a price!  a)  eBay b)  Bazee c)  www.gmailswap.com  At GMAILSWAP  you can exchange some of your good things for a GMAIL account!!!! Sounds perfect right???   So what are you waiting for??? Rush before your name is taken !   
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Eureka! Eureka!   Its finally out  Harry Potter's sixth book will be named 'Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince'.  Whoa!  And if you think this is just a rumour; check it for yourself on  urlLink www.jkrowling.com   ___________________________________________________________________________________________________  BTW if you're wondering who the Half-Blood prince is; lemme help you; its neither Harry, nor, the *sweet* Voldermort - according to JK Rowling! 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Looking for Fedora Core 2 in India but don't know where to get it?   urlLink Click here  for a no-nonsense page where you can buy FC2 (@ the cost of medium and shipping) 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Hello World.    I'm back after a long long time. I have deleted the boring blogs and  started afresh.  Hey! This blog is now accessible through  urlLink www.scribbler.tk   urlLink www.ankit.uni.cc  and  urlLink ankitmalik.blogspot.com   ____________________  P.s. You can now even post your comments.    Long Live Blogspot    
    
    
</post>


</Blog>