<Blog>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hello and welcome to my first official post, weel relevant post  Well i've been packing, and helping move into my new place, and help my aunt uncle and gramma move storage stuff out... and i've been trying to keep up in school and hope to go on this new field trip to vancouver..you get to go to UBC and the museum of anthropology and BCIT and the aquarium..and i have free time for 4 hours and i can hit metrotown to look at grad dresses and shop a bit!  I have been having issues...just with my lack of sleep and lack of understanding in the school work departement, mostly math...and then there is stupid people that i can't stand lately and want to make disappear...  I hate stupid people, with a firey passion, i wish they could all just get a life and stay out of mine, they are so nosey and stupid, and have nothing intellegent to say, it pisses me off and they bring the hate on themselves, and they think their so cool, which is quite pathetic...  I want to get a job... I have been handing out resume's and letters of recommendation, but I seem to be having no luck in that departement..It sux...I've been trying to print more, but have been so busy that I haven't had time...  I have been asked to return to myvolunteer experience job... they loved my help and enthusiasm...but Im really busy with the things that are going on and have not much time for a life...Im drinking right now, so im not thinking too straight...  Well I must be going for no I'll write more later possibly tomorrow  ~Nicki~       You are going to Marry Josh Hartnett. He is really shy, but don't let that fool you. He is really outgoing and sweet with those he loves and will be loyal to them for the rest of his life. Congrats!!    urlLink   Which male celebrity are you going to marry? (now 12 (i just added more, and still more to come!)results that have pics!)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey hey all, this is my first entry...but i'll emphasize when i have something interesting to say!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Ya divorce, the dreaded word you hear parents say when they don't get along, and feel they need other people to make them happy. I heard that word almost&nbsp;1 year ago, but its still in progress... my parents separated about 2 and a half years ago now, and it was a good thing, but that doesn't make it easy to deal with.. I mean there's kids involved, ones that get caught in the middle, there is a lying father, who tries to be there now that he's not part of their lives and a mother who does everything in her power to keep her kids safe, even though she only works&nbsp;1 job, and if it wasn't for child and spousal support, she'd never be home. But no matter how every 1 tells me divorce is a good thing, I can't help thinking that there is an easier way, its not that I want my parents to get back together or anything, its just that if my dad could see how his lies and deciet are hurting his kids, then maybe he'd understand that we love him (even if we don't like him at times) and maybe he'd&nbsp; see that we have good reason for not liking his girlfriend...for example, we may like her if she hadn't ended a 4 year friendship with my mom, rudely&nbsp;I might add, and kept my father and her's realtionship a secret, which hurt the kids in the long run, because she wouldn't have my brother for the weekend as she was guilty for hooking up with my dad, then maybe we would try to tollerate her, but she took this family for a ride, and deserves every look we give her, good or bad, thats the price you pay, and she has to except that. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; And it doesn't help my dad by putting his girlfriend in front of his kids, which he's proven, by saying we have to tollerate her, and that he won't go&nbsp;a weekend without her, and the fact that he gets home on weekends and spends them with his girlfriend instead of calling his kids or comming to see them for a couple hours...I know what your saying, some people have every right to see their boy/girl friend, but not at the expense of blowing off his kids....my brother and sister are gonna rebel one of these days, and there isn't a damn thing he'll be able to do about it. &nbsp; well i gtg, leaving &nbsp; ttyl &nbsp; ME!!&nbsp; 
     

    
</post>


<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      this is my new site...i will be updating it often, however...i do not apreciate stupid comments on my chat box...so please refrain for you immaturity, thank you..and another thing if ur passing thru and u happen to see something on here that disturbs you or you don't get, please don't be afraid to ask me.   Today i am babysitting, its not so bad one is sleeping right now so s'all good, and the other is watching lilo and stitch, so he's quiet too. they're not that bad, but sometimes they scream when they don't get there way, but other then that they're good kids.   I have been finding out a few interesting things this week. Like the only person in this world you can is you, and that you always need to watch what u say around your supposed friends, because some of them miht just turn around and stab you in the back, and trust me im learning that the hard way. you see i have this male friend for reasons i won't explain now, lets change his name, well call him todd. Now i thought todd was my friend, you know a good guy who was fun to hang around with and are pretty cool, but i was off on that one...on his website he wrote that i was a mental case and that i worshiped him, and that i needed happy pills to make myself feel better. So i had a few stressful days, does that make me a mental case?? i don't think so. And as for having to stay home from school to take care of my brother and sister...he totally switched my words around..i said that while i was home sick, if my sibling came home sick at least i'd be there to take care of them while my mom was at work. He irks me so much. how in the hell can he think of himself so highly?? He shits and farts like the rest of us? so why does he think he's all high and mighty? he has flaws, he has issues like the rest of us. So why doesn't he come off his high horse and spend a day in reality for a while??  Anywayz...my mom had surgery schedualed on the 18th, but she had to cancel it, because she schedualed to work the next day, so she has no healing time...but she still has to pay the bill which is shitty...thats $300 that could go to something more important, like food and supplies for the house...not a surgery she isn't getting. I think it plain out sux..she shouldn't have to pay for it if she's not getting it done.  But hey Im 17 in 7 days...one whole week and i start a new year...yeah..Im going to be having a party on the 27th, the day after i take my driving test, cuz i can't have it the same day, cuz if i fail i'll be too embarrassed to see anyone. Im just gonna rent movies, order pizza and chill with a few close friends. Im not having a big blow out. Theres not much point until im old enough to legally drink, cuz then it'll be huge and awsome. But i'll probably watch fear & loathing in las vegas with the gang then another one with the sleep over buds, but im not sure which one yet!! im so indecisive when it comes to that sorta thing, i wanna see every movie, so it doesn't work that way. But thats just me, i like good movies...and i know there's some i've never seen that are probably really good. My friend emily tries to open my eyes to new movie swhen she can, and tries to be the best friend ever, which she is, and im sorry to those of whom i've been a bitch to..with the stress and the PMS i gues my attitude got a little out of hand, and i don't mean to spaz on people, but i feel strongly about so many things that my opinion takes over and i defend my beliefs...im sorry if you don't like that but its who i am, and i won't change for anyone, so if you don't accept me the way i am, then get out of my life, because i don't need or want friends like you.  I am in a very good mood today, but i had to express myself, because of my open minded opinion....lol...irony eh?? anywayz i must be going...i need to relax for a bit cuz im kinda tired...im trying to put together a dance for a talent show comming up...me and my over extending myself...*big smiles*...i'll be sure to write in here again when i have the time...and i will try to write in here everyday if i can...Well i'll talk to you all later   Your Sincerly  Lil' Nicki    
     

    
</post>

<date>19,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      WOW!! worshiping men! now thats a topic and a half eh?? well i don't worship men...i don't believe any living woman should ever worship a man, its wrong in so many wayz... Its so degrating and de-evolutionizing...In Fact it makes me quite sick to my stomache to even consider worshiping a man...its not my thing..  Just a little tid bit u might wanna know!
     

    
</post>

<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hello hello..and how is everyone this fine evening?? tee hee hee..im doin awsome...i took my food safe today, and.....i got 82%!!!i PASSED!! im so happy, now i have my food safe. Its good training, and it looks awsome on a resume, so its all good. Oh and hey, my moms working and doin great, and she doesn't have to pay the $300 surgery bill... so its good...she didn't get it done yet and it kinda irritates her still but she'll get it done later...She knnows its not cancerous however so thats a good thing!!   Anywayz...im trying to get a picture in the backround and im not quite sure how... I know i have to upload it onto the comp, but Im not exactly sure just how to go about that yet...but im gonna go, i'll write some more later!!  From Ur             Lil' Nicky
     

    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      HEY HEY HEY!!!!    How goes it everyone??? long time no talk...i've been busy and totally swamped with homework cuz i've been sick for two days!!! It sucked but it was still pretty cool staying home..... I felt like I was dying but im glad im better now....    I saw "todd" the other day.... i made sure he knew i was doing well now.... and i know he's seen me without me seeing him cuz in his sight he said he saw me and noticed i was much happier, but i don't remember seeing him, but whatever...    I GOT MY LEARNERS!!!! I can drive...yes!!!!!!!!!!!!!! im sooooooo happy.  I've been out driving once, and i wanna go again, but i need someone to take me first.....    Well i guess i gtg...i need to get some homework done...ttyl...  Lil' Nicky
     

    
</post>

<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ewwwwwwwwwww...biology is icky..... I have to do i stupid project about the worms humans can contract....it is wrong in so many ways...im sitting next to Miss Emily, who's site is  http://www.bardintraining.blogspot.com, and she feels that same way, no one deserves worms in there butt...The pictures make u wanna vomit, and the info's so descriptive its not much better... you most definetly don't wanna see these pics people there awful...    On a new note...I have allergies, to what i dunno, but my sinuses are acting up hella lately, it sux...And i never had allergies before, why do i have to have them now??    I talked to "todd" yesterday...and i've decided that he'll get whats comming to him, and im not gonna be the one to give it to him...though im definetly not attracted to him anymore, i will still be his friend!    Im soo tired, i've not got a sufficiant ammount of sleep in the past couple days...because i've been staying up working on due projects and studying  for tests that i have to take before the long weekend...it sux lotz but whateves, no biggy, i'll just sleep lotz on the weekend, other then saturday...my dad is comming down on that day, to see us and give us stuff from the "Easter Bunny" that he left at dad's house...like its real or sumthin?? And then I have to go up there on the weekend, and try to make the best of it...so i won't be on the comp from the 16-18 because he lives in the stone age and has no computer, and if he did, we'd never be allowed to go on it, and i doubt it'd even have internet...stupid old people....tee hee hee...well i guess i'd better go and work on this project thing, cuz i think i only have today to work on it, so i gotta get lotza stuff done....Oh ya, and only about a week left in term 3..then i get a spare..YIPPEE!!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      OH MY GOD!!!!!! capp projects suck major ultimate ass!!!!! there is almost no information about heroin on the net, i can't seem to find any decent usable information, and nothing i can really use to get my point across...not to mention my blog is be way stupid...it doen't want to work for me today...im gonna go get a drink while the comp goes to hell i think...write more later...bye  Your        Lil' Nicky
     

    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      OH MY GOD!!!!!!! shoot me now someone please!!!...i don't wanna go to my dads...its so totally boring up there, there is nothing to do at all, and everyone looks like a hillbilly, hillblillie, oh god i dun't even now how to spell it, so i put both ways...i mean so what if i get to see danielle, my best friend, but who else?? no one else talks to me anymore, because of stupid jelous people spreading rumours about me...its quite pathetic...I really don't wanna go, I mean he has me so emotionally scarred already, because of all his bullshit.     And he's the one that left, he walked out, my mom didn't kick him out, he thought it would be for the best if he left...so he cannot turn around and say my mom kicked him out, because she didn't. But of course he lives in his own little reality so as far as he's concerned she kicked him out....and he has been telling everyone that...saying my mom wanted him gone, and booted his ass out the door...he's so full of shit...GOD he makes me so mad.....     I wanna see a bunch of people up there and see if i can get some shorts, but i have no real reason t stay other then to watch my brother and sister and make sure "dad" doesn't brainwash them into wanting to live with him...so i go.    Well i guess i'd better go, im in a spare block right now, and have a few things to finish. write more later, bye 4 now     Your             Lil' Nicky
     

    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Peace. You Truly Desire Peace. Just relaxing somewhere calm with a light breeze against your cheecks is our ideal of pefect. You don't like to start fights, but instead, end them without using violence.   PLEASE RATE     urlLink   What Do You Truly Desire? *PICS*     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
        well well well arent u lucky.lestat loves u with all his black little heart and would never want to leave u.he is divoted to pleasing u and would do anything just to be with u. he loves ur looks persinality and ur voice. and he loves taping into ur mind. he finds it a very odd but wonderful place. he see that u have very great intelligence and are way past ur time. check out the sequel to the quiz and PLEASE PLEASE PLEASE RATE    urlLink   how would a vampire react after meeting u?(girls only)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
        your asshole.    urlLink   What swear word are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Your: Wondering eyes. Your not quite focused and your quite the day dreamer. Your a bit odd and as many say "Your head is in the clouds."     urlLink   What type of eyes do you have?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
        You're Exotic Dancer Barbie.  You have some moves, and will do anything for a few bucks.  Take it off girl, but keep it PG-13 please.    urlLink   If You Were A Barbie, Which Messed Up Version Would You Be?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Forrest Gump!    urlLink   What movie Do you Belong in?(many different outcomes!)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     

    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i just got myself a new gmail address its hotty.in.black@gmail.com, so mail me on that too if you'd like, just tryin sumthin new...chat at ya'll later ME!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink     
     

    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink     What lame pick up line are you?  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
        A GARAGE-GURL. Youre into loud music, hot guys and wild fashions. Youre most at ease when you've got all your mates around you and you like to party. Boys are a game and youre always on the ball because you make sure youre always number one. Your virtues: Confidence, fun nature, sociability. Your flaws: Loudness, jealous tendency, need for attention..     urlLink   What kind of girl are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hello an welcome to my site... Im not in tip top condition today, sorry...i guess it kinda hard when u will probably have to move outa your house cuz the landlords put it up for sale, and its possibly sold to a couple from calgary, so it definetly won't be a rental home, which basically means i have 2 months to find a new place to live...which is really stupid because we have been excellent tendants, never had a lete check or anything... but i guess they just decided they don't want the house anymore... they don't like being landlords or something... whatever i don't care... wel i do, but im not going to bore you with the sad details that piss me off... I talked to "todd" the other day ( remember, i changed his name for personal reasons... im actually curtious of other peoples feeling, unlike him who pastes my name all over his website) and he's doing ok, i guess, hey was playing in the hall with a ball, and we got sent outside for makin lotza noise, guess we were laughing to loud.. I dunno, no big or anything... Oh hey, if any one out there knows Destiny Cusson...tell her i wanna kick her ass...she said i was ugly and a basically called me a virginic whore (now theres an oxymoron for ya) but she's not exactly the brightest crayon in the box...but im sick of her shit, and if she can't back off and let me live my life im gonna beat the piss right outa her perma-pregnant little body (she just recently got another abortion, whats that #5??) but whateves who cares about her or what she thinks?? i don't, and no one in duncan should either, because nothing that comes outs her mouth is believable...  Wowits amazing how writing here makes me feel so much better..ttyl....~Hugs to all my friends~                    Sippie (new nick name...long story)
     

    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am an  Aries .  (Also known as "Ram")  My  urlLink  Horroscope   starts like this:  "  Aggressive to the extreme, the Aries is primitive - warlike and cruel. Not the sharpest tool in the shed, he often has trouble remembering the simplest of things. The Aries will often try to backstab his peers, but luckily, he usually lacks the mental capacity to succeed. He is vulgar and blunt, and incapable of subtelty.   " ( urlLink  Read more   |  urlLink  Find yours  )
     

    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey hey hey every 1 and whats shakin with ya'll??? me basically nuthin new 2 report, other then i went driving today, and i past parkland and went down a road i'd pretty much never seen before, until now...and it was a dead end, there was nothing there...the road just ended with a chain and a do not enter sign...oh and backing up in a van is definetly interesting... nothing like i've ever done before, but it was still lotxa fun...   I had a drink the other night, a rum & coke, and i might have another 1 tonight if i can, but other then that im just gonna do homework and chill before i try (for once) to get a good nights sleep tonight.  I've been having a pretty good week, other then the fact that my house might be sold and i might have move out of the house, even thought i just moved into it in August...but other then that, I've been talking on the phone to my friend and Im gonna be driving more this comming week, hopefully to dean park, and home again...  Oh hey i have a job interview tomorrow, and i really hope that goes well, but i can only work on weekends, and possible evenings, it depends on if my mom is working or not, because i'll have to babysit.  Well I best be going for now...but i hadn't writtien a letter in this thing for a while so i had to update it instead of just putting quiz results in here  write more later  Nicole
     

    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey hey hey  how is everyone this fine almost afternoon??? It is 10:57am and i am stitting in my library at school, and i am writing a book....im not quite done yet, but when i am i'll be sure to let ya'll know, hell i may even get it published if i think its good enough...but i just started it a while ago, so it will take some time before its finished....depends on how motivated i am...lol....i get to go driving today, my mom is gonna take me out and teach me how to back up properly i think...but i might get to go over the overepass too, well my gramma said she'd take me over that, so i might not get to, but with my mom i might get to go past 30km/h...and i ight not spend lotza time in the church parking lot by my grammas house before that.... i really don't know whats going on after chool, but i know i wanna get a drink before then....  well i best be going...get some work done before the bell rings.  write more later or ttyl  Nicki
     

    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hello everyone...im just letting you all know, for whoever reads this, that i may be changing my site...certain things have occured as to force me to possibly end this blog, and again begin it anew...but it depends on how things progress...i hope it doesn't come down to having to change to another site, as i've done it before, its not fun... well i must be going, for now write more later ~Lil' Nicki~
     

    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hello everyone...and how is the world today??? me im alright...my house go sold and im gonna have to find a new place to live, but im good other then that..i have to go apply for jobs, because i need to get one.... i want one, just cuz...don't ask me why...maybe im just nuts or something...so if im writing random thing rying to figure out what to say on an interview, pay it no mind as i tend to write a lot of stuff...  I talked to my dad on the phone the other day, and for once we actually talked about something other then hs truck, or his job...it was quite spectaular...nothing like that has ever happened befre...but hey guess what..we get out an hour early today...parent/techer interviews or something, but it's all good, we get out early, so im not complaining...  I have been getting migrains a lot lately...2 this week, one at the start and one at the end...it sucked...and now i notice the chest pains im getting are becomming more severe, and my mom wants to get that checked out..i haven't had any so  far today, but i do get them on my left side, where my heart is, but im hoping its just my boos that hurt, cuz i don't want anything to be seriously wrong, believe me i can't afford that right now, i have to much work to be doing...  My mom has been working hard trying to find a second job because she isn't getting enught hours at safeway..and we need to bring in more money then $50-$120 a week...because there are growing kids in the house that actually need to eat....  My mom has been doing well, the best she can anywayz...whick is hard work in her case...and she joined curves and wants me to join with her, and i think it would be fun...and its for a half and our a day...so itsnot to long..bu i wanna help py for it so i gotta get a job....  oh and just another random note: i saw a dead seagul on the road, got squished by a car, i've also seen one get hit..i was with chris Tuttle, not havin the best of days, and watchin it get hit didn't help any...  write more later  ~Lil' Nicki~
     

    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      well hello again everyone, well whoever is kind enough to read my site...and how are you this fine almost afternoon?? me im doing alright, if stupid people up islad would stop spreading lies about me that is...but i'll bother you with that later, not right now, im in a good mood...  My play is officially called Abatoir...and i'll post a preview of it and you all can tell em what you think of it....hopefully you like horror stories...because thats what the script is, a hardcore horror idea...Abatoir means A Slaughter house, thats why i liked it, its a new word it'd larned, and im putting it to use!!! lol talk 2 ya'll l8er if i can  ~Lil' Nicki~ P.S. Almost didn't sign my name *oops* ~soft smile~ :P 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I found these lyrics...and it was insane how like me they were so i gotta post them, i think their awsome, and i have changed a lot in the last few months, and not everyone likes that, well im gonna jet, and add more stuff to my blog ~hugs 2 all~ Lil' Nicki   Changes 3 doors down  I'm not supposed to be scared of anything, But I don't know where I am I wish that I could move but I'm exhausted And nobody understands (how I feel)  I'm tryin' hard to breathe now, But there's no air in my lungs. There's no one here to talk to And the pain inside is making me numb.  I try to hold this under control, They can't help me, cause no one knows.  Now I'm goin' through changes, changes. God, I feel so frustrated lately. When I get suffocated, save me. Now I'm goin' through changes, changes  Feelin' weak and weary Walkin' through this world alone Everything they say every word of it Cuts me to the bone, (and I bleed)  I've got something to say But now I've got nowhere to turn It feels like I've been buried Underneath all the weight of the world.  I try to hold this under control, They can't help me, cause no one knows. Now I'm goin through changes, changes God, I feel so frustrated lately  When I get suffocated, save me. Now I'm goin' through changes, changes  I'm blind and shakin', bound and breakin' I hope I'll make it, through all these changes.  Now I'm going through changes, changes God I feel so frustrated, lately When I get suffocated, save me. Now I'm falling apart, now I feel it.  But I'm going through changes, changes. God I feel so frustrated, lately. And I get suffocated, I hate this. But I'm going through changes, changes.  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
         How do you define a friendship?? I've been contemplating this, but only recently (certain events have occured, making me queston it). A  friend  is someone you can talk to, hang out with or at least stand being around them for more then 10 minutes at a time, but  friendship , for me, is a little different. Friendship is a 2 way street, and can only work if there is trust, and a friend-like love, a base/backround if you will.    A friendship is not easily broken, and if its strong enough you will always get back together, nothing can stand in the way of a true friendship.    But of course if its not meant to be, it will eventually break up, but don't get yourself to worked up about it, because you can always do better, because there is always a friendship waiting to be started, you just have to open your mind, and your heart and give it a shot...No fear, right??    Personally, I have had a few confrontations of this sort... some have ended badly, and some haven't ended at all, but what i do know, is that the ones that did end aren't meant to be... and i've accepted that, im not going to beat myself up about it, there's no point.    You can't base a friendship soley on decisions that are made, or you might as well be asking to end your friendship with this person.  We know not all decisions are the smatrest in the world, but hey give them a break, after all wer're only human...and sometime we don't give our decisions much thought.     Some decisions are based on anger, done soley to make another person feel bad, or unimportant, and sometimes we say things we don't mean...but for thoes things you have to dig deeper, and find the meaning of the words, don't just lash ut at someone becaus ethey call u a slut (for example) find out why they called you it, maybe they're just jealous.    The reason people hurt other people is because they hurt or want to feel good abou themselves, and by hurting other people, they don't hurt alone.... Like i've heard many times before -->  Misery loves company 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hello again everyone, and how are we doing this fine afternoon??? I am doing ok I guess, I am at school, "studying hard", well actually im not, i have a spare, and have finished my homework... I just got out of tag, and now I hear there will be a lock down next week at lunch, we had one in tag but i guess they want to try it in the real world, so to speak...incase we're not prepared for the real thing if it is ever to happen, but i guess its sort of a good thig, because if it ever happened and we didn't know what to do, we all could be dea and that wouldn't be cool...  We were also talking about schooling, and how next week on fridays we will be getting out 32 minutes later, so that 2:00pm instaed of 1:30, or we'll start school at 8:00am, instaed of 8:20, to make up for the lost time, because next year we're getting extra holidays, and we miss school time, so they want to keep us at school longer just so we can learn, and it could be a good thing in the long run, but bad as well, i'll have to get up early, and get ready faster, and try to have breakfast in the morning, which i rarely have cuz i got nt time...  Speaking of time, i lost my watch yesterday... i feel so naked without it, i went to check the date and time, so i could pu it on my project today, and i went through a withdrawl, it wasn't there, i took it off in Biology, so I could do my grasshopper disection, and put it in the breast pocket of my jacket, and did the disection...but when i went to put it on in my spare yesterday, and it wasn't there, so i walked around the school staring at the ground hoping to find it, but with no luck,then i figured, being me, brain dead and all, i must have put it in my back pack, or my purse...so i took everything out and searched, but still with no luck...so now i sit here, typing to you, watchless, and hoping someone turns it in to the office, where i left a discription of the watch, so they can call me if it turns up...  Any wayz as i totally side track from what i was saying... We may actually have longer school days, yawn...zzzzzzzz.... oops sorry fell asleep at the thought of more school ,and more math *screams in terror* not more math...i suck enough as it is...bit of course im me and am too stubborn to ask for help, because i will figure it out on my own, have done that with several things, what can't i do it with math class too?? LOL!!!  Biology was pretty basic today...It was a work block to finish up on any assignments...me and emily had to finish our dissection questions... That was a pretty fun dissection...come to think of it, I enjoy disecting things very much...my mom says i should be a veteranerian when i grow up (im 17 tho) because i have no problem cutting things open in order to see whats wrong... but hte things i look at are already dead, so im not sure how sewing them up after im done is gonna go over but i should be fine...  The dance last night was Awsome...I had soo much fun... I veen got to go on stage with elvis and dance (i was his hips.. :P), It was so cool being up on stage, having everyone look at you and say you looked awsome...and i even got their new cd, and one of elvis' scarfs (The bands name: The Timebenders) It was awsome... no to mention I had to do the famous elvis love pose, that was wicked... but i was told to do it in chris tuttles direction, he's and great guy and all, but i really don't understand how i truely ever had a big crush on him, and im glad im over him, but i do like someone else, and he smacked my ass at the dance, but don't worry, i got him back, but now i have to watch my back cuz he says he'ss get me today (dun dun dum) but im not worried... but im not sure if i should ask him out or not, cuz i don't want him to say no...  Shawn came to the dance, he snuck in the back and came drunk, it was hillarious... i ran up to him and tackled him, scared the living shit out of him...it was priceless, he was so far gone, you could easily smell it on his breathe, it was kind of obvious....but he acted sober so he got away with it....  I didn't get home till 10:00pm, an had a bath to get the make up off my face and the hairspray out of my hair... i wish i'd got pictures, it was priceless, I think im gonna dress up like that on haloween, so  get a picture of it at least... Damn my back hurts now, and my neck too, i really gotta pace myself at these dances, stop shakin it so hard (hee hee hee) But it was fun and i was good, so no worries... but i still ave to tell dave the thing andy told me to tell him, and the cookie dough (long story, i'll write it in my other blog later)but cookie dough was no where involved, its interesting...  Well i must be going  ~Love ya~  Later  Lil' Nicki   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hello hello every 1!!! I decides to create a whole new illusion to my blog...no more plain jane colors for me...no sir!!! I've jumped in to the future of technology...Im even learning html!!! stand back all, i might hurt sumthing ;)  So whats new in the life of my readers??? Not too much to report here, Im definetly getting my belly button peirced this summer, and i hope my tongue...and i wanna get a tattoo too, but im not sure of what yet...but i might get to go to vancouver for 1 day and a bit, for a biology/ capp field trip...we're going to UBC and the museum of anthropolgy!!! but i have to make sure its ok with my mom first...and it only costs like $60, because you hve to pay for your own food.. and you get to go to the mall and shop aswell...and im gonna get money for that too if i can! so i hope i'll get to go, i mean its educational, and funn all at the same time...but i will most likely get to go if i do all my chores and help pack some before i go...  Oh ya im moving into my grandmothers old house, the one they live in at the moment, and the reason is that my house im renting got sold and my granma and uncle and aunt bought a house so they're moving into their new house, into the area my mom like and we are moving out, beside noisy abnoxious children, talk about a good deal??? right, s is ur do winning the million while you get a bullet in the head!!!  I've been feeling a little edgy lately, a little more then usual... I have a few friends that refuse to talk to me, but won't give me an explanation, and then I have the ones who can't mind their own business, who nag and bitch lioke im their god and need mee all the time...  Sometimes i think of taking off, without telling any of my annoying friends where im going...just not be there for them, like their not there for me, because sometimes i need someone to talk to, someone i can confide in, and not have to worry if they think im a mental case or permiently in love ith them.... And thankfully i have a ouple of those or i would most likely go insane!!!  Well I must be going for now, its almost lunch time and i have to urinate, not that lunch has much to do with that sentance but you know what i mean!!!  Talk to ya'll later!!!  Lil' Nicki 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
        You're My Little Pony!!  Sweet and innocent and happy, you make people want to spew burrito chunks.  Even a Care Bear could kick your ass.     urlLink   What childhood toy from the 80s are you?      brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        You're a Fluff writer!    urlLink   What kind of writer are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      OMG!!! Youre gonna die of cancer for using your cell to much    urlLink   Choose your Dramatic Death (Now w/pics!!)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      Furnulum pani nolo. "I don't want a toaster." Generally, things (like this quiz) tend to tick you off.  You have contemplated doing grievous bodily harm to door-to-door salesmen.     urlLink   Which Weird Latin Phrase Are You?      brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      You are the Jewel Of The Sea. A mermaid with class and style. You are worthwhile to meet. Your freinds are mant since you are soooo populer. You live in a palace with many anglefish servants. You love your make-up and hairbrush. You are one of a kind. Please rate my quiz I think you are absolutly stunning?    urlLink   What kind of mermaid are you? (Gorgeous Pics)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      SELENE: You are selene! Beautiful, vivacious, fierce and seductive, Selene vowed she would destroy Lycans after her family was murdered by the werewolves. So ruthless is she that selene is a member of the Death Dealers. This elite Vampire warrior class's mission is to make the Lycans extinct.  Ever wish you could be a vampire?        urlLink   Which UNDERWORLD character are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      Let's not bicker and argue about who killed who!    urlLink   What Monty Python Character are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      Weapons are not your thing. You would prefer to pummel your opponent to death with your fists and feet. You show a lot of Honor but some power still eludes you. I can give you this power, I can make you stronger, join me.      urlLink   How would you Murder?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      CRAZY ONE. You need crazy partners. You dont mind if he/she takes alc or drugs or smokes he is not allowed to be boring. Open-Minded for everything our partner should spent much time with you. Your partner shall be spontaneous and love danger. It is not that important if she/he is rich or if he/she cuts his nails she/he must follow you .You take the domination over the relationship, you decide most of the times where to go. If the sex is not good (any more)you quit the relationship  For you it is better to leave than to see your love restrained. PLEASE VOTE, I want to know what you think about my quiz, I worked hard on it.You can always message me or tell me how I can improve that quiz. Ill sure write back.    urlLink   	~THE big LOVE TEST!! What do you need? With PICS! For girls and boys!~     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      histrionic    urlLink   Which Personality Disorder Do You Have?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla  
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey every 1 hows it going??? me no to bad i guess, my new room got painted this weekend,at the place im moving into, and I saw Harry Potter and the prisoner of Azkaban, it was pretty good, I loved it when Hermione punches Malfoy, that was awsome... so hows is every1's life??? mines aright...but the next time i have a crush someone please remind me to keep it to myself...I told andy i liked him and asked himhow he felt and he said "I like you...... as a friend"....talk about your awkward silences, it wouldn't have been so bad if he'd said it all at once, it was the silence that killed me...but whateves, i'll get over it eventually... so no worries... I have other crushes I could go after...but...never mind  School is ok right now, exams are 7 days away...ahhhhh it sux, i hate exams, and my dad's comming weekend is gonna screw everything up, he decided he wanted us for fathers day, so we have to go see him, but i'll write more later, possibly in my other blog or sumthing....  gotta jet ttyl            Lil' Nicki
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        You're Most Like The Season Autumn ...  You're warm, and the most approachable. You have that gentle prescence about you. People can relate to you, and find you easy company. However it's likely you've been hurt in the past and it has left you scarred so things can become rather chilly with you at times. Being the third Season in, you're mature, trustworthy and loyal to your friends but prone to depression and negative thinking.  Well done... You're the shy and sensitive season :)    urlLink   ?? Which Season Are You ??     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      ! You are Most Like A Ruby ! Passionate, in control - and very sexy. You tend to be more dominant, and people long to possess your wild nature. People find you fun, and a real live wire. You're most like a Ruby because people simply can't take their eyes away from you - your bright captivating nature draws people to you. Congratulations ... You're the sparkly fun gem everybody craves.    urlLink   ?? Which Precious Gem Are You ??     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      You are Gluttony! Nibbling a cookie at the moment by any chance? You don't just like your food, you love it. And there's nothing wrong with that. However gluttony isn't just about food. It relates to anything that you gobble up more then you should of. You tend to 'take your cake, and eat it too' - excuse the horrific pun. Perhaps if you don't be so consumed with having every little thing you'd be better off. On a plus side, you know what you like, what you want -  and you go after it. You tend to have good instincts about things, and excellent taste in your life. Congratulations, You have the best taste out of all the 7 deadly sins!    urlLink   ?? Which Of The Seven Deadly Sins Are You ??     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      You're like a Unicorn!    urlLink   ?? Which Mythical Creature Are You ??     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      Magic    urlLink   ?? Which Angel Or Demon Are You ??     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      You're living the movie The Shining!    urlLink   ?? Which Horror Movie Are You Living ??     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      Mermaid    urlLink   ?? Which Creature Of The Sea Are You??     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      Cocktail    urlLink   ?? Which Alcoholic Drink Are You ??     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      Waterfall    urlLink   ?? Which Natural Wonder Or Disaster Are You ??     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      Britain    urlLink   ?? Which Country Are You From ??     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Sneakers- funny, laid-back, and goofy, you love to make people laugh and have a good time.  You enjoy comfort and don't care to much about what people think of you.  You like to hang out with your buddies and just have a good time. [please vote! thank you! :)]     urlLink   What Kind of Shoe Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Sneakers- funny, laid-back, and goofy, you love to make people laugh and have a good time.  You enjoy comfort and don't care to much about what people think of you.  You like to hang out with your buddies and just have a good time. [please vote! thank you! :)]     urlLink   What Kind of Shoe Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Aphrodite/Eros    urlLink   ?? Which Of The Greek Gods Are You ??     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      Tomboy    urlLink   What's your sexual appeal?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      You have an animal soul! Arent you lucky! You are very interactive with animals and can understand them even if you dont speak their tongue. The birds arent afraid of you, deer can eat out of your palm, and every dog will roll over for you. As an Animal Soul, you follow your instinct, sometimes making rash decisions, and not thinking properly. If you dont understand something, you reject and push it away, and can get very disastrous when angry. At the same time, youre a very kind person who can make people feel better, and are understanding and compassionate. One of the great things about you is that your rarely jealous, and know that you have to share and help other people if you want to survive this world. You are very loyal and optimistic, and can make it through the toughest times.    urlLink   What Kind of SOUL do you posses? (For Girls only) Incredible Anime Pictures!     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      You're chocolate.  You're the old soul type, people feel that they have known you their entire life.  Many often open up to you for they view you as thoughtful and trustworthy.  Although people trust you, you have a hard time trusting them.  You prefer to keep your feelings bottled up inside, or display them very quietly.  It is alright to open up every once in a while.    urlLink   Which kind of candy are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
            I have had no time to post in this thing, but i had to make time...i just got some pretty upseting news... Mrs. Kuiper has recently seen a doctor and the results are negative...she has a maximum of a week to live...my heart goes out to danielle and the family, i am so sorry....I will try to visit her soon, I feel so bad that a friend of mine has to go through the pain of losing someone so close...it is unfair that someone so good, has to go through such pain and anguish...Mrs. Kuiper is a good, loving caring, sweet person, and it pains me to think of her lying in that bed, helplessly, unable to see her family, and the sickness must be killer in its own right, throwing up extensively, and needing help with that aswell...I will pray for her, In my own way of course, Im not christian, but I will pray...       On a brighter note....I asked Jasper if i did ask him out what would he say, and he said he didn't know what he'd say, but its a lot better then I like you....as a friend. So ya, that makes me happy, but i have feeling for a few other guys too, and i wanna get those outa the way before I date any 1, but Im working on getting a boyfriend, so people can back off, oh and just for emily, im not letting you email Jasper, I have his email and I will keep it to myself...so there :P  School is almost over, 2 days of classes and 2 days of exams, then im done, the its to tanning and to swimming and camping, and chillin with friends, with work on my plays and book of course...  Well I think Im gonna go, I have to paint my nails and do my make up before I go to my dads, but its gonna take me forever to do my nails...  ttyl later, or i'll see you this weekend...  Love you all                Lil' Nicki
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Had to post something, and since I have nothing to say I took a few quizzes and added them!!!    You are NEIL PERRY. You're passionate and want to live your life doing what you love. You're creative and a good leader. However, you tend to be somewhat weak-willed and have problems sticking up for yourself. Don't let it get the better of you!   urlLink  Which Dead Poets Society Character Are You?    brought to you by  urlLink     Hottie    urlLink  What's Your Personality Type?    brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      Pre-Hyptnotized Peter    urlLink  What Office Space character are you?    brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla       
     

    
</post>


</Blog>