<Blog>

<date>20,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I made a few phone calls for camp.  I hate making phone calls, and I just put it off as long as I can.  Blech.  I'm a mess, sometimes.  Becky and I went shopping.  I think I don't shop well with others.  Maybe next X-mas I will just do my shopping alone.  I'm not a shopper.  Her mono wasn't helping, although truly she did okay all thing considered.  I still have to get something for my dad and Judy.  Well, I got something for dad, but I need to get him a little extra something although I have no clue what.  I'm trying to figure out what kind of bike I should get.  I was looking at low end Treks today.  We'll see.  I wish I could spend my graduation money on me and not on bills.  I hate being poor.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I got an email from  urlLink FutureMe  the other day.  It was cool.  I congratulated myself on graduating and asked a bunch of questions.  urlLink  FutureMe  is this nifty service where you can email a note to yourself in the future -- even a few years later.    I wish you could send one backwards instead of only forward in time.  But then, I have always wanted to talk to an earlier me, even when I was a kid.  Beck and I seem to be doing the living together thing okay.  It's hard, because she has mono (way to start off, isn't it?).    My graduation money is paying our bills right now.  I was a little bitter about it, because I had allowed myself to dream about what I could do with the money.  Oh, well.  I should know better.  I know what it means to be poor.  Using cash gifts for not-bills is a luxury only available to people who have enough money to pay their bills in the first place.  *sigh*  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I had a really nice party yesterday.   The early part of it was sort of stilted, but it much improved after a few folks left, funny enough.  Danielle and Nathan gave me this wonderful scrapbook.  I really like it.  I am sad to be leaving them.  We had some really good times.  I am sorry about leaving Marsha, too.  Maybe I made more friends here than I thought I had.  I wish I had a more clear-cut answer about what comes next.  When people ask, I tell them about plan A and plan B.    Today marks five years since mom died.  I wish she could be at graduation.  Mom would have harassed the family to try and get them there.  But I guess they came even without any harassment at all.  I would have had to deal with awkwardness if Dad had come.  I wonder if he would have come if mom were still around.  I have been thinking a lot lately about just why it is I feel like I cannot fit in here.  I mean, I got plenty of crap for being queer when I lived in Chicago.  More, in overt ways, than I ever have gotten here.  Maybe it is just that the culture here is just different enough that I have never felt comfortable.  I will be glad to be back where I am on familiar ground.  Is it dumb that I feel like I am living amongst foreigners here?    I am glad I have spent some time in the south, though.  I feel like I got rid of some dumb ideas just by being here.  Of course, I also have some new ideas about what the south is like.  I had never even heard the word preacher used except by African Americans until I got here.    I wonder if Becky is feeling the same thing in Michigan -- like she is a foreigner.  I remember how hard it was for me my first year here.  It was real culture shock, and I did not expect that, since it is the same country and all!  Part of it was moving to such a small town, though.  I am a city girl at heart.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I was reading my journal today and I came across something that was hilarious.  It is a chart of all the women I have slept with, and where they fall as far as sex:  good ---> bad and intimacy, intimate --------> not.  It cracked me up.  I had forgotten I had even done it.  I might reproduce it and post it.  Yeah.  Guess I am a geek.  I also forgot that I had kissed a guy in Wales.  Oops.  Funny, that.  Well, it wasn't a very good kiss.  I wonder what those charts are called.  The ones with four quadrants, and  you track two variables with them.  Hrm.  Well, I just have two more finals tomorrow and then I am finished with my academic career.  I got a C in dodge ball class, though.  Well, whatever.  I hated that class.  I might just drop by to find out how he calculated it.  But I'm not sure I care that much.  Hopefully, this semester won't tank my chances at graduate school.  But if it does, oh well.  I did decently well on my GRE, so that will have to do.   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Argh.  Must.  Sleep.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I messed with my template a little.  I put a counter on it, too.   I should be asleep, since I am supposed to call Beck in the morning.  Early.  5:30a.m. kind of early.  Gosh, I am going to miss this fast connection, though.  I am not looking forward to going back to telephone modem speeds.  Huh.  It only just hit me, seeing the date.  Tomorrow it will be five years since mom died.  Five years.  I miss her.  It is amazing to me that time could go by so quickly.  I wish she could see me graduate.  I have to admit, that is not as big a deal as I thought it was going to be.  But maybe it is just that I have already done my weeping about mom not being there for graduation.  She would have been really proud of me.    I guess this is the fastest five years I have had.  I suppose I will always be able to say that, since life just seems to accelerate.  I hope nobody says anything about how mom is with me in spirit.  I might have a hard time being polite.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I do like that Google Bar Blogger feature.  It is nifty.  Google is the Way and the Light.  Well, I graduate in 83 hours.  Crazy.    Then I go live with my partner.  I was wondering today if this is a good idea or not.  I mean, I guess it is too late to wonder about it.  Since I already bought an engagement ring, asked her to marry, moved my belongings and my dog into the house, and have been paying rent.  Of course, it is rather typical of me to pick this time to wonder if I am doing the right thing.  Why worry ahead of time when you can worry when it is way too late?  Ah, well.  I pushed off my worries some more tonight playing  urlLink Puzzle Pirates .  I have become somewhat addicted to the game, for all that I am crap at the puzzles.    I have another fricking cold sore.  You would think with the massive evil cold sore I had over Thanksgiving, my body would give me a break.  But I have another one.  Smaller, thankfully, but still.  I signed up for the ACA conference in San Francisco.  And I started scouting out good bars.  I am tempted to drop Laurie an email just to say hi and find out where to go.  Perhaps this is not the brightest idea I have had, emailing the ex-girlfriend when I am about to head out there.  The conference is in February.  Or at least it is if I still have my camp job.  I guess that is going to depend on how that interview goes.  *crosses fingers*
     

    
</post>

<date>08,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I must say, I really want a Dykes for Dean t-shirt.  Real bad!  urlLink Dykes for Dean 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      So, I feel like I do not have a private place at home to put my journal, and I am posting my journal online instead.  Perhaps this is counterintuitive, but the truth is that it is pretty unlikely people are even going to read this at all, much less that anyone who reads it would be someone I know.  So, eh, whatever.   I guess I should go, actually.  I am about to go take a final.  It is the first of my last finals.  I will be graduating in JUST FIVE DAYS.  I have been waiting for this to happen.  I cannot believe it is finally coming, after all these years.  The other day I was at a party, and someone asked me why I flunked out.  I usually try to avoid the topic these days.  I do not know why, really.  I used to be pretty open about it, but the last few years I rarely say anything.  I flunked out after the rape, but I cannot help feeling somehow as if the problem was me.  Soon, I will be a gradated person.  I wonder what that will feel like.  Me.  Graduated.  Me.  
     

    
</post>

<date>06,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Thank goodness the holidays are over.  I guess that means I have grown up, if I just want them to be done with.  Still, it is hard juggling so many family obligations.  We ended up doing thirty hours of driving altogether.  I think we will not be doing that again if I have anything to say about it.  I am jobless, of course, which does not help.  I sure would love to have gotten a job for Christmas.  If those temp agencies are as excited as they sound (and they do sound excited) how come they have not called me?  Ah, well.  I guess I will start putting in some more applications at places I have no desire to work for tomorrow.  Times are hard here, though.  I heard they closed another plant.  Blech.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Mercury News | 02/11/2004 | S.F. may sanction same-sex marriage   It's strange to me that queer marriage is such a bugaboo to folks.  As someone who actually has a radical queer agenda, it's odd to see something that seems so... establishment cause such a ruckus.  Of course, that's the point, isn't it.  For queer folks to remain the "other," you have to keep some sort of distinction between us and "regular" people.  Otherwise, we're just people.  Scary.  I just wish I could get married.  I wish I had to get a blood test before I could tie the knot.  I would welcome the responsibilities as much as the benefits.  The fact that I can't get married just drives me nuts.  If it is a good thing for the state to regulate something like marriage, then surely it is just as good for the state to regulate queer marriage as straight marriage.  I wonder what kind of an impact queer marriage would have on our community.  How would it change things if we could actually marry?  It would be interesting, a chance for those right wing folks who extoll the virtues of marriage to see if the institution itself does all the things they claim for it.   I've said before that we wouldn't get full marriage rights in this country until 2050.  In spite of all the hoopla, I don't think it's time for me to revise that estimate.  *sigh*
     

    
</post>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink TheStar.com - Editorial: Bush cried 'wolf' on Iraq's threat   I am continually amazed at how credulous the American public is.  The polls shot up for Bush after his interview about the war.  And why?  Why does he continue to get away with this?  He needs to be held accountable.  I don't know that the man is stupid, but I do think he is willfully ignorant in some specific ways.  Prior to his Presidency, I don't think he gave a damn about the rest of the world.  He shares this attitude with the American public at large, perhaps, but it's a heck of a thing in a President.  World events have forced him to look abroad, but there still seems to be an underlying attitude that ignorance is preferable, even admirable.  The man embarasses me.  He blatantly lies as a routine matter of policy, and we let him get away with it.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm getting no work done at all today.  But I have added a comment thingy.  Works for me.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Since this is a crappy blog, I added it to the crappy blog webring.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm having a hard time figuring out how to balance my emotional needs with my partner's.  It's just not something I'm good at.  I'm used to just dropping everything whenever she needs something, and I don't think that's a good idea.  There always seems to be a good reason to do it.  It always seems temporary.  She's quitting smoking.  She's got a big test.  She's got mono.  She hasn't eaten dinner.  But I'm starting to get a little tired of taking care of her.  It's not that she doesn't take care of me, because she does.  She's really sweet about it, actually.  I think she's really conscious of what I do for her and she doesn't want it to be one-sided.  Still, I have days where I get tired.  Sometimes I have stressful days that aren't quite stressful enough because they get subsumed in her greater stress.  Argh.  I also don't know what to be when I grow up, but that's another issue.  I'm sad that Dean doesn't seem to be doing so well.  I wonder what the hell he did to piss off the media so much.  He's just not all that liberal.  Of course, it doesn't take much to be a radical in our society, at least if you lean left.
     

    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm leaving this crappy place on Monday.  Thankfully.  I really cannot stand  urlLink Lansing, Michigan .  I am almost gone.  Hooray! 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I missed  urlLink Obama's speech  last night, although I caught a bit of it on NPR today.&nbsp; I was impressed with the interview he gave yesterday on NPR and I really like the  urlLink speech .  I'll be waiting in the next few years for the other shoe to drop.&nbsp; Some scandal, some stupid position I dislike, or perhaps he'll just fall out of favor.&nbsp; My brother may well be right that I'm outside of the mainstream.&nbsp; Certainly, no candidate that I like ever ends up amounting to much.&nbsp; Just ask  urlLink Howard Dean .&nbsp; I'm glad that Dean went the classy route and is supporting Kerry.&nbsp; I have some hope that Dean has helped to change the dynamics of discussion in the Democratic party.  I'm afraid of Republicans.&nbsp;   Looks like I'm not alone.&nbsp;&nbsp;A  urlLink Google  search for "afraid of republicans" came up with 104 results.&nbsp; "afraid of democrats" came up with 41.&nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've started to use  urlLink futureme.org &nbsp;to ask myself political questions.&nbsp; I had been using it for personal stuff, but lately I've been reminding myself about the hot issues that are important to me and asking my (future) self how they turned out.  I think  urlLink futureme.org &nbsp;is pretty nifty.&nbsp; I've already gotten emails from my past self.&nbsp; It's also fascinating to see what other folks write themselves about.&nbsp; People write a lot about relationships, wondering how they're going to turn out. 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I got myself a shiny new computer.&nbsp; I can't wait to pick it up.&nbsp; It's a  urlLink Thinkpad T42.&nbsp;    33 years old, and I've never bought myself a computer.&nbsp; I've only gotten them as gifts.&nbsp; This is a  urlLink review  I found on it.&nbsp; I'll give my own review once I get my hot little hands on the darn thing.  &nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Massachusetts Birth Certificate Lists Both Lesbian Moms   How cool is that?&nbsp; We're planning to have a baby in a couple of years, and I would love to get both of our names on the birth certificate.&nbsp; The progress queers are making is pretty uneven, but I have to admit that I never thought there would be legal queer marriage this early.&nbsp; I figured in 2050 I might have a chance at it, but not sooner.&nbsp;   Of course, that number might still be correct if we're talking about marriage that is recognized throughout the country.  I still don't understand.&nbsp;   What's the big fucking deal about queer marriage?   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am basically trying to avoid doing any work right now.&nbsp; My last day at work is next Wednesday.&nbsp; I cannot WAIT to get done with this crap.  &nbsp;  They had us all do a  urlLink Myers-Briggs  type test at work.&nbsp; I did it like a trooper, but I'm wondering about its usefulness to management.&nbsp; It also seems really intrusive for an employer to make you do a personality test.&nbsp; Employers shouldn't be doing psych testing, even hokey internet psych tests.  &nbsp;  The test said:   Your Type is  ENTJ  Extroverted Intuitive Thinking Judging  Strength of the preferences %  78 22 22 33  &nbsp;  Evidently, this makes me a Fieldmarshal.&nbsp; Or something.  &nbsp; I'm pretty  urlLink dubious  about this.&nbsp; What does&nbsp;that score&nbsp;tell my employer?&nbsp; How would it help my co-workers work with me?&nbsp; I'm not really convinced that the Myers-Briggs model is terribly useful even to me, much less my employer. &nbsp; Field Marshal, huh?&nbsp; I wonder where I can get myself the uniform. 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Huh.&nbsp; I just went to the Kerry web site and signed up as a volunteer.&nbsp; Now that I know where I'm moving to, I figure it's time to do somethign positive.  &nbsp; Here's the little  urlLink site  they generated for me.&nbsp; I'll probably go to some events once we move.&nbsp; We're moving soon - August 2nd!  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       This is my meme of the day:     &nbsp;   John Kerry looks like an Ent.&nbsp; It's true.&nbsp; He both looks and sounds like an Ent.&nbsp; I certainly want the man to win, but he does look like an Ent.&nbsp;   urlLink  http://www.johnkerry.com/index.html   &nbsp;     &nbsp;   The truth is I don't like Kerry very much.&nbsp; He's way too conservative and he says he doesn't support queer marriage, which is my issue.&nbsp; I'm not a particularly big fan of Edwards, either.&nbsp;    &nbsp;  But I certainly won't even entertain the idea of voting for Bush.&nbsp; Bush is evil.&nbsp; Ashcroft is worse.&nbsp; Cheney is a prick.&nbsp; This country will be better off without them.&nbsp; I will personally be better off without them.&nbsp; I sure do hope they get voted out.  &nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink 'We've Only Begun To Fight' Anti-Gay Amendment Backers Say     I must say, I quite loathe George Bush.  He wants to do some truly horrid things to our country, to MY country.  He is doing awful things to this country.  Actively working to deprive people of their rights is undemocratic and unpatriotic.  My marriage does not hurt anyone.  It certainly doesn't hurt society as a whole.  (That would be a trick, wouldn't it?)  Some days, I get a little tired of being queer in a homophobic society.  I'm in the midst of trying to get health insurance for Becky, and the affadavit I'm supposed to sign to access domestic partnership benefits requires that I state that I'm not married.    Well, I am.  I'm just married to another woman.  I feel like this is going to suck.  Becky HAS to have insurance.  It's not optional.  The whole thing is just so frustrating. 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I have Short Timers Syndrome (tm) at work today. The truth is that I've had it since I started the job, since I knew (although they didn't) that I was only going to work there for a few months.  -----------   urlLink Terror Issue Raises Question of Vote Delay   I must say that I've wondered all along if Bush was going to be willing to hand over power.  I know this is sort of conspiracy-ish.  But, still.  WTF?
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I thought that this looked nifty.     urlLink http://www.successfulacademic.com/ 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So, I'm setting off for graduate school.  I'm scared to death, honestly.  Will it be too hard?  Will it be too easy?  (I am a Recreation major, after all.)  I'm scared about doing the thesis.  I'm scared about whether the professors will like me.  I'm scared about the fact that I'm 33 and I'm committing a huge part of my life to this.  I mean, I'm sort of late in the game, here, as far as getting my Ph.D. and getting a job in academia.  Mind you, it's a little easier (or so I'm gambling) to get a Rec. job.  I hope so, because the truth is that a Ph.D. in Recreation doesn't really do a hell of a lot for me career-wise outside of academia.  I read that book,  urlLink Getting What You Came For: The smart student's guide to earing a Master's or Ph.D.   Am I really going to have to suck up that much?  The thing is that I've been a big fish in a small pond.  I'm going to a real school, now.  What will it be like?
     

    
</post>


</Blog>