<Blog>

<date>22,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Well this weekend was a good one. We went to the condo and they have roughed in the electrical and plumbing. Which makes us feel like we are defintely getting there.  We also have been looking at furniture stores so we can get some new stuff for our wonderful new home.   Other than that just the normal pre-Christmas stuff going on. I went to CVS today and got sunscreen for our trip. I spent a small fortune on it. But I wanted to get the stuff that we don't break out from. I am guessing there is a reason there isn't a surplus in Michigan in the dead of winter. :)  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I am in the midst of my 2nd cold in the last two weeks. I never get sick. I think the apartment is doing it to me. Craig can't get a good night sleep here and I can't stop coughing. Thankfully this isn't going to be forever.   Last night I got to see my friend Holly and her adorable baby Kendall. I love spending time with them. I even changed Kendall's diaper and gave her a bottle. See .. someday I will make a good mom.. despite what some people might think.  Other than that, not much is new. I am looking forward to be off of work until the new year after Friday. If only Craig's company allowed him to do the same. 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I wore my new  orange   GAP pants to work. Yes they are a bright color of  orange  but they are the same material as any other pants I wear to work, and they are no means slutty. Well you should have heard all the funny comments.  "You look like Rainbow Brite." "Nice hip hop pants." "You look like a safety" "Do you work for ABB now."  Silly silly people they are just jealous they couldn't pull it off. :)    Other big news   Our friend Darrell is engaged. Of course I had to pull it out of him. Which leads to my question of the day, why aren't guys more excited about being engaged? 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was the first day where I was freezing outside no matter how warm of a coat I put on. Winter has finally arrived for us in Michigan. I am foolishly hoping that we won't have a lot of snow this winter, as we are in an apartment until our new house is done. And gosh darn it I am not into having to clear snow off my car.  It has been a day now since I have learned about the cancellation of my loved Pilates class. I still haven't decided completely what I will do. But I probably will sign up for the 7:30 class. I will just have to train my body to not falling asleep at 8:30 :)  Tonight after bowling we went to  urlLink  CkDiggs   our usual hangout after bowling. I decided to get a grasshopper ice cream drink. Then of course being the goof that I am decided it would be fun to have an ice cream drink party. Of course everyone thinks that is a gay idea.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Tonight I went to my Pilates class, which I have been going to for 2 days a week for over 2 years now. When I got there I learned that our class is Permanently being cancelled. Powerhouse decided to cancel their contract with Fitness Factory. Now I can take another session through Rochester Community.. but that class doesn't start until 7:30. Getting home from exercising at 9 pm, I am not sure if I am going to sign up for that or not.   So in amidst my disappointment, I decided to jump on the bandwagon like my friends Dave and Marci and finally start my blog. 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well it has been over a month since I have had the time or desire to post to my blog. So here goes. Let me fill you in on the last month.  We went to St. Lucia which was a lot of fun.. of course American Airlines ruined the beginning of our trip by losing our bags for over 3 days. At night at Sandals to go to any of the restaurants you can't just go in your bathing suit and shorts. So were confined to our room in the evenings.  The airline said they had no idea where they were. Luckily I had packed bathing suits and shorts in our carry on. From now I will be packing all my essentials in one. St. Lucia didn't have anything remotely close to a department store or even a Walmart or a Target where we could have gotten the things we needed.   When we returned home on January 2nd, our bags were already at the baggage claim by the time we got to them after deboarding. Funny how that happens.    I wrote to American Airlines and explained what had happened, they gave us some frequent flyer miles as if that was enough.   Then it was back to work. Which is busy of course. I also started two classes. A Business Strategy Class and an Internet Marketing Class. I can't wait until September.. with any luck I will be done with school for good. I will have my MBA.. and what else do I need?  Not much else has happened with us.  The first weekend in January we went to the Auto Show with friends and had a good time. Also in news about our friends, our dear friends Matt and Marci got their first house.. we are so happy for them.  Our house.. well that is another story.. we are hoping to get in some day.. whether it is March or April has yet to be determined.  
     
    
</post>

<date>29,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Friday night we got together with a bunch of good friends and family, and we celebrated Craig's Birthday at CKDiggs. It was a great time.   Pictures are accessible at:  urlLink Craig's Bday Celebration Pictures    After the bar, Craig, Becky, Ryan and I went to Fridays to get some food. It was silly when our bill was less than $20. 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Let's see what has happened lately. On Valentine's Day weekend we got new bedroom furniture for the Condo at House of Denmark we are really excited to get into the condo and to have new furniture.  On actual Valentine's Day, we went to our friends Chuck and Beth's place to celebrate Trent's Birthday. It was a lot of fun. I have posted our pictures on Shutterfly since liessfamily.com is still not up and running.   urlLink Pictures on Shutterfly from Trent's Bday      This past weekend has been wonderful. Friday night I went out to the bar and had a lot of fun. Then Saturday we went shopping.. and then Ryan, Becky, Craig and I went out to dinner and then headed to Greektown Casino.  Then came today, where I have done some homework and I am working on doing more. We went and saw 50 First Dates this afternoon/evening. .. it was a cute movie.   This week will be busy with work and then Friday is Craig's Birthday Party at CKDiggs.. it will be another good weekend.. at least that is what I am thinking.  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Based on Ali's blog today. I took the poetry form test.          I'm  terza rima , and I talk and smile. Where others lock their rhymes and thoughts away I let mine out, and chatter all the while.  I'm rarely on my own - a wasted day Is any day that's spent without a friend, With nothing much to do or hear or say.  I like to be with people, and depend On company for being entertained; Which seems a good solution, in the end.     What Poetry Form Are You?       I think that is pretty descriptive of me.. Thanks Ali for the fun game! 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The good news for this week, is that starting tomorrow are drywall is being put up in the condo. We are getting closer and closer to be able to move in. I bet it will about 6 weeks or so now. How exciting!  This weekend was fun. On friday night we did dinner with Mike and Megan. Then on Saturday, we took my car to Belle Tire to have my tire fixed and my car realigned. I think we are probably going to wait a while on fixing my bumper.  Insurance is such a racket, my $800 worth of damage isn't worth claiming on our insurance. Heck even it was like $2000 it probably wouldn't be. This is because they raise your rates when you have a claim. And the claim stays on for 2 years and if you get a ticket or have another claim in that time period your rates go up by 40%. Ugh.. how frusterating. Then on Saturday night I made dinner for Don, Deb and Becky. Then we went to the Abraham's St Patty's Day Party which was a lot of fun. Before we went we did some primping us girls. And everyone ended up wearing something from my closet.  Here is a picture of us girls before we left.     Then today (Sunday), Craig had a bowling tournament and did some homework and cleaning up. I took my Stats exam. Now all is left is a short write up for this game we played all semester.  I am looking forward to being done with school for 2 whole weeks!  Now if the weather would just start to warm up. I am not into driving in snow anymore at all!
     
    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tonight I decided to go to the advanced Pilates class at the Troy Community Center. The class starts at 6:30 so I thought it was fortunate that I made it home by 5:30. I changed and drove to the center, and loved the class.  My Aunt Janet is in the same class. Well we are walking out to our cars, and she says Drive Carefully, and I said you too.   I took Livernois home, figured I would cut over on Hamlin to the apartment.  I am stopped at the light at Auburn and Livernois and I see a car turning and it slides a little. I remember thinking wow it is really slippery out here. Well the next thing I know I am crossing the bridge over M-59 and my car is sliding. I hit the bridge on the South Side of the Road. I lost complete control, did a 360 and finally got control of my car again. I started to drive to the nearby side street. The woman that almost hit me had stopped there to make sure I was okay. She was on the phone with the police. I got out of my car and surveyed the damage. It looks amazingly like not much. I notice my front bumper is scratched and there is a piece missing. So I get back in my car, call Craig and tell him I waiting for the Police. The police are taking a long time so I get out and check out my car again and I notice that my left front tire is pretty much off of the wheel. So I call Craig and tell him I think I need to have him come and see if I should drive or what.  Craig comes and he says good call, the police call a towing service. Then the police leave after telling Craig that they should have given me a ticket for going to fast.. Come on it was icy and I bet I was going all of 30 mph. In fact another girl hit the same place while we were waiting. So the tow truck comes and they decide to just put my spare on and then we come home.   I am of course traumatized and never want to drive over a bridge in the snow again. But I am so thankful that I didn't get hurt or anyone else. How no cars hit me I don't know. I think my Dad was definitely  looking out for me. 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I spent a good portion of my weekend doing homework. My Marketing class had an unbelievable amount of work to do it the last week. I had a 10 page paper plus an essay exam with a mini paper in it. This week I have to write up a paper about our Business Strategy Game and take an exam in my Strategy Class. Then I am done until April 5th. I am really excited about that.   Other than that I can't say too much is new. We are crossing our fingers to get a closing date this week. We are hoping to move out of here in the beginning of May. That would be wonderful. I am really excited to be in a new house. We are going to have a lot of fun decorating.  Oh the other weekend we were driving to Don and Deb's and we saw this amazing house at Square Lake and Squirrel it had 4 two car garages and it is so impressive. Someone famous must live there.  I would love to have a house like that one day!   
     
    
</post>

<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So far this weekend was been a good one. Last night Becky, Craig and I made dinner then we met up with Don and Deb. We ended up at a bar in Birmingham and we were all home by 12 like good adults.  Today I got my nails done and Craig was at a bowling thing, so I rented Under the Tuscan Sun and watched it. I was dying to see that movie when it was in theaters, but Craig was not into that at all. The movie was really good. I think I would even consider buying the DVD for our collection. For dinner we met our friends Denise and Pete at Kruse and Muer. It was a fun time. We need to make sure to get together with them more often!  Nothing else happened this week, except for the fact that I am going to start training to be a Pilates instructor. I have been taking Pilates for over 2 years and I love it. So instead of me paying to go twice a week, I thought it might be fun to be the instructor. My Pilates instructor thinks I will be a good fit. I should hopefully be ready by the fall when I have completed my MBA and need something to do with my free time. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If you didn't know Pepsi currently has a promotion where one in three win a free song on Apples Itunes Site a.k.a. a legal place to download music, because you have to pay for it $1 per song (unless you have a winning cap).  Yesterday I got a Diet Pepsi at work and I had a winning cap.  With Itunes you have to download their software and although Craig disagrees I feel their navigation of their software is pretty bad, but nonetheless I downloaded a song. I downloaded 100 years by the Foo Fighters. I heard it on my way to Pilates last week and that it was a good song. Although I figured it was song by someone like Train.   In other great news.. Dave fixed my Comment Code on my Blog.. THANK YOU! so now all my blog fans can leave me comments. I will be waiting!  
     
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Our friends Dave and Ali were blessed with their daughter Leah last night at 11:18 pm. (Sunday April 25th)  She has blond curly hair, just like her momma did when she was born, weighs 7lbs 14oz, and is 19" long.  She's already smart - scored 9 and 9 on her Apgars, and only made mommy push for about an hour.    I was excited to read the email from Dave's sister this morning, and even more geeked when Dave called and said come visit if you have time. So I decided to take a half day of vacation and I went and met Leah. What a doll she is. Ali looks great as well. Dave is beeming although you can tell he is still a little tired.  Enjoy these pictures of Leah not even a full day old yet!         Proud Daddy       This is the first baby I ever visited in the hospital and I loved holding her. She smelled so baby good.       Happy Family       Tired after only getting a few hours of sleep, but beautiful Mother    So far her favorite thing to do is sleep!       
     
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Monday and Tuesday we went to the condo to check out the progress and found we had some good progress! Yesterday Craig's dad come over to see what they had been doing as well. Now that it is all coming together it is so exciting.  Here are some new pics  Downstairs kitchen cabinets installed    Downstairs bathroom    Upstairs kitchen    Up close Cabinet Color    Updated loft railing    Fireplace    Masterbath Shower    Stairs to the second story.    View of kitchen from the loft    These pics are from Monday, yesterday when we were there all the cabinets and windows were covered as they were getting ready to paint again. 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I forgot to add a very important part of our trip to Pittsburgh to my blog. Luckily Becky reminded me. On Sunday when we were heading to the mall, we were on some highway and there were 3 kids in the back of a Jeep Wrangler. Everytime we saw them they would give us the peace sign. So Becky and I would do it back and even did it out the sunroof when Ryan speed up at one point. Then when we got off on our exit, Becky rolled down her window and give him the peace sign again. As we were about to go out of sight, he leaned over the Jeep and gave us the peace sign. What a cutie! 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This weekend, Craig, Becky and I ventured to Pittsburgh to visit our friend Ryan. We left on Friday night about 6ish and made it Ryan's house just after 11ish. This is of course with stopping for dinner and then later on for coffee. It was such a drag once we got into Ohio and couldn't speed and it was dark. I found it amusing to turn on the car light when we were passing a truck and make the sound your horn sign. I did that with 3 trucks and got 3 responses. Then the 4th time Craig seemed to do 80 by the Truck and he didn't see me. Then Craig said enough was enough. Friday night after getting to Ryan's we did much of nothing. In fact Becky and I were cold and snuggled up on the couch (also known for this trip as Ryan's bed)     Ryan started to get kind of cranky when it was past 12 and he wasn't in bed. So after a while Becky and I stopped torturing him and off to bed we were.  Saturday morning after having 2 girls and 2 guys get ready with only bathroom with a shower, we ventured out to eat breakfast, and chose to eat at good ole Bob Evans. Then we made our way to IKEA   I don't think I have to tell you how cool IKEA is. Becky had never been and I am pretty sure she would sign up to go back. Okay so they don't have all the furniture you want to furnish your house with, but they do have some pretty cool stuff for practically nothing. We got some candles, and some pictures and such!   Then we headed to the Waterfront Mall downtown. It is this really cool outdoor mall, similiar to our Village but bigger. Becky and I did some shopping, while Craig and Ryan hung out at Gameworks. Soon enough 3 pm was approaching and we hadn't eaten such breakfast. So we decided we better at least have something. But nothing to big since we were going to  urlLink  Monterey Bay   for dinner (this really awesome restaurant that overlooks the city of Pittsburgh). So we ventured to a Mexican restaurant for some snacks. At first we ere outside but it was windy.    I kid you not that it took over 45 minutes to get our food and we were mad. The manager even took care of the bill. I think that might have something to do with me, as last week at work we went to Cooker for lunch and I got our bill taken care. This was because our server was bad, and when the manager stopped by doing his rounds I told him that he needed some training. Well then the manager offered to give us free dessert and we said no thank you, and he ended up taking care of our bill.   After hanging out at the mal at little more, we scurried home to change for our 7 pm dinner reservation.  The restaurant was awesome.  We took some nice pictures there, including our dessert!              After dinner we headed to Station Square. To get there we took the incline down the hill that was pretty cool. Of course by now I was having stomach issues. I was in a lot of pain, I think it is chocolate or lactose related. After walking around we headed downtown. Ryan and I wanted to go to Philithy McNasty's which we thought was a funny name, which is just a sports bar/burger place.   Then on Sunday morning we headed out for brunch at the Grand Concourse at Station Square. I highly recommend it to anyone. It is operated by the Muer family.  You have to walk through a tunnel from the parking lot   It was beautiful inside     And outside         Then we headed off to another mall. Did I mention that PA has no sales tax on clothes.. What a savings!  We left PA around 3 and got home around 8ish.   Thank you Ryan for being so sweet, we all had a great time. :)
     
    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Our condo is really coming along these days. They are seemingly ahead of schedule. So we are keeping our fingers crossed. I have attached some pictures of the progress in the last few weeks.    This picture was taken right after it was sanded and painted last week.    This is another picture from after the painting. It shows our kitchen area and the loft to the right.    Our Master Bath Tub Area that they tiled early!    Master Bath floor    Upstairs Guest Bathroom    View from Upstairs of Great Room and Fireplace    Downstairs Kitchen Floor    Looking at downstairs kitchen counter   It is fun to see how it all comes together. It used to look so different before it started to get closer to being finished.  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It was been a while since I have posted to my blog. I started school last Monday, one class on campus (Managing Change) and one class online (Database Marketing). It seems like it will be an okay semester.  Lucky for me I had Good Friday off from work, however Craig did not. But Ryan and I went and dyed Easter Eggs with my mom during the day. They  were really pretty once we did them, then when they dried and then were put in the fridge, they got all speckled looking. My mom said she missed the cancer causing dyes they used to be able to use. It is uncanny how almost every year that I can remember the purple is kind of blue with random pink spots, you would think technology would be able to create something better.  Below are some pictures from our easter egg afternoon.              I hope that everyone had a wonderful Easter weekend! We are going to dinner at my in-laws tomorrow and I will also be cracking down and doing some homework.   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last weekend we ventured to Casino Windsor to try out our luck. Ryan, Becky, Craig and I did not come home with any more money. But we did have a good time and we are still happy go lucky people! Here is a picture of Becky and I. It looks like we are somewhere really cool doesn't it?    Not sure what else is new. Our friend Ben is going to CPR certify me next month (he is an EMS guy who is certified to teach) so that I can start getting prepared to teach Pilates. I had a dream the other night about teaching it. It wasn't a bad dream, so let's hope this works out like I want it to.  In other news my friend Kelly is pregnant and due in October. Even though it appears to be all around me. I am still not ready, so don't anyone get any ideas that it is going to rub off or anything. :)  
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well it is Saturday night and we have been in Pittsburgh since around 9 pm last night. It was a surprisingly nice drive and apparently everyone is not on the Ohio turnpike during Memorial Day weekend. :)  As I am sitting here I am thinking about how the Internet has changed how everything is done. Here I sit typing on our laptop while connected to Ryan's network and sitting on the couch. I love the Internet!  Good News to our www.liessfamily.com fans. Starting very soon our site will be back up. Thanks to our dear friends Jay and Jesse. Yay!!!!  Well not much to write about yet. We ventured to Ikea today and got some new bedding and such. We also went and saw the Day after Tomorrow at a Loehs theatre in Downtown Pittsburgh, it was fun because sat in VIP level in leather chairs and got to have drinks while watching the movie. As far as the movie, I recommend going to see it. Tomorrow we are probably venturing to the Pirates game and meeting up with some of Craig's work friends that are here this weekend for a wedding.   That is all for now, hope everyone is enjoying their long weekends I know we are :) 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well this week on Friday morning we did our final walk-thru of the Condo. It was awesome to see how much work they did and how our house is a real house now. There a few things that need to done, but certainly nothing serious. Because we are buying a condo property, the outside work must be done before we can move in. So we should be closing no later than Friday June 4th. It is exciting now, of course it all means we have a whole lot of moving ahead of us.  Not much else to report on, which is okay for once.  We are going to Pittsburgh for Memorial Day weekend to visit Ryan. We are looking forward to a relaxing weekend. Now if only the drive would be good. How many people are going to be on the Ohio turnpike on Friday night? 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well it will be two weeks this Wednesday since the season finale of the O.C. For those of you who aren't into the O.C. I recommend you start watching it. It is a great drama like 90210 was. It is on FOX on Wednesday nights at 9 pm.  For the last one, Don and Deb came over to watch it with me. Don was well prepared with his artistic expression of the O.C.     As well as his Orange County Attire.    It was fun to watch with them. I love Don and Deb. Just like everyone else. :)  Now my opinion of the finale was that is wasn't that good. When I watched One Tree Hill last week there were so many twists and turns in the last five minutes I can hardly wait until next season. The last five minutes of the O.C. where pretty much a song.  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well there is a lot to talk about since I last blogged. This weekend was pretty eventful.  On Friday we celebrated Grandma's 83rd Birthday and Ryan's 25th Birthday. We had dinner with the Dalley family at Pasquales. The best picture from this was them blowing out their candles.     Then on Saturday we went to Ryan's parent's house to celebrate with his family. It was a lot of fun!      For more pictures  urlLink  Click here    We also took some great videos with our digital camera. Be forwarned these take a while to connect to. If you are viewing this at work be careful, you don't want to get put on the Top 10 users list! :)   urlLink  Getting ready for cake    urlLink  Happy Birthday    urlLink  Gift Cerfiticates    urlLink  What are we late for?    Afterwards we went to visit our favorite baby, Leah.. what a doll!  Then on Sunday we had a great Mother's day dinner with both of our mothers at a quaint Italian Restaurant in the plaza at Silverbell and Adams.  So on Saturday I went and got Ryan a massage gift certificate at the Sandalwood Spa. While I was there they entered me in a drawing to win a gift basket.  Tonight at 7:30ish I got a call that they drew my name. The basket is awesome and has this cute stand it will be perfect for our cute new powder room at the condo. It also included a free manicure, pedicure and back treatment. :)     This weekend was wonderful and it carried into Monday!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      On Friday night we went to Mike and Julie's to celebrate Mike's 29th Birthday. We all had a great time, Julie made a wonderful dinner and on top of that we have an ice cream cake from B&R.    Birthday Boy doing the cake thing.    Derrick holding up the special card Mike got from Mark and Annie    Mike even got some garbage pail kid stickers!    Of course there was a group girl picture, it wouldn't be a party without. Of course we were missing Harmony and Beth.  To see more pictures  urlLink  Click here     Then on Saturday I did some really fun homework. Okay so it wasn't fun at all. Then we went out with Don and Deb and saw the movie Mean Girls.  Then on Sunday I did some more homework. Then went to lunch with my mom at Olgas and taught her some Pilates she can do at home.  Then we went to the Abrahams so Craig could meet Leah.  Then Becky came over and I made some chicken salads..yummy! Then we headed out to check out our condos and got some TCBY.  Like all of them this weekend was too short!  
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This weekend was great we spent a lot of time getting the house in order. On Saturday night I made tacos for dinner and our dear friends Becky and Ryan were there. They bought us some great housewarming presents - not necessary - but really great!  We got a Bombay Sapphire recipe book, some talk abouts for paging each other on other levels in our soundproof house, and two great personalized wine bottles. Becky and Ryan sure know us well!!!!  Pictures Courtesy of Becky, are shown below.        For more pictures check out  urlLink  www.liessfamily.com  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well we are back from a fun weekend in Reno.  We had a great time in Reno with our dear friends Mike and Megan!      You can view all the pictures on our website (which is back up!) at:  urlLink  http://www.liessfamily.com/images/Reno/index.html    Other than that we are still busy getting our house together and decorated. The packing and settling in has been done for the most part and we are now in decorating and organizing mode. As soon as we get things situated I will take some pictures and put them online.  For now I must log off though I still have a few things to do before I go to bed.  I will blog for longer in the future. :)
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just a short blog to let everyone we finally moved into our new home and we are loving it.  We finally got an internet connection working today (no thanks to Comcast who couldn't get it working in over a week) yay! SBC DSL!  I am finishing my semester this week along with getting ready for our weekend trip to Reno for Craig's bowling tournament. I promise to blog soon with some pictures of the new house and of course of our Trip.  Oh one more thing. We decided to do the American Diabetes Walk again. You can join my team, or pledge us online at:   urlLink  My ADA Walk Center  
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This week's post is dedicated to our dear friends the Rhues. They left on Sunday morning to their new home in Sunny Florida, Ft. Pierce to be exact. Julie will start her new teaching job there in a few weeks.   We will miss them dearly.   On Friday night we got together for a last goodbye. It has been so unseasonably cool this year, that we were all wearing jeans, and sweatshirts, but of course since it is July you can't forget the sandals.   I got a few good pictures before our batteries died. Check them out:  urlLink       urlLink       It was sad to leave that night, I cried and I don't care that I showed my emotions I will miss them. And even though we can visit it won't be the same and it just takes some getting used to!  
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well it was a great weekend. On Friday night B (Becky) helped us get ready for our party on Saturday. Then Saturday was a lot of fun. Of course Leah being there and being awesome was the best!   urlLink         urlLink  Click here to see more pics!    Then at night we went out to a really nice new place called Seldom Blue downtown in the Ren Cen for LA's birthday. It was a great time. Then on Sunday we went to Kyle (C's cousin's graduation party) and then got straightened up at home and did some fun homework.   This week should be much better than last, my ear doesn't hurt at all!
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well this week hasn't been great. On Monday night my right ear started throbbing leaving me with no sleep Tuesday morning. I called my boss and let her know I was going to be a few hours late catching some z's.  Then it got worse, I saw the doctor in the afternooon and he said I had "Swimmer's Ear". Usually caused from swimming but also can be caused by getting water in your ear from the shower, using a q-tip wrong and even allergies. As we have not been swimming in forever it wasn't the most common cause. I chalk it up to showering or even q-tips. My doctor gave me a prescription for CiproDex drops. I suppose I am now safe from Anthrax. :) Of course I had to put them in ears 3 drops twice a day. The directions recommended someone else putting them in so I could my head down for a minute or so after. So at work, Kelly has been helping me out.  So for the last 48 hours it has continously felt like someone is stabbing me in the ear. Of course because it was just my luck, I also had to teach Pilates on Tuesday and Wednesday. This was no problem as I could feel pain no matter what I was doing and so teaching Pilates actually got my mind off it. Then my friend Elizabeth called and asked if I could sub for her tonight, so it was 3 nights of teaching in a row. Talk about a great workout. For some reason tonight I was extra hard. I think it was because I was starting to feel better my ear is officially draining. For me the non-knowledgeable ear infection person (yep that is right never had one until now) it apparently starts to leave through your lymph node behind your ear. It is actually a really soothing feeling.   Now I am officially ready for the weekend. We are having some people over on Saturday to see the new house. I am geeked.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I finally had the time to post some pictures from events in the past few weeks. Starting with Beer Fest on 7/24/04   urlLink     urlLink     urlLink      Then my Pampered Chef Party on 7/29/04. Which was super fun with Kendall, Ethan and Madalyn being there  urlLink      urlLink      urlLink       Then on Saturday we had Matt and Chrissy's Wedding Shower plus Luge Party  urlLink      urlLink      urlLink      What a great week/weekend we had. It was surrounded by some of our best friends. Of course those of you who didn't see us this weekend, you are also great friends, hopefully we see you soon!  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>