<Blog>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Miss Beth ~    &nbsp;  It's from the song call "Tell Him" and the version I've heard is by Linda Ronstadt.&nbsp; Okay, so that's out of the way.    &nbsp;  I have to apologize 100x over for being absent from your life for the past two weeks or so.&nbsp; I have been running around like crazy and it's been tough keepingone step ahead of the work. Honestly, I didn't do a very good job at allexplaining to you how I operate and all the things going on in my life.&nbsp; I feellike that was a rather rude thing to do to you.    &nbsp;  See, like I told you earlier tonight, I might be 20, but it often feels like Ihave to operate as though I'm 30. Kinda crazy, but it's how i've lived for awhile.&nbsp; I love working, but it takes up a ton of time.    &nbsp;  In addition to that, my family comes before anything else.&nbsp; They are so very important to me.&nbsp; Faith, Family, & School come first. And as of late, family has been taking up a lot of time followed by work.    &nbsp;  Honestly, I haven't been very accessible to any of my friends of late, not justyou.&nbsp; And the hardest part is that it's almost time to head back to PSU. Summer is indeed winding down.&nbsp; That sucks.    &nbsp;  But . . . I have so enjoyed my time with you.&nbsp; And desperately want to spendmore time with you before we head back to school.&nbsp; You are such a doll. So much fun to be around, enthusiastic, funny, and believe it or not,&nbsp; kind and sweet. So let's enjoy the time we have left and make the most of it.&nbsp;     &nbsp;  "we'll make the best of what's around" --&nbsp; dmb    &nbsp;  ciao bella donna,   Andy    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       So I finally got to talk to Andy.&nbsp;  Finally! &nbsp; We were supposed to go out today, but when he didn't call me yesterday, or today, I just figured something else came up for him (in typical Andy style) and made plans with Ashley.&nbsp; And I'm damn glad that I did, because he called me at like 5:30 and the first thing out of his mouth was "You're going to hate me ..." but he was wrong, because I assumed that was going to happen and took the initiative to stop the boredom.&nbsp; I could tell he felt really bad about it this time though.&nbsp; And he definitely felt bad when I started crying, because although I wasn't disappointed that he couldn't go out tonight, I have been kind of disappointed with the fact that he's been AWOL for like two weeks now.&nbsp; He feels bad though, but all ended well.&nbsp; I think.&nbsp; I sort of started zoning out towards the end of the conversation ... oops.&nbsp; My bad.    &nbsp;  On a super high note, Ashley and I had a fantastic time tonight, the highlight of my evening being when we were checking out of Giant and she said started talking about Reese's Pieces except she said Reese's Penis instead.&nbsp; That was very entertaining, although our cashier didn't seem to find it quite as amusing as we did.&nbsp; Oh well.    &nbsp;  With all of my Reese's Penis,   Your Sweetest b.  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       All the anger and hostility has just oozed out.&nbsp; Oh yeah, that's right, I said oozed.&nbsp; Even though that word is kind of grossing me out now.&nbsp; Haha!    &nbsp;  For some reason, ever since yesterday, I haven't been able to stop smiling.&nbsp; This is something I can't even begin to explain, because I don't understand what changed ... I don't think anything changed at all, in fact.    &nbsp;  Maybe the loose wires in my brains finally fully disconnected and I'm totally crazy now.&nbsp; So who had their money on July 28th?    &nbsp;  Will all my    Your Sweetest b.  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       So today,&nbsp;almost everything that could possibly have gone wrong did go wrong.&nbsp; But in the most spectacularly entertaining way!&nbsp; Let me start at the beginning ...    &nbsp;  We're on the Turnpike driving along, minding our own business when, at the Reading exit, this asshole car decides that traffic isn't moving fast enough so he  drives down the middle  of the road.&nbsp; Down the middle!&nbsp; The poor old guy he cut off must have shit his pants, I know I almost did.&nbsp; Then there was all the rain ... terrential downpours are not the most fun thing to be outside in.&nbsp; Hydroplaning (although not the safest thing in the world) was a lot of fun, seeing as we didn't hit anything.&nbsp; But the most fun of the entire day came after we were off of the Turnpike and in a crappy residential section of eastern PA.    &nbsp;  There was an accident on North 100, and unfortunately we got caught in the line of traffic ... right as we get up to the point where we could go around it, this police SUV goes in front of us.&nbsp; Well, not exactly in front of us - it blocked the other lane, and about 3 inches of the front of it were in our lane.&nbsp; Ashley and I, confused as ever, decided that we would just go around it because it wasn't really blocking our lane.&nbsp; So we do that.&nbsp; Big mistake people!&nbsp; The cop slams on his horn and pulls up next to us and screams "pull onto that road up there and get a ticket!"&nbsp; I start reassuring Ashley that everything will be okay, but inside we were both panicking and I'm getting ready to turn on the waterworks to get us out of this ticket.&nbsp; Turns out, I didn't have to do anything, he noticed that we were from out-of-town and let us go.&nbsp; Even gave us directions since that was the first time we got lost.    &nbsp;  After that, we basically got lost about a dozen times, had to pull over and ask about seven random people how to get to West Chester University (people really need to learn about the town they live in, for real).&nbsp; But we made it there.&nbsp; Eventually.&nbsp; And all the driving was worth it ... those people are pretty nice.    &nbsp;  Only real downside to my day was not getting a call back from Andy.&nbsp; But whatever.&nbsp; The boy is busy, me thinks.    &nbsp;  Sch   Your Sweetest b.  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       It's amazing what sleep and a day of talking with your friends will do to put a situation in perspective.&nbsp; I feel a lot better.&nbsp; And it's crazy, but Ashley and I have the same problem ... we let the anger fester when we don't see them, and then when we do get the chance to talk to them, all the bad mojo flies out the window.&nbsp; Andy's pretty smile has that effect on me.&nbsp; Haha maybe I should put up walls made of tougher stuff if that's all it takes to knock them down.&nbsp; I am, however, keeping the monkey I got for him.     &nbsp;   Ahhh!&nbsp; I got to talk to Kyle today!&nbsp; I missed talking to him, he was one of my favorite people at lunch every day.&nbsp; And in the band room, you know, when I wandered around everyday&nbsp;during third period (thank God Mr. Davidson never turned me in, for all the times he caught me).&nbsp; He updated me on all of the people I've been to busy to talk to:&nbsp; Travis, Chris, Ben.&nbsp; Haha I was a little off on the Jess and Ben betting, but oh well.&nbsp; I tried.&nbsp; Ben has a little more self-control than I expected.&nbsp; It's kind of sad, I wanted to be the one to deflower him, hahaha!!!     &nbsp;   Party at my house in the beginning of August!     &nbsp;   Love, hugs, and kisses,    Your Sweetest b.    
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Tonight was a lot of fun.&nbsp; Kunkel, he's just fantastic to hang out with.&nbsp; Quite the dirty mind on that boy ... but that only makes it more fun, since he's pretty much the only one in his group that will say that kind of thing.&nbsp; I loved listening to the music tonight (when I was paying attention) - it gives me goosebumps just thinking about it.&nbsp; Music is such an amazing thing, with its ability to change a person's mood or thoughts.&nbsp; I love it!&nbsp; However ... not everything tonight was good ... bad things lurk beneath the surface.    &nbsp;  I'll be the first person to admit that I am by no means the best person to date.&nbsp; Quite the opposite, I can be quite the wicked little bitch.&nbsp; However, I have been nothing but fantastic lately (all because of a very positive influence from Jess and Andy) and I haven't been getting anything fantastic in return.&nbsp; Why is it that when I'm nicer to people, people are more cruel to me?&nbsp; No, cruel isn't the word, because this isn't intentional.&nbsp; At least, I hope not.&nbsp; My love life just isn't going the way I want it to be going right now.    &nbsp;  I don't need to hear excuses, I don't&nbsp;want to hear them from Andy, nor do I want to hear them from his friends.&nbsp; Everything started out so well, and then he goes on vacation and I become second tier.&nbsp; I don't expect to be number one (not even number five), and I don't want to be the center of his attention, but damnit, I'd like to have a little of attention.&nbsp; Unfortunately, I'm not getting any, I don't hear from him, I don't see him, and I don't know what to do anymore.&nbsp; Why&nbsp;knowingly give myself that headache?&nbsp; Even Kunkel has been more of a boyfriend-like figure than him.&nbsp; Kunkel, for the love of God.&nbsp; I think I might have to stop abusing that poor kid, he doesn't deserve it.&nbsp; But anyway ... I sat back and thought about my situation with Andy tonight and wondered, "was it something I did?" and I decided against that thought.&nbsp; If I did anything wrong, it was in expecting too much from someone unwilling.&nbsp; My bad.&nbsp; Won't do that again.&nbsp; God I am so pissed off right now!&nbsp; I went into this summer with so many prospects, so much fun at my disposal, and then I met Andy and gave that up, because he was just so perfect.&nbsp;  PERFECTION IS A CRUEL ILLUSION! &nbsp; He swept me off my feet, wormed his way in, and now I hurt more than any other rejection I've ever experienced.&nbsp; And now I'm crying ... great.&nbsp; Just turn me down already, Andy.&nbsp; It was fun, I"m not sorry for meeting you.    &nbsp;  Maybe I'm being melodramatic.&nbsp; Actually, it's quite possible that that's all I'm being.&nbsp; Sorry if I am.&nbsp; I really do think that maybe I just blow this out of proportion, maybe I'm just expecting too much from Andy because I see what Jess and Kirby have and I'm insanely jealous.&nbsp; Oh well.&nbsp; If that's the case, then, well, my bad.    &nbsp;  On my final note of the evening - people who purposefully ignore the fact that you're uber pissed off and act cheerful when you're seething on the inside ... those people need to be beaten.&nbsp; It's a condescending thing to do.&nbsp; At least acknowledge the anger.&nbsp; Don't be a fuckhead.&nbsp; Especially when you're dealing with a fiery temper like mine, ANDY.    &nbsp;  I love you all!   Your Sweetest b  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         in my eyes&nbsp;...      &nbsp;     It's amazing what not seeing people for a few days will do.&nbsp; Specifically, not seeing the guys from Harrisburg.&nbsp; Without them, I really don't get to see my femme friends (although Juice and Java the other night was tres fantastique), which is pathetic.&nbsp; Since when do we need guys to define our friendships?&nbsp; And on that note, since when do we need guys to define ANY part of our lives?&nbsp; I guess I'm more or less just venting because suddenly I'm having guy problems.&nbsp; No, not problems, just one problem, and his name is Andy.&nbsp; And the answer to this problem is so incredibly simple, that when I found it, it slapped me upside the head and told me I was a dumbass.&nbsp; "Never let someone be your priority while allowing yourself to be their option."&nbsp; Wise words from my sister's profile.&nbsp; Not like Andy was top priority or anything [that will forever be myself and my mommy], but I was putting too much emphasis on him without getting anything back.&nbsp; And besides that, I do believe he just successfully phased me out.&nbsp; It doesn't really hurt all that much, seeing as I actually figured it out, unlike poor Sean, who probably is still wondering why I never answer my cell phone.&nbsp; Phased out and single.&nbsp; It just seems like a waste of like three weeks of my life, you know?&nbsp; But anyway, there are much better things to talk about.  &nbsp;  I missed just having my femmes with me.&nbsp; Which is why I think my slumber party is going to be an all-girls thing, maybe I'll still have a birthday party with the guys, but right now I think I want to focus more on the people I really truly love and care about, and that's my girl friends.&nbsp; We've gotten so crazily close this summer ... what's going to happen when we all go our separate ways?&nbsp; I'm on the verge of tears just thinking about it, because the possibility of us all drifting apart just scares me.&nbsp; I realize that I'm supposed to make new friends at college, but damnit, I'm not at college 365 days a year, and I like the friends I have now.&nbsp; Besides ... we all know how I feel about other girls, ha!  &nbsp;  On my final note of the evening ... it's about damn time, Kirby.  &nbsp;  I love you all, some more than others, but still for all,  Your Sweetest  b .     
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Phew, what a weekend!  I'm so glad it's over, but in a way I'm sort of sad to see it go.  And that is mainly because I finally got to see Corey and wow he is about ten times more amazing when he's comfortably at home.  Home field advantage, I like to call it.  He had me all fidgety and nervous while he was completely at ease ... role reversal from TSA, people.  His friends were all nice, and apparently I had met them all at TSA, but I could only remember Trevor (who's being an anti-social bastard at the moment, not talking and all), so I felt sort of bad.  Sort of ... but not quite.  Anyway, we all went to this huge drive-in movie place and Corey and I were in a car by ourselves, and I bastardized his pure little self in a fun, fun way.  That I do not feel bad about.  Because it was  awesome !  Andy always tells me that when we kiss, he gets that tingly feeling, and I've never gotten that with him, but last night with Corey, BAM! it was there.  And I liked it.  A lot.  Didn't really watch either of the movies, but it was so worth it.      Other than that, this weekend had its highs and lows.  My sister, moody as ever, was a royal bitch all of yesterday and today.  I swear, I can only take like 5 hours of her at a time, before I feel the need to kill rise.  And her boyfriend is not the most entertaining of them all - Indian my ass.  He looks like a damn potatoe.  Highs of the weekend include Teresa letting me play with all of her Origins stuff (and she has lots, people, but I managed to use it all in about 50 hours of being there) and my mommy buying me stuff at the gigantic mall.  I felt bad about spending my mom's money, once again, but she kept offering and I fell in love with this black off the shoulder shirt ... so I took her up on her offer.  It's a hot shirt people, although I'm starting to think that maybe I should have gotten it in cream or pink, since I own so much black already.  Oh well, my bad.      I's luvs you's all'n,   Your Sweetest b.  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       So today was much more fun than I was expecting.  Got to wake up early to go open a checking account (with the bling bling my grandma sent me ... who knew I could feel such love for her?) and then spent the day with my mommy in Gettysburg.  She even let me drive for most of the day, even though I almost got us hit by two cars.  My bad ... I really should learn to look both ways before I move the car.  She bought me more clothes, from GAP, which is one of my favorite places now because there's an uber hot guy working there who purposely came over to the register that I was getting rung up at (by the gay guy who makes my day every time I'm in there) just to look.  I've decided that deep purplish-red is my new color.  Which means I'm finally adding some color to my pretty much all-black wardrobe.  Then we went to Perkins and she brought me home, stuffed full of chicken and cheesesticks, only to have Ashley call me.  So Ashley and I went out.      I wasn't exactly sure what Ashley and I were going to go do, but we ended up at Barnes & Noble looking for books and magazines about prostitution.  No luck, and that apalls me.  Thoroughly.  So we gave up and went to the coffeeshop, and the adventure began.  I saw my friend Duncan from the RaggedEdge (the coffeeshop in Gettysburg that sadly burned down).  And we started talking and he hung out with us all night.  Definitely was cool enough to get himself invited to my Meteor Shower Party!  I think I might have offended his friends a little, one by calling the guy in black gay, and two by staring blatantly at them.  I had nowhere else to look, I swear!  Haha, yeah right.  I was just staring at the hot guy in the blue shirt who apparently is a bit of a pretentious snob.  Nothing new for me ... snobs are the best ones to fuck with.      But this must end here ... I've got some packing to do before tomorrow (going to see my sister is Pittsburgh, I'll be back on Sunday, I promise).  I love you all, my babies.  : )      With all my loving (and badly aimed) Gaydar,   Your Sweetest b.  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So my party was last night, and at least I know Amanda and I had a lot of fun.  I apologize for disappearing, but you people need to realize that I don't get to see Andy as much as I like (which would pretty much be at all) and I wanted some alone time.  Alone with Andy time, I mean. Haha!  Amanda and Lloyd totally hooked up on my "deck of love" and so did Andy and I and at least it was a good idea.  Candles are always fun.  Well, I'll write more later ... I'm distracted hardcore.  Ciao mis amores! : ) 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Reread some things I had printed out ... a sense of serenity has passed over me.  I'm calm.  I'm zen to the max.  The honeymoon phase is over.      My birthday is coming up ... diamonds are at the top of the list people.      Haha I saw the fattest baby ever today!  Porkchop aka Jeremy is so calm and quiet, but I think it's induced by the fat.  Sweetest little baby ever though.      Sorry this wasn't much people, I'm busy talking to people at the same time and it's hard to do both at the same time.  I love you all though!      Hugs and Many Kisses,   Your Sweetest b.  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>