<Blog>


<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The most frequently expressed complaint women have about men is that men don't listen. Either a man completely ignores her when she speaks to him, or he listens for a few beats, assesses what is bothering her, and then proudly puts on his Mr. Fix-It cap and offers her a solution to make her feel better. He is confused when she doesn't appreciate his gesture of love. No matter how many times she tells him that he's not listening, he doesn't get it and keeps doing the same thing. She wants empathy, but he thinks she wants solutions. The most frequently expressed complaint men have about women is that women are always trying to change them. When a woman loves a man she feels responsible to assisst him in growing and tries to help him improve the way he does things. She forms a home-improvement committee and he becomes her primary focus. No matter how much he resists her help, she persists-waiting for any opportunity to help him or tell him what to do. She thinks she's nurturing him, while he feels he's being controlled, instead he wants her acceptance.  These two problems can finally be solved by first understanding why men offer solutions and why women seek to improve, let's pretend to go back in time, where by observing life on Mars and Venus-before the planets discovered one another or came to Earth-we can gain some insights into men and women.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        We mistakenly assume that if our partners love us they will react and behave in certain ways-the ways we react and behave when we love someone.      When men and women are able to respect and accept their differences then love has a chance to blossom.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Imagine that men are from Mars and women are from Venus. One day long ago the Martians, looking through their telescopes, discovered the Venusians. Just glimpsing the Venusians awakened feelings they had never known. They fell in love and quickly invented space travel and flew to Venus. The Venusians welcomed the Martians with open arms. They had intuitively known that this day would come. Their hearts opened wide to a love they had never felt before. The love between the Venusians and Martians was magical. They delighted in being together, doing things together, and sharing together. Though from different worlds, they reveled in their differences. They spent months learning about each other, exploring and appreciating their different needs, preferences, and behavior patterns. For years they lived together in love and harmony. Then they needed to fly to Earth. In the beginning everything was wonderful and beautiful. But the effects of Earth's atmosphere took hold, and one morning everyone woke up with a peculiar kind of amnesia-selective amnesia! Both the Martians and Venusians forgot that they were from different planets and were supposed to be different. In one morning everything they had learned about their differences was erased from their memory. And since that day men and women have been in conflict.
       
    
    
</post>


<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Kainis talaga ung ex ko kapal ng mukha!!! sarap sapakin!!! alam nyo kung ano cnb nya??? the nerve of that guy! well, i used the account of my frend in ragna to talk to him. (janelle's account) and i talked to him. well first of all it's not my fault... it's my stupid so-called frend brandon's fault. he keeps on telling me to ask daniel questions about this and that. so i asked daniel "galit ka ba kay lev?" (remember he thinks i'm janelle). he said no. a little while later he said "eh wla naman un gngwa kundi magtanong ng presyo cno hindi mabwibwisit?"... well first of all it's not my fault! c brandon nagpapatanong sakin! damn it i even cried... i feel like trash
     
    
</post>



</Blog>