<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        counting down to nxt month... 16min52s... im home.. tmr having choir... dad n i went tm just now.. had a pleasant evening.. he bought some accesories, & bought me a shirt... hMm.. andrew must be reaching home already.. yeap bought my converse school shoe also... yayeE.. hahax.. gotta sell ard 6 pieces of mobius items for art tmr.. hope i can get ppl to buy frm me, i'lll target art freaks den aunties =) heE.. kkz sleEpy slEepy...  better get going... goodbye july~ nxt month 8 august ish mums bdae...        misS my baby*    
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       phew*   im  urlLink home  sweet  urlLink home ...   went to  urlLink school  @ 10... ppl were already there.. so we did  urlLink art  until lunch  urlLink time .. went opposite to uncle kenneth's... me, clar,mel n nat..  hahax... we laughed so hard when calarion called out to tt guy, " haAAy, yr  urlLink underwear  can be seen, pull it up ".. and alot of other crap like" so long already.. u cannot feel meh?  "  hahax... hes gf also didnt notice.. man~ it showed his butt okay~ so funNy..  the jc gurls next table were all red in the face too.. hahaha...   well we went back n met Ju @2... we have this project to do, starting with the  urlLink art  exhibition.. it'll be brought ard  urlLink schools  n eventually hospitals to teach patients who suffers frm  urlLink cancer  to use colours to brighten up their day.. more towards kids n outreach to community...   haha think im gonna get involed in it... its gonna be a long term thingie.. probably 4 yrs to establish everything..a dream to dream =] then our grp would be the pioneers.. so cool aye.. haha.. not forgetting my choir.. *  hmM clarion and i started on a pottery.. both of us.. hahax.. nt sure can finish or not but we'll try..     i moulded two pieces of heart, one with 'drew', the other with "jas"...  =) gonna post it on  urlLink http://tabulas.com/~starstarx  for ppl to go view it =] hehe... waiting for daddy to be back  urlLink home  now.. later bring me buy sch  urlLink shoes ... *yaWn.z.. kinda tired already.. lol.. ahh theres bread in kitchen.. ciao~ go munch...   
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      [[http://www.tabulas.com/~starstarx]] my images page =) created for andrew also actually =) tgif *heE.. watched I.robots wif mel,nat,clar,fiq,dil... its quite nice.. haha.." aaRRHhhCCheeEwW!! uhh im sorry but im allergic to bullshit" said willsmith.. hahax.. s o funny... i realise im really kinda short of cash.. haiz.. need buy bus pass, converse  urlLink school   urlLink shoes , we're planning to go  urlLink shopping  one day too.. but no  urlLink money .. hai..only can start saving after i buy my  urlLink shoes .. ahah its ok.. i'll survive thru though... juz cut down on  urlLink movies  n all =/ hope i can lar.. anyway tmr going to  urlLink school  @ 9am to complete  urlLink art .. den theres a  urlLink art  meeting with Mr.Zul @2pm.. probably gonna try new stuff or go to OBS for  urlLink art  again.. xD anyway dad juz came back.. hez nagging at me lyk hell.. gosh.. i hate this so much... sigh*... i wont let him bring me down.. im gonna stay nice.. yesh.. cuz i dont want ndrew 2 worry bout me.. just wanna enjoy the moment with him... hmMm how nice if i get a warm hug righ now n everything unpleasant would go away... (*_*~) 
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      long day... impact gave me a call to ask me to reschedule my audition.. i dont feel like going anymore.. haiz... class time was alright.. miss andrew here n there..lost debate to 3b but we're nt exactly the losers.. tey won cuz they did mre homework thats all.. yupp... looked for clarion in art room.. mr. lau gimme a chocolate sweet.. hahax.. den i went home with my grp of malay friends from class..arifa followed n she suddenly pull me down to convenient store n treated me peach yougurht drink.. haha.. so i walked with her ard n listened to her story...saw zenn @ park doing stunns.. hes good..=) went blading ard8.. was pouring outside.. so i came back @ 830.. khairul asked me for a favour, sadly i cunt find any info on net... today mast absent.. tmr she'll be alright i guess.. hmMm den bro louis is kinda sad.. feels sad too... failed to notice my godbro's emptiness.. or maybe he's just too happy-go-lucky in front of schmates.. hmmM hope tt i can manage to comfort him thru words.... drew msged me i miss you baby.. haha.. probably hes reached home by now cuz its 10 mins already.. wanna say gd night to him b4 i sleep later.. yea... think tts abt all today.. feeling quite tired now.. n the bunch of bad news i received today kinda 'depressed' me.. lol.. nt tt serious... n i realise... im so lucky to haf andrew too.. juz lyk hes said to me.. actually its vice versa =]... imu* goodnight everybody... if only i could fill up emptiness in every singel person on earth.. i'll start with my beloved friends n family n den everyone else... before myself.. cuz by then, the satisfaction of ppls joy n ma baby's love would have filled mine up alread...nights.. starry land time*
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       A Telephone Call that Changed my Life    &nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp; The night was cold and I was sitting in my bedroom, reading my once favourite book by Nicholas Sparks. I have read it for more than three times already.&nbsp; It was not as if I have a choice to do whatever I want after having a heated argument with my father.   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Suddenly the telephone rang and to my immense relief, it was a call from mother. I asked her if she had a good day and then complained to her about father’s unreasonable attitude, however I could sense that she was not really interested in my conversation so I asked her if she was alright. &nbsp;“Daughter, I have decided to leave the family and I’ve already booked a one way ticket to Europe. I shall be staying at a friends house. Please inform dad about this and take care of the family for me dear.” &nbsp;With these words from my mother, I found myself at a complete loss for worlds as I felt as though my whole world had just collapsed. I was filled with remorse and the fact that I was totally unprepared for such a situation made me scared. I could not hold down the sorrow and a scorching stream of tears began to flow down my cheeks. I went into the bathroom and locked myself inside for the next half an hour. When I regained my composure, I began to question myself what had affected mother so badly that she had to leave our family. Minutes drift pass and eventually the answers shot at me like bullets. Our family consists of father, me, and my two brothers. We lived in a big house but have never hired a maid, mum had to clean the house everyday and she never fail to cook us our favourite meals every evening. Father was a workaholic who comes home from business trips only for sixty five days in a year. Mother must be lonely and tired of nagging at us without our least efforts to change for the better. Occasionally she even received cold shuns from my brothers. My heart palpitated wildly as I thought of the consequences without mum around the house, taking care of our needs. My brothers are always quarrelling with each other over minor things and they never got along well. Father did not have a close relationship with us due to his constant business trips, he was absent from all our major graduations or birthday celebrations, unlike mother.  I stared at my distraught face in the mirror and wished that it was all a terrible nightmare. The telephone call on that fateful night indeed changed my life. The beginning of&nbsp; my misery.  
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      manage to complete my first layer for batik.. its so off the traditional form of art but i still like it =) its made of 3 butterflys n a face, lips, hair, hand... haha ratehr abstract... today after school went tm with lu, shron , n kanna...bought her stuff...den came back.. kannan treated me free ice cream.. lol.. wasnt exactly a good day.. not that bad either.. just feel tired now.. *tmr debate dae... we haven done anything much.. hope that by luck n our intelligence we can win =) andrew gotta recover... missing him alot alot... today we did art in artroom n jy was there also.. haha had a lil talk wit him.. hes still the same.. den andy was at workshop... lamed ard for a sec also.. >. .< irritating!! cuz shes got a neighbour who hears things... and ..yup.. jus yesterday he heard the hokkien speaking friend saying something.. but somehow he understood... it said, "i'll be ard for many days.. i haven find my photo..."kkz go drink juice.. ciao* haha hair stand*
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        i want drew to recover... didnt take my POA  urlLink test  today.. im sure mdn koh must be pissed wit me... cunt find her n i thought i was alone...was with classmates after  urlLink school .. discussed a lil bit of debate points with ikmal n the rest of the  urlLink time  was mainly laming ard, joking, singing, but there was quite a fruitful conversation @ the end of the day as well.. oh well... i have nice malay  urlLink friends  =D hmMm nearly got into trouble with teacher.. so i decided to ask clar n arihfa to acc me back to see mdm tan.. i talked to her for a short while n onvinced her tt we are good students n dont need any form of disciplinery reminders... haha.. i spoke to her quite sternly though.. haaa taufiq said shes scared of me.. hmm anyway i do deserve the respect =) haha.. heard tt mr.bernard's mother in  urlLink law  passed away... pray that God's with him to give him emotional support thru this period... but hahaha.. hes absence in  urlLink school  was greatly enjoyed by every student... =x hmmm my darl really cares abt me... i assured him i'll be with him thru thick n thin, we're gonna be acheiving dreams together n our  urlLink love  shall be a strong and everlasting one =] kkz... gtg do work...  urlLink time  for  urlLink business .. * drizzle drizzle*   
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In the hazy illusion of deception, my lungs stopped reciprocating... my heart was fooled by misconceptions and facing reality became tormenting. to love is death by choice... but is this what love's all about? watching the twilight break, and all that hectic noise Finally realise that rejection needed to be allowed. along the candlelit alley where you said those words to me, guilt and concern wasnt my obligation just want to tell u im sorry,really but tomorrow is another day, so grab yr wings n leave yr inspiration
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      done most of my posters n started t.shirt design for ignition... today was fine, english math n physics test are over n done with... went blading ard 9+.. whoa i nearly flew off the slope after jumping off the curb n landing on the road bump... hmm... didnt feel well today though... after school went tm with mic n lulu, had indian food n went times to get ma stationery.. andrew ish still ill.... pray tt he'll recover soon n that he wont feel so much uncomfort... i realised i cant sleep.. haf this habit of waking up many times in the wee hours of morn... alomost everyday i'ld wake up @ 12+(if i sleep early).. den 2+, 3+.. almost every single hour.. n most of the friends i call are already asleep.. darn cant find someone to talk to... sad* anyway tmr probably gonna stay back after school to do debate thingie.. yaWnz*... time for coffee... ciaox~ mental n physical status now:bored n concerned*n lil bit of insomnia.. >.<
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        hearing you whisper.. "i miss you"... is such a bliss...  *Sunday...klin stayed over last night... we went bedok, den geylang,den back to moulmein fer choir... i haf diff parts to sing already.. probably cuz i missed soem practices n also cuz certain parts of the lead need distinctive n @ the same time, able to blend voices.. me n phebe jie doing all creatures together.. keith klin n i haf a part in mixed voices in amazing love.. haha... kenneth irritated me 'unirritatingly' today.. haha, i wasnt in a good state of mood but hes lame jokes n retard somehow did not piss me off.. lol... actually i know tt kenneth make a really good friend.. keith msged me to apologise abt his vulgar friend darren who told us vulgar n 'cold' jokes on the train.. lolx.. actually a bunch of friends i haf could be even worse.. oh well.. @ least both the brothers are gentlemen enuff to tell me tt their sryy.. haha... hmmm.. there was a minor misunderstanding between andrew n my boyfriend AndRew* juz now when andrew msged me n reminded me to watch a ray of light featuring adam.. hurhurx.. so farnie.. hmMm.. somehow today dad denied hes act of continuous monotonous nagging @ me ard 9... n it really pissed the shet outta me.. jasmine aint made of steel n my heartz' nt cold.. i have dignity n i need to feel respected even as a daughter... ahh..or it could juz be mere generation gap... i'll manage though... i'll make my dad happy.. yes i will n i must do it.. andrew's gonna be there to support me... im self motivated but hes presence ard could do some good i guess ;)... hope he'll recover fully from flu n wadevrr irritating virus which might try ter sicken my baby... haha.. mua* sent him a anti-biotikA kish on the forehead to make his nights nt so cold.. n hope he'll miss me less.. if nt hes bill ish gonna cost a bomb frm all the 3 letter words he send =) hehe*.. (uh uh.. nt ilu... its imu*) hmmm.. tmr i shall study more in school b4 coming back... den we'll see wad happends.. hope tt things @ home will change for the better... ahh.. yess.. i need to shop for stationery too.. kenot forget* kaex.. orh orh timez here.. nights 
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1.51am. *m i s s i n g y o u*
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       ·¨·.×*¤£öv€ ïs sËêing yrsêlf thrü §ømËonêz êy€s+f!nÐ|N ¥rsêlf ïn §ôMêönËz h€åRt·¨·¤     *~You can chase a butterfly all over e field n never catch it. But if u sit quietly in e grass it will come n sit on your shoulder~*   Friday... after the competition for racial harmony collarge, we came in the 3rd position.. we deserved 1st.. really we do... although we didnt do any plainning beforehand or wadsoeva but we came out with the most original n creative 3d work!1 man... 1st n 2nd prize was 3a n 3e... haha... maybe they won cuz of the way they organised their 'given fabric n probs' neatly.. tts all really.. as for us, we started from scratch, from drawing n cutting island to the rainbow... anyway it took an hour.. sorta rush but we managed =) after  urlLink school  went  urlLink home  with lulu.. today mic joyce huiying we all gathered once again.. was quite nice =) haha.. ma treasured  urlLink friends .. went for lunch with lulu n siulun.. ate so much ok.. i was becoming a pigg. oinkoinkz... hahha... nvm later or tmr go jogging for a while.stay fit.. =) i miss andrew.. haha so cute.. messaged me at ard 9 n said i miss you.. den 9.15... same thing plus a lil bit more.. den at 12+.. i miss u alot alot... haha.. [drewjas.blogspot] hahaha.. he changed it cuz there actually exists a jasdrew.blogspot!!! some unknow person of cuz.. haha... anyway tmr shld be a  urlLink family  day .. evening we're going to aunt jo's hse near the beach for bbq... hope it dont clash with choir somehow... yeapp... im out`* dont forget today ish deardears bball dae. tmr mast's bdae n following day, fiq's bdae... 
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       hmMmm my  urlLink baby  got sick.. so heartbreaking... but nt bad aye... hes recovered 80% already =] hehe... if only i could be beside him taking care of his needs.. hmm... Andrew.. :) He said "i need you".. ~m i s s y o u s o m u c h~ im really keen abt our current progress n how i wish  urlLink time  could freeze... when everything seemed so right thru our deep yet enjoyable conversations.. awWw.. haha.. we're gonna make it look good n be slendid in everyway no matter what ppl might say... heE.. i have a hope... n it is you  urlLink baby ... teach me how to  urlLink love  right from the start.. like you've said, pure emotions of a  urlLink baby ... *imu*kkz back to a.m. In  urlLink school  everything was pretty fine... its aqils b.dae.. he seem so lonely n sad as eva.. hope ash n him will once again be rekindled to  urlLink love  deeply.. haha @ least i know tts wad hes hoping for...manage to finish chinese exma compo with louis n jy's 'help'kekex... urlLink school  end.. mast didnt wanna do napha so well, i skipped too... darn im down for english remedial.. shock* haha y?..cuz i failed my compo.. i mean the overall... hmMm bascically i attempted highly ambitious essay on teen suicide n some other story by the title of 'windows' haha mr. peters asked me if i wrote tehm myself.. he cant believe the authencity of my piece of work.. hahaha... anyway i took it politely as a indirect compliment cuz the compo was too good.. hahaha.. ppl think its surreal n mysteriously cool.. but i think its rather realistic.. if u really allow yr thoughts to run deeper, yes it is.. urlLink trust  me =) hmMm maybe i shld accpent d fact tt not everyone will appreciate certain things u do n certain opinions one tend to show in forms of words.. hahaha... ok nuff said..  den i walked to interchange with alvin... we chatted abt life.. urlLink school ,  urlLink family , our discipline masters who are actually pretty cool ppl.. hahaha probably cuz we know them better den most students do =x anyway we ended up in long johns...  urlLink chat  futher until we saw victor fer the 2nd  urlLink time ... he sat down n we began chatting.. lolx.. victor has a pretty iq intensive n void of eq kinda character, but anyway he opened up to us and we indulged in a good conversation... haha.. actually all along i thought victor was quite a nice guy... hmMm one down, few more to go.. * err.. i mean him singing for my beachpub in future cuz he has a passion for  urlLink music  =) wahaha...span>  
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       He calls out to me in transparent dreams... blinding me from what lies before... i once thought he was my greatest nemesis, but he is my arch enemy no more... his name is misery* he is just an illusion, alwaez there tryin ter bring me down... thoughts are daunting but im a fighter... leave me alone, i've got a backbone stronger than yours...  :+:wish for you on a falling star, wondering where you are... do i ever cross your mind in the warm sunshine?... :+:
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         "Accidentally In Love"     So she said what's the problem   urlLink  baby     What's the problem I don't know  Well maybe I'm in   urlLink  love     &nbsp;Think about it every   urlLink  time     I think about it   Can't  stop  thinking  'bout it  How much longer will it take to cure this  Just to cure it  cause  I can't   ignore  it if it's   urlLink  love     &nbsp;Makes me wanna turn around and face me but I don't know nothing 'bout   urlLink  love     Come on, come on   Turn a  little faster   Come on, come on  The   world will  follow after   Come on, come on  &nbsp;Cause everybody's after   urlLink  love     So I said I'm a snowball running  Running down into the spring that's coming all this   urlLink  love     &nbsp; Melting  under blue skies  &nbsp;Belting out sunlight   Shimmering    urlLink  love     Well   urlLink  baby    I surrender To the  strawberry   ice cream   Never ever end of all this   urlLink  love     Well I didn't mean to do it  &nbsp;But there's no escaping your   urlLink  love     These lines of lightning  Mean we're never alone,  Never alone, no, no  Come on, Come on  Move  a little closer   Come on, Come on  I want to  hear you whisper   Come on, Come on  Settle down inside my   urlLink  love     Come on, come on  Jump a little higher  Come on, come onIf you feel a little lighter  Come on, come on  We were once  Upon a   urlLink  time    in   urlLink  love     &nbsp; We're a  ccidentally   in    urlLink  love     Accidentally in   urlLink  love     Accidentally  I'm In    urlLink  Love   ,  I'm in    urlLink  Love   ,  I'm in    urlLink  Love    ,   I'm in    urlLink  Love   ,  I'm in    urlLink  Love   ,  I'm in    urlLink  Love       Accidentally Come on, come on  Spin a little tighter  Come on, come on  And the world's a little brighter  Come on, come on  Just get yourself inside her   urlLink  Love    ...I'm in   urlLink  love   
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Dont ask her why...      Her tears cant stop streaming...      The days she had waited...  
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Andrew called me today & we chat abt his best friend gw n amanda... hope tt andrew can take care of himself.... hmMm... i assured him today tt im still the same...   hmMm.. lets see.. i woke up extra early this morn &amp; went moount V to visit mum cuz its her birthday today.. 8 August.. Shes 40 tis year.. cant believe   urlLink  time    flys so quickly.. after church, as usual choir.. after choir kenneth msged me n told me he had tuition @ novena.. cuz ususally i go   urlLink  home    with him n his brother but keith is sick anyway... den i went tio orchard n met breda, got to know Gabbie n Dan.. shes inviting me over for helloween party.. anyway we shopeed @ far east n bre got 2 more piercings..omg so freaky when we walked a guy of age 30+ said hi to me, he smiled n was kinda   following me.. i was liek wtf?! is he my dads friend or casual wear cop.. cuz   urlLink  friends    were   urlLink  smoking   .. so i walked really fast n turn @ an alley.. den he stopped following.. lolx..Dan exchanged numbers wit me @ the station.. after tt i went to city hall alone.. FREak i was so stupid! i tot not many ppl would be ther but i was wrong.. thousands flocked up Esplanade n i was practically sandwhiched between sweay ppl, thin ppl, fat ppl, tall ppl, short ppl... haha.... eventually  the firework stasrted n i found myself protecting a little malay girl n sorta scolded the guys who were pushing n pushing.. they apologissed n went red in the face.. ahha.. hMm this well educated looking chinese guy was beside me.. think he was alone too.. exchanged glances n truth was hes kinda cute.. charming would be  the word.. n when everything was over.. his sister n mum called him over.. lolx.. the fireworks were so beautiful.took a pic posted it in jasminejj.blogspot... nic called n said juz wanna ask me how am i.. =) hmMm after tt i decided to stay a while longer so i walked down the river side.. den i came across this local arts performers.. was featuring local hip hop bands.. a lil bit of jazz, reaggae... hahaha.. haf fun alone =) i moved ard the areana to get the best sit in the middle.. the   urlLink  host    was edmund.. hes so funny he kept looking @ me n guess wad he blushed when i smiled like a total retard.. anyway probably cuz he finds me responsive so in a way, encouraging... heE.. glad tt i could bring up the ambience for some   urlLink  time   .. maybe i shoud become freelance hosts for roadshows in future =pPp.. hmm later i walked back to   MRT n hung ard the breakers underground.. the 2 groups of guys decided to have a break battle.. it was so cool so i sat down n watched.. 10 mins later 50 over ppl were behind me watching too! hahaha omg.. so wierd.. n when they left i was the only one there so akward so i tried callign xan n aske dher if she would come down or if her   urlLink  friends     were there.. anyway my back hurt n i was tired.. so i juz sat @ one of the pillars n watched .. BeEp*bEEp* i received a message from Dan.. he sorta beat ard the bush n told me he likes me.. the next min he was like, oh im just kidding.. cuz i told him.. thanks but u know i have a gd relationship n blah.. ahha made up some stories.. so lame.. ok so later later, i realised tt a guy was kinda 'waiting' for me.. i didnt know what to do so i sat longer until another grp of guys came.. after 20 mins i left... haha im nt sure wads ahppening to me but one of the guys said "excuse me".. i pretended i didnt hear and walked on.. but eventually he caught up.. he told me his friend wanted m,y number n another 2   urlLink  friends    followed after... i said need to go.. he told me juz be   urlLink  friends    ok.. please?.. den i asked which friend.. he was like, the one sitting with me jzu now..   haha how the bloody hell i know which guy i didnt even notice you!! anyway hes pretty tall n has nice features.. handsome lar.. wore white shirt.. but.. haha.. i can tell tt their grp of guys are chinesy chinesy type.. =p even if im   urlLink  single    also nt my type @ all... bleh*... alrightie.. rikel also msged me today.. rach told me chris thinks i was hitting on him @ the camp.. wtf.. NO* thick skin man.. i talk to him more doesnt mean anything.. i was merely bored n asking questions.. hahaha... anyway today is pretty cool.. i didnt feel lonely @ all lyk some otehr occasions.. probably cuz mum was with me all the while.. =)jasmine misses tammy* n for goodness sake.. my real name is Jasmine! JJ.. ppl who are clsoe enuff would understand y.. >.<> *.m.i.s  s y.O   u sO   m.U c h .    
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       went   urlLink  school    @10 though slept only @ 4 in the morning.. did soem   urlLink  art   .. waited for ju... and left   urlLink  school    @ 5+... blehz*.. zzz went eastpoint.. han's river for dinner with   urlLink  family   .. manage to sell 3 pieces of batik to my aunts... well im getting better n better @ promoting out idea.. =) hahax.. shell has agreed to sponser us on the exhibition ... thousand plus i tink.. gre8t.. it'll be an opportunity for NYAA.. den go into a good arts   urlLink  school    n uni... well... but studies gotta be firm first.. sigh*.. anyway linda spent all her do today.. bought me pair of shades n other stuff.. i refused.. she shouldnt spent   urlLink  money    liek tt.. anyway... shes behaving wierd.. unlike her true self.. but maybe tts the true linda shes been hiding for all these years.. well.. God has a plan n i   urlLink  trust    tt its good for her.. tmr is mums birthday. waking up ard 6+ to go mount vernon with dad.. hMm after curch n choir i wanna go esplanade to watch the fireworks... tink tmr ish hk team's work.. yup.. hope tt i wont have to go alone... again.. hmmm louis dont intend to do anything.. i think tts an accceptable choice.. might as well study n clsoe an eye on it... aint gonna cost him anything much either.. hmm might be starting the babu tuition with him after national day.. haven talk tp dad abt it yet...but he agreed last week.. yup.. kk... gtg now... rikel msged me again today.. asking me out some   urlLink  time   .. dammit.. Enuff of nagging.. sighs* father is skinning me alive! wtf.. ciao bloggie... nuff said for today... nights   
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       okay so its 2am n i still cant sleep... i created jasminejj.blogspot.com for picasa acc. to post  urlLink pictures  mainly... hmMm looked thru devian today.. got more ideas runnin thru my mind now.. tmr going sch for  urlLink art  .. meeting clar @  10 den ju @ 2..  wonder wad good  urlLink news  she have for us.. curious curious* haha.. i went for a ride with bro dominic juz now.. hahax.. the dude didnt  urlLink trust  him with the  urlLink car .. plus hes got no licence.. but oh well.. he drives well.. we nearly banged into another  urlLink car .. actually its tt freakin drivers fault he simply didnt give way n shot out.. damn.. anyway after handling  urlLink car  to dom, went to pick up two of hes  urlLink friends .. hes cousin jasper asked me if i smoked.. haha.. i quit.hes so funny, after dom n the other guy got outta the  urlLink car , he looked at me and said"fuck i dont ven know a  urlLink single  shet abt driving this  urlLink car ... he acted thru.. wahahax =) hmm.. nic told me he was @ bishan too.. when i was waiting for dom frm 9 to ard 10.30, weiluo came back n he sat with me @ void deck again.. haha.. alwaes him.. sadly i dont feel a thing for him.. hes really a good n caring guy.. all i can offer him is my friendship.. wish i didnt hurt him those times i rejected.. ahh.. i dont think i wanted a sorry from nickey... lyk he said,  urlLink people  changes.. if he wanna say sorry, i only have one thing to tell him... tt is, "ive forgiven you already"... :) we're purely  urlLink friends  frm this point onwards if he accepts me in friendster... yea.. glad tt all my troubles seem so far away or resolved now.. although my  urlLink friends  ard me are suffering frm all kinda shet, @ least i can pull myself together now n b strong for them... haha.. as for me, i definitely need more motivation for studies n perhaps a change of strategy.. hippo king was chattign with me juz now.. its 1am+ here n in UK its like.. 5+ goin on 6 pm. he'll be back on monday for granny's b.dae.. well alright.. im getting dizzy now.. shld be abt  urlLink time  for starry land.. ahaax.. andrew, im still holding on... day by day , harder i pray.. tt you'll be fine, and we'll soon be one... i aint exactly sure y n what im doing this for.. but on 15july when i made the choice to be hes gurl, i told myself i'll be responsible abt this n treat it maturely.. even if timing affects our progress, hope tt he'll commnicate more with me too.. yea.. no matter who comes into my life frm now till when i get married... i wanna be myself, the woman i think i should be.. gimme strength in everything i do...  
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Friday is beautiful... damn.. i slept thru frm 1+ to 6... missed the sunshine n all.. dora n i were so bored n i cunt go town cuz im being watched.. wth.. AndreW and i din talk... only an occasional i miss u... well... hope everyting ish still fine with him.. im juz helpless... louis sent me a message to ask me go town this evening... but hes out by now... anyway my hse is blasting with    urlLink   music      now.. im sick bored.. zzz.. haha..Dom picking me up ard 9+ he say... we're going for drive with a few others... today would be a good opportunity to get drunk... anyway i    urlLink   chat      with caro for a short while today regarding the    urlLink   phone      call frm hes mum.. again, im helpless.. cant do much as a sista.. haiz... @ least i told aishhaa a lil bit abt how alv's feelin'... frm wad i can se... tehre was laugher.. nt sure if things r going right.. hmMm today alv n vic n i wore the shirt i designed yesterday.. many ppl came up to me n say hey tts pretty cool.. =) gre8t.. its really a walk to remember... maybe monday or tuesday i wanna go sentosa b4 sch starts.. destress... no    urlLink   money      to    urlLink   shop      anyway.. alrighty.. gtg do figure drawing.. im    urlLink   moving      into    urlLink   fashion         urlLink   design      now so... yup yup.. gotta get started.. going to scho fer ju'z art tmr.. hopefully she rmbrs my blue coloured batik orders.    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       i can almost feel the pain... life is going on.. its constantly changing and changing and i am suppose to love changes but htis time, ive had enuff.. i wanna be who i am deep down... i realise its so hard to show how much i really really care when i come face to face to my loved one... im warm but im cold.. i look strong but im not the strongest... somehow imperfections seem daunting to me.. haf i become too obsessed with other people's affairs to negelct myself already?? gosh my surroundings are stressing me.. some guy from online told me i needa luver.. wth.. ben msged me asking how i am n tt he misses me alot.. i told him studies i really need guide.. im fallin once again.. louis asked me too.. hmM guess there're alot of people who still cares enuff to slap me back to reality... i just cant explain today.. what was it tt intrigued me?.. y did those tears flow when it shouldnt have?.. talk abt guilt with andrew last night.. i did some thinking... am i selfish?.. to let dad down.. allowin myself to fall over n over again... what abt my heart?.. how many times has it been hurt but aint tt a factor tt my hearts growing stronger?... noo.. nt tt positive, it became weary n numb in the process... feels like i cant read myself anymore n my shadow is morphing into nowhere.. ahH.. everything might just be pms.. *breaths deeply*... well maybe i should set myself free in starry land later n things will be fine tmr... and 1 sweet anticipation which can keep me cheery is ::our1stdate:: could tt be the estacy pill?... till then, i dont need to get drunk no more... cuz tts nt only gonna be a pill. but wings, warmth, truth, sincerity, abundace of appreciativeness in actions n in our eyes... nothing shall matter anymore, searching for the one, keeping d faith n trust... finally feeling each other.... till then... love, Jas 
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        failed my maths test.. 6/20.. it aint extraodinary cuz ive alwaez been on tt mark... but i tried my best this time.. i still failed.... really gotta do much better... what a day... p came n im cramping awae... andrew and i chat alot mre today... there are things which are causing him depression... 'guilt is killin me' it sure aint a easy word to deal with.. its mre lyk, conspiracy of the heart and mind... this sick game that life can play on us can be so irritating sometimes tt i juz wanna silence it once n for all.. too bad i dont posscess the ability to do that... is there a way i can protect my love frm harm and unwanted burdens?... i wish i could be the angel way up high.... in an indirect way im really hurt too...   hmMm... love is a strange yet beautiful thing... why do people choose to love when   they know that possibility of a love nt reciprocated exists, and in some cases, defitnitely obviously...      why does one love when she does nt having  the courage to set him free?... why do we hold on to what we have yet nt cherish it until they break or shatter? why do people take feelings for granted? why is it that little things we do outta care does not matter no more...   theres no logic when one expects returns from what we once gave out of free will... selfishness, insercurity, loneliness, expectations...   ahh , yes, the word is expectations..great expectations often bring disappointments doesnt it...   live life the way it should be lived... walk, run, jump, risk, fall, pick yourself up, overcome the forces tt seem to be obscuring what goodness lie ahead, treasure those you love and care for, and be careful with those who loves you... they did have a choice.. although love tt happens naturally seem one in  million... stand firm in whatever you believe and dont let anything bring you down...   stop crying your hearts out & wake up to reality~ yess, it hurts.. but it is these occasional setbacks in life which can open windows for us to see the meaning of life... the ones who are there for you, were they there b4?.. what have you acheived to deserve such attention?.. did u call for it deliberately?..some yes, others no...  @ tt point u will see how much u mean to ppl who care n everything u once thought you didnt deserve just falls right into place... everyone is appreciated in one way or another...  dont deny yr sweet presence, neither should anyone blame society for their self-centre and self destructed outcomes..   ultimately you are yr own boss, u once made those decisions, be ready to face the consequences...   females an males do not differ much... women are naturally more family oriented and instinctively mre thoughtful n alert on the tiniest details... physically, lots of differences.. but tear away the pretty face, tear away the skin... look inside and you'll see.. the capacity of hatred, love, truthfulness, faithfulness, passion, lust... they are all   equal..   dont see y its always the guys hurting the girls n not the other way round...very few people on the face of this earth have perfect judgements... and for those who do not have this gift, they turn to unrealistic demands over obsession n everything they do seems senseless n irritating..   whens the world gonna wake up n live like we've used to before ?.. simplicity is pure bliss ... the darkness lingers in hearts of lost souls... hope tt they'll soon find their  stars  n reach beyond...   if i get to choose to be any element on earth, i wanna be oxygen... so that i can give life to the worthy only and make the world a better place~       sigh* im nt ging to school tmr... stressed n pissed... wanna spent time studying @ home... ive actually written a song but lost it jus a few minutes ago... should just forget about it cuz its way too sadistic n not like jasmine.. its scary when i look into the mirror n see how deep i can become.. i dont recognise myself anymore sometimes..i want my simple passionate self back.. the lover of all rights and wrongs and the peace maker...hmm... life with a lil bit of twist seem to suit me best afterall... tts why im gonna make good use of my understanding and with the help of my love, im gonna discover and learn until i can become the best for us and i wanna be there supporting my man, lean on him and dream sweet dreams.. letting go of all my doubts and fears.. sadness shall fly on wings of time and living each day with the one i cannot live without will be the key to our questions n locked doors... nothings gonna stand between us as we share a love so strong, so true and pure...trust in me baby... yr wish is my wish and that star way up high  shall shine on it for many lightyears to come..   . however...nothing is certain... love came crashing thru on us like a light train, it might be taken away as quickly.. the moments we've shared might never turn into mesmerizing memories... the faith and trust we have in each other now, might not endure for as long as we expect, you might not love you anymore if a brighter star shall run along our road... this is why i said in the begining " please dont fall in love with me"... im imperfect..  dearest baby...for all the times ive said i might... i think ive found the right one this time... so,     i might... but i *      WoNt~     hehex.. mua miss ya alotalot       
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        My baby sang songs for me..."  How do i  live","Lost in you","sorry seems to be the hardest  woord","amazed".. n alot alot...he shows  'sluts' frm clubs my pic on his phone  juz to ask them  bug off.. he resisted these irritating  distractions n temptations juz to stay true to me... he luvs to mua mua mua mua mua mua mua mua me.. from begining to end as long as we can chat.. . we miss each other for hours  n hours.... wow... im gonna write  101 things  we do together one of these days man =) miss ma baby so so much... today we chat for super long... frm the time he was soaking himself in tub, feeling rather stressed n angry to the point  when chemical reactions took place and e became totally siao... haha he melted my heart.. told me hes gonna cherish me  n even made a pledge n the sun, moon stars as witnesses... muaaCh*      
    
</post>


</Blog>