<Blog>


<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well. I got the comment thing up so now you can all tell me how crazy I am :P . I'm busy working on another website at the moment. Though this one is actually turning out to be a pretty good site.  I finally got my game finished and once I have finished this site I'll be working on my next game. Hopefully Coldstone will be updated soon so i can get rid of the last few bugs in my game.  On the music side of things, I have managed to get my iPod working again though it does still go weird sometimes. My music collection has grown to a healthy 375 songs and is still growing. The soon the iTMS comes to the UK the better :)  Hope you are bored now. Good. Now sod off and let me get back to work :D
     
    
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I know nobody ever reads this but I have seen that quite a few of my friends have been blogging recently so I thought I might as well post something. Oh well. I'll post more tommorow. I only got 6 hours of sleep last night. I really should get out more. I've been on the computer all day.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I've started writing one of my songs and it is turning out pretty good. I spent about 5-10 minutes to get the chords down and then I started applying them to the tune. This is better than the older version as it has a proper baseline and some chords to fill it out. I'll start adding a drum beat tomorrow to see what it sounds like  UPDATE: 19/7/04 : Added drums and intro  And my popular request (from one person ;) ) here are the lyrics. I have made what the music has in bold. They need changing a bit but are basically the final ones.    Tonight I'm gonna stay till tommorow If only it lasted one day Today I'm gonna stay till I fall asleep Till the voices in side of me say  Just forget all these things that you think that you have in your life Just forget all the memories. Forget everything that she said Forget yesterday  Today i heard you say that your sorry But tomorrow you'll change your mind You say that you will stop playin games with my heart I'm sorry if i find that hard to believe  Just forget all these things that you think that you have in your life Just forget all the memories. Forget everything that she said Forget yesterday   Forget yesterday Forget yesterday I'll forget yesterday  I heard the phone ring at midnight You said that your on your way You try to say you didn't mean what you said Though I cannot believe what you say  Just forget all these things that you think that you have in your life Just forget all the memories. Forget everything that she said Forget yesterday  Tonight I'm gonna stay till tommorow (They tell me to forget yesterday) If only it lasted one day (Forget yesterday) Today I'm gonna stay till I fall asleep (Till I fall asleep) Till the voices in side of me say  Forget yesterday Forget yesterday Forget yesterday 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Just when you think that you have some people as your friends they turn out to be complete and utter dicks. Strange thing is that 1 of them was a complete and utter dick before i became friends with him and the other one, well, I thought she was all right but it turns out I was completely wrong.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, I've just had my last piano lesson. I won't be going back again for other lessons. I'll still be playing the piano, of course, but I'll be learning by myself. The weird thing is that I have been going to piano lessons for the last 7 or 8 years which is about half of my life. It just seems odd that that has ended.  I just hope that I can get this band going as it will give me a good reason to play the piano still, other than for my enjoyment.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Here's to the crazy ones. The misfits, the rebels, the troublemakers,  the round pegs in the square hole,  the ones who see things differently.   They're not fond of rules and they have no respect for the status quo. You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them, but the only thing you can't do is ignore them.   Because they change things, they push the human race forward.  And while some may see them as the crazy ones, we see genius,  because the people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world,  are the ones who do
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I need a job to get some money to get a laptop. The problem is:  a) I am to lazy to get one b) Everywhere I have asked isn't accepting job applications at the moment  I'm going down to the job centre tomorrow to see if I can get a job involving what I do best. Computing. I would look on their website but the crappy Job search won't work on Macs. Damn websites.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I hate them. As soon as the sun comes out my mum wants all the windows open. Then the flies get in and they are trapped in when we close the windows at night. Then they start buzzing all around you. They fly in front of the TV several times they start to fly around your head and land on you. They are quite possible the most annoying creatures ever. Though my brother and sister come close ;)
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I would write one but I can't be arsed. I really need some motivation for this blog. Maybe if I didn't keep posting in it at midnight and actually went to bed relatively early for once. Oh well. There's always tommorow.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I urgently need to write in this blog. Last time I wrote anything was 10th of April and that was complaining that I hadn't written anything for ages. The annoying thing is that everyone seems to have blogs. And they all seem to be interesting. And mine don't as nothing ever happens. And I need to create some smiles for me to use in this blog. And I need to put it on my own server. Oh well, I can do that later. At least I have posted, for once.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, here it is. The finished version of Forget Yesterday. It has a few minor problems but I'll fix them when I get some extra Ram for my computer. Below are the (slightly) changed lyrics:  Today I'm gonna stay till tommorow If only it lasted one day Tonight I'm gonna stay till I fall asleep Till the voices in side of me say  Just forget all these things that you think that you have in your life Just forget all the memories. Forget everything that she said Forget yesterday  Today i heard you say that your sorry But tomorrow you'll change your mind You say that you will stop playin games with my heart I'm sorry if i find that hard to believe  Just forget all these things that you think that you have in your life Just forget all the memories. Forget everything that she said Forget yesterday  I heard the phone ring at midnight You said that your on your way You try to say you didn't mean what you said Though I cannot believe what you say  Just forget all these things that you think that you have in your life Just forget all the memories. Forget everything that she said Forget yesterday  Tonight I'm gonna stay till tommorow (I'll me to forget yesterday) If only it lasted one day (Forget yesterday) Today I'm gonna stay till I fall asleep (Till I fall asleep) Till the voices in side of me say  Forget yesterday Forget yesterday  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>