<Blog>

<date>31,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Sorry I didn't get to write yesterday, it was a busy day.  I had a dentist appointment and then had to run errands and didn't get to write to the blog or do much of anything.  Well anyway my life is pretty exciting, probably because it is New Years Eve.  I am also going to clean out the home office today and do some organizing for my mom.  I did sleep in late today though.  I got up at 10:30!  That may not be late for you, but for me that is vvvvveryyyyyyyyy late!!!Nothing much has happened in the community so not much to say there.  I am so happy that I don't have to start school back for another week!  My sister has to start back on Monday.  Of course she deserves it.  I love getting to sleep in late and not have to worry about tests, homework, teachers, quizzes, FINALS!  But I know that I will  have to go back sometime, but until then it is party time :)  I am also happy because my mother got her 4-runner back and we no longer have to ride in the company car, thankgoodness.  Also be prepared for some changes in my website design.  I am looking for a whole new look.  Dont know when it will change, but it will.  If you know of any place to find or have suggestions yourself for backgrounds, feel free to e-mail them to me.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Man today started out early, I had to get up at 6:30 :p !  Now usually that wouldn't be considered early for me, but with Christmas break happening I have gotten lazy and love to sleep in later that I would if school was in session.  The reason that I had to get up so early was that my parents, didn't have to work today and my mother's 4-runner needed repair so we had to take it to the company today.  So until we get the 4-runner back, we have to drive one of the company that my mom works for cars.  It is so much different than what I am used to.  More bad news also, McDonalds had a fire and are closed for a few days.  So it isn't that bad of news, but in this small town this is something.  At least we still have another McDonalds on the other end of town.  Everything is crazy with people returning gifts and everything.  We went to the store this morning after we dropped off the 4-runner and the shelves were bare, there was nothing much left to sale.  I considered that stop a waste of my time.    And when I get home, there is nothing on TV and I can't think of anything to do on the internet, so just as every other day in my life, it is a boring and plain day.  Oh well, life moves on.  Ta-Ta for now, really to tell you the truth until tomorrow.  And remember "Today is the tomorrow that we worried about yesterday"  PS^2:  I also may start just putting links to pages that I find interesting in the blog, so be on the watch! ;*)  Andrew Out...
     
    
</post>

<date>28,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Christmas break is a great time of the year ;)  But even though I don't want to I have to go back to school on the 8th.  Oh well, the only thing that I am worried about are finals.  See we were supposed to have finals on the last day of school before Christmas break, but it snowed too much and we had to miss.  They have changed our calendar and everything to make up for that day.  We were supposed to go back the 9th but now we have to the 8th, that sucks.  Yesterday we took down everything related to Christmas and put it away until next year.  This is awful early for us to take things down, but my parents wanted to take the decorations down, so I had no choice.  I thought I was going to break my neck when I was up on the roof trying to take down the lights, one wrong move and I would have killed myself.  And just to add to the fun there was snow and ice on some parts of the roof as well.  At least I am alive.  Everyone in my family is sick.  I don't feel too bad, but I don't feel perfect or anything.  I am just glad that I don't have to worry about homework right now or anything.  That is a big relief.  Although sometimes I do put off my homework until the morning at school.  I am just happy that I get to spend some time at home with my family and don't have to worry about getting up early.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Blog Now Open ;)
     
    
</post>

<date>02,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hey what are you all doing?  I am not looking forward to going back to school.  As I am sure that you all can see from all of my earlier posts.  The days are winding down, but I still have some more to go.  BTW my archives are working without a hitch now and hold decembers posts and I have set them up to archive all the posts every month.  I may end up having to change that, but it should work out ok.  Next week my shows should be live again, those of you who watch TechTv know what I am talking about ;)!!  I just now finished rearranging the home office and it looks alot better than it did, but just something about it sticks out and I can't figure out what it is, oh well.  I have been thinking about starting up another aquarium and that had been the bulk of my research and thoughts lately.  Hopefully I will get what I want.  Nothing has happened much in my town, of course does it ever?  So I have nothing to post about that.  So I guess this is the end of my very short update and posting.  Just thought I would fill you in on what is going on, even if it isn't much.  TTYL  --Andrew
     
    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Same old same old.  Leo still has not received his job back from TechTv and the petitions are flying.  I don't know of anything else to talk about except that in English we are reading Romeo and Juliet and Thursday is preregistration for classes next year.  I hope I get the ones I want.  Until later talk toots
     
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Apparently terminating Leo upset many people and there is now an  urlLink online petition going on , and I encourage you to sign it.  Maybe he will get his job back.  If he doesn't get it back right now, maybe he will when comcast and techtv merge.  Techtv will be merged with comcast's G4.  Hopefully this will be a positive change.  I am sorry, but Leo belongs at TechTv hosting Call for Help and The Screen Savers again, sorry Kevin and Cat.  But as I said maybe with the petition and a little luck and prayer from you all, Leo will once again be in our homes 2 times a night.  Good night America.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      My favorite tech host, Leo Laporte, no longer works at TechTv all thanks to Vulcan Ventures.  He was a huge lost.  He is the best and it will be hard to imagine TechTv without him.  It will be so sad.  It was hard enough when he left Techtv's The Screen Savers about 2 weeks ago on his own, but now Call for Help without him!!!  And this time it wasn't his choice.  They wanted to sign away all claims of some shares of stock or else he wouldn't have to worry about working for them.  He stood by his principles, way to go Leo.  But now He doesn't work at TechTv, but hopefully when TechTv and Comcast merge they will rehire him.  To read all about this in his own words on his website visit  urlLink  .  He helped to build up the channel to what it is today and this is how they repay him!!  Good luck Leo we will be cheering for you.  Your the best, no one can replace you or your humor.  I hope in the future that you can get your job back and we will try our best to help.  Until then you can still listen to Leo on his radio show on  urlLink   and visit his site at  urlLink Leoville.com .
     
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I haven't been able to post for such a while due to my webhost.  The ftp services are down even still.  Something is going to have to be done.  Oh well, I have switched to another host for this blog and plan to start to post a lot more.  Well anyway that is the reason for what was going on.  Also I have registered  urlLink http://www.drewtown.com/   that will link you to my home page.  You can email me at  urlLink andrewflanery@gmail.com .  Sometimes and more likely within the next 2 weeks to site could be shakey.  So if it isn't working just try again later.  Thanks again for all your support.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I have thought about it and have decided to give blogging another try. I will try to post every morning or afternoon, but it may become every other day. It is just as my schedule permits! I am also thinking of switching to a new blogging service, I will post more about that if I decide to. On a side note, keep watching for gmail invites for those who want them. You never know when they are going to be posted. Have a great day. 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well I thought about it and decided to post some Gmail invites on here, so all of you can enjoy Gmail. I will put them up randomly, so check back often. Don't give up, there will be more if you don't get it when you want it. And lets try to keep it to 1 account per person, so everyone can enjoy Gmail, the service that I feel in love with, and now you can too. Keep watching for invites ;)&nbsp; 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>