<Blog>


<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, never in my life have I made a layout that looks like this. It's different isn't it? Empty and bare.   The site's been closed for over a month now and the 'under reconstruction' bit is a lie. I know for a fact that I haven't been working on the site, and I have no idea if M-Feared is. But I certainly do hope he's got something brewing in that whacked up brain of his.   AS Modular results came out yesterday, I managed to score a hefty 83 out of 100 for my Mathematics P1. That's an A grade by the way. Unfortunately, for my Module 2 Physics, I could only go along with a pathetic 48 out of 90. However, I'm grateful because I obtained a D grade. To be honest, I expected a lower mark than that, so I'm happy. But, I still cried as I was seriously disappointed with myself.  Sigh, oh well.. two more modules to go and hopefully I can boost up my grade up to at least a B.   About a week ago, I went to Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia, with the school basketball team. We left on Thursday morning at 7:30am using the school bus. I guess on that day, fates were against my boyfriend and I since he wasn't able to see me off (he came to school at eight). It was a dreadful day, rain was pouring non-stop. It rained on the way to the Terminal in Muara, and it wasn't exactly my idea of a cheerful morning. I love the rain, especially during the afternoons. Unfortunately for me, on that day.. all the rain did was depress me. I sat with my best friend,  Aimi , during the entire duration of the trip. The boat ride to Labuan made me sick and drowsy but the fun bit was that  Aimi  and I got to gossip with  Norhana . They played Spiderman on the boat TV set.  Randy  made it to into the guys basketball team, so he went along on the trip as well. I realize that throughout the trip, I didn't really talk to him. I guess we were both busy with our own issues. Anyway, the whole trip from Brunei to Labuan to KL took over thirteen hours. When we arrive at the hotel, we saw Ms. Stevenson. She was my PE teacher back in Year 9 and also  Aimi ,  Maria ,  Norhana  and  Elwin 's basketball trainer back in the day (sounds old doesn't it? lol). We had our first game against them the next day. At the end of the trip, we managed to win one game and lose two on Friday, and we won two games on Saturday. Making us the Plate Champions.. hehe we won medals too =) Over all, I spent about $350BN in KL (and that was for two days).. mostly on food and other expenses. I didn't buy much, I bought maybe a few shirts for myself and a bag for my sister.   I turn seventeen in about three weeks, I'm looking forward to it even though I never receive presents most of the time except from my sister and a few loved ones. It's going to be on the first day of school, first day of term three. Fun. I'm probably going to end up having a bad day and at the end of that, I'm most likely to end up crying.   I'm fed up with myself. I've gone through more crying sessions than any teenage girl should, well, in my view anyway. I'm happy. I'm back and I'm happy. Do you believe me? No, I didn't think so.   I like to zone out every now and then. My thoughts are usually distracting, and they tend to be depressing. I feel bad for my boyfriend since he has to put up with me every single day. He says I should always smile because when I don't, I look like I'm going to cry. What he says is probably true, so I try not to think about it too much.  I know I don't talk about my boyfriend much in my posts. At least I don't describe him as well as I should. I try not to because of personal reasons.. and there are some people out there I don't wish to offend (you know who you are, don't you?) Ah, who cares? =)  Julian  is a year older than me, he's in my PE and Physics class. I have lunch with him everyday in school.. and I see him everyday before class and during recess. I spend as much time as possible in school with him since we both can't really go out during the weekends. I've been with him for almost four months now, and we've been going through and past obstacles, and we've still managed to stick together. None of us, including myself and him can believe that we have lasted this long.. and I'm happy that we have. He's a great guy and he has never failed to cheer me up when I'm down. I can describe him like he's a Japanese Anime cartoon, and as my best friend  Aimi  has once said, "when I see  Julian  walking, I imagine lines like the ones you see in cartoons". A lot of people have said that he and I look alike, though I've failed to see what it is that makes us look the same. I'll pretend not to understand the next time someone says that to us again. His best friend (and mine),  Randy , says that we're so much alike. That I can agree on because my boyfriend is my partner in crime. Especially when it comes to picking on Randy. =) My boyfriend is cute, and he's funny. And I love him so much. xoxo  Sayang, I know you're smiling like a nut now.   I've been doing a lot of thinking. I think I mention that fact whenever I post. I do think a lot. My thoughts usually end up with me getting a massive headache, with my eyes trying hard not to cry. I'm a pessimist, I know that very well. I used to be happy like 24-7. I mean, there was a time when all I could see was sunshine. Now, I've learnt that mistakes happen all the time and life isn't just a bunch of roses.. there's still the thorns. It's the thorns that cut you more and nothing as beautiful as the rose petals can ever cure the pain you feel so quickly.  It takes a while to get over things, doesn't it? My boyfriend and I were talking about this last night. I know that I'm not over a lot of things in my life, and I'm thankful that he understands and that he allows me to take time in my life to slowly work on what I need to do. It ended with a cheerful note, and honey, I did mean what I said. My boyfriend is a doll for being able to be so cheerful all the time, and I've always asked him why he's that way. And every time, I get the same answer, "well, you're always depressed. It's my job to make you happy". Yes he's a doll. haha =)   On Tuesday last week, 9th of March, I stood up in front of Green house for house elections. There were about 150+ students and teachers in that small dance room, and there I stood scared and nervous. I was so shaky that I thought I was going to faint. lol, my friends.. scolded me because I sounded like I was going to cry. Yes, I was nervous.. I felt like my legs were going to fall off. I began my speech with a very shaky tone, and I doubt it impressed anyone. Now, I'm just glad its done and over with. However, with that chaotic speech presentation.. all I can do for now is hope and pray that I will get what I want, which is to be the Head of Green house. Sigh, but I really shouldn't get my hopes up too high. Oh bloody hell, I think I deserve the title. I've been in JIS for almost four years now, and I know that I love Green house more. =P p.s. If my competition reads this, don't kill me. 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I never really did enjoy watching other people have fun while I didn't. I guess sometimes the only fun you can get is when you're actually in that part of ' fun '. I've been the way I am since the end of 2002. Everything's so different now, I don't think I could have imagined that I'd turn out this way. I always thought things will always stay the same, because life back then was so routine that it was predictable. I guess that made everything boring. Personally, I'd prefer to be spontaneous which makes it more fun. I get bored easily, but there are some things in my life I would have rather kept the same.   I'm not saying that I regret what's changed then and what's different now. I'm just saying I would have preferred it stay the same. I'm happy with how my life is now, and how it has made a full swing turn. I never thought I'd be this strong to move on with my life, because I know there was a point when my world revolved around two people and all that mattered was keeping them happy. I gave up my time, my nights.. for them. Now, I'm learning to be more appreciative towards myself. I promise, that this time, I'm not going to let what happened then happen again. The most important thing to me now, is learning to love myself more and appreciate what I've got. I can't stop tears from running down my face, but I know I can try and find my way out.   Why did everything disappear so fast? I've always wondered how one decision can change everything for the rest of your life. How can something so small make such a significant impact on a person's life? It doesn't make sense and it's crazy. I can't find words to express how deeply hurt I've been and reminiscing about it doesn't really help much. I try to talk to  him  about it, but it somehow just gets me really riled up and then I'd get totally upset. Being upset, probably upsets  him  . It's unbelievable. I can't lie about how I'm not over a lot of things, and he knows I'm not. I'm just glad that he's allowing me to take things a step at a time and no forcing me to forget it once and for all. He's a great guy, and being there is all I need from him for now, and he always has. I know he always will be.   I used to write a poem at least once a week, my depression used to be my inspiration. I could write about my persona, my thoughts.. and they would be buried in a deeper word path, inside a world that only I could understand. I guess I've lost my muse, since I haven't written a single line since early 2003. It's beginning to scare me because writing was my only way of getting rid of my pain and sorrow. I don't show how much I hurt in front of others, I know I'm good at that. I know that my smiles can always be seen as 'real', but only a few know what is 'real' and what is not. And sometimes through pictures, you can see still images of my 'forced' smiles. I always thought I'd be forever happy. I always thought you'd be next to me. I always thought you'd be my best friend, just the way you promised to be. You broke your promise. You broke it.  I thought by then you'd know how much our friendship meant, I mean I threw one away so I could keep ours. That's how much you meant to me. Now, all you see when you look at me is dirt. You and your so-called 'friends', each and everyone of them hate me because of that f***ing image you created of me. They don't even know my side of the story. I always thought you'd be there. I'm trying hard to accept that you're no longer there, but that's something I can't accept. Why? Because you're my best friend. You're my best friend. Despite the fact we haven't spoken, nevertheless, you're still the person I'd imagine you to be, you're still the person I wanted you to be, you're still that person that I wanted to forever be friends with. I'm suppose to be strong, but I can't.   Nothing makes sense when I think about it.   And I'm hating every moment of it.  [ADDED] My  urlLink  sister   is being stalked by a preacher. My god. " Well, I'm not exactly being stalked, the guy is all the way in the 'amazon' world " - tee hee hee, that's like the quote of the day lol =)  Anyhoots, .[/ADDED]
     

    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've got this book where I write my thoughts. I call it my purple love book. I don't exactly write them in detail.. they're more in poetic form and they've got their own hidden meanings to why I've written them. I can't exactly put into words my description of hate and betrayal. Only I can picture it because I'm the one who's experienced it. My words, my poems.. tell its own story and from that, people can make their own judgments of what actually happened. I wonder how Jane feels about the songs Maroon 5 made.. 'about Jane'. How twisted.   I turn seventeen in twelve days. =) Its funny how time seems to jet past when all you want is for it to slow down. Then again, when you feel like you're in complete torture, you'd be wishing the next day to come by faster. I wonder why time seems to fly when you're having fun while it seems to drag when you're bored. Maybe its the enjoyment :S I wouldn't really know. Time seems to pass easily for me. I know I'm suppose to be studying at this time of day, but noo.. I'm sitting in front of the pc now, typing away.  Dreams are usually said to be warnings, wishes.. sometimes even predictions of the future. I don't dream much, and when I do.. I tend to take them seriously because I think every dream we have has its own meaning.   My boyfriend said, "I hate it when you're right". Funny how I always am, especially when it involves him. I don't know what time I slept last night, but I was on the phone with him around midnight. I saw some photos for the yearbook a few weeks ago, I found a photo of him and I infront of the gym. lol, I think we look cute =) I'll get a copy and post it up when I find the time. During this two week break, I absolutely  have  to take  Aimi  out. I don't know where to, but I have got to take her out. We haven't gone out together for so long.   Throughout the years, I've been close with so many people. Most of which have drifted apart, or just suddenly ended. It hurts to think about it, but I guess it's just a phase of life. It breaks my heart to think about it, I guess everyone has their own versions of heartbreaks. It's a natural part of life. I don't think I can think of anyone who's never suffered a heartbreak before.. getting hurt, is normal I suppose. You'd experience it at least once in your lifetime. That's what getting disappointed is all about. I wonder if I've learnt my lesson yet.   Eh,   urlLink Adeline   look: Jessyca. Jessyca Lim? Jessyca Tan? Ng? Mm.. think about it. Hehe get back to me. mwah.  Today is the fortieth day since my grandfather passed away. My family and relatives will all be headed down to Tutong to mark this day. I still miss him and I guess I'm still learning to accept the fact that he's actually gone. Death is another natural part of life, I guess its just something everyone will go through in any stage of their life.   I'd start talking about love, but who am I to talk about it? I think I know what it is, but I don't think I know enough about it. Love isn't something that a person can describe fully. There will never be enough words to desribe the feelings felt, and the hurt experienced.. I wouldn't really know. I've wasted too many tears and time about it. Then again, I'd like to say that I'd rather have a memory of what I once had rather than having to be alone and not know how different things could have been.     'Cause it's breaking my heart When I look in your eyes And I don't see me anymore and you're all I'm living for   -  All 4 One : Not Ready for Goodbye.  I know how it feels to be loved, and I know how it feels to be in love. I also know how it feels to hurt, I guess my frustration and rage still seethes inside of me, waiting to explode. I'm not revengeful. I don't think.   At least I try not to be. 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm not good at lying and I don't want to start.   urlLink She   can read me like a book, just by a gesture or even shrug.. she knows when somethings wrong (p.s. I love you). My head is always filled with questions and wonderings about what goes on around me or even about what goes on behind my back. I don't like ignoring these thoughts because that would make me go insane with unanswered questions.   You could say I'm happier now, but I don't know. Am I really? I don't know. I saw an old friend today, it was nice seeing her again though I didn't even say hi or smile at her. It made me think back to six years ago.. up to this present day life I lead. Wow how things have changed. I'm another person and so is she. I have my values and she's thrown away hers.. maybe she's rebuilding it again, I don't know. I take pride in myself, and to me.. there's no one more important in my life than me (with a few exceptions ;D).   I'm depressed and I seem to only get my insperation to post when I'm upset.   urlLink Ade   pointed out that most of my posts are depressing..haha and girl, I know that you agree that the only time a person can truly post is when they are at their lowest moods because thats when all the thoughts come in. It's true really, you don't think much when you're happy.. because what's the point? You're happy, live the moment! However, when you're sad.. that's when you start all the hating, regretting and hurtful thoughts. it's true right?  Care.. in the dictionary it means 'feel concern'. Take care of means 'to dispose of'. Funny how they seem to have different meanings. lol =) Okay seriously.. do you really care? How do you know? Is it really a feeling of concern? Are you sure? I'm always worried about my friends. I've got this weird sixth sense that always seems to alert me when somethings wrong. I don't know. Most of the time I'm right though my friends tend to say "no yas, I'm okay", but in the end of the day they'll say "There  was  something wrong. Everything's okay now". Sigh, there's a point when I wish I could have helped, but sometimes its best I keep out of whatevers troubling them. There was a time when I gave up on my friends all together because everything just seemed wrong.. I've lost too many things and I've got too many troubles. I really don't know what should be troubling me at this point of my life... but believe me, I have more than my fair share of troubles in this so-called carefree teenage life I have.   I finally went out to play pool today with  Adeline  and  Eddie . I *almost* (maybe that sounded a bit hopeful) kicked her ass, but sadly.. (heh) she won twice. I miss my boyfriend =\  Ade  says that I'm begining to sound like him and our attitudes nowadays are a complete reverse. Well, there's some truth in it.. then again, I'm still me =D I found out today that  Koko Jay 's gone to Miri.. for Army camp. It hurts that I don't know whats going on in his life anymore, he shut the door on me a long time ago, I guess its time for me to lock it and put the key somewhere safe in case he comes back knocking.   I talked to  Mimi  for a bit today. I saw her car and climbed in. We started talking for a bit until her man called her up. Then I had to get out of the car =( So yeah, I guess I'll meet up with her another day.  If you were allowed to turn back the pages of time, would you handle events the same way? You probably wouldn't. Unfortunately, clocks do not run backward and what's done is past.. or is it really? Do fates give us a second chance? Sometimes, in a strange and eerie way.. they just may. I think the fates have given me a second chance to make things right. I love my boyfriend, and I'm just hoping that he feels the same way.. and this is one part of my life that I'm determined not to mess up. I  have  got to change that stereotypical view of 'me'.. geez.  All I need now is a chance.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Have you ever wondered why the first thing that usually pops into your head is something that usually either pleases you or makes you want to hide away from the world? It can be either a happy thought or, sadly enough, an unpleasant one. I woke up this morning feeling as if a rock had fallen on top of me. My head felt heavy and the rest of it is a different story. I stayed up crying in bed last night, it's cruel really they way I've been treating myself. I shouldn't bring myself to do such things.I know eveyrthing will be better and all this will seem like a bad dream, but right now.. that dream is living up to reality and once something starts spinning, it won't stop until an equal or stronger opposite force stops it.   Remember Romeo and Juliet? They were a classic tragedy written by William Shakespere about two young people who fall in love with one another despite their family feud and resulting into tragic results. I wouldn't say that my life is like a play, or that it is still called a regular 'chick flick'. It isn't anymore because my life is no longer filled with beautiful roses and bright sunny days filled with love and happiness. It's more like a bush of roses, plus the thorns and weeds that grow in the ground; sprinkle in some grasshoppers and other things that eat leaves.. and there you have it, another effect of nature and how it represents me.   I watched The Eye 2 a few days ago (on Sunday I think), and watched Gothika the night before. Both movies are pretty scary, and Gothika freaked me out, hands down. The Eye 2 didn't seem so freaky once you got to the ending when everything began to make sense. Other than that, you could say its as freaky as Gothika. Cat in the Hat was another show I just watched yesterday with my sister and eight little cousins. I think the movie is overrated, but that might be just me. The jokes they had were more like satire and they had a few corny lines that only the adults would understand..where as the kids would just see it as another line. Heh, other than that it was pretty funny. Stupid, but it had its perks.   I need to know what I should take in the next step in my life. All I've done so far is sit around and wonder if what I'm doing is right or wrong. It's funny how people’s first impression of me is someone optimistic, happy-go-lucky and carefree. I guess that's the impression I want to leave to people, I don't want them thinking I'm some sort of weirdo who thinks about death and how to make my life more miserable than it already is. I'm miserable, but I'm not that miserable.. funny how I don't seem to show it though. I try not to because I don't want people feeling sorry for me. So why am I typing it up online where everyone to see? I want people to know my thoughts, just because I don't show them out doesn't mean I can't express them through words and thoughts.  My boyfriend and I have our differences, and yet its those differences that have kept us together. We fight every now and then, but the fights aren't really that major. We disagree on a lot of things, and yet we agree on some terms. Like today for instance, I was on the phone with him. I was listening to Britney Spear's toxic.. and the topic went on about being open and such. Britney denies that she sleeps around and 'claims' (or claimed) to be a virgin whereas Christina openly admits that she is not. Basically, what we agreed on today was the fact that we think it's better off to be honest and admit to whatever wrong has been done so that people can change their views of you and accept what you've done rather than denying whats happened and having others accuse you of wrong doings.   I miss   urlLink Adeline  . I miss you so much girlfriend xoxox.   How will things be for me in the future? Sometimes its easier to think back rather than thinking ahead because, the past is what has happened..and the future is never really that predictable. I'll go now and think about it. 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I don't understand how a person can break another person's heart, one of which has already been broken several times. i guess the pain takes a deeper cut than before, and then the wound would take longer to heal. I don't understand how I can continue on with my life this way, with all these negative thoughts filling up my mind and only adding confusion to my heart. I don't know why I hold on when I know everything is just wrong and I don't deserve to be treated this way. I'm better than that, and I know that one day everything will be brighter for me.  I never stopped hoping for things to go back to the way they were, but that feeling of hope is slowly fading away with my desperation and sadness. I don't know why I'm still crying and why I still hurt. Every night I'd pray that one day I'll wake up and forget that anything has ever happened. Sigh all I've been wanting is to feel complete happiness..even for just a minute.  You know how you think things are going to end up throughout the day? Then again, you know deep inside that nothing is perfect. So even if that moment even comes close to being described to 'perfect', it never really is. I've never been that good at lying, I'm a bad liar. I can admit to that, so most of the time I try to avoid situations that would make me lie. Maybe the better word for it is 'bending the truth'.   Everytime he looks into my eyes and asks me if I'm alright.. he has no idea how much it hurts just looking at him that way. Every day my heart is breaking more because I know, I know more than ever, that everytime I tell him that I love him.. he wants to believe me, but he can't. He wants things to go the way it should, but we both know that it really can't. Not with the way things are going right now.. not with all the interventions and the pain I keep feeling in my heart.   Life is like a song. Everything seemed so perfect.. it is too good to last. I should have known better, but I guess I was being too hopeful. I should have learnt my lesson years ago, because it has happened once. Look at it now. There's a cut in my heart, and the memories are engraved into my soul. I should have known..   I'm trying so hard not to cry right now. 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I do a lot of thinking don't I? It seems like I always get these random thoughts whenever and wherever I might be. I stayed up crying last night after two fights with my mom and my sister. Nothing special really, it was just another one of those family feuds. I swear we fight over the dumbest things. Then again, I should have seen it coming because I've been on the verge of crying throughout the whole of last week (more like the whole of last month). I let it all out last night, and I feel a lot better.   Last week was the last week of term; we get a two week break from school... more like a two week non-stop study marathon. It seems that each of the teachers' are all reminding us that their subjects are more important than the others. Sigh so which one do you prioritize? The subjects I'm taking for AS levels are a handful. Though Accounting and Business seem to be less stressful for me because I know the basics and my foundation of the subjects are primarily strong. Physics, Math and General studies however are beyond my knowledge. I'm trying hard to remember why I'm taking Physics in the first place. General studies, as a subject, won't even be recognized by some universities in London because it's still quite new. Maths, most of the things we're studying now are quite new to me. I was seriously lucky to get that A grade for my Module Pure Maths 1.  I've been trying to get online for the past hour. I promised  Rez  I'd come online at eight and now its almost half past. I finally saw him online this afternoon while I was hanging out at Adeline's house. My god, I've missed him so much. lol two months to go  Rez  babe =)  The student council announcements were last week. Sadly enough (and I've got tears and a stab in my heart to prove it), I didn't get any position in the council whatsoever. I cried in the gym right after the announcements sigh. But I'm proud to say that my best friend,  Aimi , is now the head girl of JIS. I'm so bloody proud of her. I mean, it was expected but wow, the shock in her face when they announced her name. =) Sigh. Congratulations to the new House Captains of all houses.. especially Green;  Michelle Wong  and  Shahyzul Rahman .. even though it was the position I seriously wanted. I guess you two deserve it more than I ever will. Yes, I'm envious. Yes, I was upset. I don't think I'll get over it for a while, but as for now I guess I'll cope. That's life right? You win some.. and you lose some.   My birthday is in exactly two weeks from today =) I'm looking forward to it because I'll be turning seventeen.. hey! the quicker it gets here, the sooner I'll be eighteen and the sooner it will be until I go abroad to a foreign country to continue with my further studies. So I'm happy. However, my birthday will also be the first day back to school, hei~ I wonder what I'm going to do on that day.  Sometimes I find it hard to breathe when I think back. My mom says I'm strong.. and I know it takes time to let go. I'm still not ready to because little things take a lot of time. I've always wanted to forget and sometimes wished that I could turn back time. I've always wondered how my boyfriend can cope with me with my always changing moods. I guess he's grown used to it because its normal for me to be so indecisive. I'm still growing up. I pierced my left ear last week, lol. Now I have two piercings on my left ear and one on my right. I've been meaning to get another one soon. I don't know what posessed me to get one that day. I guess I was that frustrated about how things were going.   I've been having misunderstandings with  Juls , sigh. We're okay now, happier than ever. It was our four month anniversary last weekend =) We had dinner at Fratini's and watched Gothika at The Mall. We've been having misunderstandings every now and then, ending up with me being really upset. I get upset over the dumbest things, well.. they're not really that dumb because I have a right to be upset over what has happened and what's been said. So never mind, I take back what I said.  I've got tons of things to get done this week, errands here and there. I've been catching up with my sleep and my eye bags aren't as bad as they used to be when school started (I wonder who's fault that is? heheh *ahem*). I've always wanted to go to bed at nine, but everytime I feel like going to bed.. my boyfriend says to me, "the night is still young". lol, can you blame him? He's a great guy, he seriously is. He goes to bed at the weirdest hours, like say four or five am and wakes up in time for lunch. So you can guess in the morning that he's half dead while I'm always perky in the am. lol, but lately it's the other way round because.. well, I've been sleeping late (11pm is late to me okay? bed time is at 9pm). He, on the other hand, sleeps earlier (11pm is early to him), and wakes up the morning feeling fresh =P Sigh but he's such a doll. He has no idea how adorable he is. He's got the cutest face, and the most darling eyes haha yes, I've been totally smitten by this cartoon character. He wrote me a letter the other day, I know now that he will go (and has gone) through endless lengths to make me happy. I don't know whatever made me think that he was going to dump me after a month of going out togehter..haha =)  i love you luv =)   I bought the orange-est bag while I was in KL, lol. It's noticable and its bright. I can be known as the girl with the orange bag.. sigh It's been over an hour since I've been trying to connect.. and I still haven't. GEEZ. It keeps telling me that there's no dial tone. Whatever that means. My phone line is screwy. ARGH. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I finally bought credit for my phone. It's made me feel better seeing that I had someone to text with through these bloody lonneelly nights. I also bought a recharge card for my text buddy so that I have my dude to talk to when I get bored (p.s.  i wuuvvvvvvv youuu ). It's taken me a while to settle things in my head, I finally got around to doing my homework. Though I only did  ONE  out of the oh-so-many stack pile I have. Yes, I'm a lazy person.. but that's not the reason. I'm not generally like that, I usually do my work a few days before the due date. I guess my depression got to me so badly that I just couldn't be bothered to do anything. Making this layout took a lot out of my head, though there isn't much production in it. However still, it's the thought and the hidden motive behind it that counts.  I've been listening to a bunch of seriously sad songs all day. They made me cry. Hah, I kept thinking about what was going on in my life, I guess it began to build up.. and as always, it lead to numerous amount of tears. Now, since everything's all dandy and happy ( Oh la la ), I can listen to them without wanting to cry. :) My head's not above the clouds, but it'll get there sooner or later.  I know that I'm going to get upset for the next few days. I know the reasons why but I don't think I ought to talk about them right now. The skies are dark, and yet.. the good sign about it is that we know it won't get any darker. I was in love once, maybe I still am. I hurt every now and then, but things will get better. =) I promised myself that it will.  Nevertheless, two of my many beautiful girlfriends,  Rachael  and   urlLink Adeline  , slept over the other day. It was totally impromptu and we only decided to do around five when we were at the swimming pool. Earlier that day,  Rach  stopped by because she was on her way back from Limbang (in case some people don't know, I live 5 minutes away from the Limbang border). After that we drove down to Gadong, where we met up with  Ade  about two hours later. We had a blast, even though  Rach  was constantly on her cell phone. We knew that her phone credit was dying, just like the rest of us, but that didn't stop her. We had under $1 each. I had exactly 5cents remaining in my phone credit.   I hung out at  Adeline 's house this afternoon. She's got braces now =P I totally forgot.. being the silly person that I am, guess what I brought to her place? =) I brought chocolates and a huge bag of Lays. Oops. Oh well yeah, I ate most of the crisps while webcamming with my best ever buddy,  Reza  (p.s.  Shout outs to you, my babes ;D hooollllaaaaa ).  Rez  babe, I miss you so much. I can't wait till you come back, we're going to have a screaamm!!  Ade 's web cam is so nice! It made me look so cute (don't mind me, I'm being vain today), then again it might have been my hair =P I webcammed with  Wajy  and his friend,  CJ , as well. Haha.. oh and   urlLink Rano   too!!  My mom picked me up after work and we had dinner in Kiulap. When I got home, it was about eight past and yeah, I had been sending text messages back and forth with my text bud since I bought credit (yay!!!). It's my mom's birthday today.  HAPPY BIRTHDAY MOM!!!!!!  I love you soo much. Don't worry about me, I'm okay now. Everything will turn out right and everything will turn out fine. xoxox  I think she's worried about me since I've been crying a lot. I guess it shows when I'm upset huh? =) I remember someone used to tell me that when I don't smile, I look as if I'm going to cry. I know a lot of people still tell me that. In fact, my mom and my text bud just think that I'm liable to cry when ever I'm not happy. Sometimes when I look in the mirror, I wonder what people really see. Am I the bubbly person that people used to love and adore (yeah, I know you agree with this =P) or have I changed my ways into a sinking pessimist?  I'll look in the mirror and I think I see..  Me.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I could never understand why people seem to make me cry all the time. This past week has been hell for me, maybe even throughout the whole month. I get upset, then I'll cry my eyes out. I'm frustrated more than ever, my tears feel hot and I turn into a blubbering idiot. I cry myself to sleep, because it hurts too much.  It's been one of the worse weeks of my life. I don't know why  he  had to break my heart. I don't know anything anymore, everytime there's a question.. I'd just get pushed away and they'd be left unanswered.   My birthday's in three days, and I don't think I want to live for so long. I know what I'm suppose to do, oh but why does it have to hurt me so much? Life isn't worth living alone, and I don't know what I'm going to do now.   My eyes hurt from crying. I broke down last night, I couldn't handle it anymore. I just wanted to be happy, I was being selfish just once. I know what I wanted, and I had it. Now, it just slips away..   It's just not f****** right.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Unangelic's back up and running. I'll try to update whenever I can, but this time I won't be posting for the sake of posting. Hopefully, everything will go back as planned and that no one's gonna throw a monkey wrench into my plans.   Everything's messed up, as always. My life is sadder than ever. I'm bloody depressed and this is where I'm going to ramble on. Other postees aren't in this blog.. they'll be redirected to another one soon. But for now, enjoy my posts. Because I won't be the one who's gonna get a kick from typing it up.   I should learn to relive my life now, and revamp my wholeself. So get ready, be prepared. More detailed posts will be up soon.   hugs.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Being closed minded isn't something many people can tolerate. Being opened minded is being able to tolerable. At most times, people have their own set views of how they see things and of course, their own opinions. But I think people ought to learn to be able to take in what others think. There should be a time when a person is able to voice out their own opinion (without being interrupted with an argument) fully, and then any comments should be spoken at the end. Personally, I find it annoying when I'm saying something and someone interrupts by trying to throw your words back into your face.  My head is hurting like crazy. I should learn to calm down and think rationalier about how things are going between me and my friends. I don't know why everyone right now seem so distant from me and it hurts. Maybe it's just me. Maybe I'm the one who's moving away from everyone else. I don't know, I'm still thinking about it.  Love can come across a person in different ways. I am aware that I have loved many people in many ways. May it be the dumbest reason to the most obvious; love plays an important role in life. Being loved the way I have, has molded me into the person that I am. Even though at times I might be so pessimistic, that my friends become fed up with me, I somehow still manage to put my head up above the water. As I've said before, I'm a horrible liar, and smiling through fake intuitions isn't something that I like to do. Nevertheless if that's what it takes to make sure that it doesn't cause a further problem, that’s what I'll keep on doing.  I don't know why I'm so depressed today. Heh, scratch that. I'm lying. I know why I'm depressed today though I'd rather not talk about it right now. I hate the notions going on in my head and how much faith I'm losing in myself isn't something I'd want to be proud of. I believe in myself very much, I think I'm old enough to tell the difference between what's right and wrong. So why is it that I'm still blind to see what's really going on in front of me? I still cannot pin point where I'm going wrong in my life.  Sigh, I wish you’d tell me.. I'd like to know what's pulling me down and how to cut it loose.   I break down every now so often, I don't like talking about it to other people because I don't think they'd want to listen to my daily troubles and unforgettable burdens. I think with every thing I hold back inside me, I keep pulling myself down. I don't know anyone I completely trust, but I do know a few that I trust up to a point. There are so many things troubling me, and I can't bring myself to talk about it to even my closest friends. I guess I'm still scared of what they might think and because our circle is so tight.. It might shatter. I feel better that I've begun to talk to an old friend again, I feel like I can tell things that I wouldn't feel comfortable telling others. It takes a lot off my shoulders and its seriously good therapy. It's made me feel better.  I'm stressed out and no one seems to be able to come up with a remedy. I think I'm losing out on what I enjoy most. Maybe I'm just pulling out. What if it's my destiny to end up alone? Sigh. My eyes are full of tears and I can hardly see the screen right now. Someone tell me I'm crazy and that I've got it all wrong.   Things seem to get more depressing everyday.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I haven't felt this alive for a while. It's a feeling thats almost unreal. I do a lot of thinking in my free time, because that's all I ever have: a lot of free time. My life isn't exactly a bed of roses, and I'm not always as seemingly happy as I am. I spent my whole evening feeling miserable and what did I get from it? Nothing. I didn't get anything from it, instead I felt worse. I feel terrible right now.   I just got back from a hip-hop fiesta. I saw most of my friends perform. Their performance tonight proved to be better than any other of their old performances, I guess this time they really worked hard to make sure that the show turns out a success. Thumbs up to the organizers and I hope there's more to come. I hung out with some guys I ran into in Gadong, offered them a lift to JP and well, being the gentlemen that they are, they paid for my ticket since I gave them a ride. =) Such sweeties. Anyway, I hung out with them most of the time. I almost fell out of my seat when I realized that  urlLink  Fez   was performing alongside M.o.R. I didn't know he was gonna perform, but man. I love that dude when he's on stage.   urlLink Haz  , the other half of  urlLink Illogic Elements ,  did a fantastic job on stage. Two thumbs up to them. They were fantastic. As for  urlLink B-style , what can I say? As always, they did steal the show and being the last act before the guest artists, Triple Noize, they pumped up the crowd up to its highest notch. Damn awesome. Even though I didn't stay until the end because I didn't want my sister waiting for me too long. I left at about half past ten.   The sky's so dark tonight. I wonder how dark darkness is. It's a silly question but I can't help but ask. I made three new friends tonight, I don't know two out of three of their names. Yes, I'm horrible but I couldn't help it since they weren't exactly introduced to me. They acted like they were my life long friends. A few days I go I thought that my life was ruined, and nothing will turn out alright. I can be so f***ing suicidal at times, it's just scary. I know it scares my mom because I tend to make a lot of threats. I know that it's stupid and I've always thought that people like that should get help. Then again, I know I could have prevented myself from doing unpredictable things; so why did I start them in the first place? I think everyone's human and that there are points in life when you just wish that you were dead to take away whatever’s hurting you. I'll agree with that for now, until I can find a suitable argument for it.  Scooby-doo 2: Monsters Unleased started showing on Thursday. I was supose to go and watch it last night with  some friends, but a sudden change of plans somehow lead me to go as I had originally planned about a month ago to go to Jerudong Park. Sigh what a night I had. It's pretty late right now, and my head is hurting more than ever. I need to learn to unwind and let loose a bit more. I've been keeping so many people at bay, I guess I'm still scared of history repreating itself.   Eh,  urlLink  Adeline   luv, Chan? haha that sounds good to me. I'll work on it kayz. mwah. xoxox.   Broken hearts have never been easy to mend. I think everyone should know that. We've suffered different kinds of disappointments, but I think instead of healing.. my heart keeps on breaking every day. There are a lot of things that go around me that I should avoid thinking about because I know it will end up hurting me. I wonder why people like to find out things that they know will hurt them? Curiousity always seems to get the best of us. I wonder what's gotten the best of me. I should stop thinking about the b******* in my life and just move on with whatever's left of me. I should pick up the broken pieces of my heart and put it in a box. I should just leave my heart at home so it can't be broken. I mean, my eyes are still full of tears with anger, hurt and frustration. So yeah, maybe I ought to do that. Maybe I ought to stop feeling so much for the things that matter to me.   Maybe. I'll think about it.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's been a long week. Holidays are done and over with, two weeks of meaningless, timeless sufferrings. As much as I hated the thought of school starting again, it was a relief. I hated staying at home, time is best spent in school is what I think.  Nothing's going my way so far, yesterday.. as most people would (should =P) know, was my seventeenth birthday. Thanks everyone who remembered, for the text messages, birthday wishes, requests that I don't kill myself (lol, seriously guys..haha), phone calls, hugs, presents, money (hehe) and everything else I got. I really thought everything was going to go wrong yesterday, I've always known that I've got my friends whenever and wherever. I always knew that they would always be there for me. Thank you for proving that.   Thank you to  Adeline ,  Rachael ,  Aimi ,  Randy ,  Pheng  and the rest of the people that were at our lunch table. Thank you. They surprised me with a birthday cake, I swear I could have cried. lol =) I love you guys so much. Thank you. It meant a lot to me since I had been on the verge of crying throughout the whole morning. I really didn't expect anything. lol, I don't think I can say enough thank yous to you guys.   Monday morning, I woke up crying in the middle of the night. Geez, it was my birthday. I was finally seventeen. Sigh, but something's missing.. I wish I knew. So anyway, I'll try and be a bit more optimistic for now. I dyed my hair a few days ago, its a lighter tone now.. more visible I hope. I think I'm trying to turn back into my old self. Haha, with the hair and everything. Yeah, but this time with a different personality and attitude. No one really appreciates something until it's gone. It seems that way doesn't it? How you take things for granted, sigh. I'd like to say that I'm happy. I really wish I could. I wish I could make a mask that smiles all the time, like that character from  The Mysterious Play , it's this Anime series I used to watch on AxN. He wore a mask to hide the scar on his face. You could say I'd like to hide something.. something as deep as a scar. Sigh.   There are a lot of things I'd like to say right now, but I'm worried about getting someone into trouble, or even worse.. myself into trouble. I've made some peoples lives a living hell. I think. I don't know. Maybe. Sigh. I'd like a lot of people back in my life. Living in regret is not exactly something I like doing.. but I wouldn't trade everything I have now for the world, except maybe one small problem I have. I doubt many people know what's been going on for the past few weeks, I have, without a doubt, been miserable. It's not right is it? Personally, I don't think its fair to be like this. I'd like it to be settled and over with, maybe  then  I can bitch about it. It'll just be a matter of time until I do.   Ohh,  urlLink  RANO  . LOL Thank you!! haha lol, look at what this sweetie posted up..haha (p.s. I didn't save it so I'm showing it off via YOUR server..haha) Haha Its interesting by the way, I never saw myself in such rendered photos :P Was that at the airport? hahaha I look cute. LOL. You should e-mail me the photos you have of me..haha I tak pernah nampak.           I hung out with  Adeline  and  Eddie  after school in Gadong. We ate at the foodcourt, hehe and  Adeline  spent about 30 minutes analysing me.. lol. She had me down to a T. Geez, that girl..hahaha so what if I get hungry every 15minutes? =P It's not like you don't. Well anyway, before I left Gadong, I ordered a value meal from McDs..hahaha I guess that proves her theory right. =) Love you bumz.  I bought myself an early birthday present. Francine Pascal, The Fearless book #32, I don't remember the title right now..and I haven't gotten round to reading it. It came out about a week ago, and I squeled when I saw it.  Ranz  was suppose to buy it for me :P but oh well, I already bought it. Oh and I bought myself a pencil yesterday. How nice can I be to myself? I pamper myself too much =P  When a ball comes flying towards you, would you catch it or would you duck out of the way? I don't know what I'd do, I guess it would depend on how I felt at the moment. I should have seen it coming, I should have known better. Sigh. Everyone else saw it, why I didn't I?  If I knew this was going to happen, would I have let it happen?  I probably would have.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      What I think will stay the way it is, for now. It's not what you think, but what you actually know. I know that deep down inside, everything has a reason. All good things must come to an end (from that so-called pessimestic view), and well, if you can't accept the end coming at your face..then you're just going to have to live with it.   You know when you read a book, let's say, a love story.. you get to read what goes on on both sides of the guy and the girl. In real life, you can only get to see one side, yours. How you'd analyse it and put it down into words, well, that's only your side. Your perception.   The things you wish to believe in, are your choice. No one's forcing you to do things you don't want to do..and the choices you make are the ones you think are correct and well, its just the moral and most ethical thing for you to do. Even if it means breaking someone else's heart so that they won't feel anymore or take in deeper pain when its too late.  Growing up in the untold world, where the society is mostly closed. Especially in this region of the world, where I'd think people try to look at life through one perspective. Where everything is controlled, and there is actually no such thing as 'indepencence' because everything has rules.. and breaking them is, against the law. I think we, the 'teenagers' or the new generation of the millenium, who live here, live a totally different life compared to those who live in 'independent' countries, where critisms are taken in with a smile. And there's pressure to improve, where as here.. we just have to accept things the way they are, because rules are rules and you can't change them.   Let's just say, living here is an 'experience'. Only about a year and two months until I get to go to UK and continue my studies there. I can't wait. We're suppose to write up personal statements, but I haven't even begun.. and to think that we're suppose to start applying with our predicted grades in August. AS Exams are in exactly a month and a week. Starting with a General Studies and ending with a Physics Module 1 exam. Unbelievable. Time seems to fly so fast, who would have thunk that exams would come around so soon? It seems like just months ago I was sitting some exams..heh, it was exactly four months ago. I've got exams every six months now, not something that my system can take in.. haha it's still a shock to me. Two years, and a six month gap is not something someone can take in very easily considering that for the past 12 years you only sit exams at the end of every three or two years.  Time just seems to fly and drag around at the same time.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I get so confused at times when I think about how or what I want things. Lately, its begining to make things harder to see, and its getting difficult to smile. It's one of those times when you realize that you're smiling, and then your smile would just simply drop off the face of the earth.   What are you suppose to do when the one you want doesn't want you? Or can't have you.. or whatever the hell the reason is. I've been trying to keep myself busy from thinking or reminiscing.. of happy times, it just fucking hurts. I can say right now, I'm just crying, now. Sitting here, starring at the screen.. crying. Alone. Oh god. I just want things to be over and done with.. sigh. It hurts just watching him, quietly   in my own table or corner. Sometimes I just can't help but want to cry, that's when I try to walk away as soon as I can.. it's just so pathetic of me. I miss  you , and you just don't have any clue about how I feel right now.   Sigh.  Today, was weird. Happy-ish-er, but good. The question of the day was from  Harris , " Why are you so afraid to smile? It's like you smile, and then you realize that you are and you just stop. " I don't know.. I really don't. I'm   hurting inside, and I've got to smile on the outside? That's just lying to myself.   If I could live my life over again, and that I knew things were going to end this way..and if I was able to change it, I don't tbink I would have. Because I'd rather have memories that I've shared with  you , rather than knowing and regretting that you and I could have had together.   I try not to think about it so much, I remember just yesterday I was in study period..and I swear I was going to cry if  Aimi  didn't bail me out of the common room. Funnily enough, I ended up crying at the end of the day instead..    Listening to:  All 4 One - Not Ready for Goodbye.mp3  I think I cry too much. I might be one of those people who enjoy being miserable. Maybe that's it. I just enjoy being miserable until something better comes along.. eh. No. I want what I want, and if I can't get what I want.. I still want it. =(  Argh.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Almost a week has gone by, and I'm alright. I'm not dying (see  urlLink  Nizam  ?) and no, I don't have cuts on my arms. I slept early last night, eight30pm. Woke up in time for school, without an alarm. Went to school with a pasted smile on my face. Today, was different. We started the day off with a house assembly, which I, funnily enough, hosted because some girls thought I did a good job hosting  Just Red  last year at JP. I'll always remember the fun times I had with JPCC Reality :) Those days were fun and carefree.   Wounds take time to heal, and I guess in a way, the pain you feel inside would eventually heal. Wounds would probably leave a scar to remind you of what happened, so what about the inside? Memories are all what's left. I wasn't ready to let go of what I had with  him , I really wasn't. As much as I would love to say that I feel a bit stronger today, I feel like I've been thrown down to my weakest point. I can't believe it hurts to just even look at  him .   It'll heal right? Not this week, maybe the next.. sigh.   E-mail threats, I don't mind. My e-mail tracks down I.P addresses.. so yeah, I have a rough idea of where you might be located and if I don't, one correct phone call can do a lot. Here's a tip though,  never  bring in religion when you want to pick a fight. It's just.. wrong.  Things are different now between me and everyone. In my eyes, I'd be in the center, while everything else revolves around me. In their eyes, it'd be them in the center while everything else revolves around them. Note how ignorant we can become? Do you know how it feels to be betrayed? I can't exactly say 'betrayed' directly, but yeah, something among those lines. It hurts.  I just don't understand..
     

    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Break ups are painful, it hurts like shit when it does actually happen. But as someone has once said (probably more often than he should), " all good things must come to and end " .. and to continue that sentence, another someone said, " you'll die anyway ". Talk about being pessimestic. Heh, he broke up with me.  I can sit down and stare at the sky all night, and allow my tears to flow endlessly. I can just sulk throughout the whole night and remind myself how pathetic I can get. Haha, that.. fortunately for me, is not possible. I'm better than that, and I know it. However, it doesn't stop me from crying at almost every thought of what I once had, and how 'happy' I had been.  My best friends, they are the best of friends, are great. You guys are beautiful. Thank you for pulling me out of my room during the weekend, thank you for calling all the way from Australia.. texting me all the way from Switzerland.. and most of all, thank you for being there when I needed you guys the most. I love you =)  No one is suppose to be worth tears, and the one meant for you shouldn't make you cry so much. I'd love to say that I'm strong, but words don't mean much if there are different actions taking place. I admit that I cry, and its painful when I think about it.. and everyone who has come up to me with the first question: " are you okay ?" I'm most definitely not. I'll be okay soon, not now.. maybe not tomorrow, but soon right?  Tag-board posters: people people.. thank you for defending me in whatevers going on in that damn tag-board. =) I respect the person, who ever you might be, for saying what you thought in my board, but if you're here only to insult me. Don't bother. It won't do much.   Things in my life are different. How I see things may contrast to others. In most cases, I'd probably see the cup as half empty. I don't really care much how others think of me, because no one knows me better than myself. Despite the idle rumours people may say about me, I'm not what they say.   No one knows what goes behind closed doors, so what others think or say what goes on around me..   I should be the one who knows the real story behind it. 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hehe I stole this off  urlLink mona 's   TIME STARTED: 8:36pm  FIRST NAME: Ida LAST NAME: Patera BIRTHDAY: April 5th, 1987 CURRENT LOCATION: Batu Ampar WHERE DO YOU LIVE: at home. WHERE ARE YOU FROM: Brunei WEBSITE?: http://www.unangelic.org EYE COLOUR: dark brown HAIR COLOUR: light/dark brown RIGHTHANDED?: no  ZODIAC: Aries YOU WEAR CONTACTS OR GLASSES? both. WHAT ARE YOU AFRAID OF? getting shot. YOUR PERFECT MAN/WOMAN: hahahahahahahahahaha MOST EMBARRASSING MOMENT: when I fell flat on my ass at Soon Lee. haha YOUR FUTURE KIDS' NAMES: One of them is gonna have  Adeline  somewhere. ehehe and the girls are all gona have  Ida  in their names :P YOUR BEST FRIENDS? I've got plenty. YOU EVER HATED ANY PERSON IN YOUR FAMILY? Not really GOING TO COLLEGE? yup!    FAVOURITES   ICE CREAM: chocolate DINNER: microwave chicken VEGETABLE: baby kailans! FASTFOOD: fillet o fish burgers MEAT: steak. SWEETS: caramel sweets o:) BEVERAGE: ice lemon tea MOVIE: I don't think I have one. ACTRESS: no. ACTOR: JET LI! PLACE TO VISIT: museums =D JEWELLERY: necklaces, earrings and lots of bracelets SPORT: basketball, bowling, netball. NUMBER: 91, 19, 89, 54. ANIMAL: cats BRAND OF SHOES: Nike PERFUME/COLOGNE: I don't have one. CAR: BMWs, Mercs. SUBJECT: Accounting and maths. POSSESSION: my letters. FEMALE SINGER:Aaliyah MALE SINGER:  I don't think I have one BAND: without a doubt, it's Busted.    HAVE YOU ...   LOVED SOMEBODY SO MUCH IT MADE YOU CRY? That's normal isn't it? RAN AWAY FROM HOME? lol, I've done that so many times when I was a kid. I don't do that anymore =)  BROKEN A BONE? No, I lead a very safe life.  CHEATED ON TEST? Yeah, but nowadays I try not to because it won't benefit me when the real thing comes along. SKIINNY-DIPPED? hahahahaahaha no. PLAYED STRIP POKER: hee. no. i can never remember how to play. PLAYED TRUTH OR DARE? haha yeah. FLASHED SOMEONE?  lol no. MOONED SOMEONE: no KISSED SOMEONE YOU DIDN'T KNOW? no. That's silly..hahaha Brunei is so small. You'd probably end up knowing them anyway. BEEN IN A PHYSICAL FIGHT? Ah, I remember that very well.. RODE IN A POLICE CAR? No. BEEN ON A PLANE? Yeah, but right now I've got a fear of flying because I haven't been on a plane for ages. COME CLOSE TO DYING? nno BEEN IN A SAUNA? yeaps! I love saunas. haha GOT ANYTHING PIERCED? Yeah, I've got two piercings on my left ear and one on my right. The top of my left ear is next..and then maybe my belly button >.    WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT...    ABORTION? I think it depends on what type of situation it is. I don't think its wrong, but it's not fair to the person because of the choices they have to make. COUNTRY MUSIC? that would depend on the mood I'm in. CLASSICAL MUSIC? um, not that much of my taste. OLDIES? love them! AMUSEMENT PARKS? heh.    WHAT IS...    YOUR GOOD LUCK CHARM? I had one, and I gave it to my koko for luck. He doesn't wear it anymore. sigh. WORST SONG U EVER HEARD? oh there's this song these Bruneian rappers made.. man. lol. I support the music industry in Brunei and all, but oh my god.. that one was the worse I've ever heard. MOST EMBARRASSING CD? I don't buy CD's much unless I really like the group/singer. So.. I don't have one. YOUR BEDROOM LIKE? It's red, my bed covers have orange patterns on it. Nothing in there matches..haha I've got green spiral stairs, leading to my second bedroom. I don't have any closets (yet) and my pc is near the window. My bed is next to my veranda and I have the coolest carpet!    ARE YOU A....    VEGETARIAN? hahaha yea right. no way. GOOD STUDENT? I can be the 'perfect' student, but then .. hhaha no lah, I'm generally good. I do my homework, I pass my work in on time.. so I think I'm a good student. DRIVER? Nope, my parents think that if I knew how to drive I'd run off with the car. GOOD AT SPORTS? I'm more of the average type person. But I love bowling, basketball and netball. GOOD STORYTELLER? no, I'm horrible at story telling! GOOD TALKER? I'm a flirt. lol, does that count? :p    HAVE YOU EVER HAD...    CHICKENPOX? lol. I'm the one who gave it to my sister. SORE THROAT?  every now and then. STITCHES? no. I'm very safe..haha BLOODY NOSE? I had one just two days ago. lol =) CANCER? no =) SURGERY? once. I had my tonsils taken out. hahaha SOMEONE BESIDES YOUR FAMILY SAY THEY LOVE YOU? lol, yup. I love being me. haha SOMEONE PUNCH YOU? no o=)    DO YOU...   ENJOY PARKS? yes! I love parks! That's where I can have funnnnnnn ENJOY SHOPPING: yea, but that would depend on my mood and how much money I have. WANT TO GET MARRIED: lol, sure in about ten years time. =) LIKE TO SING: I love singing. lol =D Sang for my yr11 dinner once..ehehe so embarassing. LIKE TO DANCE: yes yes yes! HAVE A CRUSH: haha yes. I've got a huge crush on this guy.. lala BELIEVE IN YOURSELF: I believe in myself more than ever.    WOULD YOU...    EAT A LIVE HAMSTER FOR A MILLION DOLLARS? Cook it really nicely, and I'll eat. ehehhehehe $$ GO TO A HANSON CONCERT IF YOU HAD A FREE TICKET? Free ticket? Yeah. lol Okay, I'm there. GET ANYTHING PIERCED? yes. I will.. soon? lol =) IF YOU WERE STUCK ON AN ISLAND, WHICH PEOPLE WOULD YOU WANT WITH YOU? I'd want my best of friends and probably my parents and my sister. YOUR HOUSE WAS ON FIRE, WHAT 2 THINGS WOULD YOU COLLECT? things? That dooesn't include people. So I'd probably grab my wallet and probably my mobile phone. IF SOMEONE OFERED YOU A SMALL PART IN A MOVIE WOULD YOU ACCEPT? hahaha yes. WHAT ARE YOUR NICKNAMES? yas, yaz,  YARZ , yazzie, yazabum, yaza, angel, unangelic, viXen-. hahaha I used to be called sam once.    WHICH DO YOU PREFER   PEPSI OR COCA-COLA: Coca-cola MCDONALDS OR BURGER KING: Mc Donalds. SINGLE OR GROUP DATES: single ADIDAS OR NIKE: nike LIPTON ICE TEA OR NESTEA: lipton ice tea CHOCOLATE OR VANILLA: Chocolate CAPPUCCINO OR COFFEE: coffee    IN THE PAST MONTH HAVE YOU?   DRANK ALCOHOL: no. I don't drink. SMOKED: no. I don't smoke. DONE DRUGS: no. I don't do drugs. HAD SEX: no. I don't do sex. MADE OUT: nope. I'm as fresh as ever GONE ON A DATE: yeah last week :p eheh hunnybunz~ GONE TO THE MALL: I went this afternoon. EATEN AN ENTIRE BOX OF OREOS: I haven't had oreos for ages. EATEN SUSHI: Yeah, about two weeks back. BEEN ON STAGE: Not this month. I did last month =) BEEN DUMPED: sadly enough, yes. Who the hell dumps me? hai~ GONE SKATING: no. MADE HOMEMADE COOKIES: I'm making some maybe tomorrow. GONE SKINNY DIPPING: nope =) DYED YOUR HAIR: I dyed it three weeks ago. STOLEN ANYTHING: haha I stole my friend's pencil :p but I think he knows I took it. So that doesn't count! So no :p    FIRSTS:    FIRST BEST FRIEND:  Norhafilah bte. Abdullah . She's studying in MS now. I haven't seen her for about four years now. We haven't spoken for about six or seven years. I miss her tons. FIRST REAL KISS: =) FIRST JOB: sales girl at a freaking bookshop. lol. I only lasted two weeks! FIRST SCREEN NAME: ahahaha I remember. It was viXen- and baking on undernet. FIRST FUNERAL: my grandfather's. last month. FIRST PET: goldfish FIRST PIERCING/TATTOO: my ears FIRST CREDIT CARD: I don't have one yet. FIRST ENEMY: Oh, I had plenty. FIRST BIG TRIP: The KK trip. FIRST PLAY/MUSICAL PERFORMANCE: ahahahaha KINDY!!!! FIRST MUSICIAN YOU REMEMBER HEARING IN YOUR HOUSE: Hm, I don't know.    LASTS :  LAST CIGARETTE: none? LAST GOOD CRY: about a week ago. but I realize it's not worth it anymore. LAST LIBRARY BOOK CHECKED OUT: you know, I haven't checked out a book for like two years now since my school bag containing two library books got stolen.  LAST MOVIE SEEN: Into the Mirror. It's a Korean horror. LAST BOOK READ: Fearless, #32 Terror. LAST BEVERAGE DRANK: water LAST FOOD CONSUMED: bananas LAST PHONE CALL MADE: to my dad. LAST TV SHOW WATCHED: Civilisations on Discovery LAST TIME SHOWERED: about an hour and a half ago. LAST SHOES WORN: Nike Basketball shoes :D LAST CD PLAYED: a cd mix my sister burnt. TIME FINISHED: 9:26pm.  Okay. I'm done.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Thoughts are endless, they never seem to let up. Even when you're doing something that distracts you from thinking, look up for one minute..and there you are having another thought. Some people are multi tasking, they can think and do things at the same time. Blab.  I slept over at  Rachy 's house last night along with  Adeline . And I also watched the JIS team play basketball, I was the score keeper =) We won 37 - 19. Every player in the JIS team scored at least 2 points. Hehe, anyways, I dropped by  Rachy 's house around ten-ish, and we went to bed around midnight. This time I slept in the middle instead of  Rach  jumping in in between of me and  Adeline . She tends to do that a lot :p mwahs. I played pool at Riggs. Hehe played a couple of games against some of my friends. My dad picked me up around six30pm. And look, here I am now.    You confessed your love with dying devotion, and I confessed my need to be free~  I know I've made a lot of mistakes in the past few years, I'm trying my best not to repeat them. Its not easy trying to start a new especially when it means giving up the things/ones you love. Maybe I should start again. Perhaps it'd end all the hostile feelings I've been experiencing for the past month, and maybe it'll make my world brighter and happier than ever before.   Most, if not all, good things come to an end eventually, it takes time for it to happen.. but it will. It's hard to believe that I'm actually seventeen already =) another year's gone past, and well.. I don't know. It's just unreal. I can't put down a life time of emotions into this site, but I can put down my thoughts. I can talk about the troubles that seem to come by every day, maybe not directly.. but vaguely, but once again it is in a sense that only a selected few can understand. =) 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Every aspect in life, every moment that has gone by has not only one meaning, but more. Take your pick, two or three or infinate. When things happen in your life, and another person is present to see it happen. How many meanings does that have? It's got a minimum of two, depending on how much impact it has on each person.  To whom it may concern:  Wtf. ARGH. Screw you lah. Ouch man, ouch. OUCH. Sakit you know? Yeah you don't have anyone 'special' right now, you know why? Because you just broke up with her that's why! Yeah, go on. Keep saying to those girls, "I sayang you", "I miss you", "you're so cute!" whatever. GO ON. YICH. Keep telling me you still love me when you don't mean it. It's just another act to take care of my heart isn't it? So that I don't cry right? ^.^ Well, fuck you.  As hard as I'm trying not to think about it right now, it's not going to work because it hurts so much. I hate it when people lie, that's why I try to avoid lying. I'm not alright with people pretending around me, even though I, myself, pretend just as much. I pretend, sure but not in a way to take care of how others feel. I pretend because I want an illusion of myself as 'happy'. What I find offending is when people pretend to ' jaga hati '. A person has feelings. That's just rude you know? It's stupid. I'm getting pissed off by the minute.  At least I know I'm in pain. Screw it. It's not worth me crying over  him  anymore because he doesn't want me. I'm not good enough for him. Oh wait, "he's not good enough for me". Break ups are painful, and I'm sure I've said this before. They hurt like shit when it happens. I'm alright if the reasons are reasonable. So what if right now I'm thinking that he just wanted to bail out because he couldn't cope? Don't use names if you just wanna chicken out. "Fed up" that's the word for it. Think about it will you? Think about it before you decide to break another person's heart. Think about ti when you start hitting on another girl. Think about how it feels to be lied to, to be lead on they way you did me. I'm not that stupid. I've got feelings, please remember that. Think about how much you're hurting me right now when I don't even have a clear idea why you and I broke up. No, you're explainations are too vague. I know there's another reason behind it. Stop lying to me.  I need to vent.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Everything is so weird nowadays. It's a change of pace, I'll admit. Well not really, everything feels normal in an ironic sense. Heh. I think I scared  Randy  this morning when I bursted out crying after physics..  sigh, sorry ti    I was thinking about the nature of exams. Right now, I'm questioning why I took physics in the first place. Not that I don't like it, I seriously do enjoy it.. but I just can't seem to grasp its style and method of asking questions. It's so different compared to the type of questions we get in tests in school :S maybe it's just me. Hai~ I don't know.   I think I think too much. lol. Thinking is bad. My thoughts wander and I always seem to end up crying =( It hurts. I thinks I fell down to hard. I had gymnastics this morning, lol. I did I hand stand and landed on my trick knee.. and it's still hurting like crazy right now. Sigh.  I should see a doctor about my knee soon. lol. I've been putting it off for months now.  Anton  shaved his head! I miss  aQilah  and  Lina .  A month and a half til  Reza   I've missed you soo much babe    Okay okay, for once I'll listen to  Juls  and  Ranz , they're fed up with me and my complaints.. *sniff*  haha I  will  see the doctor by the end of this week k? lol. =) 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      What's the point really? I try to look happy, and in most the eyes of others.. I most probably am. I appear optimisic, and where does that attitude put me? No where. I'm trying to look happy for  him , so that he wouldn't have to worry about me, because I know he does. Shit, he can't even bring himself to look at me without feeling a rush of guilt. I don't blame you.. I really don't.  I've been trying to get used to the fact that he won't be sitting next to me in classes anymore.. or lunch, or even stay back after school to hang out. It's feeling weird. Trying to keep myself busy is just another excuse not to think about it. It's a lame pathetic lie to keep me away from feeling mixed up emotions which may lead to hate and vengence.. and maybe even hope. Sigh.   I can't change the past, and I can't change how things are the way now. I found the nicest quote to live by: "Never be affected on how others think, because eventually in the end, all that matters is what you want." Or something like that, I'll re-type it when I check it again. It's in my phone archives.   Exactly 30 days until my AS exams. Not bad eh? I had a Pure Maths 2 mock today, I think I did pretty alright although I messed up the first question. Of all the silly mistakes I could have made, I made that one. Yich. But its alright, all that studying I did over the weekend with three past papers paid off. I just wish I could do something like that for my physics.. sigh =( I'm seriously desperate for my physics paper. I just can't bring myself to leave my grade to that lousy D grade, a low 48 out of 90 marks, I got back in January. I think I'll be resitting that paper again in January next year and see if I can bring it up. I can't wait for my accounting papers though =) but oh well,  alhamdullilah .. thank you God for everything.  Y'know, the school or uni I'd like to attend requires a minimum of ABB. Ohoho.. So high =\ yich, not that I'm not confident. I am, with my maths and accounting.. now I've just got to decide wheather I'd like to keep on studying Business Studies and Physics or just one of the two.   I want the dress I saw at the Mall. I want. I want. I have a date to my Sixth Form Ball this year =) yay. Silly baby butt. lol =) It's Earth Day walk tomorrow by the way.. does anyone wanna sponsor me a buck?  Sikit sikit, lama lama jadi bukit~ . Text me or leave me a message..  Here's a something from me for being so unappreciative: " There are millions of others, but I seem to be just wanting you. "  Bleh. I don't feel like blabbing on today. =(
     

    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Maybe today God is just testing me on how far I can tolerate things in my life. Sigh. Thank you. I've got one of the worst tempers ever. I can be such a pain at times, some people have no idea. Yeah, I'm seriously pissed off with  someone .. and he probably has no clue cos he's too busy  buaya -ing every girl in the world. Useless piece of git.   I went out with  Reza   Rachy  slept over last night, we had dinner with   urlLink Adeline   and her parents at Escapade (sp?).  Ade 's parents dropped me and  Rach  off at the mall after dinner and we went to check out the new Joenah shop at the mall.   I ran into  Faye,  urlLink  Mel  , Fez, Hazz  and etc at Ideal. haha I was with Shafz and Rach who were helping me walk around gadong because of my leg. Did I mention that I'm limping? Yeah, my leg is as messed up as hell. I went to watch the basketball match in school yesterday evening. I did the scores, JIS won 38 - 29 against St. Georges.   Exams are in two weeks. I've been practicing with my mechanic past year papers. It's so screwy man =( I had a mock a few days back and got my results back. 52% is not enough to get my my grade A in maths!!!!!!!!! ARGH. My teacher says I just need more practice, I think it's because it seriously still does not make any sense to me whatsoever. Sigh. This is depressing. Whatever you know? hai.  I had three business mocks this week alone, on all units. Those mocks were oh, HARD. Well, not really.. I'm just not satisfied with the way I answered the questions. Hopefully I'll turn out with a B average. Sigh, my god man. I had a physics mock as well, it was divided into two because we had only one single period on Thursday and Friday. The teacher's annoyed because we miss our Monday double because of the holiday.   Speaking of Monday,  Sal 's birthday is on Monday. =) He's gonna be 19. Happy Advance  Jijoy ! *hug* It's  Tina 's birthday today. HAPPY BIRTHDAY BABUNYA!  What else happened this week? Hm. I injured my leg during basketball practice. Sucks. I have a craving for ice cream. I made chicken rice today. I also made some biscuits for mom. Sigh. Tomorrow's a Sunday. I think I'm gonna study.. see first lah. I've been meaning to take my mom out. Or maybe I might hang out with  Reza  again. I bought myself a self belated birthday present. I bought a new  Busted  CD. I'm so happy   I've been thinking, I think today was the only day I see myself with smiley faces, all giggly and happy. Like sincerely happy. =) Thank you to that person who kept me company today ehehe *hugs*  Rez  =D I haven't felt that good in ages..haha and funny enough how you and I seem to click and get along very well =)  Anyway.   I need to learn to control my temper.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I hurt my left leg again. This time I twisted my knee pretty badly and well, I'm suppose to pick up a pair of crutches either Saturday or Monday. I couldn't walk just now and I think I spent quite a while crying in the sixth form common room. Thing is, I wasn't sure if I was crying because of the pain from my knee, or from the bitter feelings I was still experiencing from yesterday. Heh, it's swollen..but no worries, I've got an ice pack on it and the doctor gave me pain killers to ease my pain.   Today was the pits. Well, not really because I was generally happy throughout the day until my mechanics mock started. The day started off with a whole year assembly. Nothing new really, but one of the senior teachers talked about a book called "Forget you had a daughter" by this lady called ..I don't remember now. Sorry, I'm a bit ignorant (I tried to look for it in google, it didn't work). It was an interesting talk anyway, from what I heard. It was deep. Never mind, I don't feel like talking about it anymore.   I had a physics mock, I have no clue how I did..but I answered most of the questions and hopefully my answers were right :S I don't know eh. *sigh* The thoughts are begining to look more depressing. Hai~  I'm getting sleepy.. sigh. I was hoping  someone  would text me tonight. But I guess he's busy. Tsks. I'm suppose to be the score keeper for tomorrow's basketball game.. =D whee..  Oh, the doctor said I can't do sports anymore for I DONT KNOW HOW LONG. argh. That's like telling a fish to breathe without water =( It sucks so much. I'm annoyed.   Tomorrow is a Friday. FINALLY. The week has seemed to dragggg itself.. it's been a seriously long week. I've got a business mock, and another physics mock. I probably have to do some more work in accounting. Sigh. Exams are in two weeks. Wish me luck. I'm not that confident with two of my subjects :S  It's  REZA 's birthday tomorrow!   HAPPY 17th   BIRTHDAY   BABYJOE!   MWAH.   I love you rezzzzzzzzzzz :D You're finally gonna be 17 babes! The 25 day count was bloody long! I'm counting the days til you come backkkkk.. I missed you soo much. lol. and why aren't you online right now huh?! I'll try call you tomorrow, so BE WARNED if someone calls and screams happy birthday :P hahaha I'll probably end up killing my credit..but who cares?! My bestfriend kali ah. Buleh?! :P ehehe mwahs. love you.  Ah, I know my posts for the past two days don't consist of 'deep' thoughts. I don't know, when I think..it usually leads to seriously distrubing thoughts. I'll post more about that soon. Right now, I'm gonna levitate my leg and rest.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I think I must have connected, reconnected like at least eight times this evening. It's such a pain. I don't even know why I keep disconnecting. Grr, jtb wants to die. *pulls out samurai*  I'm in a good mood today~ yay. ehehe I spent the morning whining to my mom about my problems and my fears. I have weird phobias. Did you know that I have a fear of getting fat? My god. I'm scared of getting my hair cut. lol. I had a hair cut about a month ago, and like I swear that I could have cried just watching them cut my hair. My friends that know me well seem to enjoy threathening to cut my hair. They're so evil >.  It's my  urlLink sister 's 15th birthday on Tuesday, April 27th. She hasn't said anything about it. ehehe and from asking her friends, she's gonna want something that's not 'girly'. lol I KNEW THAT. She's definately 80% opposite of me. She doesn't like my taste in guys, but she loves green as much as I do. =) We'd probably do anything for green house. Hehe I love my sister xoxox   Anways, I've got a secret. lol. I so wanna tell my bestfy,   urlLink  Reza . I can't wait until he comes back to Brunei. He is  so  gonna spend time with me. Or I'll pull him by his ears from KB to Bandar and back! haha  Nazmo ,  Maxxx  and I were talking about him just now while we were bumming around at the Centerpoint couches. They were saying how  Rez 's first stop in Brunei would be to the top of the mall, where this guy works. ahahaha so tht he can make fun of him. lol, knowing  Rez  that's probably gonna be true.   Oh I've been shopping for earrings. I think I bought about five pairs this week alone. lol =) I'm in a good mood eh? I love being happy. It's such a feeling that takes time to get used to. xoxox. It's getting late, and I've got a secret~ lalala  lol, it's not gonna be much of a secret once everyone knows what it is. I'm not gonna place any hints right now. I don't feel like it. hehe let's just say I'm very happy right now   I have netball practice tomorrow, and I might even show up for cricket ASA.. see lah. I still haven't seen the doctor about my knee. I haven't had any time. I've been revising my Mechanics 1, and I've got two business mocks next week on all three units. Oh damn~ I've got Unit 2 and 3 on Tuesday and Unit 1 on Friday..and my mechanics 1 mock should be on Wednesday. Oh damn oh damn.   I had fun sleeping over at  Rachy 's. eheh that girl is like the bomb. :P mwah. i love you babes. We're gonna wear our star earrings tomorrow..lol It's pink with white stripes. ehehe I feel like shopping, I guess I better start saving money. o=)  The Sixth form ball is three weeks away..and so are my exams. whoah. The ball is going too be held in Empire and I'm probably going to stay over night with  Aimi  and  Rachael . ehehe hugs. we're gonna have funnnnnnn.. I haven't even thought about what I'm going to wear yet. I don't know. I'll think about it later. I don't feel like wearing black, but I also don't want to wear anything bright.. hm. Then again, I don't feel like wearing anything dull. hai~ knowing me, I'd probably end up wearing something dark. I always do. ehehe =)  I haven't charged my phone for like three days. My battery is dying. lol. I'm enjoying my nights alone, being happy. Eating my Lays potato chips. lol. I eat too much. I'm so going to gain weight if I don't start exercising soon.   It's so cold in here.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I finally found my exam time table last night. lol, I've been studying.. but not as much as people (i.e. my teachers) would like me to. Heck, I don't know what's wrong with me. I'm seriously relaxed with all the exams coming up to my ears, and I don't feel that much nervousness as I usually do when it comes to exams. I guess I'm still in shock and my system is still trying to register the fact that my exams happen every six months throughout my whole two short years of A levels.   I've been out almost everyday. No, I'm not feeling guilty about it because I study before I go out. =) I went out with  Reza   Win a date with Tad Hamilton , then we met up with  Hafiz ,  Zura ,  faye   Pinky . They are seriously a funny bunch. lol I had fun =)Bumped into   urlLink Adeline   and her mom at West Street Cafe (that's the new cafe next to the cineplex). Her exams start on Monday next week, exactly seven days from now. My exams start in about two and a half weeks, starting with a general studies paper on a Wednesday evening. I've got twelve papers to sit for and one physics practical.   Exam list: 19th May - General Studies: Conflict 20th May - Physics Unit 3 Practical 24th May - Mathematics Pure 2 & General Studies: Power and Space. 2nd June - Accounting Multiple Choice and Structural core papers 8th June - Business Studies: Unit 1, 2 & 3 9th June - Mathematics Mechanics 1 14th June - Physics: Unit 1 & 3  Haha, good thing is my papers are nicely spread out. Although I'm annoyed that my accounting paper is during the school term break! Yich. Oh well. =) I'm browsing through random websites I got via my hostees' links. eheh, my god. I can just feel my eyebrows arching up.   Sigh. =)  p.s Happy birthday  Sal . Hope you have a great day! mwah. xoxox
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's not so clear when you're not even sure of what you want in life, or what you're actually getting from it. In about five days, it will be the start of my AS examinations, the results of these examinations I sit will either pull me down or push me towards the edge of where I'd like to be in about a year's time. It's always been my dream to continue my studies in the UK; it's always been one of the things I've aimed towards since I was a little girl. It's hard to believe now that I'm an actual senior in school since the year 13's have left JIS now.   I had a talk with one of my best friends' today, and I was listening to my best friend tell me about how things are so different and how their perspective towards school has changed. I love school, I still do. But to them, it seems like nothing seems worth it anymore because most of the people they've ever loved and cared for (besides me of course) has left JIS. Now, all she wants is to get things done and over with. In a couple of years, we'll be graduating from university... and hopefully, from there it'll be a stepping stone towards our dreams and hopes. Maybe then we'll achieve self actualization (oh business term!! ;P) like in Maslow's Hierarchy of Needs =)  I've been in JIS for four years now, it's still hard to believe (think I've said this already) that next year I will be graduating out of the Sixth Form. It's funny; when I came to JIS I wanted to be in the student council. That dream is gone now because I didn't get a position. It hurts, but unfortunately I didn't get a position. I'm frustrated, but I can't let that get to me. Everyone's saying that it's better for me because then I'd be able to concentrate on my studies. I'm a freak I can admit to that, my confession is I can do things better when I'm doing two things at once. I know a lot of people who can vouch me on that.   Heart aches come and go. I guess I have so much free time that I spend that time making myself feel depressed. I don't know why I do that because I think that I do deserve to be happy at times... but there are times when I feel guilty when I'm happy. I've been hurt so many times by different people, and all because of different reasons. I know that at times, those people might reminisce of the times we've spent together, and I know that those memories may bring them pain as well. I guess I've got so many people in my life that after being happy for a while, I go back to my depression to make up for feeling happy. I'm not making much sense am I? Ah, they're just thoughts.   When I think about it, maybe it's true. Maybe I am afraid to smile, perhaps its guilt... or a different motive behind my fake smiles and pretense happiness. I don't know. I thought about a lot of things last night, ranging from my feelings to the times I've cried for reasons I thought as then were good enough. I talked to  Reza    Maybe what I'm saying is not worth saying, but at least it's cleared my head. I made promises to myself, I'm determined to do well in my AS exams. I can't afford to mess up because part of these results will help me determine my future. Sigh. This is depressing.   I need to drink some tea.  I need to clear my head.. I need people to set me straight with what they really want from me.. because right now, I'm not so sure myself.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So I haven't updated for over a week. I'm not sorry, I've just been really busy living up my life to its 'expectations'. My exams start in exactly seven days, I can't wait to get them done and over with. I really need to score during these three weeks of constant poundings of AS examinations.   I've been sitting for mocks almost every day, fun fun fun. >.  and it has changed its layout! What the hellllllllll.. sigh. Ah, it's gonna take time to get used to. But the layout is nice and fresh. It's a change I suppose.  My phone credits are low. I'm complaining..haha because I'm broke. I have no money for the rest of the month. THANK GOD for my exams. Three weeks. $5 x 21 days = $105 saved. haha yay =) yes, i spend at least $5 per day, in and out of school. I don't know what I buy, don't ask me. I never have anything to prove my purchases.. its usually food anyway =P  I've been out with  Reza   Reza Mustappa ?  BABYJOE !!!! Hellloo besttfrieenndddd..where the hell are youu? email me goddamnit. YOU KNOW both my school and hotmail emails. Argh =(  I miss you babes. I really need you.   I finally signed in my MSN. Hehehe, I was amazed to see that in just three days I've received more emails than I can possibly handle. I'm thankful though that I've got my girls emailing me again =) I miss you guys tons!!  Lina , if you're reading this.. EMAIL ME GIRLFRIEND! mwah. ehe  JIS Idol is this Friday. I've got my tickets. Ah. I don't feel like posting anymore. I'll be back. I guess you could say I'll be taking a break from blogging for a while.. =)  I love you.  xoxox.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Saturday morning! It's half past eight.. and I'm at  urlLink  Ade  's house! I came here to pick her up and finish baking my brownies in her oven..hehe silly girl went back to sleep. Haiyoh. We're suppose to go swimminggg.. but she went back to sleep!!!!!!! Argh.   Listening to  Frankie - F.U. Right Back . Heheh, it's a nice song.. ah screw it. I'm waiting for my brownies to bake. We're suppose to go swimming, I guess plans for that are cancelled. sigh, twice in a row I don't get to go swimming =( So annoying. I'll go tomorrow alone lah, maybe then I'd get to work out a bit. I was so bloody pissed last night, I did a 2km run on my trendmill. Heh, I haven't had any workouts for a while. I should get around to it since I can't do any extreme exercises because of my leg. Anyhoots, I guess I'm just annoyed right now. I feel so blur. Hai.   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, that's another girlie moved out from unangelic's family.  urlLink Iyra , hehe you've been a great hostee :D I'm here when ever okay? ehehe hugs.   Anyways, time for another whining session from me. Today has been  fucked  unenjoyable. I had a very  shitty  unpleasant morning, thanks to SOME people. But that post is at home, I'll post it up as soon as someone comes over to fix my phone line. I'm at  urlLink  Adeline  's house now, she called me up and asked me to come over. We (Ade, Rach and I) were suppose to go have dim sum this morning, but both girls over slept.. and I was pretty ticked off this morning. Seriously was not a good start to the day. My sister left for KL this afternoon, she's watching Saturday Night Fever this weekend.   Oh, my babyjoe  Reza  (the one in Paki) finally emailed me the other day. I'm so totally relieved =) 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Where do I begin? Yesterday's general studies exam came out alright though I didn't get to finish my last sentence. I answered every question (there were five, and each had equally 12 marks) with a full page length answer. Come to think of it, I should have written less because my writing is small.. ehe those of you who've seen my writing can agree to this =)  Well, this means four days until my next three exams. Pure Maths 2 which should go okay since I've been practicing and I got 85% for my last mock.. which is excellent and lol, pleased the hell out of me =D And there's two other general studies papers, power and space I think? It should be because last night was the gs paper on conflict. The physics practical, I have obviously messed up. lol I don't know.. I didn't get enough time to think so *hope* that I'll do well.. bleh, I don't wish to talk about it.   The  urlLink JIS  Euro 2004 cup is going to be held in school this weekend. I had no idea that this was gonna happen  this  weekend, yich :S I want to go!!! haha  I think I got upset last night, like very. I was missing my one of my best friends,  Reza . He's in Pakistan now, doing god knows what. Funny, my best friend and the guy I'm dating are both called  Reza . Huge coincidence? I don't know. Anyway, about the  Reza  from Paki, I haven't spoken to him properly for ages.. since like before and after his birthday which was just a few weeks ago. I've e-mailed him and waited for him to come online =( but he's not there and he's not replying. Call me paranoid, but I have a right to be since he's gone missing. babes, I hope you're reading this.. please get back to me? I really miss you.   Anyway, on a lighter note.. I was on the phone for a while last night, felt tons better after talking to  him . I think it was midnight when the phone line got disconnected. Haha my hello kad ran out :S My phone credits are running low, god.. what a bitch the phone lines are. I recharged on Saturday y'see.. and that means I had a fresh $20.25 in my phone. It was the night of the sixth form ball, so of course you'd expect a busy night with the phone constantly beeping with messages like "where are you?" "what are you wearing?" "are you staying over?" "who are you with?" etc etc, and well, you just gotta reply to them right? It would be so mean not to. Then there are the phone calls from mum and dad (who are without doubt worried of what you're up to) or from other people.. and there's also people borrowing your phone to call home to confirm what time they're getting picked up and all these other reasons..haha Okay okay, the next thing I know at the end of Sunday (that's a day and a half since I recharged, I am left with about $8.25 in my phone credit. Die liao. lol Now, I'm trying to get through the rest of the week with $2.25 in my phone. I don't know how..haha but I'll try.   I'm wondering if I should start putting a comment thing on my posts. Haha not that many people would have much to comment, but maybe it'll be good for the site. What do you think? haha comment on my tag-board please =D I still have tons of work to do with the site.. hopefully when I get a permanent internet connection the site will be up and running with links to other pages within the site e.g. the pictures section and maybe then I'll be able to open back up the unangelic.org group blog which features posters like myself,  Kenneth ,  Randy ,  Yazidy ,  Adeline ,  Rach  and etc. I closed it down because I wanted unangelic.org to be worked on a bit more. They'll be back, no worries =D I know they've got a lot of  bitching  ranting to do..hahaha mwah.  Okay, the next paragraphs are to my two angels,:   urlLink Adeline Ng  , eh hui..hahaha I miss you mwah. I wanna go for dimsum. Get back to me when you can k? Tell me when you and  Rach  are both free and we can go together =D Pick a day when you  don't  have exams..ehe I don't have exams from the 25th of May til the 1st of June. Anytime during those days is fine. =)    Rach , eh yin..hehehe when do you wanna watch troy? Pick a day and we'll go. Fasterr..because  he  doesn't wanna watch it. to quote: "I am not going to sit through 3 hours watching you pay attention to  Brad Pitt  when you should be paying attention to me!". ahahahaha =D So yeah.. Personally, I don't find  Brad Pitt  cute.. I don't find many white American/European actors cute, I find Asian actors like  Jet Li  and  Chow Yun Fat  cute.  Jet Li  is gorgeous, he's my favourite actor of all time. lol I find people like  Usher  and  DMX  hot hot hot. hhahaha Then again, maybe that's just my taste =) Yes, the guy I'm going out with.. *glares at  Rach  and  Ade * hahah I KNOW what you're going to SAY!!!! awu, he can be cute. He is cute. Not my usual taste, but he is cute. hahaha =) neways, love you two. text me as soon as you can.. I'll try to reply if I have a phone k? mwah.  Well, my days in general have been happy. I've got a guy who drives me into depression when he's not around (lol, you said this yourself baby), and I've got friends who mean the absolute world to me. haha I've been jumping around a lot (eheh hi   urlLink Rach  ).. aghh.. I miss the days when I used to hang out with mummy Una and Rach at coffeebean..   This is to   urlLink mona  .. I totally agree with you. It's so disturbing. I cried, because the thought of it is scary.. it's like letting go of dreams and hopes. At our age, you haven't even made a mark in the world.. heck, you haven't even had time to trample on the flowers. I'll talk more about it soon, maybe after the whole thing blows down. sigh I can't talk about it as openly as you can cz I'm staying in this country. I might get arrested..haha =) I wish I could tho. hugs.   So anyway... To everyone else, happy belated mother's day (lol) and happy .. happy happy. SMILE! =D
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, today's the day I have my first exam. General studies, conflict. It's only AS level because we're suppose to drop the subject since it's only a core and isn't recognised by most universities (it's a very new subject).   I'm suppose to write up a personal statement, and I don't know where to begin. Can someone please help me with a starting line? :S I have no idea where to start. We're suppose to start applying in August with our predicted grades. I'm still unsure about dropping physics, I don't know if it's a good idea though I don't plan to continue with it in university. I guess my subject options are a bit narrow, but only because those subjects are the only ones of interest to me during the time. Math, Accounting and Business seems narrow huh? I wonder what LSE and Imperial would say if I applied with those subjects :S I guess I'm just paranoid. I know that I want to apply for accounting and finance in both universities..and maybe just keep my fingers crossed at what I want? :S Ah heck.  I don't remember what time I slept last night, sis and I were watching  thirteen  but mum made us switch it off.. heh =) Those who have seen it, you know what I mean. Blegh. I found the show disgusting, about one third through mum made us turn it off. Ah well.   I think I've gained weight. I've been eating and haven't been doing my usual exercise routines. yes, bad bad yasmin. *spank*. I went to the doctor's last week, on Saturday morning. He said I can't do any sports for six weeks instead =) That's a good thing right? School ENDS in six weeks. Gah =( I start school again on the 15th of June, that's when we'll be commencing with our A level studies. Maybe I should just carry on with four A level subjects instead of three.. or drop two and continue with another AS level subject? Oh man, I need to decide =( This is so depressing..  I'm trying to think what's so special about today. What is it. What is it. Maybe it's someone's birthday and I forgot. Argh. Ten days til my best friend,  Aimi , celebrates her 18th birthday =) Five days until  Shawn  turns 17 with the rest of us!  I had the weirdest dream last night. I dreamt I ran into an old friend of mine, one of which I haven't spoken to for ages. We haven't spoken because of a misunderstanding maybe, I don't know but right now.. all I know is that I miss her. =(  Anyway. Went to my baby  urlLink  fwap  's site. lol She's one of my youngest hostees, I'm not close to her but I sure do love her. =D I'm not sure who's younger.. nayt or her. haha you decide xoxo. AnyWAY. I stole this off her:   [Spell your first name backwards]:   adi (my name is Ida Zetty Yasmin btw :P)  [The story behind your screenname]:  unangelic is just another name I made up from thinking about someone who's not really an angel but isn't the devil. lol k, this was THREE years ago okay! :P  [How old?]:  17  [Where do you live?]:  Brunei   DESCRIBE YOUR:   [Wallet]  It's an orgininal burberry's that my mum bought for me when we were in Japan. It's the light brown one, lol. It's heavy and it costs more than the money I have in it. ahahaha  [Jewelry worn daily]:  watch, a stud in my second ear piercing and whatever earrings that match my clothes during the day.  [Shoes]:  I've got soo many shoes. lol my favourites at the moment are my basketball shoes. They're from Nike and they're blue. High cut, and they say MAX at the front =)  [Handbag]:  I've only got one! hahaha Guess 91101.  [Favorite top]:  oh wow. I don't know? The fcuk shirts are my favourite..haha  [Perfume/Cologne]:  I've got plenty but I don't usually wear them. haha   [Piercings]:  I've only got ear piercings. two on the left and one on the right. I'm getting more soon, when I build up the courage to go again. haha one of these days I will get my belly button pierced! I wanna get an eye brow piercing too..but I think mum would kill me.   [What you are wearing now]:  Adidas tank top and my red school basketball shorts.  [Hair]:  tied up in a bun.  [Makeup]:  not wearing any!  [In my mouth]:  nothing  [In my head]:  hahaha reza reza reza. I'm hungry!!!!!!!  [Wishing]:  to stop thinking about food.  [Talking to]:  no one  [Eating]:  later not now :S  [Some of your favorite movies]:  I've always loved movies by Jet Li because of the whole martial arts thing. I should learn to do karate one day..haha  [Something you're looking forward to in the upcoming months]:  upcoming month? Well, my bestfriends.. Lina, Aqilah and Reza (no not the one I mentioned just now) are all coming back next month! I can't wait!!!  [The last thing you ate?]:  Microwaved chicken.  [Something that you are deathly afraid of?] : I'm scared of losing :S  [Do you believe in love]:  yes  [Do you believe in soul mates]:  yes  [Do you believe in love at first sight]:  yes  [Do you believe in forgiveness]:  not really. it takes time for me to forgive. i have a different philosophy for forgiveness.  [If you could have any animal for a pet]:  kitty cat!  [What are some of your favorite pig out foods?]:  salt and vinegar lays!!!!! cheezballs, malteasters, m&ms.  [What's something you wish you could understand better?]:  I wish I could understand why people always try to keep me apart from the things/people I love.  [Anyone you miss that you haven't seen in a long time?]:  ARGH. I miss Reza 1, Reza 2 (rofl), aQilah, Lina, Masyitah..    In the last 24 hours, have you: [Cried?]:  um. yes.  [Bought something?]:  I bought cookies!   [Gotten sick]:  yes.  [Sang?]:  I sang along to the whole busted album yesterday.  [Eaten?]:  yes.  [Been kissed?]:  no.  [Felt stupid?]:  totally.  [Wanted to tell someone you loved them, but didn't?]:  not really.  [Met someone new?]:  nope.  [Moved on?]:  little steps will eventually lead to bigger ones.  [Talked to an ex?]:  yes.  [Missed an ex?]:  a little bit.  [Talked to someone you have a crush on?] : definately!!!  [Had a serious talk?] : no because no one EVER takes me seriously.  [Missed someone?]:  yesssssssssssssss  [Hugged someone?]:  nope.  [Fought with your parents?] : yesterday  [Dreamed about someone you can't be with?] : no   Personal: [Who is your role model?]: oh I got plenty. but I only take different parts of them and together, they combine the perfect person.. that's who I wanna be. =D  [What is some of your pet peeves?]:  what's a peev?  [Have you ever liked someone you had no chance with?]:  yes  [Have you ever cried over the opposite sex?]:  that happens a lot doesn't it?  [Do you have a "type" of person you always go after?]:  i used to, but screw it. haha the guy I like meets   my   requirements.   [Ever wanted to get revenge on someone because they hurt you?]:  sometimes. but I don't want to because that's not nice.  [Rather be dumper or dumped?]:  I'd rather be a dumper. I hate getting dumped, it frigging hurts.  [Ever liked your best guy/girl friend?]:  lol yes, we went out together after that. Lasted almost two years, but sadly enough that had to end.   [Do you want to get married?]:  yes  [Do you want kids?]:  yes, but not too many :S two or three is enough. haha  [Do you believe you know the person whom you will marry at this point in time?]:  I don't know..  [What is your favorite part of your physical appearance?]:  I like my eye brows. hahahahahahaha oh I like my legs too..hehehehehehe  [What is your favorite part of your emotional being?]:  my thoughts are distubing, so I don't like that. i like the fact that I love to type up my thoughts.  [Are you happy with you?]:  sometimes, but most of the time, especially when I'm alone, I'm not that happy.  [Are you happy with your life?]:  yeah, but there are times when I think I'd just want to give up.  [If you could change something in your life right now, what would it be?]:  Take away these depressing throughts in my head..  ANYWAY. lol =D I'm done. I miss  urlLink the   urlLink three   urlLink girls . I don't really know why, haha I guess it's because I didn't really hang out with them before they left to NY =\ It's okay, you guys are gonna come back soon right? =) We'll catch up then.  urlLink  Diya  , I'll e-mail you when i get the time k? lol. I'm so busy with exams right now. luv ya tons! xoxox.  I'm so friggin hungryyyyyyyyy..
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I don't really know why I came online tonight. I'm happy. I'm deleriously happy. The past three and a half weeks have been amazing for me, with my moods swinging up and down.   Okay, I just realized that my templates are messed up. lol.  It's fixed. Stop whining   urlLink Adeline  . I feel so goddamn loved  

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      First. lol,  urlLink Beelz  has moved away from meeeeeeeee... haha but its okay sweetie. Gluck with your domain. love you lots! mwah. xoxox Come back soon! hahaha We'll go have a drink at Cz ;D as always, you, me, your sisters and my sister.  Second. Argh. lol ALL I EVER DO NOW IS EAT. I know who to blame because he's making me miss him to much, as a result I EATTTTTTTTTTTT.. hahaha k, I hope he's not reading this because he's going to feel very insulted. But I do miss you =(   Anyways, I added a calendar on the site. What you see there is from my phone calendar. So don't start getting offensive on me if your birthday's not in it :P Hehe I've updated some of the links, I'm offline as I'm typing this so I may have forgotten some people :S I'll get round to it soon.  Third. E-speed2 is supposedly out already, I'm waiting for my parents to pick up the modem. As soon as they do that, the wireless network around the house will start up again so then I can update via my angel13's screen. In case you guys have forgotten, angel13's my pc's name. ehe   Forth. Over the weekend was the JIS Sixth Form Ball at Empire's Indra Kayangan. I stayed over at the South Lagoon with  Rachael  and  Hazirah . I didn't bring a camera (I don't own one =\), but I did take photos with a lot of my friends. I wore a red dress, I'm bad at describing things.. so I'll just post up the photos when I get them from my friends =)   The guys looked beautiful! haha  Randy  was wearing a red tie,  Juls  wore a red shirt and white tie (yes, they matched me..haha), Shawn with his blue shirt..mafia king liao. hahaha Eng Hock in a suit.. oh man, I could just imagine us in about five years time, still friends and having dinner somewhere. Hahahaha Looking so dignified and professional.  Brandon ,  Randy  and  Juls  living up their dreams of being someone in the medical/engineering field.  Eng Hock  and I becoming the business people..hahaha wow.  Aimi .. she looked fantastic in her black and white dress. She had a date who bought her roses~ =P me, I walked around with different people. lol =D   We sat with  Ms. Claire  and  Mr. Lauder  at the table. Eee.. so fun.  The dinner started at about 9pm, the dancing started at about 1030pm. Oh wow, you should have seen the teachers' that were dancing on the dance floor. What moves. hahaha It was a blast!  Reza  came around with  Hafiz  and then I hung out with them until I don't know when. I had a long talk with  Reza  about everything. He's so.. I don't know =) Sweet. He's really nice. I don't remember what time they left but I know that I went to bed at 4am, after having a nice heart to heart talk with  Shahyzul . Haha, I remember knocking around at people's rooms at 3am in the morning. I remember seeing  Bong  running around downstairs..hahahaha I rememberrr a loot of things that happened that I don't think I should talk about right now. lol..haha but anyways, other people went to bed around 530am or later.  Funny because I think most of the rooms at the Lagoon were being occupied by JIS students because everyone was running around, singing and everything else  there , not at the main lobby, but at the lagoon! we were all there, laughing after the ball ended. I think most people stayed on the 2nd level. It was so much fun! =D   urlLink Fee Fee   stayed over with  Nazree , their room was a level below us. Ahh.. Someone called my room at 6am in the morning, IT WAS A BLOODY WAKE UP CALL. Geez, it was a nasty prack. lol NOT FUNNY. ahahaa okay, fine. If the joke wasn't on me, it would be funny. I had breakfast with  Rach, Hazie, Yazid, Iqbal  and  Khairul  around 10am.  Rach  and I went back to our room to pack, and we checked out at about noon.   Fifth. After that we went down to Gadong and had a drink at the West Street Side cafe. I just recharged yesterday, and now I'm left with an $8.15 credit balace in my phone. Yergh. Mum and Dad are on leave for the next few weeks, I'm on study leave. They're not home right now, they left early this morning to get some errands done. I haven't even eaten breakfast yet. Sigh. It's so hard staying somewhere where everything seems to be half an hour away. haha I live in the rural areas of Brunei, where there aren't many houses or shops. Gadong is a thirty minute ride, and so is Jerudong. That goes for school as well, the quickest time I've ever gotten go Gadong is twenty minutes. But its alright I guess. Did I mention I live near a chicken farm? My house is on a hill, the chicken farm is up an even higher hill. So weird.   Sixth. It gets freaky here at night when the wind is blowing because sometimes your imagination start to run wild and you're thinking that the wind that is blowing is actually a little child crying or calling out for help. Yes, it is that freaky living here.   Seventh. I don't smoke, I have never tried. And I hope I never will. I don't drink either..haha I'm so proud of  you  for trying to quit smoking =) Keep going! hugs. Just think of me kicking  your  ass if you even TRY to light up. hahaha I miss  you . xoxoxo. 5 days to go til I see  you  again =D     urlLink Melon !  i miss you girl. lol hugs. We'll talk soon k? xoxo.  Prac exam in two days! 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Finally home from Gadong. I've changed and I'm exhausted. I spent the night at  Aimi 's house last night, but I fell asleep well before midnight. hehe but I wished her a happy birthday before I dozed off.     HAPPY  BIRTHDAY  AIMI!      urlLink  Joe   texted me last night from Pakistan. He never updates his site..haha It's so nice to hear from him considering the fact that I don't see him online much anymore. I watched Troy yesterday afternoon with  Aimi  and her brothers,  Raimi  and  Jamri . We got to sit in the VIP seats because some people stole our seats. Whoop whoop. lol. After that we went to their aunt's house and had dinner, met up with  Nana  and  Lydia  there. Went home at about 10:30pm, and I must have went to bed around 11:00pm.  Mum and dad picked me up from  Aimi 's house at about 1:00pm. Then they dropped me off in Gadong. Watched Shrek 2 with  Reza  :) met up with Hafiz, Ping and Sham. I went left around 9:30pm, went to Jerudong. Came home at 11plus.   blegh. can't think.  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Is there a book called that? haha Anyway, I'm online now. Chatting with  urlLink  Diya     I just signed up for  urlLink Gmail . Hehe I've got a new email address: unangelic@gmail.com. Not bad eh? I still like unangelic@unangelic.org though. I have 1000MB for my e-mails, that's so totally cool. I can keep as many e-mails as I want. Aweesommme.. Anyway, today, I've decided to make more use out of the clothes I have. I'm wearing a skirt now, its so nice. Haha I'm not used to wearing skirts, so I guess for now I'm going to have to live with it.  I have stacks of clothes around the house, yet I stick with only a certain few shirts and my favourite jeans. If I count the number of jeans I already have (and that still fit!), I've got just under a dozen.   I'm suppose to go out with   urlLink Yazid   and  urlLink  Choong Hoe   this morning, we were going to go play tennis at the Empire Country Club. Blegh, mum already left.. so I guess  Yazie  and Hoe are going to have some nice male bonding today.   I'm hungry. Lately all I ever talk about is me me me me. *smile* baby says I'm vain. mana ada. He's as vain as I am. There's this top I saw the other day, it's black. It looks like any of my other tops except this one has words on it,  I'm no Angel . Oh la la. I want.   Okay, now I have a craving for pizza.   Hungry hungry hungry.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Have you ever sat down and realize that you're upset about something, when all that time you didn't realize what it was that was causing you hurt? Heh, I've been feeling neglected. I don't know.   I can hear myself saying over and over "they don't care about me anymore" ' I've been saying things like "they don't love me" and even, "they don't like me y'see". I realize that I have said those words a number of times, part of me doesn't want to believe it's true.. but I see it as true now. It hurts. They keep saying they'll make amends. Lies. They say they're sorry. Lies. They say they won't leave me alone anymore. Lies.  Yes, I'm a negative thinker. I don't see the world as half full because in many ways, and from my perspective, it isn't. When I think about the times when people make me cry, it makes me sick. I'm not tripping any more, I shouldn't.   I remember just yesterday, hearing my parents talk. It hurt. I don't know, maybe that's just me. Maybe I'm just sensitive. I wouldn't really care right now. All I know is that I'd like to cry tonight.. the same way I did this afternoon and the days before that.  Anyway, as I've mentioned before, I slept over   urlLink Adeline  's house two days ago. I'm sleeping over  Aimi 's house tomorrow. Yeah I have a busy weekend. Soo.. web cam photos we took at  Ade 's house.      Adeline ,  Rachael  and  Yasmin .    Ju On Remake. haha  Rach  &  Ade .     Ade  with hair tips. Me looking away.    Us looking at the screen.    I never knew how friggin pale I am. See that, I'm as white as a ghost. It's weird..     Hehehe one photo without teeth. ahaha we look like we're pouting.  I just got off the phone. I'm probably more upset than ever. Argh. Currently chatting with  urlLink  Yazid  ,  Sal  and  Rach . Blegh.. maybe someone's gona cheer me up. What a day. What a day.  I've got a list of things to do. Like what I said in my previous post.. but I'm probably going to postpone that. The whole  things I like about me  list. I didn't watch a movie today, my leg hurt so I thought I wasn't going to go out. But I went out anyway around 2plus.    Quick summary of today:  I ran into  Alim ,   urlLink Mel  ,  Emily ,  Roy ,  Ali ,  Sham  and some other people.. (yes I'm bad with names. but I know what they look like! Give me credit for that!) of which I only knew maybe four out of the many people I ran into.   Anyways.. after that  Alim  and I had chicken rice at the Mall food court. I met up with  Pie , who lanja-ed me a drink and ice cream at McDs =) Thank you~ ehehe then we met up with  Rach . Sat down at West Street Cafe, it's now labelled our 'favourite' for now..ehhee I like the place a lot.   I left around four plus, picked up my sis and then my mom. Went to my grand aunt's place. Went home. Took a shower. Talked on the phone. Oh look, here I am now.  Okay. Bye.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       10 Years Ago, I...  1. was 7 years old. 2. went swimming every day. 3. ate fish & chips and ice milo everyday. 4. studied in PGGMB Telipok. 5. was labeled a tom boy.   5 Years Ago, I...  1. started attending STPRI. 2. almost got beaten up by a bunch of senior girls. 3. loved bowling. 4. thought Sweet Valley books were cool. 5. had red hair.   3 Years Ago, I...  1. moved to JIS. 2. fell in love with my best friend. 3. had orange hair. 4. loved bowling. 5. began to love the colour green more.   A Year Ago, I...  1. watched my spirit die. 2. had my heart broken by my best friend. 3. broke down crying every day. 4. moved on. 5. had brown hair.   So Far This Year, I...  1. dyed my hair again. 2. got dumped. 3. didn't get a position in the student council in JIS.  4. met someone new  5. obtained a grade A in my Pure Math 1 exam.    Yesterday, I....  1. cried. 2. slept over   urlLink Adeline  's house. 3. hung out with  Hadi  &  Khalid . 4. watched Shrek 2.  5. went crazy with  urlLink  Titz  .    Today, I ....  1. woke up at 9am. 2. went to Gadong with  Rachael  and  Adeline . 3. watched Mean Girls on dvd. 4. went over to  Ka Fiza 's house. 5. called  Reza     Tomorrow I will...  1. sleep until about 10am. 2. watch "The Day After Tomorrow" with  Hadi  and  Ka Fiza . 3. miss  Reza . Both of them. hehe =) 4. smile. 5. write a list about the good things I find about me.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      [ added @ 2:03pm ]  I just added in a commenting system thanks to blogger! Unfortunately, I'm not gonna allow unknown comments from people, so you have to have a blogger account or something to comment. lol, I probably will change it to allow people without blogger accounts (yes, I know a lot of people like to complain. Anyway..how this works, you gotta click on the comment thing..and it'll take you to a page where only that one posts appears. Go to the bottom and click 'post a comment' and then enjoyyy.. ehe hugs. xoxox.  love,  yarzx. [/ added ]  I've been trying to post for the past few days, but lately.. nothing I type up seems good enough to be put up on the site. I guess its because of the change in feelings ater typing up what I wanted to say. It's stupid really, nothing new from what I've been feeling so far.. having ups and downs in my days.. looking up and waking up to a new day. There are days when I wish I could just wither away and disappear.. I keep looking forward to the weekend because that's the only time I'd feel happy with the people I love and care about. I'm counting the days for the weekends. Heh.  There was a time when I'd look forward to school days, but lately.. I'm uninspired and at times, half-dead (not literately speaking of course). Sigh, I guess I'm just depressed, I can't exactly figure out why. Currently listening to  Christina Aguilera - Walk away , it's a nice break free song isn't it? =) I should have known~.   Here are photos taken on  urlLink  Adeline  's birthday. 9th May 2004    That's me sitting down on the floor at  Ade 's house.     Rachael  and I outside  Ade 's room.     Ade  and I in her room.    ehehe That's  ade  being silly. =P  Details about that day.. Hm, I don't think I said anything about her birthday in my previous posts..ehe you see,  Rach  and I met up in Gadong at 10am in the morning, on Sunday. Then we drove down to  Adeline 's house and suprised her. Man..her first question was "what the hell are you doing here?" talk about being so welcoming! haha =) anyways.. after that we took her to Taurean where we met up with  Eddie  and  Randy  (who was late!!) Photos of that below.      Randy , myself and  Rachy  reading a magazine..ehe    Us again in a proper photo.    Three bums and a boob..haha the last time we took a photo like this was on  Rach 's birthday..which was in NOVEMBER last year!!!    Last but certainly not least, a photo of  Rach , myself and  Ade .  So anyway, I'm at  Adeline 's house right now. I slept over last night. It was so last minute.. doesn't really matter. I hung out with  Hadi  yesterday. Picked him up and we went to Gadong. We've been wondering around in search of a birthday present for  Aimi , hehe he doesn't even know her..haha nice thing is that he didn't mind going around shops with me looking for her present. Sadly enough, this was my 5th hunting trip and I've still come out empty handed. I'm such a dofus when it comes to birthday presents..hehe ah well. Saw  Juls ,  Ranz  and  Yen  at the Mall.. didn't stay them because I was with  Hadi  and  Khalid  at the time. Oh well, I got a whole month to kacau them. ehehe  I've been doing some thinking.. and a lot has happened this month. It's been totally weird and I'm not sure about how I feel about things that are happening around me. Most of my best friends are coming home either next month or sometime in July. I can't wait! Unfortunately our summer holidays start on the 9th of July. Hehe, we start our A2 course on the 15th of June. Bleh. I don't like the date.. it's so full of memories.   I watched Shrek2 last night, it was freakishly hilarious. lol =) I might watch The Day After Tomorrow with  Hadi  tomorrow afternoon and some friends. My parents are still on leave, I see them around the house a lot. lol In exactly seven days, I'll be sitting my accounting exam. Man, I just want these things to be done and over with. The days seem to just drag on..  4 more exam days to go and I'm free..and HELLO A2! =)  Now, I gotta figure out which subject I'm gonna drop. Haiyoh. I'm watching Troy again on Friday night, I'm probably going to sleep over  Aimi 's house that night since her birthday is the next day.  I miss  him .   bleh.  Rach  and  Ade  are watching another movie. Hehe we just watched Mean Girls on dvd. That one sucked. I'm going to my cousin's house later..but I gotta take a shower first. Hehe, I'm still in my pink pjs. lol.   They've been complaining about my opposite personality today. I was the one who slept early, and I'm also the one who stayed in bed the most..ehehe usually its the other way around. I don't know why I'm so tired. Must be something I ate..haha
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hello,how is everyone feeling today? good? bad? happy? sad? silly billy? bleh.As you can see  Yasmin  has gone a little out of her head today. She's changed. She's been sleeping longer than  Me  and  Ade  now. Oh btw, This is  Rachael . We're staying over at  Ade 's place and I'm going to blog for  Yasmin  because she's being a lazy bum. Anyways,  Yas  was the earliest to go to bed after watching  Shrek 2  at the mall last night and yadida.  Ade  and i went to bed at almost 3am and woke up well early. Yas on the other hand, woke up at umm,late and she's still lazing around on the sofa in her pink PJ's reading. Haiyoh this girl! Ade's got new braces colour...Wheeeeeeee!so ugly.Kidding.Anyways, I've done a summary for  Yas  now. Oh yeah, She's been on the phone 24/7 so opposite of me. Usually during sleepovers, I'm on the phone 24/7 and i don't even layan them or anything.This time its the other way round. lalala. Breakfast calling. Gonna watch mean girls now before  Adeline  goes all crazy. Bye Bye World.    SPIDERMANNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNN !!!  I'M A BIG FAN.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have espeed 2 set up on my sister's pc. Hopefully next week the wireless will be set up around the house so I can connect online through my pc. Anyway, p2 exam is in 3 hours. Wish me luck. I'll update later when I get home. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I can wait for school to start. By then, my batch.. the year 12 August batch will be officially known as the senior-est batch (other than the Year 13 Jan people). Cool eh. I don't know. I'm just feeling a little reluctant to see school start again. Sigh, we'll be starting with the A2 course as soon as we come back. I duno, I guess I have a lot of things to think about. Thankfully, we'll only have about four weeks of school before summer holidays which should last about a month plus.   Funny thing this  urlLink friendster , I don't sign in for about a day and I ended up with 30+ messages :S It's so hard to reply or even read them one by one. Sigh, espeed2 isn't as cracked up as its suppose to be, unless maybe there's a problem with my computer. It's receiving but it's not sending? Someone help me out here please?  Sigh. My head hurts.   Ade ,  Rach .. I miss you both. I've been depressed again, and nothing seems to be working..we'll hang out soon k. I've js been really busy. I miss you both. xoxo. love you.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       [note]  I typed this up on Wednesday, June 2nd 2004 around 18:30hours. So, heheh yeah.. think about it. I was extremely angry.. words cannot describe how I felt that day  [/note]  I just got back from Supasave Gadong, and lets say I'm not in any of my good moods. I just finished ?my AS accounting exam which was pretty okay besides the last question which was utter bullshit because I only had a rough idea of what they were asking and well, the other kids (other THREE students) had a hard time answering it as well. The multiple choice I sat through was alright I suppose, the questions weren't hard but they weren't that easy either. I had to change most of the answers I wrote down the first time because after 30 minutes, that's when your brain actually starts to gear up properly. I answered the MCT with the first answers in 30minutes, but after going through them again.. I realize most of my answers were far from perfect. Other than that, and after re-doing and rubbing out the wrong answers, I think I did pretty well. The structured questions however, a.k.a. paper 2 AS accounting was blegh. The first question was about ratios, which I had already learnt by heart back in the IGCSE days of accounting about two years back. Thank god for that. Then there were the 'comment on your findings' part and there were things like what are the advantages and disadvantages of rations. Yup, did that. Hopefully that stuff allowed me to score close to perfect marks. The second questions, which Brandon and I had hoped to come out was the partnerships. I'm not sure, but I think I mixed up my balances and forgot where I should put my salary in the current accounts.. blegh. I don't know eh. Hopefully, it'll turn out okay. I hope and I'll pray that I do because I didn't exactly get ANY time whatsoever to recheck my answers. The last 30 minutes of my 90 minute exam was spent on the third? and final question which was about comparison of options and finding profits for the company it was talking about. Yes, that was the one that I think is utter bullshit because I cannot believe that I spent 30 WHOLE minutes just trying to finish it up. I didn't even get a CHANCE to go through my other previous questions to check if my answers were okay or not. I didn't even get a chance to CHANGE any of the answers that I had rethought about. Blegh, it was utter utter crap. Okay, enough ranting about my exam. On to my ranting about Supasave. All I wanted was to buy four slices of meat. The guy ignores me, and I was NOT in a good mood. When his friend comes up to me and asks me what I want, I am on the verge of screaming. So, I control myself and say "never mind" and walk away but under my breath as I walk past the guy who was SUPPOSE to serve me earlier, I start cursing him and well, I feel like killing him right now. I'm so fucking pissed off right now. Today, I woke up at 8:30am. I'm never in a good mood in the morning anymore not since the election announcements. I couldn't care any less about the schools conditions and everything that's in it. I'm still frigging hurt about not getting a position in the council, but that doesn't really matter because now, the school ranks somewhere in the  bottom  of my proriety list. Now, I don't even want to bother. It sucks that I didn't get anything, yeah so the voting system was democratic. Screw you. You're not the one, the ONLY one, out of the seven that stood up for elections and NOT get a blood position. I was the ONLY one. How .. what's the word.. never mind, how the hell do you think I feel? I'm not embarassed. No, of course not. I'm hurt. SIX out of SEVEN that stood up got in, yeah. SOMEONE had to be kicked out right? I was unlucky enough to be THAT person. Argh. School starts again on the 15th, that's in two weeks time. Oh how dandy. The night before that will be my physics exam. Whooptedo. Blegh. Okay, enough bitching.  I'm trying to calm down, but the more I try.. the more frustrated I feel. I've got a bad temper, especially when I don't get what I want or when I'm not able to get things to go my way. I'm bad at pretending that nothings wrong because most people can see from my eyes or when I'm quiet. I can be such a pain when I'm ticked off, you can ask any of my friends. Sigh, but I usually try to brush off negative thoughts and vibes off me because it's not right to be angry I guess. At most times, I can be patient.. but I can only be patient up to an extent. That's when things begin to build up and my anger would be 1000x worse. I'm horrible and I guess it's my fault for allowing tension inside me to build up. Antah eh.   You know what's even more frustrating? I'm OFFLINE while I'm typing this and e-speed2 is being a pain. The connection is saying that it's at 12.0Mbps, but the sending packets of data are so low that it's NOT moving. Sigh, maybe it's my computer. I'm done with this. Sigh, I'm outta place and out of my mind.. It's been three hours since I typed up this post. I'm feeling slightly better thanks to some people. I saw  my  angel just now in his car, doubt that he noticed my car passing by his. Doesn't matter. I was texting with Reza in Paki, yesterday. Silly bumz didn't know I was having my exams. =)
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Actually, I wanted the title to be 'im a fucking genius' but never mind. I just finished installing espeed2 in the computer downstairs, and now I'm suppose to install the wireless around the house. Blegh, can't do it yet because I can't find the plugs that connects the wireless modem to the pc. Oh well, I'll look for it later. Mum and dad think I'm this computer prodigy, uh. Okay. I don't agree, but it doesn't really matter. I got a C for my IGCSE back in Year 11 which felt like a slap in the face. I'll admit to it now, I suck at theory. But hey, who uses theory in the art of computers anyhow? "what is a virus?" how the hell am I suppose to know?  got this off  eng hock  via e-mail. eheh thanks babes.    
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I was browsing through these various websites.. and now I feel sick. No offense to those sites, but some people just make me feel so  fucking  bloody sick. It's disgusting. Blegh. I've got my accounting exam this afternoon, wish me luck on that. I'm dressed for it already, I'm suppose to be going somewhere with my mum.  I stuck myself in front of the pc yesterday and ended up reading two Wicca books, the first and second. I can't start on the third one yet because my sister lent it out to her friend. I'm annoyed. I hate lending out books to people who never return them. Sigh, hopefully her friend will so I can carry on reading because I keep getting the images of the scenes from the book in my head. I see them in my dreams, shit. I gotta finish reading the series..how ever many there can be.  I'm a freak when it comes to books. Get me started on the series type and you'll see me start from the first book all the way til they stop publishing them. Heheh, yes I'm that type.  Anyway, mum's calling me to go downstairs now.  later.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       [added]   urlLink  nayt   is up and running with a new layout made by ME. ehehe  urlLink  GO THERE NOW  . mwah! xoxox  luv, yarz. [/added]   I was talking to  my  angel yesterday, and he always makes friggin' sense and I guess that's why at times I'd call him  my  savior. I love him to bits and I don't think he will ever know that because he's ignorant and refuses to acknowledge that fact. It doesn't really matter right now because even if he does read this, he's not gonna know that I'm talking about him. Sooo.. anyway.  I've been browsing around through my  urlLink friendster , it's so cute. There is, without doubt, no day that I won't receive a message from a person I don't know at all.. saying something among the lines of "wanna be friends?" Personally, I don't mind all these e-mails, but heck.. they get a bit annoying. Heheh, but keep them coming.. They're funny though but I don't usually respond because I allow friendster to let anyone add me as their 'friend'. The only ones I reply to are the people with common interests with me, for example the whole book interest thing. So far, I've met four people who like reading Fearless by   urlLink Francine Pascal  . I'm waiting for Book #33 and The Silent Hand to come out. It should be out by now. Anyway, I think it's cool meeting people with similar interests as me. I've met people who love   urlLink BUSTED   as much as I do. I'ts all in fun right.  Anywayyy.. I've got a commenting system now. Only ONE of you uses it :p ehehe use it use it! blegh. I'm clearing out the folders in my site. Deleting everything that I don't know about.. and umm.. yeah. I'm deleting most of the folders except for those I know are my hostees. dumdedum.  I've been stuffing my face all dayyy.. I miss  Reza . ba da ba bum. I went out yesterday to Gadong. I wanted to watch Day after tomorrow, but it was full. I hung out with  Rez  at West Street Cafe. Just sat there with him and talked for hours. hahaha I don't know what we talked about, but we did :P We had sushi before that with  Hafiz  at Excapade. BEFORE that we were at Takara. So there were like four of us: me,  Rez ,  Hafiz  and  Ping . Hehe eating green tea ice cream.  Rez  and  Ping  had a wasabi fight. lol, man.. it was seriously funny. Hehehehehee talk about 'manly' challenges.. WHATEVER.. lol. Before takara, we were at the food court.. stuffing our faces again. These guys make me eat too much. lol :P   babbyyyyyy i misssss youuuuuuuuuuuu 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
          me,  Randy ,  Aimi  and  Brandon . lol   Okay that's one photo.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      What did I do today? I think I'll just list them out since it's late.  1. I got to see  Reza  today   2. My other  Reza , the guy who is supposedly my best friend in the whole world, is back in Brunei and I got to see him today as well. He cut his hair and we made fun of him while sitting down at the salon.  3. I hung out with a number of my favourite people today, i.e.  Reza ,  Reza ,  Hadi ,  Khalid  and  fatzeem   4. I watched the  Punisher  and I found the part where the bad guy killed his wife funny..ahahah I laughed so hard.  5. I saw a lot of people today.. saw  Chua,  urlLink Hazie  (!!!!!!) Brit, Ummie, Sofian,  urlLink Iggy   and a whole bunch of other  urlLink JIS  people.   6. I ate at excapade, food court, mcdonalds... o_O  7. I didn't go to a single girlie store today.  8. I HAD SO MUCH FUN.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I just got back from school a few hours ago. Sat my OCR Mechanics 1 paper. It was not good. I didn't like it except for the last question, which was the one I thought I'd get stuck on so I revised that one like crazy.. and the other questions turned out to be worse. Sigh, guess today wasn't that much of a perfect day. I was jittery and had pre-exam nerves. It really wasn't my day.  Here's an interesting article: ( urlLink click , courtesy of  Brandon )  Regular sex helps students  A German sociologist Werner Habermehl says regular sex can help university students pass exams and get better grades.  Habermehl from the University of Hamburg said he and his team had tested students before and after sex.  They found that regular sexual activity significantly increased mental capability, but they found celibate students found it harder to make the grade.   As well as decreasing the length of time needed to complete a course, students with a healthy sex life also received better marks, said Habermehl.  The research was carried out together with German research institute GEWIS. *giggle* Sigh, anyway.. I'm currently chatting with  Brandon , we're talking about the mechanics exam.  Rach  is online as well, we're talking about her exam..read the tagboard to get a vague idea how she's feeling. Anyways, I'm going out with  Kaka Fizah  tomorrow to watch Harry Potter and her brothers' might join us, I'm not that sure. I'm meeting up with  Khalid  and maybe  Hadi  before that though. Oh, my best friend's back. YAY  Reza Mustappa  is back. YAY. YAY. YAY. I'm gonna see him on Friday. YAY. YAY. YAY. After one year of not seeing him in the flesh, let's hope he's bulked up ;D ehe mwahs.  missed ya babyjoe. hugs.   I've got a lot on my mind right now. I don't know why I'm hurting so much.. I can't really start pointing fingers. It's just not right. I'm thinking about the promises I've been given by people, most of them have been broken. I guess that's why I don't bring myself to make promises to anyone because I know there will be a point when I can't keep them. Everything feels like a burden right now, my head hurts and I feel like crying. It's not right is it?  I remember dating this guy who used to tell me I was his world. I always wondered if girls actually fell for that line the way I did. I guess I was too guilble to see what was really going on around me because to me, he was my world. As a result of having 'love' blind me, I had everything that had meant  everything  turn around and slap me. Now, eventhough I can say that I have slowly moved on (not fully, but I'm getting there), I know I will always think back every now and then.. because that's part of life.. reliving memories.   I've got beautiful friends. They do mean  something  to me.. and yet, they still cannot see what really goes on in my eyes. I don't really confide in people that much, not even to my closest friends. I find it hard to let people see what happens inside of my morbid thoughts because I don't know how to trust people that much anymore. You see, almost four years ago.. I saw my life shatter in front of me.. I had my heart broken. I know that as of that point in time, I will never trust anyone as much as I used to. blegh.  Geez, I wonder why I'm still up at this time of night. I think I'll go to bed now.. I miss  Ade  and  Rach . I wonder how you girls are doing? Nyah. I wish you would use the commenting system =P I mean, that's what its there for right? hehe hugs. I put it up for  ADE  and the other people who TAGGED and said that I SHOULD put it in. God I miss you two..
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I sat for my AQA business papers about three hours ago. The first paper was at 5:30pm til 6:30pm. I can shamefully say that I messed that paper up, because I took long doing the calculation question.. and somehow didn't get enough time to answer the last two questions. Sigh. It sucks, but hopefully I made up for it in my Unit 2 and Unit 3 papers with the ScrewLoose Ltd case study. I'm listening to  Hoobastank - The Reason . I remember agreeing with  Reza  that this was a great song..and that we both liked the group. I wonder what else we have in common. hehe =)    I'm not a perfect person As many things I wish I didn't do But I continue learning I never meant to do those things to you And so I have to say before I go That I just want you to know   I'm really hungry right now, I don't really know why because I just ate some pieces of bread. I ate up a bag of Lays Salt and Vinegar potato chips during the exam breaks just now with  Kenneth . I've been chatting with  Brandon ,  Khalid  and   urlLink Yazid  . Someone said this to me about 10 minutes ago, it's cheered me up like crazy because I'm feeling a bit depressed with how everything is going on around me: " you know i really love you.. more then most of your crappy boyfriends prolly have XD and if you're still not married in 20 yrs, and neither am i, i'll be hitting on you.. by then, give me a chance yea? XD XD " heheh, only God knows who said that to me..ehe =) I'll give it some thought okay? haha 20 years, fat chance sweetie ;P    I've found a reason for me To change who I used to be A reason to start over new and the reason is you   I wonder if its the same for everyone about the changes in their lives. Here I am, learning and trying not to blame myself about the things that have been happening to me and other people. Here I am, just simply struggling. Here I am, empty and completely apart from the person I'd like to be and who I really am.     I'm sorry that I hurt you It's something I must live with everyday And all the pain I put you through I wish that I could take it all away And be the one who catches all your tears Thats why i need you to hear   I wonder if every teenage girl goes through the various stages of confusion, frustration and anger? Nah, I'm not angry. In many ways, I feel a bit content.. and maybe a little bit frustrated. I feel like crying actually, and I let out a lot of things just now..that I think I mean. No, not think. I know I mean. I'm risking a step, but who cares. I wouldn't do it unless I know it'll benefit me.. In a year's time, I see  us .. happy, sitting down at our favourite cafe, drinking and laughing. So am I wrong to take that risk or even take a chance of being happy again?    I'm not a perfect person I never meant to do those things to you And so I have to say before I go That I just want you to know   I probably don't make any sense right now throughout the whole post.. but never mind, that's one title wasted =P dum de dum.  I miss you baby =D 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      That's true right? I received a testimonial from an old friend of mine. I totally have forgotten about the incident back in form 1 when I touched a tripod stand that had been heated by a burnsen burner. I had three shiney lines on three fingers of my right hand. I looked at my hand this morning and realize that the so-called scars from the burn have faded. I guess memories will eventually be hidden, buried somewhere along with angered thoughts and compleling forgiveness. I wonder how long it'll take me to let go of memories that I've held on to so long.. I guess, in a way, I am taking baby steps.. walking away from it. I guess, somehow, I'll eventually take long strides and simply forget. Right now is not the time for it, it'll come sooner or later.. just not now.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My cousin slept over last night, we went to bed around midnight and were both reading novels before actually drifting off into dreamland. We didn't even talk before going to bed. Haha, but we had nice conversations in the car which was totally cool because I prefer talking outside the house rather than in.     I'm sitting here thinkin' about  How I'm gonna do without  You around in my life  And how am I gon' get by  Ain't got no days, just lonely nights  If you want the truth, well I'm not alright  Feel out of place, and out of time  I think I'm gonna lose my mind    I woke up around eight past, because I could her my cousin's younger brothers screaming downstairs playing with the fooseball table. I have had strange dreams before, and I always take my dreams seriously. I don't really know why but I guess its because at most times, my dreams are like predictions and I have a weird sixth sense. Even though they act like predictions, they don't exactly happen word for word.. but some of the things that happen in my dreams do happen. It's just freakishly weird.     So tell me how you feel (I'm lonely)  Are you for real (so lonely)  Do you still think of me (I think of you)  Baby still (you only)  Do you dream of me at night  (It's like I dream you all the time) so lonely  Oh let me tell you how it feels  (It's like everday I die)  Wish I was dreamin' but it's real  (When I open up my eyes)  Oh let me tell you how it feels  (And don't see your pretty face)  I think that I will never love again   Funny, because I woke up this morning with full of mixed emotions. I feel sad, and yet at the same time I feel relieved. I feel happy and yet, at the same time I'm holding back my tears. I've been going through a lot I'd like to think, and seeing things I didn't wish to see didn't really help me much either.. but in a way, I should have known that things would turn out the way they did. Sometimes I am grateful that they have, but there are times when I'd just curse those people to the other direction of heaven.    I miss your face, I miss your kiss  I even miss the arguments  That we would have from time to time  I miss you standing by my side  I'm dying here, it's clear to see  If there ain't no you, God knows there ain't no me  Don't wanna live, I wanna die  If I can't have you in my life   I am totally head over heels over someone. I'd like to think of it as a good thing, I would say.. but I guess I've got a lot of thinking and re-thinking to do before I do anything that might involve another session of happiness mixed with emotions of sadness and probably sandbags of tears (heh, didn't make sense did it now?) never mind, that's between me and my thoughts. Let's just say that I'm totally happy and I'm grateful that I've met my  someone .   I've got a bruise on my arm. I bruise too easily, I don't know. Blegh, I think it's from an accident I had just now when I accidently banged into  Reza 's watch. Maybe. I met up with  ko Jay  and  Jon  today after not seeing the both of them for maybe over three/four months. I was eating with  Kaka Fizah  when  ko Jay, Jon  and  Rez  came to join out table. =) Ko and Jon went to watch Harry Potter. I watched the movie with my mum and sis on Thursday afternoon, personally.. I think the movie could have been better (i.e. it wasn't all that). Despite the hype that the movie's created, it wasn't as good as the first one or the second one. I lothed both the movies, but I'll say this now: both movies were seriously much much better.   I still haven't seen the   day after tomorrow  movie,  Rez  says it's not that good. Mum and dad loved it :S I don't know. I guess I'll have to find out myself ey. I'm gonna watch Harry Potter again on Thursday cz I'm bringing  Kaka  out. it feels weird typing up kaka..haha because those of you who know me.. I don't have an older sister, a real one for that matter..haha  Kaka Fizah 's my mum's younger sister's daughter. She's the only one I refer to as just 'kaka' where as all my other cousins will have the full uh, name.   I'm online now, chatting with  Reza  from Pakistan and  Hadi . Both are very close to me. ehehe and VERY open to me. haha =)  Tonight and yesterday were confession days..hehe an 'outpour' of emotions right baby? =) I'm thankful though. I miss you like crazyyy though.. 5 days til I see you again =) blegh, so long. miss ya! xoxo.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today was the first day back for all the Year 12's. We're now the 'supposedly' Year 13s. How cool is that. We're like the senior-est students. Anyways, out of the many many students that Key Stage 5 has.. less than twenty Year 12 students came to school today which may have been a great disappointment to the teachers, tutors, head of years and the senior staff. Tsk! lol =) I'm glad I came though, the teachers were like "you did the right thing", and there I was thinking, "why am I even in schooooooooool?" I slept late the night before, probably around midnight and my alarm went off at 5:30am. Sigh, I pressed the snooze button like 3 times to get an extra half hour of sleep.   We applied for  urlLink UCAS  today, it's so cool that it lets us search courses and stuff. I know that I'll definately be doing accountancy and finance in a university in *hopefully* UK, and I'm aiming to get into a uni in London. =) First period was maths, and it's week B. If it were week A, I'd be having TRIPLE study period.. i.e. three free periods (45 mins x 3 = 2 hours and 15 mins of free time) and then I'd be having break.. add another 20 minutes to that..haha niceee =D  Y'know what I did which was weird and out of the world? My business teacher offered to the class to either do the work he just gave out (which included drawing break even charts, reading about sensitivity analysis and etc.) or help him clear out his books and sort out his papers. There were 4 of us in the class, the three girls volenteered to help him with the papers and books.. guess what I did? heheh, clearing out the books and papers meant labour.. sooo.. I did the work he gave out and had more fun doing it :P eheh I love calculations and drawing break even charts, they're so cool. lol =) My tutor was impressed that I did that..haha he told me =P I had a double free period today, right after lunch.. I should have just went home and slept. haha I didn't do anything until school ended except surf around  urlLink Brutalk . Interesting stuff there..  Brandon  was telling me about it and it was my first time visiting the site or even hearing the web address.. I even surfed around the  urlLink  way back machine  .. eheh try typing in UnAngelic. It's so cool,  Brandon  showed me the site ages ago..and it was the most 'romantic' thing I've ever experience..haha especially when you're a web geek like me. lol =)  In todays ever changing world, and fast pace lifestyles..(okay this isn't going to make much sense), have you ever stopped to think if anyone struggles to keep up? Everything is rapidly changing, and I never noticed that there were different groups of teens existing in Brunei. It's ignorant of me, but its true. Teens in Brunei are divided, most of us follow a similar dress code: pair of jeans, t-shirt and a pair of sport shoes.. and that whole outfit would usually consist of at least ONE Nike item. Weird huh? =) Well yeah, that's for me and most of the guys. The girls, it's bootleg jeans, a party-24/7 top and two-three inch heels or platforms. Okay, maybe that's just me being ignorant but honestly, thats how I see things. Anyway, just recently I saw a whole new group emerge.. jeng jeng jeng~ (hums to the Jaws theme song). lol. I saw these bunch of so called punkers around Gadong. I found them quite interesting actually, how they allowed themselves to be set apart from the usual groups you'd see around. Never mind, that whole paragraph is nonsense.   ANYWAY..   I received this offensive email, well..its not offensive directly towards me because it's talking about someone else. It's stupid. I don't like it when people fwd emails, especially about someone local and advertising them like they're pieces of cheap paper. Geez, give people some privacy and respect. I find it offensive because it's about a woman with kids, and its obvious this guy is either an ex-lover or obsesive maniac.. he ought to leave her alone and not make her sound so bad.. agh. He should burn..  I've been getting a lot of headaches lately. The teachers said that we should use these four weeks to unwind from the AS exam stress we had over the month. A lot of people have been telling me that I've gained weight and now I'm just freaking out. I'm paranoid when it comes to my body and my face.. guess I should stop eating so much. Ever since study leave started, I've been stuffing my face non-stop. Thank god school has started so I can control what I eat again.. and now, I don't have basketball until the acedemic year restarts in August.. I don't know about netball, but I'm certainly going to be free from Tuesday to Friday. I think I'll just go to the gym after school with  Hadi  and  Rz  if they want to accompany me..or just go alone. We'll see. I might even go tomorrow.. an hour at the gym would do me so much good. lol =) I wanna learn how to use weights. ehehe
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Why do people always snoop around to find things they  know  they won't like? Blegh.  I haven't posted properly since Thursday morning. I made cookies a few days ago, I must've made at least 8 dozen batches. I gave some to my friends, and I think I enjoy cooking :) Anyways, I was suppose to meet up with my best friend,  Reza  (but we'll call him  rz  to avoid confusion between him and the guy I'm seeing), on Friday.. sadly enough he couldn't make it but I met up with  Hadi ,  Khalid ,  Tubbies ,  Fatzeem  and  Hakim  instead. I think I stayed in Gadong til about half past nine. I met up with my baby before I left..hehe I hadn't seen him for a week.. sigh it sucks cos I only get to see him on weekends because he's staying in Seria on weekdays.   I had a date with  Reza   It's not gonna work baby, you ought to know by now how much I love sushi. heheh :P . Anyways, I watched  the Punisher  with him..hehe  Rz  came with  Hadi  and  fatzeem , but they sat a couple of rows in front of us.  The movie was great, I found it hilarious..hehehe I think I bursted out laughing too loudly. HAHAHAHA but the part where the bad guy killed his wife was seriously funny.. I was the only one who laughed though, I think everyone in the cinema was just to shocked :P  After the movie,  Reza  and I hung out with  Rz  and the guys. We met up with  Khalid  as well, and ate at McDonalds. I had to leave while  rz  was having a haircut. man, it really felt good to see my best friend again =) even though we don't really talk much in front of people..ehe but hey, people don't really know what goes on behind closed doors. xoxo  Today, I met up with  Reza  again in Gadong. No, we didn't stuff our faces..hahaha man, every date I have with him.. we're always eating. =P Yeah anyway, met up with him after lunch.. and me, I'm always hungry so I made him go with me to West Street to get french fries. hehe =) and I had shumai at the food court. So fine, I stuffed my face. He didn't. We had long talks today about how things are..hehe and I'm glad that things have turned out this way. Personally, I'm grateful that I have met him. Sigh =) He's like my twin; attitude wise. Hahaha we have so many common traits, except sometimes I find him weird due to his funny phobias. I think he knows me well enough now since we've been dating for almost two months now. I saw  Himah  and  Ruzanna  at the Mall and McDs. Man, those two..ehehe I miss them tons. It always feels good to see old friends, the ones whos friendship you know will last with you forever. =) They're seriously good friends of mine from my old STPRI and primary school days.   A lot has happened the past few days.  Reza 's back in Seria.. 6 days til I see him again. ehe though right now it feels like forever. I'm gonna meet up with  rz  probably on Wednesday and we might watch a movie at the mall. He's gonna be here for two months or so =) YAY. Hehehe he's got a LOT of explaining to do and we have a LOT of catching up to do because we haven't been talking to each other properly for over a month now because of exams and very busy social lives.. *wink* I think we're gonna watch the Big Nite Out on the 19th of June this week, Too Phat's performing. =)  Anyway, it's late and I have an exam in about 16 hours. eheh so, good night. xoxo.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I don't post on the site for over a week and you complain! lol =) I love you guys too. I just don't feel like posting nowadays because I don't have much to say unless you want to read about me being all giddy and happy again, coz these days.. I AM. Oh yeah,  Adeline  closed down bittersweet. Silly butt. Oh well, she doesn't post much there anyway. Bye Bittersweet. I will miss flooding your tag board  *evil grin* Oh that's a photo of me and  Rach  when she slept over a while ago =P   I typed up my personal statement on Tuesday with intentions of passing it in by Wednesday. Unfortunately for me, I was absent on Wednesday. I've been sick since last weekend (thank you  Aimi  =P) I was too weak to get out of bed on Monday and Tuesday, and my mom decided I was still too sick for school on Wednesday as well. Heh. Mum and dad did, however, take me to the clinic on that very Wednesday. The doctor didn't do anything new, she gave me the usual pills.. Antibiotics, cough and headache pills. Da da da. I had a cold I guess? She didn't really say. Blegh, no one has ANY idea how BORING it is to stay home. The boyfriend ( hahahahaa nada wah baby ), heheh yeah ANYWAY..  Reza  says I'm a geek for loving school. Whateeevveerrr.. The last time I posted was on Tuesday, last week. And I cannot believe how many people msgd me on MSN...hahaha Its like, "yas, you know you haven't posted since Tuesday". Oh yea REALLY? =P   I would have thought that the 15th of June was the day that I'd dread most.. every year. It's been that way for the past two years probably. What sucks is that I can't seem to forget things back then, and right now.. as much as I'd love to deny it, it did hurt.. but not so much because someone I love told me if I want to forget I'm going to have to let go.. and here I am, trying. I'll make it one day I hope. One of these days, there will come a day when the thought of what was then doesn't even cross my mind.. In many ways, time will always heal broken hearts and memories will be long forgotten. Maybe not today, tomorrow, next week or even next month.. one day.  I went to the Too Phat concert on Saturday night. I met up with  Rz  there because  Reza  didn't want to go with me. Blegh. Anyways, I hung out with  Rz  and a bunch of our other friends. We got to sit in the front because the security didn't do any checks so we just walked in and sat in the second front row seats. Goddammn. The concert didn't meet my expectations, I'm just glad that half way during the concert,  Reza  decided to come along.. hehe =D so yeah, I sat in between my two Rezas. hahaha =D  Rz  got to perform on stage with Reshmanu (sp?), that was the first time I've seen him on stage despite having listened to all his mp3 songs.. I didn't go to his first ever performance because … I don't remember and he still has grudges about it. ehe =) but I'm proud of him. I stayed home the whole Saturday morning and afternoon, didn't really do much except hung out with  Reza  and made brownies. We watched  Sgt. Bilko  on Cinemax. Haha it was hilarious.   In Business Studies, we're covering Unit 4 of the AQA course which meant we were studying Accountancy and Finance in a deeper perspective. Guess what?  Yasmin  doesn't have to listen. Do you know why? Because we're learning about basic accounting.. pssh, so year 10 stuff. Haha Sigh, I guess it just puts me in the advance level of the class. So, when I was absent during the three days.. my teacher said I picked the best time to be absent because I didn't miss a thing.  I found out that I'm going to have two accounting teachers next year. The usual one and (hums Jaws theme song), my business teacher. Goddamn. That's going to mean I might end up seeing my business teacher TWICE in a day. Oh my god. I guess I don't mind that much because he is a very cool Australian teacher.. hahaha he's funny >.  I went over to the best friend ( lol, wassup   babyjoe  ;D),  Rz 's crib on Wednesday. I just finished seeing the doctor and decided to pay him a visit because HE'S ALWAYS ALWAYS unavailable to me. Hmpfz. ehehe I texted him and he said that I should come over in about an hour and a half..haha guess who managed to shorten that to 15 mintues? ;D ehehe Anyways, I made him sick..haha he's coughing and he has the same symptoms as I did, do.. never mind, I'm still sick.   I saw  Rz  again on Thursday, and on Friday. We watched Honey yesterday at the mall with little  Wafi ,  Irwan  and this other guy..haha I don't remember his name because I didn't talk to him at all cz he's shyyyy.. I see a lot of people hanging around Gadong nowadays..  macam inda balik rumah saja .. hahaha lol, yea whatever yas, look who's talking =P   Today, I hung out with  Reza   layan  me when I wanted to eat.. God, he's evil. He's MEAN.. but I'm dating him. hehehe =) I love you xoxo. I went out with mumsy early this morning after we dropped off my  urlLink  sister   and  Karen  in Gadong. She bought me make up! hehehe =D Yeah I'm having a seriously good weekend. Speaking of  Karen , she's been sleeping over since I don't know. lol, plus mum doesn't seem to mind. And I like her around. =)  Oh yeah, I got to clear this up.. I'm YARZ..not Yasz. Yasz is a rapper from Singapore who used to (still does?) live in Brunei. hehehe please straighten that out.. I don't rap and I don't do music beats ;D  Kwang kwaaannngg.. HOLIDAYS ARE IN TWO WEEKS!  baby  finishes his attachment next week, then I'm going to see his face every day (or so he claims =P I bet you can't do it!!) for TWO months.  I love you  =) Anyways, it's late.. and tomorrow's a SUNDAY and I have to wake up early because mum wants me to make her biscuits in the morningggg..
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It really sucks when you're just sitting there, watching as things happen and moments that just pass you by. It's amazing how you can just hold on to something and not let go for such a long time that you begin to feel sore just holding on it.. how you're able to struggle&nbsp;to hold on to&nbsp;something your not even sure that you still believe in anymore.   Why is it that a person is able to just hold everything in and not allow their feelings to let loose for all to know? How can a person survive just watching the person they love destroy themselves because they asked them to? How is it that you can love someone and never let them know? How is it that a person can just hide behind the truth and allow for mistakes to happen and not retrack them? Wouldn't that just lead to a bigger mess? Man, I've screwed up so badly that I don't know what to make of it anymore.   I've watch so many things happen for the past month. I have allowed so many things to happen. I haven't done anything about how I've been feeling. It stupid really, I feel so stupid.   
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A month of not posting, wow that's a record..hehe It's been a while, I suppose since I've posted.. and I guess it's my own fault to an extent and there's also the fact that I don't have  urlLink internet  at  urlLink home  because of techincal problems with my  urlLink computer  and the espeed2 modem. The  urlLink wireless  around the  urlLink house  still hasn't been set up so I can create layouts with much creativity.. or with much enthusiasm because the pc doesn't even have  urlLink adobe   urlLink photoshop  :S I seriously do not like working or creating things on other pcs.. I'd much rather do my work on angel13.   Anyway, I've editted the post settings to only one post because I don't want to read the things I've typed up previously. I guess I was being very bitter about my break up and just can't bring myself to type up any posts or comments about how my life is doing now.   So, if anyone's wondering.. I'm doing alright. I'm not bitter anymore and things will turn out okay eventually. A lot has happened over the month, as I've always said in my lack of updates. A lot of messy things have happened in my life, some of which as lead me and some  urlLink friends  thinking that I have screwed up very badly. BUT I'm trying to forget that and let go of difficulties I'm facing because I don't want to get my heart broken again because of stupid decision and unavoidable thoughts. The problem is that I did something stupid, which could have been avoidable but I allowed it to happen. And now that it has, there's no turning back.. and I suppose I have to live in my life with that, but I don't know if I regret it or not.. or that I should.    urlLink Moving  on. I've been out and about in Gadong, a hell lot.. I should start avoiding that place. Haha, but most of the  urlLink time  I'm meeting up with different  urlLink people .  aQilah 's back in Brunei til January so I should expect to be spending a lot of  urlLink time  with her while she's here :)  Lina , however had to go back to Geneva, Switzerland for the attachment course of some sort. My best"guy"friend,  Rz , is leaving to Pakistan today. It sucks, because I was really hoping he'd stay.  I've been plaing  urlLink basketball  a lot.. heh. I'm in the 4v4 JIS group that's competing. Anyways, my  urlLink car  is here. I'm going  urlLink home  now. hehe I'll try post again soon.. xoxox     
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       It's weird when you just have a sudden burst of wanting to cry. Well, maybe not sudden.. let's just say unexpected. What is there to do when you hear someone say really hurtful words to you? Here I am, taking deep breaths as I go along and taking in the pain very slowly. I know sometimes words just slip away and at times people can be uncomforting and very blunt. They wouldn't really know what they've said.. or they don't realize that it actually hurts. I wonder if I should just carry on as if nothing's wrong.
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I unagree says:  WHAT'S HAPPENING ON AUGUST 19TH!???  I unagree says:  EVERYONE SHOUT!  I unagree says:  EXAM RESULTS!!!   heh, leave it up to  BRANDON  to do that. Geez.   My turn.   EXAM RESULTS COMING OUT IN LESS THAN TWO WEEKS or um, 13 days. Good luck to the AS/A level students. Best of luck to the I/GCSE students whose results come out a week after that.   xoxo. 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      That's what I keep telling  Eng Hock . Damn, I guess I won't be getting ANY good things because I'm so damn impatient. It's either that or someone seriously messed up that quote. Well, I'm finally home after not coming back at all yesterday. I think I've already mentioned the fact that I slept over at   urlLink Adeline  's and well, mum seems to know whatever the hell I've been up to because she reads this site.  I took a cam shot just now, I've nothing better to do. I just had my dinner and I'm stuffed. I feel bloated, or maybe that's just me. Sigh. I feel depressed and I don't really know why. I think I'm addicted to online pool, haha not think, I KNOW I'm addicted. I've been playing it every chance I get.     
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm at  urlLink Adeline 's house again. I slept over last night.. ehe  urlLink Rachael  slept over as well.. smelly butt. I quote from her, "we slept and woke up at the same time  for once ". hahaha Usually, I'm the early one up, however .. after last nights excitement, I couldn't fall asleep until 4am. We just woke up about an hour ago and now she's watching some tv show on the chinese  urlLink Astro  package.   Anyways, I watched  the Prince & Me  last night with some friends. I can tell you now, the movie wasn't as good as I expected or maybe I just expected too highly of it..but over all, the movie sucked. lol Sorry, but I didn't like it. The actress was lovely as always of course, but the whole idea of the movie was the part I didn't like. After that we had dinner at Gadong properties. Then to Arena where we played pool til midnight or something.   Oh yeah, I watched  House of Flying Daggers  earlier in the afternoon with Pheng Seng and Clement. We managed to sneak drinks in in our huge PE bags..haha I didn't understand a word because it was Asian Chinese dialect. So weird man. But yeah, the translations helped a bit I guess. Anyhoots, that movie sucked too. haha  Bin  and I both agree that the ending sucked. Shall I spoil it for you? :P BLEGH. The movies nowadays are too overated and they never come out as well as the hype makes it seems. Sheesh.   I made a new friend online last week, his name is  Arvin . But we'll call him  Bin  because he's cool. lol I met him on Yahoo! Pool and we've been playing online pool a lot..hehe he's from Singapore in some sort of poly.  Okay, I'm hungry so I'll post later when I get home.  much love, yazarunie. 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       So I didn't post yesterday, whoops. I woke up late, around 10-ish or something like that.. I went downstairs and caught "A Walk to Remember" on HBO. I think I've seen it at least 5 times even though each and everytime I watch it, tears would never fail to fall. I guess the whole movie is touching, about perfect love and stuff..haha figments of impossiblility maybe. Sigh
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      All I can do right now is be helpless and unmoving because, what can I do? I think I've listened to about three people tonight, talking to me about their problems. I feel useless when I don't know or cannot do anything to help them. I love my friends y'know? More than anything in the world, they have no idea how special they actually are to me. In many ways, I suppose I'm to blame.  I know that my friends have been accusing me of being distant. I'm sorry if you feel that way, I do sometimes regret it.. but please understand that when I keep something away from you, it doesn't mean I don't care because it's probably just nothing or something in intentions of protecting you, and never never hurting you. I might be living a life full of regrets and unsatisfaction, but I'm grateful that I have wonderful people in my life to keep my spirits high and bring light into my life. And I hope that never changes.  Sitting here in my room can sometimes feel lonely and even at times, dejected. I am in many ways, unhappy with myself and no matter how hard I try to be, it just doesn't seem to work out. There are days when I do feel that the whole world has turned its back against me (no, I haven't turned my back on it either), and there are times when I just feel like breaking down and crying my heart out. And yet, what is there to cry about? Nothing. Nothing because nothing means anything to me anymore. So what's the point in wanting to cry? I have no reason to cry..  And if I should not have a reason to cry, why am I so down? Why do I feel like I am placed at the bottom of the shelf? Why do I feel lower than dirt? Sometimes thoughts and old memories can bring a person down, they can take you a walk down memory lane and at times, they can even make you tearfully remember the have-had's and could-have's. Shaddup lah.  Maybe I'm just upset, perhaps slightly off my rocker. I'm just very ticked off right now and I can't think of a reason why. I want my friends to know that I am still there for them, anytime and always. I just wish I could have someone I could turn to as well. I don't know, maybe I'm not looking hard enough, maybe the person's just too in front of me that I can't see.  I'm not asking anyone to ignore this post because I know I sure won't. I guess I just have too many things floating through my mind that I have had a lot to think about and I wish people would just stop trying to drag me back into my state of depression because for once, I would seriously like a day when no one yellls at me or pisses me off.. I would, with all my heart, want a day where I can be completely happy with the people I love.  Ah hell, what do I know?  Regards, yas.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      me :) hehe I just finished taking a shower. I was at the MD indoor gym the whole afternoon from 3pm til 8pm. We went against St. Andrews girls basketball team just now, and guess what? :) We won!! :D :D :D :D :D :D yeah, lol. 16 - 8. Two losses and one win, and one more match to go against STPRI. I'm just praying that we'll win the next game as well.   urlLink Adeline  ,  Zara ,   urlLink Michelle  ,  Aimi ,  Eileen ,  Nicole  and  Yvonne  all played great today.  I woke up at 9:30am today actually, then I fooled around at angel13 for a bit before going back to bed.   urlLink Adeline   says I'm noisy when I wake up because I drop everything..and haha yeah, she's right. I'm noisy when I wake up, even when I try not to be o:)  I'm chatting with  Hiang ,  Leslie ,  Rachael  and  Sal  now on messenger. I'm bored. So so bored. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       The girls and I slept at 4am in the morning..but I woke up at 9:30am cos  Eddie  just texted me. It's his birthday today .. hehe so..  
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Ello. I'm at home now.   urlLink Adeline  ,   urlLink Michelle   and  Aimi  are sleeping over tonight. We just got back from having dinner at Mamih, which cost us all about $9, including  Eddie . Which to me, felt damn cheap because usually when I eat somewhere my meals about $6 per person lol :) so a table of 5 people totalling to $9 is damn cheap. Hehe 
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       It's so frigging hot today. Then again it might be because my air conditioners off.. I don't feel like turning it on, just the ceiling fan. My Kazaa program sucks, either that or I don't know how to download mp3s anymore. I haven't downloaded anything since November last year when I was still living in Gadong and living off the normal espeed. I'm happy now though since I'm able to use the espeed2 modem on angel13 :) it's mucho easier for me anyways.
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Currently chatting away with  Hadi  and  Nicole . I can't believe that I just woke up at this hour.. its noon already. Haha not bad ey. I had an interesting night, hehe went to Gadong after staying home the whole day with only a tensy bit of whining. My sister was suppose to come home at three, but she ended up arriving back at 4:30pm which pissed the hell out of me that I said I didn't want to go out anymore because it was already late and I wouldn't be able to see  Adeline  anyway because if I left the house it'd take half an hour to get anywhere and she had church at 5:30pm. So there was no point..  Anyway, there I was.. staying home like a good girl. Being a lazy bum as always, I could hear my mum calling out my name every ten minutes to help her move furniture. Geez, my mum just can't leave well enough alone. Once she starts rearranging something, may it be just CD stacks, she'd end up rearranging the whole living room.. and she did just that yesterday. I'd call her crazy, but she's my mum.. a serious perfectionist. I ended up carrying and pushing tables and sofas all over the living room. lol. My favourite sofas are now on the north side in front of the stairs.. the blue sofa is now next to the huge window and the big curtains. She even carried out my sofa bed to put downstairs! Now my room looks a bit more bare than usual that I can see the stacks of teddy bears I had hidden behind the sofa bed. Ah well, I guess I'm going to have to find a new spot for them.  I should seriously start arranging my room and my clothes. I don't have a closet yet since the house is still new and mum hasn't gotten round to ordering any so my clothes are hung on these umm.. whatchumacall it.. haha i duno, metal bars that have wheels at the bottom. I've got three of them in here so its like a walk in closet without doors. Other than that, I've got four big containers full of my junk. On the carpet, I have another pile of teddy bears and stuffed toys near the window. Next to my bed is a drawer table and next to it is a pile of Archie comics and other books along with my bags and purses. Sure, I have a bookcase..but I've got everything in it but books. haha I've got pictures, food, make up, letters,  barbie dolls  :P  Its the same story with my pc table, angel13's motherboard is on the floor while the espeed2 modem is right next to the monitor along with Ms582 speakers which suck big time. The webcam is put down randomly depending on my mood on wanting to webcam or not..most of the time it's just facing me. I've got stacks of paper on this table, along with text books, more stuffed toys, earrings, the house phone, letters and cards..hehe just a lot of junk I don't bother clearing up or cleaning.  The only time I stay in my room nowadays is just to use the computer, sleep or take a shower. That's pretty much it. When it comes to homework, I usually do it downstairs at my kitchen table so that mum thinks I'm studying in my 'free time' when I'm actually just doing my homework..ehe  ma, you didn't see this  ;P       That's a photo of me with  Adeline  a few nights ago when we went to JP with  Rachael . I think we went on Wednesday, the night I slept over. We left around 7:30pm and met up with  Eddie . I made three new friends of  Eng Hock  that night, but I don't remember their names. Haha :P Whoops.       The JIS basketball team..haha Back row:  Eileen ,  Nicole  and  Adeline . Front row:  Michelle ,  Maria ,  Aimi  and me :D  Anyways, I went out last night to Gadong. I had to pick up a few things before meeting up with some friends. While waiting for them to arrive, I went to coffee zone and sat with  urlLink  Deez   and   urlLink Wafi  . They were going to watch AF on Astro..hehe they're  Bob 's supporters.. :) I don't know who I like, but it sure was a hell shocker when I found out  Linda 's out of AF. Ah well, I like  Adam  and  Kaer  more anyways..hahaha I met up with  Leslie ,  Alex  and  Lit  last night, we went to play pool at Riggs.  Hafiz  and  Zaza  joined us for a bit, made silly jokes and comments that I couldn't stop laughing..hahaha its hilarious how they can sound serious yet funny at the same time. lol :)  The layout isn't my handy work.. I just took one of the blogger templates and modified it a bit.. I'm going to change the header soon but I haven't found time to. I can't seem to be able to open my Adobe image ready or even my Adobe photo shop :( so I can't make any images right now. So annoying. I'll get it fixed soon I hope. I'll come up with a layout soon I guess, I had one in my sister's PC. I've deleted all the layouts I've made on angel13 and I just finished deleting over 50mp3s along with a huge number of documents..heheh I deleted tons of pictures on my pc. I'm not worried about it though because most of the photos I have are saved on my site's server. Hehehe, yup that's right..make use of my unlimited webspace and bandwidth :) abuse it!! haha  
     

    
</post>


<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        guess who'se back. back from thailand. Oh, Thailand so smelly.  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        dum dee dum.. hehe so tired.. just came home from Empire.. went swimming right after tuition.. had a big big headache just now.. but its all okay now hehe.. din go gdg cos i wanna go next week so yeah.. today's fine except for de fact dat i got  sunburnt .. i wus only in de water for like around 2 hours only den i got sunburnt.. ceh i no likes it..  i woke up around 8 this morning.. so early yes? Hahaha had tuition la.. im now at my cousin's place.. there's noone except for my baby cousin.. everyone's gone out.. sniffs.. but yeah i'd rather stay at home cos im so fcuking tired.. nyeh~ and yeah..  simmie 's back from miri! miss dat doot so much.. im having a lil flu and fever now.. maybe cos i went in hot and cold water just now.. went into de jacuzzi den went into de pool den de jacuzzi again.. mixture of hot and cold.. =S im so sleepy.. ill end my blog here.. my arms r aching.. tata!  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        dum dee dum.. hehe just came back from de mall a while ago.. just jalaned jalaned mostly.. saw lots of ppl la.. lazy to mention.. hehehe woke up around 1 just now and  simmie  msged dat he wus gonna go miri.. miss  you  so freaking much! i went to tuition first just now.. haha wus a good girl.. had so much laughs wid  chia . got so carried away dat we din know we had to copy some stuffs on de board.  oops~  then  jordan, marvin, jasper and kylie  waited me outside aplus and we walked to de mall.. jordan wus walking in de middle of de road as if it belongs to his father's ahahaha..  we waited der for  sim . went to pizza hut to makan after dat.. wus SO hungry cos i din eat my dinner hehe.. i went to get some patchi again! weeee.. bought onli a 100g dis time.. nyeh.. yeah we went to kokoberry go get de drink dat i like..  nyehehe.. simmie jez msged~ wee..  goina gdg tomoro wid  chia  again.. hafta haf lunch before tuition.. probably meeting up wid  Fiz .. long time no see that pokleng liao.. we're gona go get patchi yah? hahaha laps u kacheng.. gonna go empire after tuition tomoro.. probably gonna sleepover or something hehe.. hope it'll be fun cos i miss simmie like a badass now.. i wanna swim! i wanna get into a jacuzzi! hahaha nyeh.. just had to get dat out.. bah ill end my blog here.. TATA~  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        happy 7th month-sary  FEL  and  CLINT ! Happy 1st month-sary to  simmie  and  I !    
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        TITZ! you didnt tell me that you were going Thailand ah! i saw the blog i also blur2. u faster faster come back i wanna chat with the  small children  hahaha. woke up 8 in the morning just now. had tuition again.  my pc screen just changed colour? =S  came back around 10.15 then went gadong again at around 12.  chia  was supposed to accompany me jalan but noooooo! she put me aeroplane. *sniffs* had to be alone for like one and a half hour?  senz  accompanied me for like half an hour. he said he was gonna be there at around 1? ended up he went there around 1.30. i went to patchi just now. bought a box of 200grams chocolate. didnt really eat, i onli took around 3 pieces? got a pair of earrings for  chia  too. saw  clinton  while he was on his way up and i was gonna go down haha. then.. yeah hehe  simmie and soon  came around 2 liddat. met up with them and then went to  coffee zone   to makan. i only took some chips and simmie didnt wanna gib me his drink! so jahat. nyeh =P did nothing much la. just walked around the mall and i really wanted to sleep in the lobby at centrepoint. i was so so so tired. reached home at around 5. and here i am blogging while chatting with  kylie, erika and betty . i think i'll end my blog here la. and i miss  simmie . bah ciao!  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Hi. I'm bored. Hi Gladys. I'm going to Thailand tomorrow. I don't wanna go. I think its smelly. Anyway, I'm not going to be blogging until next week.. I think I'm typing like a retard. My brother is an ass. Thank you  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        im sleepy! hahaha woke up at around 8.30 in de morning jez now. had tuition. no i didnt want to but i  HAD  to. went to gadong at umm.. 11.45. had to wait  Chia  for  20 fucking minutes . and i was so HUNGRY! haha had a bad tummy ache and gastric this morning plus my flu and a bit of fever. we makaned with her family and her aunt drove us to de mall. was walking around until i asked  Chia  to msg  Simmie  then we saw him walking with  Melvin . saved her 10 cents hahaha. We went to err..  blue mountains?  to makan.  Chia  and i had our laughs there. shtoopit man. i think there's gonna be a wedding party or what there cos there were decorations around haha. i wanted to go get some patchi chocolate but i didnt. ceh. im craving for some chocolates now! im now chatting with  Betty, Clinton, Titz and Vk . nothing much to do really. jez finished watching chucky. HAHA man it sucked. i used to like it when i was a bit younger? =P bah gotta go now. so sleepy. CIAO! oh and yeah, i like simmie's perfume! bah im off.    
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        HEHE just came back from a movie. went to empire to watch chronicles of riddick. was okay though. woke up at around 11 a.m just now. was late? haha then yeah. did everything and went to empire around 1.15? EH noone was there yet. had to wait for like 15 minutes. saw  clint, fel, vee  and  fiz  outside then baru i went out. then we had to talk all the way to jasper's room. IT SUCKS! so hot! HAHAHA chun's gonna say me this and that again if i complain some more.  played some ps2 games la in the room. so bored. and i was so hungry! first one to get the nugget xP.. then we went down to swim. it went all good leaving out chun-and-william-wanted-to-throw-me-into-the-water part. haiyo~ my contacts spoilt everything. had to take off and put on jasper's googles for like a few times. and my elbow is luka and i dont know how i got it. haha was so freaking cold when clint, fel and i wanted to go up the room after swimming. had a good time swimming with vee. kesian her she had to pull me here and there cos i couldnt reach the ground? HEHE  went home around 5.30 la. walked with  sally  and  amilyn  to the hotel lobby there. and  fcuk  i left my cap in jasper's room. reached home then bathed then slept for like an hour or something then had to go empire to catch a movie. i almost fell asleep during the movie. opps~ bah i gotta go. so tired! tata..   
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Boo just came back from Zaza. Went to get my haircut. Ahh it sucks. I no like it cos it sucks. Did nothing much la these few days.   Rita, Jacin   and  Nigel  came over to my place yesterday. Played ps2. Kicked their asses in this game HAHA. Nyeh.. Im so bored and I've got nothing to do. Chat till like crazy last night with  Titz . Tonight again have to be online at the right time. Shtoopit my computer's so laggy. It always says this and that is not responding. Haha this is gonna be a short blog cos Ive to go play some bball. Ciao!    
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Yay! The layout is out. It's so nice. Just wanna say thanks to  ADE . Actually NO. I don't want to thank her. SHE CLOSE DOWN BITTERSWEET. haha. But that's ok. Anyway, she helped me do most of the codings cause I don't know how to use tables. Only CSS but thats ok. Oh yea, I did the picture. haha. Well, I just cut the background out and my sis helped me with the effects and everything.  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Okay, I made this layout for my brother and it took me almost about 6 hours to just code this because there were so many errors. I know it might not be as great but at least it's good enough right? :) Anyways, enjoy the layout everyone and I do accept your opinions. If its bad, try and keep it to yourself alright?    
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Hey ho~ Hehe just finished my shower. And Im hungry now. School was alright, cos today's the last day of school? HAHA we din really study though. Just playde around and stuffs. P.e was great! Got to catch up wid Ellia quite a lot. Hehe played basketball for like half an hour. GOD it was HOT! But I was always under the shade HAHAHA. Dont wanna get dark no more. Oh and right, yesterday went gadong. It was quite early la, met up with  Chia  in aplus. Then her parents drove us to the mall to have lunch after her tuition. I din really eat la, just took bits of  Chia's  food hehe. Then we went around the mall. Went to  Patchis  and got some chocolate. YUM~ there was this computer exhibition, umm Concepts isit? Then yeah, jalaned around till around 1. Met quite a few ppl there la.  Simmie   and  Soon  came around 1? HAHAHA it was funny la. Chia was the umm.. spy or something? lazy to mention what happened la. We went rigs to play some pool. Chia and I din play though. Just sat down there and talktalktalk. Had to go tuition then. HEHEHEHE went home around um 3.45 got home then SLEPT. Cos I had to wake up around 8 in the morning. hell tired. Goina mall tonite for movies probably. Hehe gotta go now. CIAO~    
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Wee~ Im blogging now~ Has been quite a while since I last blogged. HEHE thanks Titz. Umm.. First time blogging here so dont know what to say loh. HEHE I'll blog tomorrow though. NITE!  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         diiiinnnggg doooonnngggg    "Attention. Attention. My fellow bloggers and readers, it has come to my knowledge that this site needs some Gucci. And to satisfy your needs, I present you with the one, the only GLADYS GUCCI"    *applause   ________________________   
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
          I'm not a perfect person There's many things I wish I didn't do But I continue learning I never meant to do those things to you And so I have to say before I go That I just want you to know    Ah that song. I remember  Dana  askin me to listen to it a few months ago. Yea, its a great song. :P    I've found a reason for me To change who I used to be A reason to start over new and the reason is you    Just came back from school. They had the  Battle of the Bands . It was kinda nice but I don't know why I didn't have as much fun as I thought I would have. :S Stoopit me.    I'm sorry that I hurt you It's something I must live with everyday And all the pain I put you through I wish that I could take it all away And be the one who catches all your tears Thats why i need you to hear     Rita  and  Grace  were there too. hehe.   urlLink Wei Chun  's group so funny. Too bad he didnt win.    I've found a reason for me To change who I used to be A reason to start over new and the reason is You    Just wanna say congratulations to  XGS ,  Pinheads  and  Masturbator  ??  for winning.    I'm not a perfect person I never meant to do those things to you And so I have to say before I go That I just want you to know    Tomorrow is the start of the  holidays . IM SO DAMN HAPPY. I don't think we will have classes tomorrow. I still wanna go school tomorrow though. bleh~ Stoopit no ?    I've found a reason for me To change who I used to be A reason to start over new and the reason is you    Oh and I wanna say good luck to  Mel  later with her running. hehe.    I've found a reason to show A side of me you didn't know A reason for all that I do And the reason is you    Well thats all. See ya.  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        OmG. U know wat ?!     urlLink BITTERSWEET   IS    CLOSING   DOWN      After four years, they're closing down. WHY CLOSE ?!!! It's like been part of almost everyone. GRRR. ADE DALENG!!! DUN CLOSE BAH!!!  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        I'm in such a bad mood today. I hate it. I hate today. I just hate it when a nobody is trying a somebody. I've been in SGS since pra-sekolah. I actually liked it then but I'm starting to hate it this year. I'm not saying the school sucks. I'm just saying the community that makes the school sucks. I'm not saying anyone in particular but everyone is just following what the other person does. It just gets on my nerves. There's this particular person who really steps it. Shit. I hate him. No, it's not Binoy.   Gosh and there's Miss Bheng. What the hell is her problem ?!! When I steped in the class, she was already looking at me like shit. Askin me to wait outside until she finished her "speech". watever man. Calling me a bad influenece in front of my face. Sheesh. If I was a bad influence, why make me the freakin monitor ?! And what's with her accent ? Bloody wannabe British.   And somebody in my class, it doesn't mean you're get good grades and is good in sports, that you can boss people around. sheesh. And those wannabe some rap stars girlfriend. WTH ?!! And that group, sing sing sing only, your voice so horrible still wanna sing. Think you're one of the originals but you are  NOT . And what's with the cock touching and the alubas. crap man. and the Muhammad Ali teacher is so biased. I got a reason why. I'm not gonna tell it here cause someone might snich on me here.  I just wanna shout out loud man. I should put a password on this site so I can say what I wanna say. Don't hate me because you  THINK  its you.  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
          Are      you      retarded ?    Gosh. This is the question I really wanna ask Bloddy Binoy. Today is the worst day of my life man and its all because of him. Shit. Hate him so much. I wanna go poke his little retarded eyes out. I know Im being really mean but wat the hell, he's not reading this. Heck, I don't even think he knows how to use a computer.  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Testing my tittiez. 1,2,3.  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        HEY!! I CAN BLOG!! My espeed at ome is so screwd. When I'm using, the connection was broken. Then when my sis use, the connection is like so erfect and fast. Shit ah Anyways my inspiration to blog. I actually wanted to blog a really long blog yesterday. But crap the connection. anyways, piss it lah. HI BI. GROTESQUE AND FLABBERGASTED. HAHAHA. OMG.  Yea. New layout. the pic from MUARA. HAHAH. STOOPIT. NEVER knew muara can be so beautiful. =) Have to make another layout for my sister later. She was telling me, make it in frames. What is frames ? I dunno. Im so stupid. =(  It's exactly one week to my birthday. =( Hate my birthdays. Makes me feel so... crap.  Me, Ade and Fiz has a song. Me and Ade are lead singers and Fiz is the background singer.  Titz - Listen Fiz - doooddaaaddooo Ade - Do you want to know a secret Fiz - dooodaaadooo Titz - Do you promise not to tell Fiz - OOOoooHHHoohhh Ade - Closer.. Fiz - doodaaddoo Titz - Let me wisper in your ears. Fiz - Oohhhaahhhohhh Ade - Say the words you love to heaaarr.. Titz - I'm in love with you. Fiz - OOHHOOOUUUUOHHH OHHH  Ain't it nice.  Let me tell you a convo between me and a really close friend. We shall put her as Female  Female - Titz! I miss her. Can't wait for her to come back. Shit. I think I'm lesbian. Titz - Wth?! Wat? You get horny when you think of her? Female - Yeap. (With a face like this ---> =D) Titz - How bout your bf? Female - Dump him lah.  Everyone has hate blogs now. I want one too. I have loads of shit to get out.   Dear you,   I hate you. Never liked you. Hate everything about yourself. Your voice, your singing, your wannabe atitude, your ohsofake accent and mostly your face. =) Your popularity never ceases to amaze me. Its a no wonder why everyone hates you. All because you are so fake. You want to be a crazy child, hunnie you don't know the meaning of crazy. *im so perasaan now* Yea. Bet you think its you right. Because it is you. I know you come here everytime but you just never tag. Oh and please do stop singing. It really is horrible. And you  are  really fake.     I just came back from my aunt's birthday party. I watched AF. Its really fun.  GOOD FOR YOUR SOUL.  The host really loves to keep people in suspense.   Well thats all. Remember my birthday. =)   
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
            Someone accidently/purposely sent me something today. =) Me being a busy body, obviously opened it. It's the image on top. Funny rite. I think thats going to be my new nick. "_titz' // a kiss from me is like heaven to you" I can see it now. I'm so bored. I want to get my OWN table for the gala night so I can invite my friends to sit with me =( I don't wanna to sit at the table that was booked. Anyways, I watched White Chicks today. Well, half of it that is. Will watch the rest tonight. AFTER I do my work. I'm a good boy now for your information. I think I will sleep now.&nbsp; =) Gooch Day to you and you and youuuu.     
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Saturday night I went out ninja-ing. Shit So dayme scary. So many calls were made. I have no more credit. Yea. Went ninja-ing then was too freaked out then went to Sie's house. Slept there. Slepth about 1 to 2. In between there. I was high on JILA. HAHAHA. Yea. On saturday I went to church in the morning. After that I went home. Then I went to my aunties house for this reneunion for the X-SGS people. I saw some of their OLD photoes. When there was no colour. I saw Teacher Mary, Florence and other teachers. Woah. They looked different. After that I went to Serasa beach with Ade, Fiz & co. I WENT CANOO-ING. HAHA. SO DAYME FUN. I WANNA GO THERE AGAIN. HAHA. After that I came home. Got changed. Lay on the bed fo' a while. Then fell asleep. Then went to school. SCHOOL ROCKS!!!. AHAHAHA. School is now the most fun place to be. :)  Do you guys realise that my posts are getting shorter ? :)  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Hi friends. Hows you ?  Yea. As you can see. It's a new layout. Dun diss it k. :) Made in a hour but  the about me part took another hour. It's postal service cause every other theme was taken. Anyway, thxs friends.  Today. I woke up at around 9.30. Then bathed, changed and brush up. Then I went to Miri. Then first we went to the contact lens shop. I got 3 differrent colours. I can now say that I have all contact lens colours in the list. Then we went to get stuff. Then went to eat. Then get some pics. Then get the glases and then we went home. :) Now I'm here. Tonight I'm going to Gadong to watch I-robot. :) Bye fren.  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        I LOVE SCHOOL TODAY!!! NO BINOY. NO MD ALI. I had so much laughter with Vero. HAHA. OMG. SO FUNNY.   p.s my bd in 2 weeks and 2 dayz. whee~    
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         The best day of my life. Feel so colourful   Saturday was the funniest day of my life. And the funniest. It all began after church. Rachael came to church with me. Wow. You should have seen her hair. PINK. My goodness. I was like "What happened to your hair?!" when she came to my house before church. But that's not the funny part. Yea, after church we were telling jokes in the car. I don't think she can tell jokes very well. Not good. INDIAN AIR. haha. Then droped her off at Kuilap.   Then I went to Gadong. I msged Fiz she asked me to go to the old coffee bean. And I was at McD. Lucky not that far. So yea anyway, I think i had a stalker. Shit man. I was at the dark alleyway. then the dustbin fell and made like a weird sound and then I got a miss call from someone I don't even know. Then when I reached the place. Fiz, Clinton, Watson, Larrie, Jasper and Chun were there already. When I came, Clinton said "Ey, Motorcycle boy". Ahaha. Oh. There's a story behind that name. Then I ordered fries. Everyone else food came earlier. Then I'm like how long does it take to make fries ? Then I said to the waitress "Um, Can you check my fries?" Then Wei Chun started laughing. Shit. Not that funny la. Fiz, Serves her rite. Hahah. Remember. Then my fries came and everyone was already done eating. celaka. Then I asked for sauce like very rude. haha. I'm so spoiled. After&nbsp;that we went to the mall, met up with Ade, Rach, Eddie his friends. then more people come. whee~ Vk, Ronald, Raynal, Heng Lee and the rest came. So we were basically there for a while, talking to everyone we met. So cool. Like just talkt o anyone who passes you. Then we the original people we came with, went to Rigs. I didn't play tho. Just kacau. On the way to rigs, Fiz was telling me the she was afraid to walk in the dark parts cause she got stalked and molested once. I was laughing my arse off. But I'm nice. Chun is such a pokleng. "Yo wazzap my nigga". Yea, in Rigs Fiz was telling me that we need to meet Joo. So when Vanessa came in I asked her. So off we went to find him. We were searching for him for abou 30 minutes. On the way, we saw Siew and both of us were like "omg" after she want to follow. So we quick walk. past them. shuushh. In searching, both of us really needed to pee. I went to Centerpoint to pee. Babes didn't want to pee cause she was scared. Ahaha. Then, we went to the mall and met up with Ade they all. We jalan jalan for a while. Then we went outside. The Vanessa, Joo, Randy, Natasha and all the F5 people came. Then after that Wei Chun came. So it's the big group thing going on again. We were outside for awhile making few calls. Then we went we went in. Now most of us has already left. So it was Fiz, Joo, Chun, Eddie, Ade and me. We were outside of the ticket booth. Laughing our arses off. I tell you. Not like your ordinary laugh. This laugh was like hurt your stomach but you cant stop. We kept laughin for like ages. Shit. The whole mall could hear us. But what we laugh about was a secret.  Flat arse and big mouth.  AHAHA. OMG. HUGE MOUTH. =O. That was me and Chun's funniest moments. AHHA. Then we went to the food court which was completely empty. Cool. I think we were the only few people in the mall. Then our last minute decision. We went to watch movie. We got tickets from Carrie. In CINEMA 4 . Shit. Fiz scared the shit out of me. That was the cinema with the ghostt. OoOoo~ In the cinema, me and Chun were shouting. ahaha. Funny arse. Since we were the only 2 who watched it already, we laughed at the known funny parts. AhAH. After the movie, when we were going down, at the main entrace there was this shop rite. So many manicans. We looked at them rite. Then Chun BoO'ed me. Scared the shit out of me. Ahaha. So i ran out of the mall like in a rush. Freak. Then Chee Ming, Jin Ping and William came to pick Chun up. they waited for us to go home first. Nice rite. So yea. Came back bout 3. Forgot the rest. Go to   urlLink  here   ,   urlLink  here   &nbsp;and   urlLink  here   &nbsp;for the rest. ahaha. Ciouz.   NIGGA PLEAZE      
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
          Im tugging at my hair    Im pulling at my clothes    Im trying to keep my coolI know it shows    I  m staring at my feet    My cheeks are turning red    Im searching for the words inside my head     &nbsp;   Im feeling nervous    Trying to be so perfect    Cause I know youre worth it    Youre worth it    Yeah     &nbsp;   If I could say what I want to say    Id say I wanna blow you... away    Be with you every night    Am I squeezing you too tight    If I could say what I want to see    I want to see you go down    On one knee    Marry me today    Yes, Im wishing my life away    With these things Ill never say     &nbsp;   It dont do me any good    Its just a waste of time    What use is it to you    Whats on my mind    If aint coming out    Were not going anywhere    So why cant I just tell you that I care     &nbsp;   Im feeling nervous  Trying to be so perfect  Cause I know youâ€™re worth it  Youâ€™re worth it  Yeah     &nbsp;   If I could say what I want to say  Id say I wanna blow you... away  Be with you every night  Am I squeezing you too tight  If I could say what I want to see  I want to see you go down  On one knee  Marry me today  Yes, Im wishing my life away  With these things Ill never say     &nbsp;   Whats wrong with my song    These words keep slipping away    I stutter, I stumble    Like Ive got nothing to say     &nbsp;   Im feeling nervous    Trying to be so perfect    Cause I know youre worth it    Youâ€™re worth it    Yeah     &nbsp;   Yes Im wishing my life away with these things Ill never say    If I could say what I want to say    Id say I wanna blow you...away    Be with you every night    Am I squeezing you too tight    If I could say what I want to see    I want to see you go down    On one kneeMarry me today    Yes, Im wishing my life away    With these things Ill never say    These things Ill never say       Wheee~ I like that song you know. Obviously you know cause I posted it up. Anywayz, yesterday was joke day in my calender. I love joke day. You wanna hear some ? I know you do and you know you do.  &nbsp;  1. My  twin  forgot my birthday.  &nbsp;  2. One day, a man walks up to a woman and tells her that her hair smells nice. The woman immediatly goes to her boss and tells him that she wants to open a sexual assault case and explains.  &nbsp;  The boss, puzzled "What's wrong with a co-worker telling you that your hair smells nice?"  The woman"He's a  dwarf !"  &nbsp;  3.One day, a boy ask his dad "Daddy, what's a transversite?"  Daddy "Ask your mother.  He  will know."  &nbsp;  4. If physics know all the winning lottery numbers, Why are they still working ?  &nbsp;  5. One day a bangladeshi man, call his boss  &nbsp;   bangla man &nbsp;: Boss, I can't go to work today. I am very sick.    &nbsp;   boss  : Oh ok. Sure. Let me tell you something. When I am sick I usually have sex with my wife. Go do that and I'll call you back tomorrow.    &nbsp;   bangla man  : Ok sure.  &nbsp;  Next day.  &nbsp;   Boss  : How are feeling ? Did you do what I told you ?  &nbsp;   Bangla man  : Yes, I'm feeling very much better. Oh and  nice house  by the way.  &nbsp;  6.&nbsp;2 women are dicussing about their husbands.  &nbsp;   1st women  : my husband is cheating on me. I found a condom in his wallet. In my anger I poked it full of holes with my sewing needle.  &nbsp;  The second woman fainted.  &nbsp;  7. Micheal Jackson, Bill Clinton and Nelson Mandela were on a plane with 20 children. the plane suffers an irriparable failure and is doomed to crash. As they came to realise there were only 20 parachutes.  &nbsp;  Nelson Mendela : We should let the children have it.  &nbsp;  Bill Clinton shouts in anger while showing the middle finger: SCREW THE CHILDREN!  &nbsp;  Micheal Jackson : Do we have time ?  &nbsp;  8.  FUCK . the word that explains everything. Pain, Pleasure, hate and love. The same word that can cover all.  &nbsp;  Transitive verb = Tom fucked Betty  Intransitive verb = Betty was fucked by Tom  Active verb = Tom really givs a fuck  Passion verb = Betty really gives a fuck  Noun = Betty is a fine fuck  Adjective = Betty is a fucking beautiful  &nbsp;  Emotion...  &nbsp;  Aggresion = fuck you  Confusion = What the fuck ?  Despair = Fucked again  Difficulty = What the fuck is this ?  Dismay = Fuck it  Displeasure = What the fuck is going on ?  Fraud = I got fucked by my insurance agent  Incompetence = All fucked up  Pssive = Fuck me  Rebellion = Fuck off  Surprise = Fucking incredible  &nbsp;  To tell...  &nbsp;  Time = It's fucking five thirty  Business = How did he get that fucking job?  Prediction = Oh, will I get fucked  Maternal connection =&nbsp;You motherfucker  Political = Fuck Bush  &nbsp;  It can be used to enchace a word  &nbsp;  beauti-fucking-ful, ter-fucking-ful  &nbsp;  Tell someone fuck you today.  But not your mother  &nbsp;  9. A woman annouces to her best friend that she is getting married the 4th wedding.  &nbsp;  Best friend : What happened to your first husband?  Woman : He ate poisonous mushrooms and died.  Best friend : Oh my. And your second husband ?  Woman : He ate poisonous mushrooms and died too.  Best friend : Oh my goodness. Your 3rd husband ?  Woman : He died of a broken neck  Best friend : A broken neck?  Woman : He wouldn't&nbsp;eta the mushrooms.  &nbsp;  10. Before and After falling in love.  &nbsp;  Before - Passion  After - Ration  &nbsp;  Before - Dont stop  After Dont start  &nbsp;  Before - Turbo thrust  After - Jump start  &nbsp;  Before - Twice a night  After - Twice a month  &nbsp;  Before - She takes my breath away  After - I'm suffocating  &nbsp;  Before&nbsp;- Once upon a time  After - The end  &nbsp;  If you don't get the jokes, just tag and I'll explain to you.   
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
            there was only 10 people REALLY online without aways and busys. grrr. WHERE EVERYONE ?!      
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        happy birthday sultan. Just came back from gadong. Went with the usual people. so yea. i didn't see anyone i noe. which is like so sad. anyway,  first we went to eat at west street. talk. laugh. be manja. after that we went to eat again at kyros kebab. yes. we like food. then went to eat again at Dq. then went back. i used the motorcycle. saw clinton going back. then came back. then blogging now. my sad little life.  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Went to gadong last Saturday. My god. So empty. Ahaha. My sis was tellin me about the "sex and the beach" drink she drank at chills. I only drank "bloody beach". It's not the best drink. I'm gonna try the sex thing soon. So yea. At Gadong, empty. Went at bout 11.30. Met with my sis. She went with "her" friends. Yea. Me and Han went around the food court. He hasnt seen the mall in like 5 months since he came back from Australia. Yea. Joo is back too. whheee~ Yea. Nothin much to say bout gadong that saturday night. came back bout 2 in the morning. We all slept in the same room cause Han slept over. We were makin stupid jokes. "You want some Prawns ?", "You just realised you ass was yellow?" HAAHAH. SO FUNNY. Didnt sleep at all cause laughing too much. So cool to see a sunrise. Like noone else is awake but you. So peaceful. Then went to somewhere near Gadong for breakfast. The lunch 10 minutes after breakfast. So hungry. Spent the whole Sunday "workin" in Gadong. Then went to the airport for dinner. Came back bout 9. Nothin to do there. Now online. Bah, here's the pictures.        Me and my sis at the airport. stupid pic.        We were bored in the plane so we compared your eyes. Mine nicer rite. Greennn..        At Fuji. The Japanese restaurent.        Ahaha. Stupid random thing. Linkin park was in Bangkok too. :P         On the huge chair in the giant house thing.        In the boat thing. It's like bumper cars on water. And the boat thing has a motor. So cool. So fast too.        In snow city. So cold. The giant snow man was so cool.           Another snow man picture. Just closer and my eyes were closed.           At the ginger bread house thing in snow city. It was fun in snow city.  Throwing snowballs and stuff.           Our swimming pool at Pattaya resort. So cool. The hotel had it's own  amusement park and a monorail. Like Jerudong park at the back of the hotel. It was so huge man. All the pics of the pool and stuff were taken from the SO BLODDY high restaurant. We were on the 60th floor. Scared me man. Then we went to the roof of that building which was 4 more floors up. So windy up there. You could see everything. So nice.    &nbsp;        Another angle of the pool. The rollercoaster and part of the giant drop is  there too.   On our last night in Pattaya. We went to the gay show. Seriously. They looked  like real girls but they were guys. The pics here. ALL of them are guys ok.         &nbsp;
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Trace!!~~ OMG. Guess wat. I just went into my mum's toilet. And guess wat I found.   SHUREI   AHAHAHA.OMG. SO FUNNY. NOW I WE ALL CAN HAVE AMOLANG HAIR. WHEEE~~  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        I'm going to be nice to everyone today because I'm gonna be in a bad mood tomorrow. Tomorrow is open day. My parents are going to meet my teachers. I'm so damn scared. Miss Bheng didn't give our whole class our report books back. Maybe she wants to see all our parents. I think I will get bombed tomorrow. Tonight I will lecture my parents about tomorrow.  Anywayz, today I didn't shout at anyone. I didn't scold anyone. I'm nice. I think I'm in the mood to create a new layout.  Well, Gladys leave this site already. I'm gonna find a new blogging partner. I don't like blogging alone.  Oh Shit. I just remembered. Binoy wants to see my parents.  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        If you like ghost stories or horror stories, and supernatural themes the visit this  urlLink website . You can even submit your own horror and ghost stories or even your own personal experience with ghosts or the supernatural beings. Read the terms and conditions before you attempt to submit stories, your own comics and your own old folk legends.   Thank you from The Terror Of Horrors Site creator and management,  Lee .  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Eh celaka. Give up on the pictures. Don't want to post up anymore. You know I tried 7 photo hosting thing. Shit man. All cannot work. Fark. Ahaha.  Shit. Jia Wen going to Malaysia for 2 bloddy years. Shit. Will miss her. Will go out as much with her as her mother allows. :P  Anywayz, just came back from Gadong. After church. AHAHAHA. There's was a little kid in church. SO NAUGHTY AH HIM. He climbed the chair and tried to do a somersault. HAHAHA. He landed on his face. I laugh so suddenly until my nose came out with all the gross stuff. AHAHA.   So happy. When I went to school the other day, everyone was like "OMG TITZ IS BACK!!!" "TITZ I MISSED YOU!!!". Not meaning to brag lah. Just telling. Well, I got kisses and hugs though.  Some people ahr. Just dont get them. You are standing right in front of them and they go "Eh where's titz ?" So irritationg ah. Then I will be like "U ass, I right here."  In the afternoon, Eddie came over. Then me an my sis, waxed part of his legs. So there is like a big rectangle on his leg now. HAHAHA. SO FUNNY. There's this hairless part on his legs. Then Yasmin called. We went to pick her up in Gadong cause she had a bit of a problem. We are such nice people. Dont YOU agree ? AHAHAH. In the car, we were trying to cheer her up. So me and my sis told the lamest jokes ever. My joke was the funniest. nyeh~ Ok. Listen up. I'm gonna tell it to you.   [titz]  Ok yas, we prepared this to cheer you up.   "One day the was an aeroplane which needed to get higher in the air as possible, if not, it will hit a mountain. They needed to throw something out. What did they throw out ?  A PIANO   WTH ?! I also don't know why the answer was a piano.   continuation    "There was a postman. He is VERY VERY healthy. He cycles to work everyday. One day, he just dies. OK. Keep in mind that he is VERY healthy.  Most of you will think he got hit by a car of something. But NO. He died because  the piano fell on him . HAHAHAHAHHA. OMG. I almost peed on my pants. Don't know why im telling you this but yea.   [yas]  AHAHAHAHA. OMG. FUCK YOU MAN. AHAHAHAHA. Chi Bai u guys. Love u so much. (while laughing her head off and smiling AND shakin my shoulder like mad)  Anywayz, I went to Gadong with  Fiz   the other day. Met up with  **GLADYS!!!,  * *SIMIIEE!!!.  And their friends. Sorry. Don't know your names. They were walkin to A plus. Then  Vero  msg-ed my handphone. Told me to go to the mall. Celaka. I'm like at Aplus there. And have to walk to Mall. So dayme far. But then they were worth it. LOVE YA GUYS. Then at the mall  Vero and Jin Ping was there. We all walk walk around. AHAHA. I remember Jia Wen and me chatting the night before. About wearing sexy clothes. Then she DID wear sexy clothes in Gadong. Got like low back and eerrr.. Aiyah. It's just nice ok.   Saw  Grace . She like to touch me ahr. I don't know why.  then go McD. Sit for a while. Go Jaya. Me and Jia Wen saying Jaya is the place where you go with like your mum and stuff. And why were we there ? HAHAHAH. Shit ah. Dana stood me up. She say she go. But never go. PUKI. aHAhA. Then we went to the mall again like sad lifeless people. AHAHA. Go round and round. Then Jin Pin go get chocolates, and we went to McD again. Then Fakhri came. aHAHA. So funny. He shake my hand. Dunno why. Then Racheal came. AHAHA. I WAVE TO HER. SHE DONT RECOGNIZED ME CAUSE I WORE A CAP. AHAHA. SO FUNNY. I'm gonna shout her name next time. There was somany more people. I noe there were. But I was sleeping. Then went home. VOMITED AT HOME MAN. SHIT. Gosh, I love my bean-bag chair. Can't live without it.  Anywayz,  back to Gadong. Well, after church. Went to my grandmother's house. Then Yasmin picked me up. Went to escapade for dinner. Me, Eddie, Ade and Yasmin eating loads of sushi and stuff. Remember the sushi sandwhich.  Randy, Julian, Natasha, Vanessa  and  Shawn  were there too. Then me and Yasmin left. Went to get her  tampons . Then went to coffee bean, she introduced me to a new friend. Hi fren. HAHAHA. Then Ade miss called. Met up with her and left Yasmin. AHAHA. DITCHED HER. Then we went to the mall. On the way, met with Carrie watch out eddie . Yea. Jalan everywhere. Shit. So late noww. tired. But will continue. The saw  The Blendursh , Oh yea. Before I forget.  TRACIE. HAHAHA. SO EMBARrASED. I SAW U JUST NOW. Bye Mocha . Then had to go back. Ade lah. She has to wake up early. Got the Nbt treasure hunt thing. My mummy going to Singapore tomorrow again.  Bah. Go now lah. Byez.  p.s. Briget Jones' diary is nice.  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Im going to blog a pre-birthday blog. Tomorrow is my birthday. And I just wanna thank everyone who wished me happy birthday before hand. Muah. Love you guys to bits.   
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Hey. Sorry for the lack of blogging. Well, many things have happened. Just now me fiz and yan had a very REFRESHING conversation. bitching about people, even our closest friends. our life. Jonan punked me. shit man. grr. my parents left for paris today for a month. free. im going to be good and obey the rules. yea, tomorrow is yo kwong hui's birthday. and the day after tomorrow is mine. =) I think there is going to be school. crap. wanted to stay in and sleep. i think im going to watch tv now. UNVIRGIN. HAHAHA.   
    
    
</post>


</Blog>