<Blog>

<date>25,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      http://sugarnet.webmediastrategy.net/mesmus/artisti/elisa/video/heavenisdn.wmv  Elisa - Heaven Out Of Hell  Intro e versi: C#- A E B  chorus: E B C#- A  Testo:  So are you turning around your mind Do you think the sun won't shine this time Are you breathing only half of the air Are you giving only half of a chance Don't you wanna shake because you love Cry because you care Feel 'cause you're alive Sleep because you're tired Shake because you love Cry because you care feel 'cause you're alive Make heaven Heaven out of hell now Make heaven Heaven out of hell now Are you locked up in you counting the days Oh how long until you have your freedom Your freedom Just shake because you love Cry because you care Feel 'cause you're alive Sleep because you're tired Shake because you love Bleed 'cause you got hurt Die because you lived Make heaven Heaven out of hell now i want you to Make heaven Heaven out of hell now Are you still turning around the same things Are you still trying that way Are you still praying the same prayers Are you still waiting for that same day to come Climbing the same mountain You're not getting higher You're running after yourself Can't let go Hiding in that place you don't wanna be You push happiness so far away But it comes back To give you all that you've given before To love you the way that you do, like a mirror Look in the air 'n catch that boomerang Can't fall anywhere else but in your own hand  Make heaven Heaven out of hell now Make heaven Heaven out of hell now ... Make heaven Heaven out of hell now Make heaven Heaven out of hell now are you still waiting Make heaven Heaven out of hell now are you still praying Make heaven Heaven out of hell now are you still losing Make heaven Heaven out of hell now Make heaven Heaven out of hell now i wanna fly because i dream
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hi! this is my cool radio. it&#39;s my only real friend. im going to dedicate my life to music and animation. im just here to say that im shutting down my site due to reasons that i have become too exposing of my personal life onto the net... the net is a very big and unlimited space. it is it&#39;s own world. i dont want anyone to know about my personal life... im going to enter the film industry and something like this could either ruin me or make me successful. im not willing to risk all that information. sorry you guys.. thankyou for understanding...&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>




<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       
    
</post>


</Blog>