<Blog>


<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Eight and a half hours, at a laundromat. Gah, ah well, it was better than washing tents. I got caught in this flash rain. it was raining on one side of the street, but not the other. it was crazy. Meh. I'm kinda tired. I'll find something cool to write about later. Until next time.
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Gah, working sucks. The 'rents go out on vacation staring wednesday. Wednesday to next Wednesday. Who wants to do something? I got a surprise raise at work. I make 7.25 now. Meh. Doesn't make it any less sucky. The acoustic version of Pardon Me owns all of you. I wish I could have some drama to bitch about, but, I'm pretty sure I don't have any. Stupid summer, you take all the fun out of it. I keep thinking about Andrea. I just really want to talk to her again. It hurts. There's nothing I can do, but...it doesn't make it any less painful. My Mom is going on some OCD cleaning phase. I try to hide. Out of sight, out of mind, so I don't have to help. Anyway, I should get back to...whatever it is I do. Later.
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Overthinking, overanalyzing. I hate it all.
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      How come no one tells me what the hell is going on? I'm so confused, just freakin' tell me. I need a nap.
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ahh, life is starting to get to me again. With Andrea's death, Ashley and I haven't really talked in a few days, and work just SUCKS. ahhhhh....  Andrea's memorial was today. That was hard. It made me realize just how much we really lost touch. I didn't know 3/4ths of the people there. But, they only knew her for the last 8 months. She changed a lot though. I'm gonna miss her.  twenty bucks says she doesn't call tonight. she never does anymore. maybe I'm just worrying and being stupid. I haven't seen her in so long. ahhh.  until next time...
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The memorial service is Monday at 6pm. That's going to be hard.   Okay, I guess I should probably stop talking about it. In lighter news, I got a GMAIL account. Thanks Google! Heh.  I'm also planning a trip to Texas, maybe end of July-ish. I'll let everyone know how that turns out.  I'll write more later.
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Brand New really helps out a lot. And I'd like to thank my friends for all of their support. I'm not really sure what to say anymore. I just felt like making an entry.
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've felt no emotion. I'm speechless. But, if I could do it differently, I don't think I would.
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      R.I.P. Andrea Deller
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Ashley's blog  is better than mine. 
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I forgot. I dyed my hair black just cause I'm sweet like that. I'll put pictures of it up here soon. I'm at work right now, slackin' off. I wanna go work at harbor center. It looks really sweet. Anyway, I need to get me one of the license janks. Yeah, it'd be really helpful right about 'naw. I'd better get back to work before I get busted. Later.
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Me, defined by the stars and the chinese.  Libra (Sep 23 - Oct 22) - An air sign represented by the scales, Libra symbolizes balance, order and justice. Librans are diplomatic, easy-going, social people who always promote good will and friendship. They're also more artistic than people of any other sign. Some less appealing traits include indecision and self-indulgence.  Tigers are sensitive and emotional deep thinkers who are capable of great love. They also have tendency to be short-tempered and rebellious, and sometimes clash with authority figures. Tigers are most compatible with Horses, Dragons and Dogs.  Is it really sad that I agree with most of this?
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, Ashley and I are dating again. 3rd time's a charm? Haha. Anyway, its probably going to work this time. Things just seem different, in a good way. And, work sucks ass. And I've got lots of plans with Ashley over the next two weeks ;-). Oh yes. Hahaha. Yeah, I'm just in a pretty good mood. But yeah, I just wanted to update this shiz. Not that anyone reads it. 
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Someone make me some breakfast... please?
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've seen what happens, to the wicked and proud, when they decide to try to take on the throne for the crown.  bwahahahahahaha.
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You just gotta believe. You have to have faith. (not that whole, God crap, that's BS, this is something else.) This entry seems wack, cause it is. It's just a reminder to me, and everyone else. Party on party people.
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      That whole, getting off at noonish thing? Yeah, didn't happen. Try 4.30, didn't get home till 5. Dead tired. My boss worked me like a dog, and then, I had to mow the lawn. I was so pissed. Now, I have to clean my room. AHH! Anyway, I'm gonna try to take a nap. Maybe watch that bootleg DVD of fahrenheit 9/11, gotta check the quality. Gatorade is teh rox0rz.
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I finally convinced my Step-Dad to buy a new computer. Took him six years though. damn. He finally started bitchin about how long it took him to open up Outlook. Oh well. Ryan got the POS comp now. Anywho, Nothing else is really happenin' socially. Groundation is teh suck. Next Sunday biatches. Oh yeah, its HOT AS HELL! Tomorrow is supposed to be even worse. I'll probably get off work at noonish. That'd kick ass. I'm tired and hungry. But, in a good mood. Heh. I think I'm going to sleep now. Meh.
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok, this is going to get into some weird stuff right about now. Time is predetermined. You can freely move along the fourth dimension as you could any of the other three. Time is an axis, a way to map a point. Therefor it should be predetermined just like any other axis. Therefor, in theory, you should be able to freely move along it. However, we will never master time travel. This is proven by, "the reason we know time travel is not possible, is because we have never been visited by someone from the future." I know I haven't really explained it in full, but Joe and I debate it like crazy. That's just my opinion on time and time travel.  Chaos Theory: I agree with Chaos Theory, because it's been mathmatically proven, (google it yourself), and it just makes logical sense. Boo-yah. However, you shouldn't associate chaos theory and time travel, seeing as how time travel, is not possible, making the Chaos Theory effects nil. You should associate it with just regular life. The butterfly effect (the quote, not the movie) explains it all.
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got to thinking today, after watching Butterfly effect, about journals. (Yes, I have an opinion on Chaos Theory and time travel, but that's another post.) I never kept a journal. This was probably a mistake on my part, seeing as how journals not only are gateways into the past, but also guides into the future. Writing down your thoughts about a particular subject, or your feelings about something that happend, is a huge outlet, and also allows reflection on a later date. So, I guess in keeping with the digital age, I'll just keep this online journal.
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was so freakin' awesome.
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's four o'clock in the AM, and I'm crazy hungry. This is the latest I've stayed up in a long time. The best part about the weekends is not having to wake up in the mornings. My boss at work is totally sweet. He's an older version of me. I think I'm hella sweet. I got off work at one in the PM today. Kern wasn't answering his damn phone, so I talked to this dude I knew from tech. He came two hours late, and Kern was on his way by that time. Stupid...rides. That reminds me, I need to get a car and license. Stupid parents.   This journal is weird...it's becoming everything I didn't want it to become; me just talking about how my day was. I wanted it to be creative, deep, insightful, and interesting. It seems I failed on all of those levels.  Well, I'm starting to see spots, so I'd better wrap this up. Gah... I should learn to write better, and stuff.
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Right now, as I'm writing this, I'm sitting on top of a big truck, (the kind we deliver huge tents in, fairly big) getting a nice tan, stuck on the hampton bridge. Apparently, a car caught fire in the tunnel, and ruined some stuff, so, we're here for a while. I've already been here a good hour and a half. (I'm posting this from my sidekick.) It's nice though. Cloudless sky, good breeze, we are right on the water after all. Gettin' a tan, and gettin' paid. This is the life. I wish I had a camera on me. 
    
</post>


</Blog>