<Blog>


<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Amazon.com: Books: The Bachelor List   In his grief at the loss of his wife, Lord Duncan made a poor investment and lost his fortune, leaving his daughters to find a way to make ends meet and support their aristocratic lifestyle. In a show of turn of the century girl power his daughters start charging for the newspaper they took over upon the death of their mother. They also initiate a fee for service matchmaking enterprise. To add a twist the Duncan sisters must keep their venture and identities secret from all but the housekeeper, the butler and his sister. In this fist episode all seams to be going well until Constance, the oldest and card caring suffragist, attracts attention to their newspaper, The Mayfair Lady, with her political articles. Along with this attention came Max Ensenor, an up-and-coming member of parliament. Fireworks ensue as Constance and Max battle it out politically and romantically.  I found the relationship between Constance and Max a little forced. They story did not carry it along in a natural progression they way one might hope.  I was enjoying the book none the less when a certain scene caught my attention. It was a sex scene involving a condom. Now I am all for safer sex, but I thought it was ridiculous for it to be mentioned in a book set in 1906. I was sure this was blatant historical inaccuracy, so, librarian that I am, I looked it up. According to Encyclopedia Britannica, condoms have been used for contraception since the 17th century. At that time, most were made of animal intestine or fish membrane. By 1840 they were made of vulcanized rubber and in 1930 of latex.	 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      
       
    
    
</post>


<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ok this is just a test post, i don't really know what I am doing here. I just wanted to see how this thing works
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      what do you mean you can't display my blog 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I made a couple changes, just want to see them 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My automatic deposit goes in at midnight. Its barely 8am and  already trying to figure out how to spend all my money. I got the trial versions of Microsoft money for PC and Ultrasoft money for my palm. I filled out all the little budget information and they claim I should have plenty of extra cash floating around. It will be interesting to see How much I really spend. I know that I don't have any extra cash, So it must be going somewhere. My next big expense is going to be a car with air conditioning. Of course I want a newer car, so its going to cost me.   I had a program last night at the library. It was about the titanic. I died, not me personally, but my character. A sixteen year old servant. It was quite sad my body was never recovered. The Program was alright, I always wish I was better prepared for them though. Well anyway.   Big news in Big Willie (President Clinton) is going to be releasing an autobiography. He isn't finished with it yet but it is set to be released in June or July (I know it started with a J) the moved the release up because he didn't want to steal Kerry's thunder toward the end of the presidential campaign. It is good to know you can plan on adding Clinton to your summer reading list, it should be informative to say the least.  The bookworm       
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I can't say that I have been to busy to write. I could say it but it would be a big lie. I have been up to some things. Mostly work. The big news on that front is that I finally got my own computer, and I have a folding table to put it on. I have worked their for nearly a year. I guess it is kind of my anniversary present from the library. I was most suprised when I started the computer and everything seemed functional. I have heard horror stories about the computer people only installing part of the program, some times they come back and sometimes they just don't see why you need to so something like, run a report to see if any of the books have gone out. Anyway I am happy about the computer.   I am a Palm pilot maniac. I love the silly gadget. I got the programs I use installed on the computer at work with no problem. I seem to be syncing just fine. My latest exploit in palm land has been trying to find a financial tracer software that I like. I used a program on my palm that suited me just fine. The only problem was that it didn't have a PC component so I had to do every thing on my palm. I started looking around and I decided I'd give Microsoft money a shot. There is a program that syncs automatically with it, I think Money is a little much, It does way more than I need it too but I'll give it a shot see if I can get used to it.  Be sides that I have been working on my websight, and this blog. Although it obviously hasn't been writing in it. I keep changing the colors and I'm very slow at it. I'm not good enough at reading the code to know what I'm changing precisely. I still haven't figured out how to change the color of the sub title. And I haven't added the links yet. But I'll get around to it soon.   My parent are coming to visit. It will be the first time they have come since the wedding 3 years ago. We have been running around trying to get everything cleaned up. So far we haven't done a good job.  The writing is going nowhere. I haven't done a damn thing on the book. I guess procrastination is part of the deal.   Love, Luck, and Lollipops   The bookworm 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I changed the title of the blog but it didn't actually change yet, so I am hoping that if I post someting new it will change
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yesterday I attended my state library conference. I did find one session interesting. I was on blogging. I was so excited to go as I am a new blogger myself. The session was mostly about how to use blogging in libraries. This could be for internal or external communication. The presenter said that is is the best way to put library websight content into the hands of the librarians, imagine that. There were several librarians from my library system there and we were all pretty excited about the idea. Now we just need to get the ball rolling so to speak. I also went to a rather boring presentation with an interesting topic. It was about librarians going international to help developing countries or places with poor literacy. Of course we need to do that right here in our own country as well. There are areas that have poor literacy or lack technology or the means to use it right here in the US of A. But I liked the idea of library missions just the same. Although I doubt I will be rushing off to Nigeria anytime soon.   On a personal note I am planning a garage sale this weekend. I've never had a garage sale before so this may be a traumatic experience for me. My husband teaches on Saturday mornings so I will be all by my lonesome for the first part. I hope I don't get robbed or anything.   I am hoping to set up a couple other blogs and get my websight up and running soon. So I hope to see you all soon.    The bookworm 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Lunchtime report   I spent the morning reading book reviews. This morning it was Library Journal. It is sort of a tedious task when you are reading about books that aren't  your style, but things perk up a little when you run across titles that sound good on a personal level. I'll share this mornings findings with you.   Elsa Watson is giving us her take on Robin Hood in  Maid Marian , which was (or will be) released this month. Watson tells the story from the point of view of, yes you've got it, Maid Marian. When the story begins we find 17 year old Marian and orphan and a widow. Her situation is worsened by Queen Eleanor of Aquiaine who cheats Marian of her dowry, and then forces her to marry her brother-in-law. But the queen's plan is thwarted when Robin Hood safes Marion from a loveless marriage and takes her in to Sherwood forest, where she set about trying to find justice.   Sarah Mason is bring us  Playing James  in June. This book features Holly Colshannon, the new crime reporter for the Bristol Gazette. She as been given the task of following Detective James Sabine around for the next few weeks. James is reluctant to say the least and now must try to solve a string of burglaries in the company of accident prone Holly and her Flamboyant Photographer. Of course we all know that James will fall for the  lovely Holly and we will have to wait until June to discover the out come of that.   Kris Webb and Kathy Wilson's  From here to Maternity  is due in May. Sophie is a single lady on the business fast track when she gets knocked up by her long time boyfriend. Problem is boyfriend does not long for fatherhood and quits the scene. So Sophie and her best friend Debbie plot to find a way to take the best care of baby than involves a new business venture. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      New Author, New diet (well, kinda)  Here I am Librarian and want-a-be author. Oh no wait, I am an author. All the books tell me to refer to myself as an author, even though I haven't published a darn thing.   Thought to self: I am an author, I am an author.   I am writing a romance novel. I'm hoping to be more humorous and less heaving bosoms and throbbing pythons of love. I have the first scene written. I want to have the book ready to submit by June 15th. This is approaching quickly but there is a competition I want to enter. That means I need to finish my rough draft by the end of April and then I can revise thought May. That is the plan anyway.   What else should I rant about. Well I am dieting, and like many others across America I am "doing Atkins." I did it last year, but fell off the wagon. Now I am starting again and dragging my husband along with me. He is the one after all the leads me to temptation.   It is only 8:40 and already I have fertilized and seeded the front and side yards of the house. Done my morning 12 minute on the elliptical machine showered dressed and had some breakfast. I feel very accomplished. Of course I am tying this with a big blue towel on my head and I need to be at work in 18 min. So I had better cut off here and g    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am very excited about the new templates. I kept trying to change mine into something I liked better, but I couldn't manage it. Although it is not perfect, I like these much better. I have managed to get a couple of links in to my book reviews page. I also managed to post a book review to this blog (see below) so if you like this you will want to check out bookworm reviews for more in the future.   On a personal note, another change. My husbands job position has been eliminated. He worked as a help desk specialist for a company that provides service and software to a certain industry. They eliminated 3 help desk positions and 2 programming positions. I don't know how they will continue to manage. Luckily the company is going to help us manage by providing 5 weeks of salary compensation. We will just hope that Hubby will find a new source of income by then.   Climate changes. It has been hotter, will at least more humid, than hell here. The air conditioner broke down Thursday night. We had a tough day yesterday. We thought it would be a good time to take in a movie. You know its always cold at the movies. Luckily the repair guy came today and fixed us all up for only $180. It could be worse considering the entire unemployed husband thing. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Amazon.com: Books: The Bachelor List  In his grief at the loss of his wife, Lord Duncan made a poor investment and lost his fortune, leaving his daughters to find a way to make ends meet and support their aristocratic lifestyle. In a show of turn of the century girl power his daughters start charging for the newspaper they took over upon the death of their mother. They also initiate a fee for service matchmaking enterprise. To add a twist the Duncan sisters must keep their venture and identities secret from all but the housekeeper, the butler and his sister. In this fist episode all seams to be going well until Constance, the oldest and card caring suffragist, attracts attention to their newspaper, The Mayfair Lady, with her political articles. Along with this attention came Max Ensenor, an up-and-coming member of parliament. Fireworks ensue as Constance and Max battle it out politically and romantically.  I found the relationship between Constance and Max a little forced. They story did not carry it along in a natural progression they way one might hope.  I was enjoying the book none the less when a certain scene caught my attention. It was a sex scene involving a condom. Now I am all for safer sex, but I thought it was ridiculous for it to be mentioned in a book set in 1906. I was sure this was blatant historical inaccuracy, so, librarian that I am, I looked it up. According to Encyclopedia Britannica, condoms have been used for contraception since the 17th century. At that time, most were made of animal intestine or fish membrane. By 1840 they were made of vulcanized rubber and in 1930 of latex.	  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I went to my offt officaial graduation this last weekend. It was great. I never marced for my undergrad so I felt doubly excited about this one. Ok so I had to listen to a bunch of speaches and I didn't even get my diploma. but it felt good to put on the rob and march with the people I'd gone to classes it. It really was an experiance I'm glad I didn't do with out. My parents came to visit everything went great. The house was reasonably clean, I made good food, Dad played handyman and Mom did a lot of ironing. I was really kind of lonely after they left, but i'm hoping that I'll work a little more seriously on my book now. i don't think mom knows I'm planning to write. But whe did mention the note card thorey. Have all the steps planned out just like you would a research paper, this way you won't miss an important step in the plot. Of course I continue to read, and analyze what I read. I'm sure there is nothing that is a perfect book. I'm sure i'll always find falt with something. I am doing my best to learn form the faults I find in others. I am discoving what is important to me in a book. I have found that the character really has to show me who she is evovle and change in a way that makes sence. I want to see the cause and effect of growth of the character, If I don't get this than I'm not very satisfied with the book. I enjoy humor in a book as will. so to recap in my book there will be cause and effect of character growth and humor.   Tootles
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok, I'm at work and I'm board. I start my vacation in 1hour and 26 minutes. So, I have decided to write my next blog entry here in my pda journal.   I have just had a brilliant idea. Just about all of my DayNotez (my journaling soft ware) could be blog entries, how cool would that be. ANYWAY.   There are a couple of things that are keeping me from being enlightened by the professional journals and enthralled by book reviews. Fist of all my parents are coming to visit. I only get to see them once or twice a year,  to make it more exciting this is only the 2nd time they have come to see us. The first time was  three years ago for our wedding.   51 minutes to go. I stopped writing to chat with a colleague. I am at the reference desk now so I also had to pause to refresh time on the computer. Be fore I started doing this I worked on my to do list as well as menus and grocery lists.  43 minutes and counting. The other thing on my mind is the book I'm reading. It is note the book it self, mind you, but the review I'm going to write about it that has my mind going.   21 minutes. Here is a rant  I'm furious. Why do people have to be impatient and rude. Don't get me wrong, most of our patrons are fantastic.  There is one that makes me angry. She is always in a hurry she doesn't pay attention to what I am saying. She expects us to be able to just hand her what she wants. They are always odd broad requests. But she is never happy with what I have to give her. And besides that she is mean to old people.  
       
    
    
</post>


</Blog>