<Blog>

<date>09,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Nebraska finally has a new football coach! Hooray.  I'm so sick of hearing about the search for the new coach.  If they had just left Frank Solich alone... The old Butternut building burned down in downtown Omaha yesterday, a 4-alarm fire.  Firemen have been down there since 11:30 Wednesday night.  That was big news, getting the coach was big news, there was no other news in the world yesterday in Omaha, Nebraska.  This town needs to get a life.  Yes, I'm sorry about the Butternut Building.  The city will lose a lot of money because the "upscale" condos downtown are lost, other businesses will suffer, this half of the state will probably fall into the Missouri River.  Geez.    In other news around the world... I guess there wasn't any! HaHa! 
      
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Only 2 more days to go in the cast - hopefully.  Another Sister from the ward brought over dinner tonight to save my starving family.  Yeah, right.  At least I haven't been stuck in bed in the summer again with everybody and their brother bringing ice cream over because it was hot out.  How do I know it's hot out?  I'm stuck in bed.  Not a good idea.  Anyway, I'm just grateful that they're taking the time out of their busy schedules to bring dinner.  And brownies.  Nothing wrong with brownies! As a matter of fact, I should go see if there are any left....   I should be working on genealogy with this time I have off work.  I just haven't gotten around to it.  I printed a boat load of pictures day before yesterday so I could scrapbook, but I haven't gotten my stuff out to actually do it.  I'd better get busy before it's July again and I have hundreds of pictures to go through.    Meg is looking for another part-time job.  She filled out an application tonight, we'll see if she hears from anyone. Steve made a suggestion the other day about setting her up with a day care, but I think her artistic talent would be wasted with just a day care.  I have to admit though, she does have fun with the little kids.  Amy called tonight and said she and Madi made necklaces last night and Madi had to make one for Meghan.  Isn't that cute?  What a sweetheart.    
      
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've decided I've procrastinated long enough and have to get this blog thing moving.  I type much faster than I write, so maybe this is a good thing?  Plus, all my *friends* can find me here.  Here, here, here I am!  Do I sound like Dory in Finding Nemo?  In my mind, I look like her! 
      
</post>

<date>24,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      For anyone not familiar with the case, three years ago an Omaha Police Officer shot and killed a man in the line of duty.  He was originally charged with manslaughter, the grand jury acquitted him, the charge was dropped and not refiled. That's it in a nutshell, but obviiously there was more to it than that. Last week Jerad Kruse (the officer) was in court AGAIN because the family of the criminal was suing him in civil court for wrongful death.  Please.  Notice I didn't say the shooting victim's family, I said, the criminal's family.  He was a criminal.  He wasn't a victim of circumstance.  A victim of circumstance trips and falls off a curb in front of a bus.  A man who with a police record (who was recently released from jail) who steals a car, leads the police on a chase for more than 30 minutes, and then acts suspiciously, acts as if he is reaching for something and then raises his arms, is asking for whatever he gets.  I just do not have sympathy for his family because of how he died.  I have sympathy for his mother, just as I would have sympathy for any mother who lost a child, however, if he hadn't done the things he did, he wouldn't be dead today.  I don't care if he was red, black, purple or white, I don't care about the officer's race either.  I think it's ridiculous that they continue to harass this officer and his family because their criminal son is dead.   I am also sick to death of hearing how he was "turning his life around".  People who are "turning their life around" are not out driving stolen cars and leading the police on chases through town.  There.  I've had my say about it.       
      
</post>

<date>23,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink     What Snack Food are You?      brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    Yes, I'm bored.  The guy is supposed to be coming to finish working on the security system, so I don't want to be in the middle of a stat report when he comes, so I'm just playing.  I really, really want to take a nap, but I don't want to answer the door with drool all over my face (grin).
      
</post>

<date>23,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Your soul is bound to the  Solitary Rose : The Alone.   "When I wake up alone, the shades are still drawn on the cold window pane so they cast their lines on my bed and lines on my face."   The Solitary Rose is associated with loneliness, melancholy, and patience.  It is governed by the goddess Merope and its sign is The Sword, or Unrequited Love.  As a Solitary Rose, you may be summed up as a hopeless romantic.  You desire love and have so much love to give, but thing just never seem to work out the way you want them to.  In life, you can be very optomistic, even when things are gray and nothing works out to your expectations.    urlLink   What Rose Is Your Soul Bound To?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
      
</post>

<date>23,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just read that Captain Kangaroo died. I'm so sad.  I can remember watching him in the morning before school, Bunny Rabbit snatching the carrots, Mr. Moose and the hail of ping pong balls... You'll be missed.   urlLink  
      
</post>

<date>23,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The blog is finally up and running! I'm so excited!  Thanks to Jaime from the LDS women site (www.lds-women.com)! I hate things that are supposed to be simple.  For people who don't know HTML in an HTML world, nothing is simple.  Too bad you just can't eat Rice Krispies and sent for a HTML coder ring.  Of course, that would take the fun out of it, wouldn't it!   Obviously it's been awhile since I've been here and I do have a lot to jabber about - like that's new, but I have to go let the dogs in and get some lunch.   Thanks again Jaime - you're great! 
      
</post>

<date>31,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's 14 degrees outside!  above  zero! I'm so excited! I think I should throw open the windows and air out the house! Of course I realize this will probably be short-lived, since we're in a winter weather advisory, but I'll worry about that tomorrow!   
      
</post>

<date>30,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I actually had to laugh at this.  I've never even HELD a gun, let alone shot one. Brother. I love some of those quizzes at Quizilla - I emphasize the word SOME.     PSG1 sniper rifle.. You prefer not to be seen, but to take out your enemy from a long range. With a good vantage point you would be very deadly    urlLink   what gun suits you..     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla       
      
</post>

<date>30,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I was reading a post over at  urlLink Sons of Mosiah , which got me thinking. Someone had mentioned their feelings about tossing garments on the floor, thinking it's a bad thing, and how strict he was about wearing garments.  This probably has nothing to do with anything, but I can remember when I went to the Temple for the first time and we were having our little "talk" about how to dispose of garments when they're worn out. The matron that was talking to us said the cotton garments are so nice to use for dust cloths. I swear my jaw hit the floor! What was she thinking! Seriously, that's the first time in my life I've thought this church can't possibly be true, with people using their sacred garments for dust cloths! I was appalled. It got worse when another woman in the room said she did the same thing. I was ready to bolt.    But then, like the angel she is, my escort whispered to me, "We'll talk about this later." Later, after we had dressed and were leaving the Temple, she said that's ridiculous, what that woman said about using garments as dust cloths.  They're not dust cloths, they're garments. And when they don't serve that purpose anymore they should be disposed of properly. I can't tell you how relieved I felt.  I know it was a totally off the wall thing to be worried about, in light of the whole situation, but it just hit me as being so wrong.    I have to admit I'm not very good about things like keeping them off the floor, I mean, there's no room in our bathroom for a hamper, so they go on the floor until after a shower, but I'm hoping the Lord will allow for that indiscretion.  I mean, after all, I'm not using them for dust cloths!   
      
</post>

<date>29,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I must believe it, I haven't been much of anywhere.       urlLink create your own visited states map   or  urlLink write about it on the open travel guide  
      
</post>

<date>29,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      We got the virus again. I'm getting a little irritated with this.  Of course Norton can't fix it, but it can "quarantine" it. I know where it came from this time, it was a friend of Steve's. Grrr. I heard on the financial news last night that 1 in 10 e-mails being sent was from the virus. I can't hardly imagine.  Now it's been upgraded so it won't let you go to the web pages that show you how to fix it. That's one smart virus. On one hand I'd like to wring the neck of whoever started it, but on the other hand you have to admire them for their ability - if they would only use it for good and not evil... *sigh*  Today was my day off, but since the hospital didn't have any work on Tuesday because of the ice storm in North Carolina I worked a bit. I hate working on my day off.  Then I did housework.  I spent over an hour just picking up everybody else's messes and never even got to scrubbing the floors. Now I don't feel like it. So, apparently it's not going to get done.   The Sisters want to come over today and watch a video - I can't remember the name of it. (I'm batting 1000 today, must be the fibro fog, or early Alzheimer's, I'm not sure which.) At least the living room is presentable and I vacuumed the entry way too.   There was a pile of dirt in the entry from the other day, when I had a little mishap.  I was carrying in 3 logs when my sweater got hooked on the garage screen door, I dropped the top log when the sweater yanked me back, the log barely missing my left foot (which, thankfully, is the never-been-injured one), which scattered snow and dirt all over the floor. I finally had to put the other 2 logs down also, take the sweater off to unhook it, and then take the logs downstairs.  When I came back upstairs, I noticed a push broom sitting against the door (first place I'd look for one), so I used it to sweep up the dirt. That should have been the end of it, right? No. The broom had been used to brush snow off a car, so it was wet, and mixing with the snow that had melted off the dropped log I made a nice big muddy mess on the floor. So, I had to go upstairs and get some paper towels because I was NOT going to mop the floor in the middle of working on a report.  I got the mud cleaned up, but there still was a pile of debris which sat there ever since because no one else in the house could see it. Oh well, done now. At least the dogs didn't think it was the outdoors coming in and use it to their advantage!   Now that I'm done ranting and raising my blood pressure, I think I'll grab a good book and go sit by the fire and enjoy the peace and quiet.  Until someone else gets stuck on our hill and the dogs feel the need to howl at the top of their lungs to let me know there's a potential axe murderer in the neighborhood. Next time remind me to get a cat. 
      
</post>

<date>28,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Last night I couldn't find the remote control. (Let's not go there.) Anyway, the TV was stuck and I was lazy and American Idol came on. Give me a break. What a waste of television time. Yuck, yuck, yuck. I can't believe people watch this stuff. I felt so embarrassed for some of those people who think they have talent (I know I don't have any, thank you very much).  Why, why, why would you want to humiliate yourself in front of an arrogant jerk like Simon. Even before I watched last night I've heard stories about Simon. I wouldn't open my mouth in front of that guy. It was just scary to see people who have the need to totally humiliate themselves. Plus, this stuff is on a television program - wouldn't reruns in 20 years be awful? Here honey, see how mommy looked as an idiot teenager.  Ick. I gotta think there's a little bit of a sadist in whoever watches this.  BTW - I didn't watch the whole thing. The pain made me get up to look for the remote.    You know what other show just turns my brain to jelly?  King of the Hill. Ugh. What are people thinking!?    Give me a good dose of ER or Trauma - Life in the ER any day. Even Cops, but please, no more singing!     
      
</post>

<date>27,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      You know what I hate? I hate it when you have a very favorite DJ on a very favorite station and one day they're there and the next.... POOF! It's like they never existed.  That really irks me.  I always tend to think they left under less than desireable circumstances when they just disappear, and I'm sure that's not always the case.  Anyway... I miss you TJ.  
      
</post>

<date>27,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I noticed last night we had THE virus.  I don't know where it came from and I tried to fix it! BWAHAHA! Yeah, right.  Thank goodness for Adam C. - don't know if it would have ever gotten fixed otherwise! I'm not the most computer literate person I know. I was thinking of taking some computer classes at Metro, but I can't decide if it's possible to teach an old dog new tricks.  Maybe, but at what cost!? (Sound of frying egg in pan...)   Anyway, I logged onto work today and saw we didn't have any jobs! That is very uncommon! Usually we get an e-mail from out team leader saying there's about anywhere from 200 to 500 jobs in the system - today there were none! So I stayed connected for awhile and waited while the solitary job came through once in awhile.  Finally got a call from the main office - the account I work on is in North Carolina so there wasn't any work because most of the doctors couldn't get to the hospital today! So the hospital asked the home people to get offline! Okay.  I didn't want to make any money anyway! Actually, they would have assigned me another account, but I really wasn't in the mood to learn another set of account specifics, so I deferred!  I'm supposed to be off on Thursday anyway, maybe I'll just work then.     This is our second day without mail - whatever happened to that old adage, 'Neither snow, nor sleet..."? I guess it doesn't apply in this day and age. Didn't get a newspaper yesterday either.  As I type this there's a car stuck on the street in front of our house.  From the sound of it, he won't have an engine much longer - or any tires, for that matter!  
      
</post>

<date>26,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hm, free association...    Political:: Ambition  Concentration:: Game  Fish:: Go  Lunacy:: Moon  Red:: Green  Imply:: Consent  Recognize:: Identify  Sexist:: Pig  Commercial:: Gain   Stricken:: Polio    Thanks to  urlLink Unconscious Mutterings .
      
</post>

<date>25,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      still snowing...lalalala!!!   
      
</post>

<date>25,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Why did we never have snow days when I was a kid? I remember walking to school with snow up past my knees (back in the days when you couldn't wear jeans to school, so I had pants on  under  my dress, freezing my rear end off. I can remember getting to school and my feet would be numb for about half an hour and then they would burn, they had been so cold. Now, every time it snows, there's no school. No fair - I still have to work. The fact that I work from home has nothing to do with it either!     I guess we have about 6" outside so far, and it's still coming down pretty good.  Steve had to go out and shovel a path off the porch and out into the yard of Heidi and Ruger won't go.  Silly Buttercup just jumps and leaps and runs around. Idiot dog!    The weather was supposed to turn nasty last night, with sleet and freezing rain, but when nothing happened.  When I got up this morning at 9:30 it was just beginning to lightly snow.  I was secretly hoping they'd call off church - but they didn't.   Then I thought maybe I'd stay home because I had a sore throat, but Jacob called to see if I could teach his class because he was sick, so I felt the Lord was giving me a good push on the back - out the door and into church, so I went.  I'm so glad I did, though.  The class I taught was the 7-year-olds.  There are only 3 in the class and they were so funny!  The Bishop's son was the only boy in the class - I'd forgotten how 7-year-old boys act!  He's so cute though!  We did have a discussion of f*rts.  Young boys always think bodily functions are hysterical - hmm, maybe I should say all boys!  I guess he was thought he was going to shock me by telling me he f*arted while we were having the lesson.  You should have seen the look on his face when I told him, that's okay, everybody does, it's no big deal! I think I let the air out of his balloon (no pun intended!).     The other two kids were (obviously) girls, and quite charming in their own way!  One little girl, Linda, who is a visitor, was very smart.  The other little girl, Amanda, asked me at one point how the Earth held up outer space.  Before I could even THINK of an answer - let alone the correct one, Linda told her the Earth doesn't hold up the solar system.  All the planets revolve around the Sun and are held in place in their orbits by gravity. Hmmm - what could I possibly add?  Then a few minutes later she told me, "I'm a genius." I have no doubt!  It was enlightening day, but it's okay if I don't have to teach again for awhile!  I'm exhausted.     This whole day reminded me of a joke I heard once. Q: Do you know why older women can't have children? A: Because they'd forget where they put them!  Truer words were never spoken.    I think dad and Pam are getting a new computer. Dad called today so Pam could ask some questions about operating systems - like I'm an expert! But I'll be glad if they get a new one, their old one is so slow it's almost ridiculous.  When I was there in November I had e-mailed him 2 pictures before I left home and it took almost 10 minutes for them to download, with an internet connection. That would drive me nuts.  I've been egging him on about getting a new computer ever since, so maybe they will.  Much cheaper than phone calls!   
      
</post>

<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My chauffeur (Steve) took me up to Fremont today for Amanda's baby shower. Her baby is so cute. I can't for the life of me remember his name. I guess it doesn't matter, he'd be cute even if I did remember his name. It was nice to see everybody again. Sometimes it sucks working at home. I'm so darn social (hahaha!) that I miss talking to people. But - I get more work done.  But - if you get paid by the hour, who cares? LOL! Anyway, it was so nice to hold a small baby again. Babies are just so precious. I think it's so neat to think that just such a short time ago they were living with God and now, here they are! It's amazing.    After my chauffeur picked me up, we went to look at a house just outside Fremont. I love it, Steve loves it, but *ouch* the price. It's been on the market since last year so of course Steve thinks they're asking too much for it. Maybe they are.  Maybe nobody is buying it because they think it's going to fall into the river. Who knows? I think it's actually a lot of house and land, which is what we want, even though we can't afford it. With our budget it's either larger house  or  more land. Not both. Not unless you want to live like Green Acres. I actually know the house I would love. The only problem is the yard isn't big enough for Steve. You would think when you work all day during the week and your weekend is filled with gun shows, hunting, cutting firewood, and hanging out with your buds in Beatrice and Lincoln, that a big yard that you're never home to take care of wouldn't be a priority.  Wrong.    Men.
      
</post>

<date>06,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ah HA! I have real weather now. Who needs you? 
      
</post>

<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Went to see the Book of Mormon movie tonight. It was really pretty good.  Actually, surprisingly good for a movie with a relatively small budget. One thing bothered me, is Nephi supposed to be so buff looking? LOL! Even Steve liked it, and since he's a NM, I take that as a good sign! The only bad part of the movie (which had nothing to do with the movie) was that it's colder than the heck outside and Steve had to park about a block away. Which was no problem since he dropped me off at the door, but we had to walk to the car. I kept thinking about a report I typed about a week ago where I guy who had previously broken his ankle and had plates and screws slipped on the ice, bent the plate, pulled out some screws and rebroke the ankle. Ouch. I do NOT want to go there. No broken bones for me again, ever! Keep your fingers crossed.    Anyway, back to the movie - there were some cheesy parts, like when Nephi brings a goat back to his starving family and his wife runs out to meet him, and since they're both so weak from hunger they're crawling toward each other (John! Marsha! John! Marsha!) And there was a kissing scene that I thought was a little looooooong. But that's about all the cheese.  Actually there were some funny parts - who thought the Book of Mormon could be so funny? There's a part where Sam goes to find Laman and Lemuel, that would have given my kids nightmares, even I jumped, but it was neat. I actually had no idea how long the movie would be, or what parts of the BOM it would cover, I mean, how do you fit 1000 years into a movie? Mini-series maybe, but a movie?  I think it was only about 2 hours long, and it didn't drag at all.  Steve just thought there should be more "smiting". I think he's watched one too many Arnold Schwarzenegger movies.    
      
</post>

<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
                                                                              BLUE         You give your love and friendship unconditionaly. You enjoy long, thoughtful conversations rich in philosophy and spirituality. You are very loyal and intuitive.           Find out your color at Quiz Me!               
      
</post>

<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Meg is off dog-sitting this week, so Ruger is in our room at night.  I felt bad for him, since he usually sleeps with Meg and our floor is so cold, so I put him in bed with us last night. I had every intention of having Heidi and Buttercup sleep on the floor, but it didn't quite work out that way.  As soon as I got into bed I looked down and there was Buttercup giving me "THE" look.  If you have dogs, you know the one I'm talking about. It's the "I hope you die and burn in hell" look. She always gives me that look when I make her sleep on the floor.  I gave my mother that look quite a bit in high school, that's why I'm so familiar with it. (No my mother didn't make me sleep on the floor!) I finally gave in and put her in bed with us. Then I looked down again to make sure Heidi was still buried in her blanket, but her head was poking out and I was getting the same look from her. What else could I do but pick her up? Steve said 3 dogs in bed was too much, but when I told him he'd have to put them down, they stayed in bed with us all night. Coward. I don't know what Ruger is going to do when Meg moves out - not that we have to worry about that any time soon, but he is such a  nervous  little dog.  Well, he's not exactly little... You know the Far Side cartoon where there's a wiener dog on a stool making cappucino and the caption says "How nervous little dogs start their day"? I'm sure that cartoon was patterned after Ruger.  He worries about everything.    Enough dog stuff. I actually got out of the house tonight and went for a little ride. I'm impressed by the size of the icicles on some of the houses around here! One house had an icicle I swear was 12 feet long, it came off the corner of the house and hung down to nearly the driveway. There were some others that I would have to think twice about standing on the front porch, it was totally overhung with icicles. Deadly. Obviously poor construction and insulation run rampant in my neighborhood!     Actually, I love the snow! I just hate the cold that goes with it.  I was amazed at how many mailboxes are nearly buried. Steve took the snowblower about by our mailbox so the mailperson can reach it, but apparently that isn't the norm.     Congratulations to  urlLink Renee and Charles   on the purchase of their house! May you have a long and happy life there!    That's it for tonight, I have a ton to write in my "real" journal.  
      
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I finally took that religion test that everyone else has been taking. Hm.   Your Results:  1.  Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-Day Saints (Mormons) (100%)    2.  Jehovah's Witness (93%)    3.  Orthodox Judaism (86%)   That's a relief! I'll be able to sleep tonight.   
      
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I tried to put some pictures of our snow in here, but alas, I am not computer literate and just can't make it work.  *HEAVY SIGH*   PS. The Weather Pixie is fired. 
      
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well I guess same  urlLink sex marriages  are official. The Massachusetts court ruled that anything less than marriage between same sex couples would be discriminatory. Oh brother. I have such mixed feelings about this, church aside, obviously. One side of me says I don't want to know about your sexuality. If you find someone to love and who loves you, fine. I don't want to hear about it. I don't want to receive invitations to Bill and Tom's wedding, or Sue and Ethel's engagement party. If you're in love with someone of the same sex, fine. Go be in love. Leave me out of it.  There's a part of me that just knows how wrong this is (okay, bring church back into it). Don't expect me to condone it or contribute to it. Your lifestyle is your business, as mine is to me. I don't think I'm homophobic, but the thought of seeing two people of the same sex kissing at the end of the ceremony makes me rather sick to my stomach. It just sounds mean, I know. I would go to a heterosexual wedding of a friend in a heartbeat, but I just couldn't do the same sex wedding thing.    It sounds so black and white until you have a friend or family member who is gay. Then what? Pretend it doesn't affect you? It does. You can love them, and want the best for them, but still isn't there a little bit of a twinge everytime you think of the phrase "my son and his husband", or "My daughter and her wife"? It just doesn't feel "normal".  But the whole definition of normal changes then.  Obviously, heterosexual isn't "normal" for them, is it?      There are situations in my own family that I'm not going to go into here, but in one situation I have totally distanced myself from a gay person in my family.  Not because they're gay, but because I just cannot deal with that person on any level, they have no conscience and no morals. That I can't live with.  The other person I love with all my heart and I truly hope that they have a wonderful life, whatever the future holds for them. No matter what happens, I will love this second person. Sexuality is not the issue here. But, in both cases, for marriage to someone of the same sex, I don't know how accepting I would be of their partner. In the first case, probably not very accepting, since I think any partner this person would chose would be of the same ilk. the second person... I would genuinely try to accept their partner, as I have accepted them, without reservation. I do think the way the second person was raised will make all the difference on how they handle life as they get older.    Gosh, now I'm rambling.  I just think we're beginning to see the end of the "family" as wel know it and that makes me sad.  I think of the homosexual couples I've known, and there really haven't been many, but none of them have remained together. Maybe that will change with this new marriage law, but I doubt it. We'll have to see what happens now. 
      
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The weather is so crappy even the Weather Pixie took off. Right, as soon as she has to work for a living she takes off. Figures. Bah! 
      
</post>

<date>02,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Ignore:: rebuff  Death::cold  Missy::tramp  Ballet:: dancer  Guest:: dinner  Campus:: college  Lonely:: quiet  Company:: picnic  Helicopter:: war  Sterile:: medicine    Thanks to  urlLink Unconscious Mutterings  - again.  
      
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I don't think I'll be attending church today.  I'm really not very compliant with wearing my CAM walker (I'm not supposed to be putting full weight on my leg yet, but with living in a tri-level house and all...) But, when I go outside the house I wear it.  Unfortunately, nothing fits over the boot (the toe) and socks aren't enought to keep my foot warm. Not to mention the snow that's piling up again, so I get snow under my sock in the boot, which makes my sock wet, which makes my foot  colder  for hours. It's still snowing...  We're supposed to have another 8 to 12 inches by tomorrow, on top of the 12 to 14 inches we got last Monday. It's supposed to snow again on Wednesday, Thursday, and again next Sunday. Just like when I was a little girl. I can remember having snow from before Thanksgiving until March. As a matter of fact, almost every year on my grandpa's birthday we'd have a blizzard, if not a blizzard, at least snow. (March 22) Since I've gotten older it seems like there's less and less snow. We don't have snow at Christmas half the time. We went to Panera Bread so we could have soup for dinner last night and I told Steve it seemed more like Christmas now than it did at Christmas-time.  Lots of snow, people still bustling around shopping - except last night it was at the grocery store!    urlLink Panera Bread , I love it! I love their soups especially.  The baked potato tastes just like grandma used to make. The sourdough rolls were hot last night when we got there... A little bit of Heaven on Earth on a cold night.  Especially when you get to sit next to the fireplace! 
      
</post>

<date>14,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Dragon:: lair  Molecule:: atom  Tire:: sleepy  Mighty:: hercules  Octane:: gas  Troll:: goat  Atmosphere:: air  Guide:: Switzerland  Leash:: dog  Dustmite:: itchy     urlLink Unconscious mutterings 
      
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have dreams all the time that my teeth are falling out. Like they're literally crumbling in my mouth. In my dreams I'm talking and my teeth are just crumbling and I'm catching them in my hands - odd huh? Anyway, today I found this site to analyze dreams. It said that dreams about your teeth crumbling or decaying is representative of a feeling of powerlessness, that I'm having difficulty getting my point across, or that my voice isn't being heard.  I may be experiencing feelings of inferiority and a lack of self-confidence in a situation or relationship in my life. That's interesting.  I have this dream, I swear, at least once a week. It's so strange when you really don't believe in something - as I don't believe in dream interpretation, but then some part of what they say just hits the nail on the head! Some of the rest of it was like I'm self-conscious about my appearance (who cares - I'm the one who chooses not to wear makeup), and women going through menopause having dreams about losing their teeth are having feelings related to getting older, feeling less feminine, and less attractive. I don't think that's it.  The other part was interesting though.    A real estate guy is coming over Sunday to give us a ballpark figure on what to ask for the house. Finally. Now I only hope I can get the place cleaned in time! I was down in the laundry room today with the vacuum, giving the place the good going over when I found a dead mouse behind the water heater. Gross. Totally gross. I hadn't seen any evidence of mice since the fiasco last year when Steve put a box of corn in the garage - and the forgot about it! That was the most disgusting thing... (shudder)  More traps tomorrow.  I should have paid more attention to the dogs.  The other day Ruger was in the laundry room with me and he was sniffing around with his nose to the ground. I couldn't figure out what he was doing since there was nothing in there, but maybe I was wrong... Ewwww.    On to happier subjects!  Mel got her engagement ring from Dan tonight - Contragulations you guys!  (I don't even think she got to the strawberries and whipped cream or the hootchie pajamas!)  She's happy - and I'm happy for her. I'm gonna cry (sob!)     We watched  urlLink Dead Like Me  tonight.  I love that show.         
      
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm starting to think I woke up in someone else's body this morning.   WHITE. It means Purity, innocence, heavenly, and charm.      urlLink What color rose are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    
      
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Unity. You Turly Desire Unity. You wish that the world was together as one, and world peace was among us. You enjoy sitting in natures peaceful spots to get away from war and hate.    I really answered the questions honestly, I really did!  Brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla . 
      
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      There's an interesting chat going on over at  urlLink Sons of Mosiah  about the world being more wicked now that ever before. It just got me thinking about how, when I was younger, my grandmother would always talk about how wicked the world was, and she's say that California was going to fall into the ocean. (Gotta love her!) Of course at the time I thought she was a little bit loco, but in thinking about it today, if you want to get rid of a lot of wickedness, that would sure be the place to start! That and Massachusetts!   Anyway, I do feel people are more wicked now than ever before. I never used to feel afraid to be out at night or to go shopping at night by myself. I'll still do it, but I don't like it. I won't go for a walk at night by myself anymore. I don't live in the inner city either, I live on the west end of town in a nice neighborhood. But it's not my neighbors that worry me. Several years ago, right after I started working at home again, a guy stole a car (I think that was the story), and ended up in our neighborhood while the Sheriff was chasing him. He dumped the car and just walked in this woman's house.  Her sliding door was unlocked and he just walked right in. That scared the crap out of me. I never leave my doors unlocked when I'm home. Even with my three dachshund alarms that will alert me to every stray piece of paper skittering down the street, I don't feel safe with the doors unlocked. Maybe that's part of working at the police station, I became aware of how much crime really goes on in this City and how long police response time really is. I have guns in the house, and I wouldn't be afraid to use one if the need arose.    I'm getting a little bit off topic, excuse me. Another part of the problem is that people aren't accountable for their own behavior anymore. I remember reading a story about a guy who broke into a house while a family was on vacation. He tried to exit through the garage, but the electric garage door opener was shut off and the door was locked. The door back into the house had locked behind him so he was stuck in the garage until the family came home a week later.  He survived by drinking the cases of soda they had in the garage.  He had the audacity to sue the vacationing family because he could have died. Never mind the fact that he broke into their house and robbed them! I can't remember how this all turned out, but in my humble opinion a lawsuit should never have been filed.  Talk about a waste of taxpayer money!    What about our poor teachers? I used to want to be a teacher when I grew up. Then I grew up and could see the change coming and it wasn't for the better.  Teachers being assaulted by students, students with guns, teachers being killed by students.  Schools should be a safe place for our children. They shouldn't have to be afraid of other students. I know when I was in school, you didn't bully other kids. Because if the principal and teacher didn't straighten you out, your parents sure would when you got home! Personally, I'd rather face the principal and the dreaded paddle than my dad when he was angry!  Whatever happened to corporal punishment anyway? I think they should bring it back.  As far as parents saying, "I don't want anyone but me to lay a hand on my child." Maybe you should do it more often and no one else would have to.  I'm not advocating child abuse here either - I'm just saying that a hand to the rear end is a good deterrent, along with a discussion about appropriate behavior. I'd love to say that every child can be reasoned with, but having had a son with ADHD I know that's not possible. I could tell your a story about a time out at our house that would curl your hair - so while I don't advocate child abuse, beating a child with a belt, spoon, or what have you, I do think a firm had to the backside isn't always a bad thing.    The other think that I think contributes to the wickedness of the world in general is that God and family aren't priorities anymore.  Since Matt lives with his dad and we rarely saw him, I finally called him a couple weeks ago and suggested that he come over every Sunday for dinner. We're going to shoot for family dinners every Sunday because that's something that's been lacking ever since Matt moved back to his dad's house.  We watch movies together occasionally, but that's not the same thing, I'm hoping this will draw us a little closer as a family and then, who knows what might happen?    I guess I've rambled enough for now, things to do and people to see. Gotta run. 
      
</post>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey Mel - what are the strawberries and whipped cream for?  Does it have anything to do with hoochie pajamas? LOL!   HAHAHAHA!  
      
</post>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Sure enough, there is plenty of work to do today, but I just don't feel like it. I didn't do anything yesterday because my wrist was acting up, and I didn't feel good, so I slept most of the day away. I could do the same today, but I know there's work to be done. That's why I'm sitting at my home computer doing nothing. I wish there was something interesting to do. *sigh*.    We went to the ER last weekend (Steve and I), and he had bronchitis. He called home and wanted me to make a doctor's appointment for him, so he must feel bad, you know how men are about doctors - and Steve is one of the worst! Anyway, he goes tomorrow, so we'll see what's bugging him.  Maybe it's his conscience because he didn't stay home this weekend and work on the touch-up painting that needs to be done. (No, I think it would be another part of his anatomy bothering him then, from the kick in the rear!)    Meg will be home again tomorrow - thank goodness! Three dachshunds in a queen size bed doesn't not make for a comfortable night's sleep! I can't make them sleep on the floor though, the wood is so cold since the bedroom is over the garage.  (Didn't I discuss this already?) Hmmm.    I guess I should get back to work. Can't make any money playing on the computer. Too bad...
      
</post>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Identity:: crisis  Reveal:: naked  Live:: die  Attitude:: adjustment   Night:: day  Nevada:: Utah  Weekend:: warrior  Write:: journal  Friend:: foe  Seventeen:: magazine     I love the new week. Thanks to  urlLink unconscious mutterings .  
      
</post>

<date>20,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The new job started this week! I'm totally brain dead, and I have 2 days to go! I can't believe how easy the other job was, compared to this one. I've knocked the dust off all my medical reference books, and learned some new things too! But, for some reason, it's now after midnight and I'm still wide awake. I'll be regretting this in the morning.   I fired off a letter to the public pulse today about the stupid covenants in new neighborhoods. I'm so disgusted. Steve and I found a perfect house on Monday. I mean it was  perfect , it had a huge pantry, laundry room, huge basement, oak woodwork, you name it. I loved it. Steve liked it (which is about as good as it gets with Steve!) But the covenants wouldn't allow him to have his antenna for his radio. How stupid is that?  Oh yeah, we have to have the neighborhood  look  good. Heaven forbid that an antenna disrupt the lovely scenery! (Can you hear the sarcasm?) I don't think people really realize how much ham operators really do - especially in times of crisis or natural disaster.  Oh well, it wasn't meant to be I suppose, but it was a beautiful house. *sigh*   I just realized tonight that I have to teach a class at Enrichment Night at relief society next Tuesday.  Maybe I better start preparing pretty soon.    Great news! It looks like our Dad and Pam will be moving back from Arizona some time this summer! I'm so glad.  It's too bad that dad and I didn't really get close until he moved, and I really hope to get to know Pam better.  Things sure started out on the wrong foot there!  Too bad mom didn't move to Mississippi sooner, then maybe dad and Pam would have been back here sooner.  I don't know if the two things are related or not, but I know I'd like to leave my ex in the dust somewhere! I sure can't blame dad (or Pam) for feeling the same way!   Okay, I've got to get some sleep, or else I'll be dozing at the keyboard tomorrow! TTFN. 
      
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I started a new job today. Sheesh - what work!  I'm used to doing ER reports, which are basically nothing. The doctors say the same thing over and over and over...  I know, I watch ER too, but I have yet to type an interesting ER report. This patient had a toothache, this patient had a sore throat, another sore throat, itchy eyes, a kid put a bean up his nose, earache... yada, yada, yada.  Today, between orientation on the phone, and training on the phone (which took almost 4 hours - califlower ear anyone?) I only typed 7 reports, but they were almost all op reports.  What a difference. How cool is that? I love variety. I'm sure I"m going to find it here.  But, for now, my brain is dead and my fingers are numb. TTFN!
      
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This week is definitely going better!  Work is much easier - the words are getting to me now, it's the formatting! Oy!  Dad and Pam are moving back - did I mention that already?  I"m SO jazzed.  We still haven't found a house :-(  We finally did find a neighborhood to build in, and a possible builder, so we'll see what happens.  I'm not holding my breath.  There's lots going on, but I don't have any time to write!  I just let the dogs out and now I have to go let them in before they turn to dogcicles, and then back to work!  I won't be gone so long next time - I hope!  
      
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Why is it every time I think I have time to write something happens? Later. 
      
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         urlLink      I'm completely down-to-earth!   urlLink  Find your soul type  at  urlLink kelly.moranweb.com .    You are the most in touch with knowledge. It's the tree of life from which you tap the sap. You know what you want and you know how to reasonably get it.  Virtues: You respect people with plans. When someone has their head on their shoulders, you know that they can see straightforward and keep their eyes on the mark. When it comes to looking at the future, you take a logical approach: what's within your ability? A fortunate attribute that you have is the ability to set a goal for yourself, higher than maybe you feel possible, but still keep yourself within reasonable bounds. You take the time to appreciate those surrounding you and they do appreciate you in return. Decision-making comes naturally to you when you take the time to consider each option. People only come to talk to you when they are looking for a logical, reasonable solution.  Aspirations: You have an idea of what you can do with your life, but you push it up a notch. You need a profession that you can enjoy, so work towards it. You want to live near your friends and family while being as far away as possible. You also want to settle down while working in excitement and variation.  Quirks: You don't appreciate drama queens and they don't appreciate you. When they need help, they won't seek you out because of your ability to see through their overly dramatic predicaments. You have leeway for humor, and sometimes love to participate in it, but when it becomes irrational behavior, others can count you out. Loud noises are bothersome, except when they come from you or your friends.  Factors: Reach for the sky! Don't decide to do something because you're merely good at it, but choose something you might like to do, despite whether you're sure you can master it or not. Don't only save room for a few empathetic friends, but open up to everyone.  Future: When looking for a job, if you work in all of your talents (logic, decision-making, planning, and definitely humor), you'll find yourself happy. Come to a compromise for location; live nearby your friends and take periodic vacations or live farther away and take frequent return trips.    Taken  urlLink here , thanks to Jaime at  urlLink LDS Women ! 
      
</post>

<date>29,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      To any LDS girls (or guys, for that matter), who think that marrying a non-member is no big deal.  Even if you're inactive now and have no intention of going back to church, it is a big deal.  Even if you never go back to church, somewhere inside you there's a little "Mormon core" and when what your spouse believes is  NOTHING  like your Mormon core, even if the your mouth is saying you understand and agree, you don't.   One morning you'll wake up and say, "What was I thinking?"  And it wil be too late to do anything about it.  Listen to that Still Small Voice.  Listen hard.  And dating nonmembers is not an option either.  You marry who you date.  REMEMBER THAT!
      
</post>

<date>29,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've been sadly neglecting my poor blog.  It really bites to have to work 8 hours a day!  I had a terrible dictating doctor yesterday - man... By the time I quit work I was ready to cry, I was so frustrated.  I just can't fathom how doctors want, no,  expect  their dictation to be perfect - and rightly so, but they refuse to put the effort into it.  They leave off dosages, mispronounce the names of drugs, dictate information under the wrong patient name, talk too fast, chew gum, eat, burp, etc., and we (medical transcriptionists) are supposed to clean it up.  That's just nuts!  We manage (sometimes I don't know how), but we usually manage to put out a good report!  Kudos to the docs who take the time to realize there's a live person who's going to have to listen and make sense out of what you say.  It's always nice to hear a doctor say, "Thank you transcriptionist, have a good day".  Makes it easier to try harder with the bumbling bozo who comes next.  Anyway - off that soapbox!   I must be doing okay, I got an e-mail from my mentor yesterday releasing me from 100% QA after a week and a half, so I'm pretty pumped!    On a totally different subject.  Steve and I went to see  The Passion of Christ  last night with Bob and Carole (my mother-in-law and father-in-law).   What an intense movie!  I was totally drained when we left the theater, it was so emotional.  Steve didn't like it.  He thought it was "sick".  He thought there was too much violence and it was too graphic.  Hellooooo!  There were times I felt like I just couldn't stand one more minute... like during the scourging and while he was carrying the cross, it just seemed so drawn out and long.  But, to put things in perspective, we watched a 2 hour movie (I'm not sure of the exact time) the entire incident lasted  12 hours !  All we saw was a portion of what really happened, one-sixth of the time that was actually spent.  Kind of put it in perspective for me.  I'll never think about the crucifixion the same.  Never.  I believe it's been sanitized over the years and this really brought home to me how much the Christ really did suffer for us.  When I was a little kid growing up and saw pictures of Jesus on the cross, there was no blood.  The cloth He had around his loins was white and  clean., and then I'd hear sermons about how Christ suffered for us.  Didn't look like suffering to me.  Seriously, I'm not trying to be an idiot here, but it didn't look like much suffering to me.  Obviously, as I got older a realized a little more of what went on, but until last night I can honestly say I never, ever,  imagined  how horrible it was.  How He must love us...   I won't see it again.  I can't see it again, but I know that my eyes were truly opened for the first time.  And the hype about the anti-Semitism - I can see how people would be afraid of raising the issue of anti-Semitism, but if you've ever read the Book, you know the story.  I think the Jews at that time were just afraid, and they were acting on that fear.  They felt very threatened and did what they felt they needed to do.  It had to be done.  It was going to happen one way or another, the Jews were only part of the process.  If it wouldn't have been them and the Romans, it would have been someone else.  Okay, enough said.    Then, the most wonderful thing happened after THAT last night! Sister Brotherson is in town and she came over - of course she's not Sister Brotherson anymore, just Michelle, but it was so great to see her.  And she brought Krissy Weekly with her, and another sister that I never got a chance to know very well, since she wasn't in our ward - Kimber?  I can't remember her last name - Alzheimer's is setting in quickly.  It was so good to see all of them again... They hold a very special place in my heart, I hope they all know how much I love them.  (I have to say that includes Allyson, Amy, Rebekah, Shalese, Natalie, Sister Moody, Sister Winkler, Sister Smith, Sister Jensen, and all the great sister missionaries I've been blessed to know.  Love you guys!
      
</post>

<date>29,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Hollywood:: Star  Censor:: Nudity  Nascar:: Race  Lube:: Oil  Mortgage:: Money  Freedom:: USA  Champion:: Spark plug  Reality TV:: Sucks  New York:: New York  Tease:: Hair    Thanks to  urlLink Unconscious Mutterings  for allowing another week of free association!   
      
</post>

<date>07,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay, I think life is back on a more even keel now.  Why is it that sometimes life throws a curve that you just can't dodge?  There wasn't any one particular thing that happened in the past couple weeks, but every little thing just conspired against me until I felt totally overwhelmed.  I don't get like that often, that goodness, but when I do - look out.     I didn't go to church today.  Yeah, I'm seriously slacking.  I hated the 8 o'clock start time because it was so early, I hate the 3 o'clock start time because it's too late... I need to just do it.  I hate getting out of church at 6.  By the time you come home and eat it's 8 o'clock or later, and the whole day feels shot - never mind that you had until 3 to do whatever you needed to.  There's just something wrong about going to church in the afternoon.  I don't know why this bothers me so much. When I first joined the church we had Sunday School in the morning and then went back at night for sacrament meeting.  That didn't bother me... But then, it wasn't a three-hour block at one time either.     I did go last week, I also got a calling last week.  Relief Society Temple Coordinator.  Doesn't that sound impressive?   I'm such an idiot too, I thought my recommend expired in December so I haven't gone  - even though I have about 150 names from my family ready to go.   Brother Jansen or Jenson, or whatever, reminded me last week that recommends are good for 2 years now.  D'oh!  The stake assigned our RS a temple time every month, ours is 2 pm on the fourth Friday.  No wonder no one ever goes.  How can women with kids be at the Temple at the time kids are getting out of school?  I think it would be so neat to live in a city where the Temple was open all day Tuesday through Saturday, but since the saints in Omaha aren't quite so Temple-minded we only have day sessions on Friday and Saturday.   I did set up another time for our RS to go - next Thursday at 7:30.  Maybe I can even make it that night.  Why is going to the Temple so much easier than going to church?  I wish someone could explain that to me.     Meg came home from church tonight a little discouraged.  She's the only person working in the nursery.  The bishopric has called other people, but no one has accepted the calling.  I don't understand why nursery works are so looked down on in the church - don't even try to tell me they aren't, becuase they are.  Meg does such a good job with the lessons, and she really loves the kids.  Kind of ironic that she's the only unmarried young single woman in our ward and she's better with the kids than some parents I see.  Hmmm.  Anyway, maybe I'll start going to help in the nursery, just so she can have a little less hectic time.  She can't even take one child to the bathroom because there's no one there with the other kids.  That's just nuts.  She had to go to RS and ask for someone to come help today, and the bishop's wife had to do it.   I think far to many people in church think that the nursery is a free baby sitting service, thay have no idea that lessons are actually planned and carried out!  Okay, off that soapbox.   Another thing that's got me going this week is outsourcing of work to other countries - especially India.  The AAMT is going to a legislative hearing in California this week to   support   it!  That pretty much ticks me off.  Here I go paying dues to the AAMT, because it's the American Association of Medical Transcriptionists, and they're supporting our work being sent overseas.  Not only that, I don't relish the idea of my medical records and personal information being in the hands of someone not governed by the sme privacy laws as the United States.  Don't even get me going on THAT subject.    
      
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Crazy, crazy week (or two)!  I started back to work at the police department in the typing pool, so in the past 6 weeks I've gone from working 4 hours a day to working 12 hours three days a week and the 8 hours on one of my days off from TRS.   I wish I could say I'm rolling in the dough, but that's not the case.  We've decided not to move.  Okay, so now I want to work on fixing this house up some more.  You know, like get the pink blinds out of the bedroom that's been teal green for five years.  (Yes, I said five.)  The vertical blinds in the kitchen are due to be replaced, and I want wood shutter/blinds in the family room in the basement.  So, I guess I'll work another job to get what I want.  Of course, just having mad money will be fun too!  I give my whole check from TRS to Steve, so the PD money is mine, all mine, ha ha ha (insert maniacal laughter here!)  So, that's about all that's been going on in my life, work, work, work.  I've kind of missed working for the police.  I don't have to go all the way downtown, they're letting me work at the Youth Services office.  That's really great - it's closer and I don't have to pay to park.  I always thought people who worked downtown should make more money, since all the other police off sites have free parking.  Obviously, my opinion doesn't count for jack, because no one's ever listened.  I even tried to explain to a former chief how it would be more productive if they even did a payroll deduction for parking and gave employees parking stickers or those little thingys that hang from the rear view mirror.  I don't know how many tickets I got because I'd get busy working and forget to go plug my meter.   Of course once I saw I had a ticket I didn't put any money in the meter all day, so sometimes I had more money for lunch!  Either I'd forget entirely, or when I went out to plug the meter I'd start talking to someone and be gone from my desk for 15 minutes to a half hour.  See?  People would be more productive (and less surly if they got a ticket) if they had just given us a sticker.  The chief told me that wouldn't work because the parking spaces had to be open for the public.  I'm trying to figure out what the heck that meant, since the spaces weren't open anyway! Oh well.  Not my problem now.  No work at TRS today - or I should say it's very sparse.  JCAHO is there doing their certification so we're keeping the work caught up.  Overtime and the whole works, but today I've only done 3 reports because I keep getting the "no work" message!  Looks like I'll be working tonight!    Well, I'm going to check for work again.  TTFN
      
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Sunday again and I still haven't gotten anything accomplished this week.  I got my first paycheck from the City (yay!), so I got a few little things that I wanted for the house - when was the last time you saw someone excited about a new broom!?  Or a new phone?  I don't mean a fancy phone, I mean a $9.99 Target special to replace the $160 cordless we had that kept cutting out while you were talking.   Oh! And a bucket that my mop actually fits in I'm so happy!  How pathetic....   Meg will be back home tonight.  She's been in Minneapolis since Tuesday for the Phi Theta Kappa International meeting.  I think they need a new advisor, but that's all I'm going to say about that!  Ruger will be glad to see Meghan - again he's been relegated to sleeping on the floor with the other dogs - what a sorry life.  If I could be a dog I'd want to come back and live in my own house, the animals are so spoiled here!     Dad and Pam are back.  Dad has a job which sucks, but it's a job, so he's thankful for that.  Pam's been offered a job, but she's kind of holding out for the one she really wants, so she should know by the middle of next week.  They're going to go look at a house today, so maybe they''l be in their own place before too long  It has to be hard to live with somebody else - no matter how much you like/love them, when it's their house and not yours!   Dorothy called yesterday - she may be coming back in September. We have so much fun when she comes back, it's almost like we're 22 again and have the world by the tail!  Okay, maybe we go to bed earlier and get up later, but it's still fun.  Hopefully this will give me a reason to take a little time off work and we can hang out, go see her mom, and just generally have a good time!  I guess that's it.  Boring, boring life.  But hey - the snow is gone and summer is coming!  Yay!  
      
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Condemn:: Prisoner  Promiscuous:: Loose  Pro-life:: abortion  Mona Lisa:: smile  Crown:: jewels  Mumble:: jumble  Hack:: taxi  Diet:: food  Introduction:: names  Latin America:: dancer    Thanks again to  urlLink Unconscious Mutterings  for making me think so early in the morning.    
      
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I can't believe this.  I was only 24 when she was born - where did the time go anyway?  It seems like just yesterday that I watched her bounce down the basement stairs in her walker (yes, she did! And ended up stil in the walker, upright, at the bottom of the stairs!)  We were sitting at the breakfast table this morning (she made orange rolls - yum) at about 7 o'clock.  I remembered calling my grandparents the morning she was born, so they could hear her cry, and my grandma crying on the phone.  Grandpa passed away just 3 months later.  It actually was kind of a bittersweet memory...   Anyway!  (Cheer up!)  Happy Birthday Meg, my little Magoo!  I've got to admit, even when we're going at it tooth and nail because we're so much alike, you're one of the best things that ever happened to me!  Thanks for keeping me strong!   
      
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink     Find out what kind of driver you are!    I don't know who thought this one up, but they obviously haven't seen me drive! LOL!
      
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So, as I sit here by myself with my husband out storm spotting and wondering if I'll be in Oz by morning I thought I'd do the  urlLink Unconscious Mutterings  thing.     Virginia::  Beach  Soft:: Hard  Carol:: King  Vanity:: Bathroom  Feminist:: Nazi  Alias:: Criminal  Coward:: Noel  Beer:: Stein  Chance:: Dice  Honest:: Abe    This weekend has been so warm and nice - I love it.  I'm not crazy about 90 in April, you have to wonder what the rest of the summer will bring, but it's so much better than snow, snow, snow!  I don't have to scrape heat off my windshield!   We had cake and ice cream for Meg's birthday Friday night.  I think she had a good time.  The cake was yummy!  I love ice cream and cake!  (Obviously!)     Steve is out near Elk City storm spotting. There's a t-storm moving our way and lots of bad weather to the north of us.  I'm home with the dogs, so if it gets bad we can all go to the laundry room, since the "tornado room" is full of junk!      Things worked out pretty well at work this week.  I've quit the transcription job and sold some of my reference books.  Steve thinks I'll go back to transcription, but I don't think so.   As a matter of fact, I don't even want to watch any medical shows on TV right now.   Well, the t-storm is fast approaching, I'm going to gather the puppies and sit in the basement.  TTFN. 
      
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink     Which Bath and Body Item Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    Come on, is this really a surprise to anybody?   
      
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I can't believe I've neglected my poor lonely blog for so long!  This has been the most crazy 6 weeks.  We finally bought a house - YAY for us!  It's a bigger house, ranch style, and the yard is bigger.  I'm so THRILLED I can hardly stand it.  We're closing on the 25th, but we're moving in on the 19th.  Otherwise we'd be moving, closing, and the people who bought our house would be moving in the same day.  That could be ugly.  We did that when we bought this house, even shared the same moving truck with Barry and his wife.  Never again will I do that!  We even hired a moving company this time to move the big stuff.  Besides, they're insured.  If they drop the 65" TV we can get another.  On the other hand, if we drop it we're SOL.  And I don't mean "singing out loud"!    Dad and Pam have been looking at a couple places, they finally found a house they really like, but Pam is having a little trouble finding a job.  I can't believe how rude HR people are.  She was offered a job at one assisted living facility, they offered her a job and told her to let them know by 6:30 if she wanted it.  When she called them back and said she was interested, they told her they had a few other applicants and would let her know the next day!  WHAT?!!  The next day they told her they'd hired someone from within.  Another place told her they had to wait until they signed some contracts - which fell through, so no job.  Why would you even be interviewing someone for a position that wasn't even available yet?  We won't even go into the places that don't even acknowledge a resume.  I know there are a lot more applicants than there are jobs, but a simple note to acknowledge they received the resume would just be common courtesy, IMHO.    Mel and Dan moved to a new place in Elkhorn, much closer than the eastern side of Council Bluffs, I have to say!  It's a really darling house, I love it!    Mike and Amy also bought a house, so the whole family has turned very nomadic this summer!    I'm still working at OPD part-time and working at home doing medical transcription part-time also.  It fits my crazy schedule.  Except, I wanted to work this weekend, but my arthritis or whatever was acting up Saturday, I spent most of the day eating codeine and lying on the heating pad.  I haven't had a day that bad in a long time, and I won't be hurt if I don't have another any time soon.    I was really sorry to hear of the passing of Ronald Reagan.  Alzheimer's disease has to be one of the most cruel diseases ever, for the families and caregivers as well as the patient.  I'm sure Nancy is very much relieved that her burden has been lifted someone and that he is at peace.  I was only in my 20s when he was president, but I think he did a wonderful job!    Okay, I promise it won't be another six weeks before I return!    TTFN
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        You are the color turquoise.  A fairly tempermental person, you're either upset or tranquil most of the time.  You can be as calm as your color. You're a mysterious person, yet somehow outgoing.  You're balanced, simply put.  You're somewhat bold.  You're generous and sophisticated--but never ever snobby.  You're lively and rich in personality and attitude. You're a beautiful person, aside from the fact that you're a perfectionist and painfully honest.  But life is good to you!    urlLink   What color are you? (Amazingly detailed & accurate--with pics!)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay, I do have a self-image problem, but this is ridiculous.      you are SHREK! you're a bit antisocial, but once you get close to someone, they find out you're a big sweetie!    urlLink   what shrek character are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla     (Yes, I am supposed to be working, why do you ask?)
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Wednesday Whatevers   1.  Do you think out loud?   2.  What color pen do you prefer to write in?   3.  How would you describe your voice?    1.  All the time.  I try not to do it when anybody is looking, but sometimes I just can't help myself.   2.  Purple.  Really.  Is there any other color? LOL!  I use other colors if I can't find a purple pen that writes really well.    3.  Icky.  I think I sound like I guy.  I definitely don't have a sweet, whispery voice.  The first time I heard myself on a tape recorder I totally freaked - but my two sisters sound the same, and I don't think they sound weird, so maybe it's just the old self-image thing. 
      
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       My Mormon name is  MindiJo Kursten !  urlLink What's yours?  
      
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yes, I changed my template and forgot that I would lose all my little links.  Bah. 
      
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      1. In the morning, do you brush your teeth before or after eating? Since I don't usually eat until after I get to work, I brush them before.  But, on weekends, when I eat breakfast as soon as I get up, I brush before.  And then after.    2. Do you believe in the emotional power of colors? Absolutely.   3. What do you do to preserve your memories? Scrapbook, take tons of pictures, journal.  I've even tape recorded some conversations with my mother-in-law about her childhood and transferred them to CD so in years to come we'll still be able to hear her voice, long after she's gone.  I wish I had done something similar when my grandparents were alive. 
      
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I need to leave this thing open all day, so I can just blog when I feel like it.  Seriously.  I think about it all the time, just never do it.   Been painting and working on the new house.  I love this place, it's so quiet!  Steve can watch TV and I never hear it after I go to bed - wonderful, blissful silence!  We got an estimate for a vinyl chainlink fence today - over 2000 smackeroos.  Yikes!  I'm thinkin' Steve'll go for the plain Jane stuff.  I just want a rug and some stools for the breakfast bar and I'll be happy.  Any takers on when that will happen? LOL! They had the stools I wanted on sale at Lowe's the weekend before we moved for $15, marked down from $45 - but we didn't get them.  (I only need 3, maybe only 2!)  Of course when I went back to get them after we moved they were gone.  That was a shocker (do you detect the sarcasm?)  I want an oval rag rug for the kitchen, we've looked at NFM, Ernies and Abe Krasne's.  Now why in the world would a normal, rational person drive over 100 miles to PRICE rugs and then got get one?  Hmmmm.... Any ideas?  As far as I know we made a little spending cash when we sold the other house.    I hate computers.  I spent over 2 hours on the phone with tech support from work yesterday and another 1/2 hour with the tech support from Dictaphone, only to find out the reason why my computer would't download voice files from the hospital was because of the wireless router we finally got hooked up again for our home computer.  The Dictaphone guy (spare me the jokes) tells me it may be from the router selecting an IP address for my workstation that the hospital dosen't recognize.  He says I should call the techies at work and have them fix me up with a static IP.  Whatever.  I talked to my supervisor yesterday and she said she tried that and it didn't work.  She finally had to hire someone to come over and hook up the router.  BS.  If someone needs the home computer they can wait until I'm not working.  Or play solitaire.  Whatever.  That's assuming we ever get the darn virus off the thing.    Meg was in LA for a week and now she's gone until Saturday for a dogsitting job.  She stopped by today and was saying how funny it was that she lived in the dorms at UCLA longer than she's lived here.  She's right - and it is kind of funny when you think about it.    The dogs are finally getting settled in, back to being very territorial.  One of them hasn't been feeling very well during the night.  Steve's had a couple messes to clean up the past 2 mornings.  All I can say is thank Heaven for Hoover SteamVacs!  TTFN     
      
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Why do I love summer?&nbsp; It's only 79 degrees outside right now, but when you factor in the humidity it feels like 89.&nbsp; At 9 o'clock at night.&nbsp; What the heck.&nbsp;&nbsp; I like summer, I really do, I just hate the humidity.&nbsp; I guess I have to go live somewhere like Arizona where "it's a dry heat".&nbsp; Whatever.&nbsp; I've been there.&nbsp; They can have their silly scorpions and those dashboard carpets so your dash doesn't crack.&nbsp; How lovely.&nbsp; No thanks.&nbsp; But why can't it be just a  little  less humid and a little more breezy.&nbsp; When the cable guy (haha!) was here this afternoon the heat index was 102.&nbsp; Ick.&nbsp; That's just  too hot  for humans.&nbsp;&nbsp; Remind me of this when I'm whining when I'm freezing my hoochie off in January and the wind chill is about 30 below.&nbsp; Then I'll wish it was 102 in the shade.&nbsp; I'm never happy.  
      
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Great Saturday! I love weather like this, maybe a little humid, but it was so breezy it wasn't bad. I'm gonna be missing days like this in a couple months!  Steve and I thought we'd take advantage of the nice day (and that fact I finished work early today) and do some shopping before we met his mom and Bob for LaCasa's Pizza. (I  LOVE  LaCasa! - they've even been mentioned on  Jeopardy!  once!) We went out to Oak View Mall, which is actually not the closest mall anymore since we moved, but I Steve had to go to a Sears store to look at riding lawnmowers... He looked and he looked, and then I went to the Disney store and bought another Eeyore, and then we went to Penney's so I could get a new wedding band (lost mine a couple weeks before the move and it never did show up), and then we went back and he looked some more, but couldn't make up his mind (is anyone surprised by this???) After we left Sears sans lawnmower by the way, we hit Best Buy looking for a good DVD. Well, our opinions differ greatly on what constitutes a good movie (me - A Bug's Life, him - Tremors - all of them!) Finally, we had to leave in order to make it to LaCasa's on time to meet his mom and Bob, so we're sitting at a red light on Oak View Drive by Old Navy when screech - BAM! Yeah, some kid rear-ended us. Like I need to be rear-ended when I already have herniated disks in my neck. I think I might be sore tomorrow. Hell, I'm sore now, I don't have to wait that long. Anyway, this kid is in the car with his dad - the car is still in-transit, they just bought it yesterday, coincidentally that was the same day the driver got his driver's license. Of course his dad didn't want to call the police. Actually no big deal for us, Steve's tank of a truck got a scratch on the bumper, but there was some definite damage done to the kid's car. I really felt sorry for him, truly... It seems the brakes weren't working on the car. Really? We called the police anyway, it took them about 15 minutes to get there and another 20 to write the accident report and then we were off.  The pizza was great - really great. Did I mention I love that place? Fried ravioli for an appetizer followed by hamburger pizza with Romano and mozzarella cheese. Yummy.  While we were waiting for the police to show up Steve had decided he was going to get the lawnmower - by the time we finished dinner he was back to thinking about it. By the time we got to 84th and Cass he thought he'd see if the Sears at Crossroads had one he liked. Oak View actually didn't have an automatic in stock of the one he liked. Crossroads did - and he's now the proud owner of a Craftsman riding lawnmower. I kept trying to get him to get the 21 hp mower that's the Bob Vila signature series, but it was a hundred bucks more. No dice. He's frugal that man is. Hey though, I'm okay with that. I got a new wedding ring out of the deal.  Well, I think it's time for some a muscle relaxer and a whirlpool bath. ZZZZZzzzzzzzzz 
      
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This week has totally sucked. Okay, not totally, but 98% sucked and 2% really great. Unfortunately the 98% far outweighs the 2%, so I've been in a funk all week.  It really all started last Saturday when I picked up the paper and found out that someone I knew had died. (I know, I know, but I always read the obituaries first. I'm hoping my ex will be in there, but I'm always disappointed.) Anyway, I see that Jacob (names have been changed to protect the innocent) has passed away. I about fell out of the chair. Long story, pull up a chair.  A long, long time ago, when I was thin and life was still fun my dad and the egg donor (formerly known as mom) owned a restaurant. It wasn't a big fancy franchise kind of restaurant, just the little corner diner where everyone knows everyone else. It was great. I was a waitress and mom, dad, and Grandma E worked there too. It was so much fun. We had another waitress there by the name of Lorraine (another name change, just bear with me). Anyway, she was a great waitress, very quiet and subdued, but I liked her. She had three sons, Sam, Tom, and Jacob. Sam was a couple years older than me and we dated for awhile, but things didn't work out very well, no car, different backgrounds, etc... But, while we dated we had fun - at least   I   did. He was a great guy, I was just young and stupid. They had a little trailer up by ours where both families spent weekends and just hung out, it was the best time of my life, in retrospect. The middle son, Tom, dated a friend of mine who also had a trailer near ours, so it was as perfect as only a summer when you're 15 or so can be. The youngest brother, Jacob, was the same age as my baby sister, Mel - this is important, remember it. They were about 6 at the time.  Long story short, egg donor and Sam's mom ended up in a big dispute over something only adults were worried about at the time and I think she even ended up suing the egg donor. (Good for her!) Lorraine and Grandma E remained friends. Every time Lorraine would talk to grandma on the phone Jacob would want to talk to "Mel Mel" as he called my sister. It was so cute.  He  was so cute! He had brown curly hair and a huge grin that would just melt your heart.  Well, the restaurant closed as we all know all good things come to an end. I didn't see Sam any more, Jacob and Mel Mel lost touch, but grandma and Lorraine stayed in touch. Sam ended up getting married (I went to his wedding with my grandparents) and moved out of state. Life goes on... La la la la life goes on... Anyway... I don't know how many years later it was, but Sam divorced, moved back to town and called me. We dated a few times, but I was entering my 20's and really thought I had bigger fish to fry (oh brother!) and didn't quite make the time I should have to spend with him. He actually sort of proposed at one time, the actual verbiage was "What would you think if I told you I could spend the rest of my life with you?" I told him he was full of s*** and hung up on him. I guess I thought if he was serious he'd call again. He didn't. Oh yeah, I was reeeaaaallll smart back then.  Grandma died, and I hadn't heard anything about Sam's family for years. Then, last year I read in the paper that Lorraine had passed away. Mel and I went to the funeral. We saw Jacob, Sam, and Tom again, expressed our condolences, life went on - again.  Then last Saturday and I read that Jacob and died. I was speechless. I called Mel and we decided we would go to the funeral. Which we did. I had the chance to talk to Sam for the first time in a long time at the luncheon. Everyone was so shocked at Jacob's funeral. I mean, he was so  young -  He was 10 years younger than me. He was the same age as my  baby sister !  For some reason this week I've started feeling very old. I know age is really all in your mind, but I guess my mind got old! I see a lot of the mistakes of my youth, not going to college in Idaho, leaving church for a time, dating Meg's dad, just basically having fun and not thinking about the future.  I see how things have turned out and just wonder why. Isn't that the 64 million dollar question!? It's funny to see how peoples lives touch, cross and then branch off in different directions and where they are at different points. I'm happy with my life, but sometimes I wonder, what if... What if I'd have said, "Hey, I'd like to spend the rest of my life with you too!"? What if I'd gone to school in Idaho? What if I hadn't gone to Debbie's birthday party? Would I have met Steve anyway? Where? What if I hadn't gone to Rosalie the night I got pregnant with Meghan? How would Matt have come into my life if I hadn't married my ex? Am I the only person who thinks like this - or am I the only person obsessing about it right now. Hm... I think too much. 
      
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      We had some pretty nasty thunderstorms run through here Tuesday night. Yesterday, all afternoon I worked out in the yard and didn't even finish picking up all the dead branches and leaves and stuff. Trees are wonderful things, I love them, but I'm doubting the wisdom of buying a house with 21 trees in the yard. Hmmm. Steve was outside for about 3 hours last night just cutting up the firewood and loading up the truck with wood to take to the dump. After I took a chunk out of my finger with pliers on Tuesday, I guess he doesn't trust me with a chainsaw. I don't know why not.  I'd be nice if I had my computer back so I could post some pictures. Crap. Some guy Steve works with is supposed to fix it for us. Um hm. Right.  Anyway, we had a huge branch come out of one the cottonwoods in the front yard and hit the power line. It snapped off and caused a bunch of sparking and stuff. Cool. Hey, you get your excitement where you can, okay? I thought that kind of stuff only happened in movies, but it happens in real life! Whoo hoo! The police had to come and sit by the wire so no one would come on it in the dark and step on it. I called the police and the power company when the line went down at about, um, 6:45 or so. The police didn't get here until after 7:30 and the power company finally came at about 2 a.m. I was fast asleep, the neighbor saw them.  Ruger is the goofiest dog, I just love him. Steve had given me one of those whatchamacallits that's a little plastic tube and when you bend it the little cylinder inside breaks and then it glows for 8 hours or so. I can never remember the name.... Anyway, Steve had given me one so when the power company came and had to turn off our electricity we'd have some light. (I know, don't even say it.) Needless to say, we didn't need it at 2 a.m., and I don't even think it affected out power, but I put the thing on the end table when I went to bed. Yesterday I was looking all over for Ruger and couldn't find him. I finally discovered him  behind  the couch with his head  under  the couch. Kind of like those little kids - if they can't see you then it must mean you can't see them. I couldn't figure out what he was doing in a position like that, but I quickly found out that he thought the package containing the light was food and had chewed it up. Didn't touch the plastic thingy though, I guess by the time he chewed the wrapper off he had discovered it didn't contain food. What I great dog, I don't even have to find his messes, he punishes himself. Too bad he can't clean up after himself as well.  I guess I've worked hard enough today. Off to today's crossword puzzle and a little relaxation time. TTFN 
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      1. In general, do you treat eating as a pleasure or a need?  Actually, I think it's a habit.  If I have to choose between the two, I guess pleasure.  But you'd know that if you saw me! LOL!  2. What is your opinion on recent low carb craze?  I think it's not good for your kidneys.  We'll have a whole generation on dialysis if we're not careful.  I wouldn't do it.  (Well, actually Dr. Klein said I  can't  do it, so there's no issue for me.)  3. Do you wake up when you have to, or do you stall / snooze forlonger?  Stall, stall, stall.  I hate getting up in the morning.  I'm definitely a night person, but I have to go to bed early so I can get up early.  Even that doesn't help much.  I must be getting older, sleep didn't used to be such an issue for me.  
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My home computer isn't working.  Hasn't worked for nearly 2 months.  I have to do everything on my work computer, which I shouldn't be doing, but hey, ya gotta stay in the loop, know what I mean?  I know about enough to install new programs and that's about it.  Maybe a little photo editing, but not enough to fix whatever the heck it is that ailing the computer.  We did have a trojan horse virus (thank you to whoever did THAT!).  We got the virus deleted, but the internet won't run right.  The stupid thing won't even recognize the CD burner or DVD burner, so I can't back anything up.  I'm a little annoyed.  I love my computer.  Steve works with some guy who I guess can fix it, but finding time in his schedule is (apparently) not going to happen any time soon.  Personally, I'd be just as happy to get a new notebook computer so I can take it out with me when I do my geneaology research, but I can't see that happening either.  As a matter of fact, it's pretty funny that I would even THINK such a thing.  Hahahaha!   We have all our internet, cable, and telephone through the same company and the bill got lost during the moving suffle last month, so the double bill today was, are you ready, $414!  I have to have internet cable for my job, but I'm thinking we may be able to dump some of the services with the phone, but then I don't think we'd be eligible for free HBO and Showtime.  I might have to check into that, I think $207 a month is a little bit excessive.  And hey, the long distance bill has gone way down since dad moved back from Arizona.   I just want my computer.  Come on, please? 
      
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Elder David Haight, an apostle from the  urlLink Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-Day Saints  passed away on Saturday.  He was 97 years old.  He had an incredible testimony and loved to share it with the world.  He will be missed, but I'm sure the heavens are rejoicing.  He and Elder Neal Maxwell both have passed away within the past 10 days, and prior to that it had been 10 years since an apostle in the Quorum of the Twelve had died.  Sad times for the church, and for me. 
      
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Did I mention I want my computer fixed?  Like, yesterday?  I have things to do!  Would you like a little cheese with that whine? 
      
</post>


</Blog>