<Blog>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In life, it doesn't matter how much you have.What really matters is, what you do with what you have.  Many of the life's failures are the people who didn't realise that how close they were to success when they gave up.  -Thomas A.Edison  The most beautiful thing in this world is the 'WORLD' itself.    To err is human, to forgive- devine   
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A question this is Which will find many takers. A gay and happy man will say, "Its a heaven my friend"; But his sad, depressed friend will say, "No dear, it is hell"  None really knows this world, Its is just a place  Where we have come to spend A few days , as a guest. Lets us just live In peace and love Lets just move on..... Towards fate and luck Lets just move on.....
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Agra, once the capital of the Mughal Empire during the 16th and early 18th centuries, is two and a half hours by express train from New Delhi. Tourists from all over the world visit Agra not only  to see the ruins of the red sandstone fortress built by the Mughal emperors but to make a pilgrimage to Taj Mahal, India's most famous architectural wonder. In a land where magnificent temples and edifices abound to remind visitors about the rich civilization of a country that is slowly but surely lifting itself into an industrialized society. The postcard picture of Taj Mahal falls short to convey the legend, the poetry and the romance that shroud what Rabindranath Tagore calls "a teardrop on the cheek of time". Taj Mahal means "Crown Palace" and is in fact the most well preserved and architecturally beautiful tomb in the world. It is best described by an English poet, Sir Edwin Arnold, as "Not a piece of architecture, as other buildings are, but a proud passion of an emperors love wrought in living stones." It is a celebration of woman's  love, exquisitely potrayed  in marble. And that's the way to appreciate it ! Taj Mahal stands on the bank of River Yamuna, which otherwise serves as a wide moat defending the Great Red Fort of Agra, the centre of the Mughal empire until they moved their capital to Delhi in 1637. It was built by the fifth Mughal emperor, Shah Jahan in 1631 in the memory of his second wife, Mumtaz Mahal, a Muslim Persian princess. She died while accompanying her husband in Behrampur in a campaign to crush a rebellion, after giving birth to their 14th child. Her death so crushed the emperor that all his hair and beard were said to have grown snow white in a few months. When Mumtaz Mahal was still alive, she extracted four promises from the emperor: first, that he build the Taj; second, that he should marry again; third, that he be kind to their children; and fourth, that he visit the tomb on her death anniversary. He kept the first and second promises. Construction began in 1631 and was completed in 22 years. Twenty thousand people were deployed to work on it. It was designed by the Iranian architect Istad Usa and it is best appreciated when the architecture and its adornments are linked to the passion that inspired it. It is a "symbol of eternal love". Having buried her down at Behrampur, it was time for the emperor to keep his promise and  build a tomb there itself. But by and by , it was felt that it was virtually impossible to transfer all the marble there, as it would cost an entire fortune and an entire lifetime. So, when Agra was chosen as the only alternative, astonishingly her grave was uprooted and brought to Agra, only to be finally transferred to the monument, completed twenty two years later. The Taj rises on a high red sandstone base topped by a huge white marble terrace on which rests the famous dome flanked by four tapering minarets. Within the dome lies the jewel inlaid cenotaph of the queen. So exquisite is the workmanship that the Taj has been described as " designed by giants and finished by jewellers". The only asymmetrical object in the Taj is the casket of the emperor which was built beside the queens,  as an afterthought. The emperor was deposed by his son and imprisoned in the Great Red Fort for eight years but was later buried in the Taj. During his imprisonment he was barred from visiting Taj. What he could have was just a little view of Taj in a reflection of a diamond. As a tribute to a beautiful woman and as a monument for enduring love, the Taj reveals its subtleties when one visits it without being in a hurry. The rectangular base of Taj is in itself symbolic of the different sides from which to view a beautiful woman. The main gate is like a veil to a woman's face which should be lifted delicately, gently and without haste on the wedding night. In indian tradition the veil is lifted gently to reveal the beauty of the bride. As one stands inside the main gate of Taj, his eyes are directed to an arch which frames the Taj. The dome is made of white marble, but the tomb is set against an awesome backdrop of the river and it is this background that works its magic of colours  through their reflection and transforms the view of the Taj. The colours change at different hours of the day and during different seasons. Like a jewel, the Taj sparkles in moonlight when the semi-precious stones inlaid into the white marble on the main mausoleum catch the glow of the moon. The Taj is pinkish in the morning, milky white in the evening and golden when the moon shines. These changes, they say, depict the different moods of woman. Different people have different views of the Taj but it would be enough to say that the Taj has a life of its own that leaps out of marble, provided you understand that it is a monument of love. As an architectural masterpiece, nothing could be added or subtracted from it.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A few days ago I read an essay of Gilbert Highet named 'Wonders are many' . That essay contains a very good poem in praise of manking. Here I want to share it with you . It reads -     Wonders are many, but none          none is more wonderous than man.   Man moves over the grey sea,          using the wind and storm,          daring the depths and surges.......   Language and thoughts          light and rapid as wind          man has taught himself these, and has learnt          the ways of living in town and city,          shelter from inhospitable frost,          escape from the arrows of rain          cunning, cunning is man.   Wise though his plans are          artful beyond all dreams          they carry him both to evil and to good .
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The whole India was shoked on July 16 when the various news channels broadcasted news of fire at  Kumbakonam , India. They reported that 93 children died in the fire which originated at the kitchen of the private school. But the question is : who is to blame for the devastating fire? The other day the I read in a leading newspaper , the letter of a person who said that the government should take measure to prevent fire, but is it possible for the government to put and end to such mishaps? It is us who is to blame.  We Indians are so careless that we don't even value human life. For safety, whether it is from fire or from any other accidents, we must change this attitude of ours. We, the people, must be cautious first. If I once cycle around in my cycle in out small town I have to remain alert that a child, unattended, don't fall before me. I often see children running around in the road or some stupid drivers driving at unimaginable speed or some young people showing tricks on their bikes. If the circumstances remail like this than safety will always be a far-away dream in India.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Leonardo da Vinci’s Mona Lisa, the world’s most enduring symbol of feminine mystique, is actually a portrait of the virtuous wife of a family friend, who had five children, including two daughters who became nuns. After four centuries in which historians have debated the identity of the artist’s subject — with theories ranging from his mother to a Florentine prostitute — new research has supported the claim first made in 1550: that she was Lisa Gherardini, the wife of a wealthy silk merchant. Giuseppe Pallanti, a teacher from Florence who has spent 25 years researching the city’s archives, has discovered the first clear evidence that da Vinci’s family was closely connected to the silk trader, Ser Francesco del Giocondo, who married Lisa in 1495. Pallanti has also established that Giorgio Vasari, the Italian biographer of Renaissance artists who, in 1550, named the silk merchant’s wife as the subject of the portrait, was a credible source, having known the Giocondo family personally. For centuries, the Mona Lisa portrait has also been known by the alternative name, La Gioconda, in acknowledgement of the Vasari claim. However, the enigmatic nature of the work and the inscrutable smile of its subject have spawned many alternative theories — encouraged by the fact that, unlike most other portraits of the time, the panel is unsigned, undated and bears nothing to indicate the sitter’s name. Among those who have been suggested as possible subjects are Isabella d’Este, Isabella Gualanda and Cecilia Gallerani, Italian society figures of their time and various courtesans and prostitutes. The artist’s mother has also been identified as the sitter. Yet another theory — based on the discovery that da Vinci’s own facial features can be closely aligned with those of the Mona Lisa — has the painting as a playful self-portrait of the artist, now widely believed to have been homosexual, in female form. Now, after delving deeply into Florence’s state archives, Pallanti has discovered that Leonardo’s father — a local notary, Ser Piero da Vinci — knew Ser Francesco del Giocondo for many years. Ser Piero, it transpires, drew up a number of deeds for Ser Francesco and his brother, including one in 1497 to settle a dispute with friars in Florence over the terms of a loan. “All the indications are that Leonardo’s father and Mona Lisa’s husband knew each other before she was painted, and socialised together,” said Pallanti. “The two lived almost round the corner from each other. “The portrait of Mona Lisa, done when Lisa Gherardini was aged about 24, was probably commissioned by Leonardo’s father himself for his friends, as he is known to have done on at least one other occasion. “This would have been Ser Piero’s way of giving a helping hand to his son, who was hopelessly vague when it came to money matters.” Pallanti also found the registration of the wedding on March 5, 1495, between Lisa, then 16, and Ser Francesco, who was 14 years her senior. His first wife, Camilla Rucellai, had died the previous year. The teacher found Ser Francesco’s will, which came into force on his death in 1538. In it, he described Lisa as his “beloved” and “ingenuous wife” — meaning loyal, honest and noble of spirit. Pallanti also uncovered records of the births of four of the couple’s five children: Piero, born in 1496, Camilla — apparently named out of respect for Ser Francesco’s first wife — in 1499, Andrea in 1502, and Giocondo in 1507. Camilla and her younger sister later took religious vows and spent the remainder of their lives in convents. Pallanti said he had found no record of Lisa’s death, which could have occurred any time between 1540 — when the local registry of deaths was in chaos, with many blank pages — and 1570, after which diligent recording was resumed. But he did find a deed which Lisa made in 1539 — the year after her husband died — in which she transferred ownership of a farm in Chianti, which had been her dowry, to her youngest daughter, the nun Sister Ludovica. Pallanti said this transfer had probably been done in exchange for the nun agreeing to look after her mother, who would then have been 60. Pallanti has been praised by other scholars for helping to solve the Mona Lisa mystery. He presented his findings in a short book just published. Riccardo Nencini, the president of the council of Tuscany’s regional government, which hosted the book’s presentation, said: “It may not prove beyond the shadow of a doubt that Lisa Gherardini and the Mona Lisa were one and the same. But with the evidence it offers, it comes pretty close.”
     

    
</post>


</Blog>