<Blog>

<date>06,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Damn its about time this stupid website lets me write...  Well he dumped me Wednesday.... and I didn't really even talk to him anyway- I guess that wasn't enough space for him. that's so stupid. Nothing has even changed except now I stop trying to attempt to get a hello out of him, so I'm not really upset about it- Happy couples still piss me off but thats nothing new.  And for a while now I've been feeling like shit for doing things Anita does or liking stuff she does. I don't mean to but I look up to her and she kinda rubbs off on me. And she may say she's just giving me shit about it but I know it must aggravate her to some extent. And I also feel crappy when I "kill" things that were before funny. so I try to think about what I'm going to say and make sure its not stupid or overdone. I just find it awesome when people laugh at things I say or do, especially her. And the knowledge that it is stupid just recks my mood- good thing it doesn't stay that way all day.          Lunch is so lonely-OMG... nothing but a mundane library to listen to music and hide my ice stash in... and today I sat in a hall way and Kyle whitehurst was in there being so stupid - "You know why I'm still here? Not only because I'm not a senior but because I'm-a one baaaaddaaassssss bitch" (i only remember it perfect cause he said it twice and it pissed me off both times). I hate how people think they're the shit because of the trouble and disrespect they give other people. I mean, what the hell?! He claims that he has met snoop dog and raps all the time as if he wrote it- drives me nuts. Sorry just venting anger- today was pretty shitty for such tiny reasons combining that I don't remember them all. At least the lunch Ice was good today (until I had to take a Porter piss like no other) bad English class- and then Turkey Jr. was taking her time to finish her stupid brochure so I was late for chemistry and felt so stupid again for not knowing what I was doing, and for Matt, Daniel and George laughing at me and hurting me with the curtain. I just wanted to cry but I was too pissed off to. Especially with Chris sitting there being all happy. Now I know why me being happy pisses people off sometimes...thanks again Chris. Oh, and of course I read the wrong chapter for history the one time I complete the reading at home- so then I felt like I was completely cheating and Im so sick of doing that. Because everyone around me is aware that I'm not really smart- just a cheater. I dont think I am completely, if I knew what I was doing and didn't have such stupid teachers I wouldn't need to cheat. I know it pisses George off; whenever I even ask him a question he refuses to answer.  You know, I wouldnt mind being alone all the time if people didn't notice I was- I find sitting by myself at lunch really embarrassing-only because there are snobby people around to sit and laugh about it (not that I would be significant enough to enter a discussion but its there mentally). I really like having music to listen to all day, Its like I'm escaping everything and venting anger in my own strange way, just to totally block out everyone and get through the day in solitude. Jeff once again mentioned I shouldn't base my life on guys and try to be free (no thanks I don't prefer to drink or smoke)- but then he said in other ways like when I'm alone to do what I want and not care - and I realized I don't act casual when I'm alone either- I sing but usually looking out a window to make sure no one is around or even walking by my house ( and generally to practice not to just be stupid)- Its really depressing. Its like I'm achieving nothing by being alone. And I take attention to a whole new level- maybe cause of competing for attention from my parents when I was little. Thats what makes me happy- Not the excessive kind though cause I stop believeing it. Also I really don't know what to say to it.    So, basically, since everything is crappy in some way or another, I'm in a really pissy mood.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Two more weeks, two more weeks, la la la la la la la- I'm still going.  I WROTE A NEW SONG!! THANK YOU CHRIS FOR BEING SUCH AN ASSHOLE!! I guess that's something positive about this relationship. For some reason I've had writer's block for making songs for a while but now I'm getting more ideas and I even got a piano background going for it- fun stuff. Here are the lyrics so far:  "Wasted Time"  Verse 1: Can you treat me like a person? Instead of someone that you met today. Don't pretend that I'm a stranger. Don't allow yourself to walk away (from me)  Bridge: My heart has grown so cold, I don't know if I can take it anymore!  Chorus: I just wanna be near you, Just wanna feel myself in your arms, I just wanna hear you Tell me that you care sometimes,  I just wanna love you, More than you'll ever know, I don't wanna realize I've wasted me time on you (that I've wasted my time on you)  Verse 2: Stop trying to make excuses You're the only one that they work for Why don't you ever want to see me? I don't even know you anymore  Bridge   Chorus  Yeah- I'm not quite done with it yet but I will finish it eventually. So happy!  Well the producer person was really really impressed after I sang "fallin" but I don't think I want to go for that- it was pretty much centered around a 14 year old Spanish singing girl who looks pretty cocky and probably thinks she deserves royal treatment. uhh no thanks... "ALL FOR VERSAILLES"  blah blah blah "we're a family" eesh. I have other routes I can take that would be better than that. Now I want my pictures back...  Besides, his demo sucks and I wouldn't want to sing his kind of music.
     
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Don't you hate when people tell you your problems are miniscule? That they've been through worse and you need to stop being a pussy and get over it? Well they're just arrogant, because everyone gets weak sometimes, and it will always have a different extremity than other people's issues. And anyone that says their life is perfect is in denial, but maybe that's how people should be. Why mope about things and analyze the life around you till you put yourself in a corner of neverending depression? What help will that provide in the end? Closure? No, because a memory of whatever magnitude you think of doesn't just become forgotten- unless you focus your thoughts elsewhere, which is what I do. At least the problems that bother me go away fairly quickly and don't totally control me for months. And I just found a GIANT tortilla chip in my bag of chips, simple entertainment, and a perfect distraction. With all this talk of food you'd think I was one of those 400lb people who broke the comp chair right? quite the contrary at 117lbs and 5'6"... I'm so damn lucky
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Another Church choir performance,eh- ok. Ever since my Mom got her new job, its been so weird. She's superbly happy, and very generous with her money-she bought me 4 outfits to wear to church...a.k.a.- dresses... and 2 plain simple shirts, nothing special about them but so wonderful!!! I love plain stuff, is that weird? Plain food, plain clothes, plain shoes... who knows... I'm proud. I got to hang out with Cory yesterday, catch up on things- And Matt Brewer too. George just happened to show up at his house also but he was NICE to me this time! It's all so shocking... I guess he was just bored this school year and I was nearby and got offended easily so, damn wish I knew that sooner. It was SO cool to talk to Matt's parents again though, I love them. And I saw a church friend at Fry's today and got to chat for a while. Its just been very...interesting in the past DAY- strange how that works. And MAYBE, I'll get my permit Wednesday...shit, it's taking forever! Just watch it get postponed AGAIN. I'm almost 17 damnit! So sad... Its funny, I downloaded this song off of Limewire, "I Thought About You" by Frank Sinatra... I just can't get enough of it- I've been listening to it for a couple weeks now and It doesn't tire me the least bit. Its been very calming, which I don't quite understand why but it's a great feeling.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I really wish I liked Mexican food. I eat at a particular Mexican restaurant almost weekly and I usually get either french fries and a cheese crisp of fried ice cream... waiters find me so weird, along with my family, oh well. I don't eat at China Star either...I only eat rice and french fries there, and that's not worth 8 bucks...no sir. And don't even get me started on Red Lobster (or any other sea food restaurant)- I can't even go there, ewww. Sub places too- no thanks. Anywho, the tortilla chips helped me much on feeling stuffed.    
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I forgot to mention something that happened yesterday that was quite interesting... I guess my  Mom  found a prank on my driveway meant for me, it was a 3ft tall, 1ft wide brownish cylinder with the words "Suck a big penis" "cock" and "Dick" on it, with a little white to/from sticker with a bunch of curvy blue marks which I couldn't decipher. It was actually funny. Cause my mom doesn't care, and I don't care- Just a really interesting prank. Real mature... was it Mr.James Markos(or Mrs.,same difference)? The big red tomato claiming to "Be the mature one in all this drama" while talking crap behind my back like a 7 year old? That just doesn't mix quite as well as it should... With all this combined, I feel like the winner of this pathetic situation called a "fight" or "battle". Who knows. All I know is im 100% amused. God I love being happy. Nothing can bring you down, nothing blown out of proportion from being in a bad mood "I want to die!" ~u huh voice of self pity. I love life at this very moment, I just can't get enough of it. And something tells me I must always listen to perky, fun-loving music, because it helps so much. Who needs to get drunk at a time like this? Mr. Roseberry does, that's for sure. And that is something to laugh at, such an obsession. I LOVE LIFE! I am at the top right now.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OK of course I didn't end up going outside, I got distracted and suddenly had to make cupcakes. The gathering was fun, George was being normal again, so that was pretty crazy. And I took a fake SAT today and scored 1090 out of 1600 (570 on math and 520 on verbal)- I'm proud. It was just a fun day, I got to see my sister and go to a brand new panda express nearby!!!! mMmM steamed rice w/salt... And then I went out with Brandon, Gina and Gwen to Olive Garden where I indulged myself in yummy breadsticks, Just the right tint of garlic. Strange how there's never much to write about when you're happy. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Its weird to look at life through appreciative eyes, every detail of nature takes a new form- it's very comforting. I think I'll go outside now, its a beautiful day, heat and all.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ahhh the fresh music of summer has arrived into my ears. Such a heavy burden lifted- 5 A's and 1 B, the B being 1.2% away from an A... Someday before I graduate, I will get straight A's, I have to. Freshman year doesn't count... Graduation was so sad, I cried when Brandon Chairez and Amber walked up- thats about it though. What will become of me a year from now? I will have to start my life, no more petty high school responsibilities... I don't want to enter into the real world, not for a while. I'm just afraid I guess.  I keep getting these thoughts of how everything will be about 15 years from now, realizing how fast everything has passed by, reminiscing about all the lost memories, and I have a large fear that my overall feeling at that point will be dissatisfaction. I'll probably end up an overweight music teacher watching all the big stars on TV, knowing I didn't amount to anything I wanted to. Guess that's why I have 15 years to prove that wrong right? Exactly. Well another day, another SAT seminar. ZzZzZzZ goodness... And additionally, the test is in Chandler. North Phoenix and Chandler are two different planets, basically. I feel so bad for whom ever will end up taking me. It's not my fault I don't have a car in this case so...ha.    Jaywalking is so scary! Once you get to the halfway mark of the huge busy street, its nothing but panic in my eyes.  "What are they thinking about?, "Are they going to see me? I hope no one will have to stop or slow down for me, I feel bad" I'm sure it pisses them off, why wouldn't it?      Boredom: A psychological state resulting from any activity that lacks motivation, or from enforced continuance in an uninteresting situation. Strange how words can be defined in such a fancy way, especially how the words in the definition are more complicated than the word itself.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The weekend has been pretty cool. I ended up getting to see my sister and my marine friend Jon, it was nice to have my Friday night like they use to be. And Saturday I actually woke up at about 9, sad. So I went to my recent joined Christian band practice (and I found out the name of the band yesterday also- "No one else"). I like the name.I had to expand on my thinking in music and totally let go, come up with lyrics and harmonies quicker than I ever thought I could. I just felt really talented after it was all over and done with, even if Marcus(one of the band members)basically told me I suck a couple times. I was offended and for a time didn't want to sing anymore that day, just thinking I lost any creative juices I had- but you gotta put the stupid shit out of your mind and try again, just keep going. Can't give up ya know? Cause your potential is just waiting for you to work up to. No one is perfect the first minute they try something. And strangely enough, since I had to sing really loud at practice, church choir went really well also- I could hear myself singing- I just feel really accomplished. And yesterday after practice was over I got to hang out with Chris (Will's brother and singer in band)and talk to him, basically just getting to know him. And later on I went to Amber's graduation party- and I got buzzed so it was just a perky mood. Well something pretty shitty happened Friday night (just thought of it) I was at Missy's and whatnot, and Amir suddenly calls asking if I know Samantha (Kattau), "Yeah I do..(here we go, he thinks she's hot or something right?" He said he was at Rolando's with some friends and would call me back. He calls back, talking of a conversation him and Samantha had, "Yeah she all asked if we had sex and I said No, we did other stuff but that's it" and she replied "Oh, I thought she was more ~ho-ish~ than that" and I guess other things were said but he mentioned her saying "You're really cute, how'd she get with you???" and yadda yadda and he mentioned his friend Nick eventually coming up to them and calling her and her friend trash and told them to get out, in which they did. I felt like shit that night- I just wanted to cry- or how about just never go for anyone cause well, I'm too ugly for them right? According to Samantha? Saturday came along and the party was going on and I forget how the conversation came up and I told Amanda Nutting what happened. So she just went off about how Sam is a big shit talker and talked about Amy Gervasio too (whom I think is a bitch also but I wasn't going to say that out loud). So Amanda calls her up and asks about it yadda yadda- blah. I talked to her and she denied all of it and everything I asked her she corrected me on what she said--- I called Amir and suddenly the whole story wasn't blown completely out of proportion anymore. Shit. "Sorry Samantha, you know I would go to you first but she called you" was what I called her back with. I sat outside to discuss stupid lawsuits and the Kobe Bryant rape case, among other rape discussions with Amber's dad and a newfound acquaintance named Larry, all while being buzzed. It was very educational- I felt smart =) . I looked over in the house and I saw a bunch of ~popular~ seniors etc. in the room. "(what are they doing here??- I don't recall them ever talking to Amber before in my life"). So I go in, and they all come up saying they wanna beat up Samantha for me cause "blah blah bitch blah blah", I guess Amanda had been talking about it the whole time I was outside-which was a while.   "Well we're cool though I talked to her, no more high school shit going on." Everyone's drunk, my words are drowned out, and I leave there around 12. I really hope tomorrow doesn't bring some stupid scene at graduation, I don't think Samantha would understand it's not my fault. High School drama sucks, that's all I have to say. But I get a feeling it never stops, cause I guess Chris is facing the same crap, and he has been out of high school for what? 2 years? WHY? Why can't it just be over huh? Haha, the tag of this new shirt I've been wearing today still had the tag on.        
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      How can I describe today... I can't. I can't even believe the person existing today was me, but it was. Well the beginning was as any mundane day of school is, without seniors as well. I was in a conversation with Rachel about Ryan and you know what? I really do like him. It's weird how my mind does that, but Amir grows more and more distant to my heart as the realization that he doesn't have feelings for me sinks in. I'm scared that I'll grow weak again, I don't want that. But I just know I really honestly like Ryan. I like the way he is around me now, not trying to impress me, not caring if I think poorly of him, its just cool. And for some reason, I just wanted to randomly kiss him, to see what happens. I wanted to chicken out, cause that's not the kind of thing I do, but something in me was strong enough to go through with it. We were walking to 7th hour as we do everyday, and we just talked for a while and I gave him a usual hug goodbye and gave him a decent length of a kiss. The look on his face before I walked away was priceless, completely. I was shaking for at least 20 minutes through the class period, and had trouble signing yearbooks, it was funny. Class ended and I went to see him, he was still clueless. I honestly didn't know what to say, I don't know why I did it either. And I know everything that happened last time broke him pretty bad, and that was not what I wanted to happen at all. I just felt pressured ya know? And I felt like he wasn't being completely himself around me, and I didn't want that (well Amir was a big reason too but that's something different). I get a different vibe from him now, he's independent now. And maybe I've just become really fond of the friend he has become to me, I confuse that often. Shit, I don't know my own mind. I don't know a 100 percent answer on all of this, I shouldn't have done that, Damn you Rachel for pressuring me to do that. I'm not a freshman who goes of and goes out with several guys with the intention of breaking it off without a care of their feelings. Ryan doesn't deserve that, period. I don't want to hurt anyone. I have to give up on Amir though, there's not even an option. I have to. And nothing is a rebound in this whole thing- I've had 3 months, almost 4. Guess I'll have to let time progress on this.      Well, after the day had been totally jittery, I was waiting for a ride home- Nick and James Markos walk by. They were continuing to talk to each other as they walked by and then James said to Nick "Hey remember when we got 1st in the talent show?," And he made absolutely sure that I heard it. Its not even the context of what they said that really angers me, it's the fact that they're low enough to rub it in, in such a way of talking behind my back and me hearing it purposefully. Shit why am I even civil to them? Fuck them! I don't need that shit from them. Well I guess the main positive point of life at the moment is I can finally be around George and shrug off his crap, I just don't give a shit. Someday, I'll be able to slap someone like girls do in the movies to cheating boyfriends-- It will either be George or James Markos when the time comes, and it will be beautiful. That will be my Hollywood square for now as I wait for the real one =).        Oops, its Friday night with the option of seeing my sister or going to Band practice- looks like I'm doing neither for the moment. I just HAD to get my thoughts out, and you know what? It helped a lot since now I have a vivid picture of Markos's already red face with a purple hand mark (George works great too), my autograph in permanent marker, and him in a hopefully unconscious state from the bat I just happened to find in the process...
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         I love this song!! It's called "Time is Running Out" by Muse. I just have it on repeat. That really isn't good to do to really awesome music, but I don't care I guess. I gave Brandon Mah some otter pops today, and I caught him eating one at school! He's supposed to wait till they're frozen!-it's just not the same otherwise. My mom told me today that otter pops were how I got potty trained; she would have me stay there by giving me otter pops, knowing I'd have to pee from them at some point. Guess it worked, I'll have to try that on my kids (a long time from now).     Today has been very slow... Its so sad that the seniors are done with school now, vocal class was so empty, depressing. I hate seeing seniors leave, that just makes more room for stupid people, no one to look up too. =( . Well Edith's sister made vocal so that's cool. I don't think vocal will be as great next year, he is recruiting a lot of concert choir and I am not positive if they're all qualified, just not sure. Guess I'll have to see what happens...
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, I was talking to Brandon Mah and the next thing I know his "cousin" is talking to me, and said I was beautiful after I showed him a picture and a bunch of really nice things and the next thing I know its his uncle and then...just guess...It's good ol' George Botsko. Of all fucking people to trick me and make me feel stupid...shit. So I asked him why he was even there and why he was being nice to me to begin with "because underneath it all I am compassionate." Oh but of course, its not really George in the end but fucking Brandon Bowley. I feel SO dumb. And I don't know why I'm crying from it but it was just such a rollercoaster of a shocker when thinking it was George not being an ass, like I was being tricked again- in which I was. I hate feeling stupid, especially at home- it just doesn't happen here, usually. Yay! got distracted! So I'm ok now- Well the first part of the day was really good, a lot of my family had a surprise B-day party for my grandma, I had never seen her so shocked in my life, which she said herself also. It was awesome to see her have so much fun. I don't know how much longer she'll be here, cause I guess 6 months ago doctors found spots on her lungs and they've gotten bigger since then. I don't know what that means exactly but I'm pretty sure it is bad. I hope she'll be ok. Crap- choir practice tomorrow- almost forgot. And I'm actually going to do some homework at home for once----crazzyy. Countdown- 6 days! 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just read the strangest page about poop... it was really weird http://www.heptune.com/poop.html   thanks Brandon...haha. Well I got my project done 5 minutes before the lunch bell rang for English, good stuff.    I'm really confused right now, and I can't quite decipher all of it. Well, Dad issues/guilt trip going on lately right? So James and I go over there tonight and visit him and whatnot. I'm basically sitting there the whole time thinking of a way to approach things and wondering if James will pitch in on asking questions or something. So I finally ask him if he's doing other drugs besides pot and cigarettes- "No".. And then he went off rambling about his dedication to God, like he has been like that his whole life, and "WWJD?" and basically saying that's his highest priority now. That does not sound like my dad. Also, He kept mentioning how he has everything set up (financially) for us when he dies and that he wants to be buried at 61st and northern and that he has a feeling that his time will come soon. This is really weird. He barely sleeps but "isn't tired" even thought it looks like his eyes will droop any second, and his back is crazy on him. He is working way too hard. Why do I seem to be the only one in my family that isn't a workaholic? Wait, I know- I can't get a job! Guess that's ok. And with that whole big issues difference, Its not that I don't care, its that I don't want to think about it. There is a distinct difference in my opinion. But in everything going on, what can I do about it? My Dad is lying to us, and I can't accuse him since I'm not really one to suddenly have a say in his lifestyle- He wouldn't listen to me anyway. I think that would be like him setting house rules on me, as if he has been around to be a parent before(which isn't entirely his fault with the divorce and all). I would definitely see him more if he wasn't working all the time, but that's him, "Everything dies when you stop working". Well that's obviously not true- since he's working himself to death, almost literally. You know its weird, I almost want to cry right now but I have no reason. Just an overall dark mood.. Maybe I'm just hungry- emotions run high for me when I'm hungry. And tired too.     I hate warning signs. People are so stupid. "I didn't know the coffee was really hot- you guys need to put a label on all coffee lids now." Then again, why would a computer keyboard have a warning sticker on it regarding avoiding serious injury...What harm could a keyboard do? honestly. I don't think people keep computers near their bath tubs. If they do, let me know. Strangely enough, I feel better now that my train of thought has been diverted elsewhere. That's my system. Oh, and I found the whole fire fighters being arrested for arson quite ironic, "don't cha think?"     "I'm singing in the rain, just singin in the rain" ... Such a perky song. I should make a perky CD someday, would help in low moments. And maybe someday, I'll write a fully, 100 percent positive journal entry that doesn't involve me being "Emo". 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This homework is driving me nuts!!!! I got some crafty stuff for it but I don't know what to do once I've covered the pages! And what really sucks is I'm going to have to mention something about the girl raping girls...In front of George and Chris and everyone else in that class... Do you realize how much that is going to suck? REALLY bad. So now I'm staring at pipe cleaners, scrapbook paper, and foam kind of paper and I don't know what I'm going to put on it---- hopefully it will just come to me in time and everything will have a good ending huh? MAYBE?!?!? shit. Well anything is better than seeing the original child's book of "tough truck drivers" getting one of their trucks out of water, ANYTHING.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I ended up going to Will's b-day party..for a 1/2 hour. Tomas called me about it so, yeah I suppose. And then Amir came and rescued me (lol j/k) And we hung out for a while and went to Sonic for the usual Strawberry cream slushes and a large cup of ice, it was splendid. "Cherry chopstick"... so funny... I will never think of chapstick the same again. Well I got home yadda yadda, and my brother confronts me about everything in my life lately and why it took me so long to physically do something about George, and I really don't know- I guess I just thought it would eventually stop. And that led into a guilt trip of how I could possibly make my "miniscule" problems change me enough where I put it ahead of Missy... SORRRRY!!! shit... I'm not perfect, sue me. Besides, I wasn't the only busy person in the situation... wtf... And I figured out something about myself that is the main difference between my brother and I: He lets big problems get to him and bother him, and I let little things bother me. Our parent's divorce rippled a tug of war over James and I for at least 5 years, I didn't let it bother me, I disregarded it. But James, he suffered an extreme depression until his hookup with Missy snapped him out of it. My Dad's drug problem is something I don't think about, along with Missy's issues with Mike- James chooses to worry about it and "analyze" it and think about it more than necessary. But everything at school just sets me off badly while James could care less if his co workers hate him. And in turn, he talks to me saying I need to worry about the big picture and yadda yadda...why? I honestly don't really care ya know? I dont want to think about it, I don't want to cause a stupid issue, and I don't want to muddle into other people's business. But I have to feel bad for how my mind works. That's stupid. I keep my grades up, I try and not be a super bitch to people, I keep my morals in line, I obey my mother's wishes(for the most part), I stay behind the lines...isn't that enough? NOOOOO sirrE, I have to get all upset about everything outside of my daily life and cause havoc about it, all while focusing on what my life requires out of me. And no, letting people like George and people at school get to me is for "pussys" as my Dad says... Problems are all about perspective. In this case, I'm dyslexic with my issues. When my Dad's drugs eventually put him in a coffin, I can be regretful and curse my train of thought today, but that's the future. Right now, I'm just too tired to say "Hey Dad, stop doing drugs and spend your money in better ways so you won't have to borrow so much money from James, cause that's really fucked up...,and you need to prioritize your damn kids for once too." The only reason I would have the push to say anything would be for James's sake, cause that is honestly jakked up, but I don't know- I think its selfish of me to try and change him to make  me  a bigger priority than his job and his drugs. I wonder how Rhonda is doing...She can't really put her foot down, otherwise BU'CAH! She's out of the house. And I guess he doesn't listen to James all that much anymore. I just wouldn't know how to bring it up. I never see him as it is, just once every few weeks or so... Just not good timing. He keeps thinking that all he has to do is give me money and he's a good parent..ok. whatever. Oh, and pressure James to beat up George over my mental issue. Real smart there Dad. I don't know it's weird how things have changed. I remember thinking he was the smartest person on the planet growing up, but now he just sounds like everything deleted. And knowing of how he cheated on Rhonda at one time and checked out a girl that looked my age right in front of me once---just makes me lose respect for him. So why am I so poorly looked upon for blocking out all of his bullshit? I don't HAVE to make it my problem to mope and think about. "Worrying is like a rocking chair- It gives you something to do but it gets you nowhere"- Van Wilder
     
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Reading is complete, all in all it is not worth reading, well as least not something appealing to the typical girl. I liked the whole demonic spirit idea, and how it gives a different perspective to psychology, since the psychologist in a new body ends up in a mental institution- smart- but what a typical male writer; with the detailed girl on girl scenes, makes me want to read another book for this project. No time I guess. Maybe there is time... its 5:42PM, it would have to be less than 200 pgs to work though... damnit! Well I had a piano recital yesterday, went ok I suppose. All the uncomfortable shoes took a toll on my feet though, got a nice cut from the showy thong sandals, weird mom. Hung out with Anita for a while, and then went to band practice. Yeah, I guess I'm in a Christian band now... don't know the name of it, and just met the other members yesterday. 10:30, Amir calls.WHOA. And after telling him I'm just at a band practice, he still wants to come over. So I'm overwhelmed with happiness, I get to see him. He loved the band, a little more than I thought he would actually. kinda weird. And then he made some comment to Chris that "when you get famous you're buying me a car"...stupid Amir... just dumb...well we left just before 12, and I went in my house to get a blanket and some pillows so we could lay in the back of the truck. My brother just happened to be awake so he could ask what I'm up to and be all suspicious...no no... not good. But eventually he let me go, only to have to return a 1/2 hour later. We just kissed anyway, spaz's... And I got to talking to Amir when I got home and I finally admitted I still felt the same way I did 3 months ago, and how I really do love him and how happy he makes me just by calling etc. , and he said he was like that a while ago when I was with other people. HE NEVER TOLD ME THAT! If I had the slightest clue that he really did care, and he really meant that, I'd go for it in a second, but I never took him seriously. And now it's too late. So maybe I should honestly let it go... just stop. Cause something bad will happen in the end and I don't want that.(wow I should uhh write a song about that or something...~another song about Amir...) So what to do tonight? no clue, think I'll just stay home or something. Well, that's what I should do...
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I finally know what I'm doing in Chemistry! It's so wonderful to depend on myself again. And I've grown out of feeling paranoid of being hated by everyone, you know- who cares- it happens to everyone. And the world isn't tumbling down on me, some people (like George) just press their problems on the ones conveniently around them... It's their problem, not mine. I was even paranoid about Anita, but lately things have been like they use to be and I can laugh again. I got Vice President for Art club next year and Publicity manager for Just One Interact (w/Anita). I'm excited. And I finally got to see my sis yesterday, it's been a while. And she's friends with Tara again, which I fully support- since Tara is pregnant now and has a husband etc., I'm sure she has grown to be a different person. And Rachel and I are really tight now, its awesome. So, my dark ages ended late, but better late than never. I have to read an outside book for English, and I chose Ghost Killer by Scott Chandler. I was expecting it to be a total murder, gore fest etc., with a possible love development right? NO! So far, a spirit (Ghost Killer)possessed a male body and raped girls and killed them in a specific way, until that body died and he has no choice but to possess the nearest body to it, a girl-- So he/she whatever still rapes girls and so there's lesbo scenes... wtf... It reminds me of that one episode of South park when Mr. Garitson (sp?) writes a lesbo book that mentioned the penis a bazillion times...    Anywho, Amir just stopped by! This is just a wonderful day honest. And While I was gone, Alex wrote me some stuff and it completely made me feel better! I'm not alone, ya know? So my wallowing stage is over I think, for the most part. This, of course, is subject to change- because I have weak points fairly often, and with that George would be the first to break my "suit" as my mother refers to it. Being able to laugh at Chris for his Roid rage imitations is much helpful in getting back to normal. You know what? I think this whole George situation had simply blinded my thought of other friends existing anymore, I felt as if everyone agreed with him, but they don't. I do have friends at this school, I kinda just forgot I guess, which is very easy to do when you keep to yourself. Right now I'm completely overwhelmed with satisfaction because...I'm peachy again...finally. I even have a sincere smile on my face as I'm typing. In a strange and unique way, I'm free...
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I had most of my seats changed today to be further away from George, its working nicely. And I had my music on all day and a book to focus on, didn't hear George either. ahhhhh...beautiful day...! And 2 weeks from now- I will be done with school- DONE. Well homework time.  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Officially, after 5 months of complete soberness, I can handle alchohol again. I'm happy, and still buzzed...on a Tuesday... HAHAHAHHA! HAHAHAHA!! I just feel like laughing, don't know why. Well, I came really close to eating chicken but.. just couldn't do it.  Anywho, well the asshole formerly known as George is continuing with his annoying rudeness. But today was different than most- Monday I sat away from him the whole day so I heard and saw no George, but today, since I had to sit by him since everyone was back, I didn't give a shit about anything he said. It was awesome. He told me to go away and I didn't listen, he basically called Anita and I stupid, which I disregarded, and he pushed my desk away from him, in which I pushed it further. These are all so small, but positive steps toward inner strength. I don't have anyone's support on this whole thing anymore, so I have to do it myself. NHS nominations were today, I could tell by the quick end of the vote that pretty much no one voted for me - I'm not surprised, but I feel like shit. I really don't like being in the same classes with the same people anymore. I just feel like I have to depend on others for partner projects etc., in which they would probably be more content without me there. If I could understand and accomplish everything on my own, I'd be fine. But I feel so dumb having to ask for help or find a partner/group to be in. Its like being the last person selected for a kickball game, just a situation you don't want to be in. At least the stuff in English flatters musically inclined people to where I can figure it out. So what's left? nothing. I guess Isaiah hates me now, and I'm sure he will never talk to me again. That's how I know he didn't really care about me, all I had to do was say I just see him as a friend and he was quick to be angered and erase himself from my life forever. For most of the people I've encountered in my life, I'm fairly positive my death would make no remorseful impact. That's sad. What is so annoying about me? I'm a "big mouth" too I've heard now. Conceited as usual too. guess that's not much too miss, or to consider anything other than annoying. Not to mention I'm "paranoid" and pathetic. Well if my journal is unappealing and naggish to you people, stop reading. Because I have nothing and no one else to nag to anymore. no one cares. I've tried conforming to personalities, but that's fake, I've tried being nothing but kind to people, but I get stepped on, and I've tried not giving a shit but now I'm alone. so maybe my only solution is to stop trying, just stop caring, stop talking. I can sit now and read, listen to music and do nothing more than observe everyone and their sociable lives, watch as people laugh at drawings I will never see and never understand, listen to shit that people give me, remembering I'm actually not worth their time, and to know that my only friends lie in places that don't get enough of me to be annoyed by. I'll "go away",... you win again George. I hate crying. Oh but I'm "just crying for attention." right. OK, think whatever the fuck you want.      If you havent noticed, my buzz it totally gone. Well had my last co-ed vocal concert last night, Mrs. Sedgwick was really impressed so that was a bonus. I was being really snobbish cause I was saddened at how everyone(In my opinion) did better than me. I shouldn't give a shit, people have heard me enough at this prison they call Cortez, I should be done now. Oh and I caught Will in another lie- "Mr.Sedgwick told me you guys are going to have uniforms for sure next year, Rachael was there too."   and after talking to Rachael about it "We're having uniforms?! Are you serious?  .... No I never heard that." Damnit Will. God I feel stupid again, I almost believed him. FUCK ALL OF YOU! I dont give a shit if I'm being melodramatic about the events of my life, they are my issues that differ from the dream world of acceptance that I use to live in, and didn't know was a dream world till now. It's dissappointing. But on a super plus, Lauryn came up to me yesterday defending herself on a rumor I never heard, and she mentioned how Ryan jumped down he throat defending me(which Lauryn said was a total misunderstanding), THANK YOU RYAN, shit I just can't seem to thank you enough. wow, I exist to someone. Gotta remember that. Summarily, I might get shit for this entry since I'm being pathetic and yadda yadda bladda "ugh shut up" but you know what? Fuck off, seriously, I DONT GIVE A FUCKING SHIT ABOUT PEOPLE WHO DONT GIVE A SHIT ABOUT ME ANYMORE.   Goodbye dreamworld, hello real life of solitude 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well yesterday,  both  of my parents noticed I was really upset and when I said what was going on, my Dad wanted to have people beat him up and my mom wanted me to ignore it. Yeah, alright, smart mom, I'll keep trying to. I shrugged off my Dad's stuff cause I just think its dumb but I guess he called my brother and so now him, Erik and Amir want to go talk to him, I don't want ANYTHING to be done about it! Just leave it alone, because I'm the only one who gets really bothered by him, and it's just him being a stupid asshole. Well that's not completely true, because he doesn't care when he makes me cry (he thinks I do it for attention) and when I tell him to stop(completely serious) he laughs- and I have said it so many times its not even funny. That's all I want though, just for him to stop talking to me and pretend I don't exist. That way, I can get on with my life and feel like myself at school. Well today I helped pack food boxes at St. Mary's food bank, Adam, Anita and Chris were there also. And Chris's little jokes didn't bother me at all... I'm starting to wonder if Chris had affected me so much this whole time because of George. Cause he was the only one laughing ya know? I wasn't being double teamed in a serious way. And guess what? Of all food to be packing, I was packing rice... isn't that weird? (haha Brandon). I had never seen so much rice before in my life. So many bags... Homework time!!!...
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Although I've heard advice just like that today, hearing it in that way makes me come back to reality, I feel like my normal strong self again. Thanks. =)
     
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wish I was strong enough to remember that everyday... I wish George was  dead , or for him to move far away where I will never see him again. He just makes me so miserable. And I'm a loner too, just to add. I didn't want to stay in Chemistry another minute to WATCH people talk to each other as I'm antisocially in a corner. It is my fault that life is like this now, but I just don't feel right talking to people anymore. So 2 minutes before the bell rang, I walked out and went toward Sedgwick's. Bell rings, George walked by  "Someone got written up for ditching class..."  WHY DOES HE ALWAYS WIN?!?! And now, I've noticed that he tries to do this to me-- everything on purpose. He kept glaring at my drawing and then me, to piss me off. And what a coincidence, him and Chris just happened to end up sitting by me for the 3 hour AP hist test (which sucked and I probably failed it). Even Daniel acts different towards me now, I feel like he doesn't care anymore. Which is understandable, (Valerie) no one likes talking to her when she complains all the time, just as no one probably likes talking to me since I'm always unhappy and crying in class. I found something to distract me though, spinning my ruler around a pencil. I just keep repeating "the pencil is strong, it keeps going, the ruler might distract it and bother it, but it keeps going.. have Strength. have strength." And strangely enough, George kept trying to knock it off, how symbolic... Come to think of it, maybe that's why Ryan, Rachael and Brandon seem to be the only people that talk to me now, they don't see me in class when George is around. They see me after class and right when I feel like I'm on the verge of breaking down, they give a smile and make me feel like I matter. Thank you. What was really really weird, as soon as Alex Salazar sat himself between me and George, I felt happier, and I was talking again. I HATE GEORGE! I HATE HIM SO MUCH, it makes me sick. You'd think me saying that would have no meaning since I "hated" Will last week and I talk to him now- But I know he's a patheologial liar, and there's nothing I can do but laugh about it. Ok, Chris did some slurping noise at me and I know its some inside joke but I don't know what it means, if anyone else knows, please tell me, cause it's bothering me that I don't get it. I hate inside jokes that involve me being laughed at. That's all that seems to happen now.         I went to Will's house today to work with Chris (Will's brother) it went well, he has a lot of ideas for my songs, and he said something that I can't seem to shrug off  "After high school sucks; you find out who your real friends are."  that's sad.      Question: Does anyone else have an extreme discomfort with their door being open when talking on the phone or being online? For some reason, I can't stand being on the phone when I know people in my house can overhear my conversation. Just bothers me a lot. ----And I think a lot more people read this than I even knew of. If you ever have a comment here's my email : SparklyBubble621@aol.com. I'm just really lonely I guess. lonely... Well on a more positive note, I ate lunch today =) shocker. IT IS SO HOTT OUTSIDE!!! I was a super cherry once I finished walking... it sucked.       
     
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        "no matter how cruel someone is to you, you can't take it personally - they're a victim of their own experiences and circumstances..maybe they should get over it, but don't be hurt when they try getting over it by taking it out on you.."  - Brandon Mah  I'm going to live by that. That's fucking awesome. Good journal, good stuff. So wise... Sorry, lol But this whole George crap has had no reason and that quote is enough for me. THANK YOU BRANDON!
     
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well good news, Edith and I got 2nd place,yay woo hoo... Yes, I know that's really good for 16 acts being involved, and the fact that we only lost by 3 points, but we lost to James and Nick... I dont care how good they did- A) they did a piece that they've been doing all year for speech team B)they didnt write it C) THEY'RE FUCKING JERKS!. As soon as Edith and I were announced 2nd they went crazy screaming and hugging each other like  "BOO YAH, Of course , we're better than you-DUH"  I felt so dumb- You gotta put on a happy face about it though yadda yadda.. Dude, if anyone else won I'd be ok. But then again, I just watched a tape of the performance and eww... My voice sounds horrible. Edith did fine, the piano was awesome, but hearing my voice..I just didn't like it. I am so pissed off it's not even funny. I suck.. But bonus- Will's brother was impressed, he was impressed...WOW. he's like...above me, lol. and he wants me in his band.? weird...   "I didn't know you could sing and play piano.."    "umm...what???? yeah....(fiddler etc)"   "well freshman year you weren't all..umm.. yeah but now, that was really good" .  And some people thought we should've won, so that was good to hear. And I guess our performance made Cristal Tafoya cry =) . But why was Chris impressed with me? I seriously think Edith did a hell of a lot better. Well if anything I guess Will should be more upset than anyone, a special ED girl beat him in making the talent show... I would never sing again if that happened to me, honestly. But it was really cool to hear people chanting my name before going up there. Ok I'll shut up about the talent show, life goes on. Ahhh the George trauma continues... I tried pretending not to care, but I couldn't. He is the only one who can effect me that badly, just because he had the worst ways of being cruel to me, doesn't give a shit if I were alive or dead, period. end of story. He could cause me the biggest depression and would find it humorous... like now. and then I'll fall for it when he's nice to me and totally forgive him just because he's being nice, and then another stupid comment. IT DRIVES ME NUTS!!!!. I feel so stupid in chemistry since I don't have a calculator and have no way of understanding what I'm supposed to do even if I tried, makes me feel so helpless, in a universal way. Haha, and I had a pathetic attempt to try and put a callous mask on for George by calling him stupid (I'm the stupid one who can't do the "easy" chem, or anything else in most classes). And of course he insulted my drawing too since I might get extra credit for it. Why does he give a shit? he's got all A's, sorry if I'm not smart enough for that. 2nd place...FUCK YOU JAMES! HAVE A GAY ORGY WITH NICK NOW SINCE THAT'S THE BASIS OF YOUR HUMOR! And if anyone who reads this has some problem with my disliking of Nick and James, you can go fuck yourself and stop reading. It's a journal for a reason, my words, my opinions, not giving a shit otherwise. Its not a sore loser thing, its a James and Nick thing. That's it. In conclusion, guys are assholes. Maybe I'm just the bitch, but oh well... "thanks" Well I just talked to my stepmom and she made me feel a lot better, I dont know why she did of all people since she didn't even go but..yeah. And my Dad liked Nick and James's piece....bastard.. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I feel soooo bad!.. Well for others unaware, I hadn't seen this guy in a year and for some reason, I confused his name and thought it was Isaac, when in fact it's Isaiah. Damn I felt dumb. I still feel dumb. I knew that..damnit. I use to remember everything but now I'm just stupid. I've never felt more embarrassed in my life. I dont ever want to talk to him again cause I'll always remember feeling stupid, lol. And I don't think people should go to the talent show... might be a waste of money ya know? My mom's boyfriend looks weird. And in a psycho way, he SLIGHTLY resembles my dad (at least the hair is alike) I guess she likes the curly-hair-mullet type..whatever floats her boat. He makes her happy, that's all that matters. I wonder what my Dad will do the day he finds out. And when will that be? Speaking of my Dad, he's starting to give me guilt trips about not calling him.I have a life now, so does he... maybe I should say something about his drug problem and stop talking to him until he decides he needs to quit. Yeah, I'd have to talk to James first, cause I don't think I'm even supposed to know. That's kinda sad though: "don't do drugs" "be good" blah blah blah about teaching proper habits of your children and not practicing the wrong yourself. Wow, what perfect parents I have: an alchoholic mother and drug addict dad... Why would I want to rebel at this point? Yay! I can be just like my uhhh...parents.... THAT'S SO COOL! Well I think my mom's issue is moderate and practically required in her bartending atmosphere. but the excess vodka honestly isn't neccessary. nasty. I guess its even worse when Isaiah notices "she smells like beer" Yeah, real mature there. Thanks for rubbing it in. A wonderful addition to my embarrassed mood. I dont know, he just made me feel utterly stupid with every word I said. I already feel that on a day to day basis, I don't need it after school.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      3 weeks from yesterday, I will be a senior, I will be out of school, and I will be rid of George for 12 weeks, it's most definitely something to be excited about.  I'm scared about college. I don't know where to go, but I feel like I want to go somewhere that's above everyone else, somewhere I can be proud of, and most of all, a place that I won't have to pay for... At first, I thought singing could carry me somewhere, but you know what? After I've looked around and noticed how much talent exists on this planet, what the hell was I thinking? Nothing makes me special; maybe at this school I can realize I'm somewhat valuble in choir but otherwise, I'm at the bottom rank of a large list of people. I could possibly have more to say if I had more voice lessons, or made state choir, haha. But since I didn't I can't say shit. SAT's are worrying me too, I doubt I'll do well. I've made no time to prepare for it, and I don't even know if my registration form was considered late or not. What happens if it were? that's so much money down the drain, my mom would kill me. Maybe I am good enough, my grades are, somewhat.     Why and how do people realize they want to go to school for business? why? There's no passion in that career, just money interest, which is normal I suppose, but lacking an inner satisfaction (at least I think so). All I know is if I ever end up working in a cubicle with the knowledge that gray walls are my boundaries, I'll find new gray walls in a mental institution. I dont know why I'm obsessed with being above the rest, I guess I just always feel unchangeably below others, I just want to be valued as something, and recognized as something special within a higher league, I guess. So maybe I can come back to a 10 year reunion and say "Hey George, who's the stupid one now?" I doubt I'll even give a shit about him by that time. Maybe that's why the pop industry is so appealing, what beats national fame? really.? Everyone knows you, not having to like you- but just to know who you are and possibly respect your capabilities. And then maybe all the people I see at Greenway that I remember from first grade will remember me too, lol- so far the ones I've mentioned remembering have either called me a stalker or feels bad for not having any clue of who I am. Brandon Mah had some thoughts for whether fellow school acquaintances would give a damn about him if he were to suddenly die, I know I would- and I'm sure many others feel the same. Maybe that's my biggest fear, being forgotten. Cause I would hope to be known after I died, remembered... thoughtful dude.. haha. Well on a more positive note, George has been talking to me less lately, so I've been in a better mood. And the talent show rehearsals went really well, alot of people think we'll win but I can't jinx it, cause anything can happen! And I'm drawing a picture of Mr.Erickson's dog Ozzy for him, it looks really good so far- I'm proud. And people can't say it's ugly, because that's just not something you can be negatively opinionated about-too much time taken to say otherwise. Well I'm off for now... yep 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Church choir didn't end up so bad today, the really really really good soprano(Roxanne) couldn't sing today from being sick, so I had to sing louder, not knowing the music. I was panicked a few times...thank god my sight-reading is ok. haha..thank god... lol ok anyways, Yesterday and today have been much better (What a coincidence, its May now...). I got my physical yesterday, TIME CONSUMING! ahh. And I met a lot of different people at Cortez I had never talked to or seen before, it was cool. And the guy giving me a physical was really cute so that was a bonus too. Otherwise, I did nothing yesterday but lounge at home, and I drew a really really accurate drawing of Amir, I'm proud of myself. I saw the school play, hahahahahahaha, It umm sucked! Well, Jessica Stephenson did a really good job, and I guess I gotta commend James and Nick as well as Manuel for being humorous. I feel bad for Jessica, she came at the wrong time--- damn she would have so much potential with Benton, It's really dissappointing... Well I guess today's agenda is going to a movie with Rachael, homework, and MAYBE working with Edith... I'll have to see.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SAT scores: verbal- 540 math- 630        Bummer... Oh well, it happens. Well this weekend... how do I start. HOT. Friday at about 6:45 I headed over to Toni's house, I was so excited to see her and the rest of her family, they're my family too. Her lil' brother is getting so big! It's crazy. But anywho, her Dad was somewhat cranky, and our other friend Ashli was a bit late getting there cause of her boyfriend (I guess from what I've gathered he is her complete world). Toni bet me a dollar that she'd start talking about her boyfriend within 15 minutes of being there. She started about 2 minutes after walking through the door, I lost. Back in elementary school, we were THE trio, best friends forever, nothing could change that- that was just how it was. And then after 5th grade, I moved. I kept in touch with Toni once every few months or so but Ashli grew more distant to me (mainly cause my mom always preferred Toni over and it grew out that way). The trio reunion was a bit awkward at first, I didn't know what to say to her, but over time things got better. After some time of conversation we had to get Toni's brother to sleep by making him think we were just pretending to sleep for their mom. In the hour of waiting, I attempted to write Ryan a letter, it was extremely sloppy and almost impossible to read until I found a digital clock to use for light, it ended up being 2 1/2 pages. 12:15, we go to Safeway for snacks; dumb me for buying chocolate milk. Anywho, then we all met at Mcdonald's, which was closed so no junk for me. I found out eventually Toni's sister is the one in girl scouts, hence why we're going along to California to go to Six Flags. Basically, I felt really white on this trip, 43 people went, and 3/4 of them at least, were black. Not trying to sound racial but I didn't know so many black people were in Girl Scouts. Kinda twisted my mindset a bit. And I found out 2 other girls I went to school with were going to stay in our hotel room, I was not going to try my usual routine of "Hey Angelina, remember me?? We both had Ms. Pickerel and you embarrassed the hell out of me by refusing not to dance in the skit I made as I followed the mess up with an Energizer bunny line..." Hell no. So at first I was thinking of not saying anything- which I didn't, until getting to the hotel room (but that's to tell later).       We get on the bus and eventually everyone falls asleep, except me- cause there were a crapload of loud obnoxious children yappin' their brains out till about 3AM, a dumbass movie (Mighty Ducks 3) playing, and a very uncomfortable 2 seats to attempt to sleep in. So I laid uncomfortably till the sun rose and people started waking up. THANK YOU MCDONALD'S. Ahhh hashbrowns... Looked like crap but oh well. I can't believe I chose to wear a 3/4 navy blue shirt with overalls for the events of that day, I had no idea what I was getting myself into.       Well anyways, we got to Six Flags at about 8:45, a.k.a another hour before even getting to go in the park. Toni viewed today as a day of shopping... for guys. I thought that would be fun too, but it got annoying fairly quickly. It's a distant place from home, who cares how they look. We first waited at the viper to find it was going to be closed for a little while, Superman was closed, everything was closed... Dejavu' was the first ride we went to, 1 hour wait- wellllll worth it, never screamed so much in that duration of time before. After that the heat was growing unbearable, every ride was line crazed, I was hungry, and VERY tired. The whole place was like a hike, uphill was a killer: "It's not that bad, just walk with your hips." "Ahh that was nice" say the superbly athletic Toni, as Ashli and I are dying 20ft behind her. We went over to the Superman ride anyway, to get a look at it- walking through the dark hallway was my favorite part of the whole day, it was so nice and cold in there, I wanted to just chill there all day. Of course, some weird guy with strange shaped ears told us we needed to leave, and that turned into a 20 minute conversation with him and Toni and Ashli kept talking to him, I don't get why, just being nice and very sociable I suppose. So then we went to get lunch, and of course Toni had to introduce herself to a bunch of strangers along the way, including a guy who makes the caricatures. *so hungry* They had a Panda Express... I was so excited, until I saw the prices... $8-9 a meal, I could imagine the price of my simple bowl of steamed rice being alike to the Diamondbacks price of $6 "for you convenience, we make no substitutions, no exceptions" Bye Lunch. Toni talked to another person, "He's so hot!" ugh. Instead I gave in to buying a desperately needed snow cone for $4, the heat was killing me. Eventually it got so unbearable I went to the restroom, took off my shirt and totally drenched it in the sink; I felt great after that. Went on the Ninja, decent I suppose, and then we finally found something Ashli would do...Spin Out, we went on it 3 times in a row, I felt really queasy after that... then Toni got food. It was 2:30 by that time, I was ready to leave at 12, I just wanted to go home. Well to pass time we decided to wait 3 hours to go on The Riddler's Revenge, NOT WORTH THE WAIT! And we met another 3 strangers waiting for that ride, I felt so antisocial, but you know what? I don't need to frolick around introducing myself and waving to random people...Just not in my nature. I gotta give Ashli a shitload of credit, she was willing to wait in those lines with us for no reason, just to hang out with us. I wouldn't even go to Six Flags if I had a fear of rollercoasters. 5:50, we got out of Riddler's Revenge. We had 10 minutes to get to the bus, so we RAN THE WHOLE WAY. The uphill KILLED me, I was fallin way behind, but we got there in time. I was a cherry at that point, a withered cherry. Not only were we on time, we didn't even leave to go to the buses till about 6:35.... that hell-run was for NOTHING. Bought a picture of the three of us for 12 bucks. And then we FINALLY got on the bus, which we had to run to since the parents got panicky.       I sat on the stinky, sweaty bus for an hour and a half, I never felt more dirty in my life. In that 3 hour wait for the ride all I thought about was how much I wanted a shower, and the thought never left my mind. I was hot, tired, sticky, sweaty, greased up hair, and VERY hungry. If I could yell at the world at that point I would've.       The hotel was nice, people rudely ran into the elevator as I was politely waiting for longer than them. I wanted to burst from complying to everyone's wants and allowing myself to be stepped on. I was second to get a shower. I would've stayed there forever if I had the time to. After that, I was ok, VERY ok. And crazy enough, both girls remembered me, so I didn't have to feel like a psycho stalker this time.        We eventually went to the nearby Mall for food, ate Rice and some chocolate chip cookie dough ice cream, and then I was the only happy one. Ashli was tired and cranky (understandably), and Toni was bored out of her mind with the desperation to rebel against everything and go clubbing. As time as gone by over the years, she has been obsessed with using her time away from home to its full extent, whenever she came over, she wanted to go out clubbing or something, even though I don't dance... And I always had felt like she wanted to be around my brother more, so her out of place wants in Cali fully raged me. Yeah, I didn't say anything, but someday I will. I just wanted to go to Virgin Records for one thing, "You've Got Mail." I FINALLY BOUGHT IT!!! HAHA BRANDON MAH!! We got to the hotel, Ashli passed out, and Toni stayed up for a wee bit, conversating with the only two guys our age at that trip, surprised? Sleep time for me.       Wake-up call 8AM, looked out the window and remembered why I love places near the ocean so much, cloudy mornings. I could wrap myself in the thought of it and be fully content. Packed up my over packed bag of 4 pairs of pants, 5 shirts, 3 sets of pj's, 7 pairs of underwear, 4 bras, 3 pairs of socks, and a lot more. yeah, that's a lot for 2 days but oh well, you never know what can happen on a trip, its always handy. Got to the ocean; seeing the face of a person who has basically never seen the ocean was amusing, very sentimental. First thing we did was walk out on the pier, I love the ocean, its so soothing. We got to the end and spent a while just looking down at the ocean, marveling its color and the starfish sticking to the pier. Then we laid on the sand for a while thinking of something to do, Toni wanted to walk along the ocean shopping around for guys (duh), Ashli wanted to relax there and eventually shop for her boyfriend, and I just wanted to swim or boogie board. Damn. So Toni and I got a couple boogie boards, which the whipped guys bought for us, Toni is loved. And then we met a few more strangers, damn the girl lifeguard recommending the next pier 2 miles away for better waves and hot guys, she then wanted to walk that whole way... Couldn't just go with the flow that time, so we stayed there and boogie boarded while Ashli watched (afraid of the ocean...), OUCH. You would walk out 20ft and waves 50% taller than us were already there, it was bad for boogie boarding, I got flipped around like crazy- scared for my life. The tide was unbelievable, I could barely keep my ground. When I actually did ride a wave to some extent I'd eventually go right into the sand, got sand all over me, very gross. Well after getting all banged up I went to change. As soon as I took off the bottom of my bikini, sand was all over the seat, top also... and it was in my hair also- didn't know till later that there were showers nearby, damn!. Well Luckily I wasn't changing in my seat, haha. Got most of the sand off the seat but oh well. Toni had to stay with her sister, so Ashli and I left to go shop for her boyfriend, Bought a lighthouse frame for Anita and a Starfish for Toni. On the way there we saw a sign that said "no stopping any time" and a stop sign 15ft behind it, we took a picture. And then we passed this store full of dresses I would never wear in my lifetime, and we found Toni, weird coincidence. They both were almost out of money and fell for a certain article of clothing there, 20 bucks each. So I was willing to pitch in. I almost left and then found a really elegant pink dress, decided to try it on, and I felt so revealed, but all four people there loved it and strongly insisted that I buy it, so I did- along with the same dress in purple for Toni, and a crochet green halter top for Ashli. That was a quick $64. Left the store in that dress, And finally got food! 2 slices of pizza. Then we went back to the beach and somehow found ourselves doin model shots, at least 10... oh well- they were entertained. Then we saw the disturbing image of a really large lady getting sand out of her crotch at the showers and before we knew it, we were back on the bus heading home, and watched the breakfast club- MY MOVIE hehe. That was the last movie so Toni wanted me to sing for her, and after that it spread to me singing on the bus microphone. Once I did that, people starting going up there to sing- even a little 4 year old girl singing "I'm feeling sexy...I'll be your naughty girl..." Damn Beyonce', now little girls are innocently singing about sex. And then I sang Fallin' for the VERY LAST time. People sang till we got to Phoenix and then I got to go home. =) Another day of volunteer work, so tired, burnt, sore from the hikes of doom, and I lost my voice for a time from all that salt water in my system. And then Ryan came over, I was really happy to finally see him, caught up on things. *still innocent* =). I guess all in all the weekend was eventful and definitely something to remember, but damn was it a pain in the ass! *note to self* : Don't go to a theme park in summertime. And don't get stepped on.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just saw it today, best romance movie EVER. I'm still crying from it, it was perfect in every way, no words can describe it. The setting of the place was so beautiful... I WANT TO FALL IN LOVE LIKE THAT!!! damnit. So precious. You ALL have to watch it, I don't care if you're a guy too macho to see it, just can't miss it. I could watch it a million times. Haha, computerized birds in the beginning.  Another day of serving lunch, and we're going back for another week! ahh... time to pack- gotta procrastinate that too...  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       "Here let me shake these Dr.Peppers!! What's your name? How old are you? I don't believe you. Let me frolick pass you!"  SHUT THE FUCK UP!!!!! - one more day of serving them lunch... I hate kids. Why would a person want one, seriously? I guess I'll change my mind in like 10 years, but for now, they just bug me.. Can I just slap one??? just one? That's all I ask, honest...  I finally cleaned my room today, I forgot what the floor looked like for a while. Measly 1250 meters of swimming as well, but one of the people that worked there asked about my habit of wearing 2 swimsuits, haha. I love swimming there, I feel so professional at swimming... Content.  Where are you Ryan? I haven't seen him in forever, I miss him.  Six Flags this weekend! YAY!!!! *I won't be scared* *I won't be scared*
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got my permit today, missed 3 this time. HAHA! And then I hung out with Matt on a lil' road trip to Prescott so he could sign something for school next year. Followed by the ghetto, kid-infested premises of their mall, and a usual trip to guitar center after arriving back to Phoenix. A fun day, all and all. So now I get to stare at this permit and go nowhere... but at least I have valid ID to view rated R movies huh? YEA! Damn I'm such a loser.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Holding anger is a poison. It eats you from inside. We think that hating is a weapon that attacks the person who harms us. But  hatred is a curved blade . And the harm we do. We do to ourselves."  Isn't that deep? Damn... I read the whole book today, "The Five People You Meet in Heaven" by Mitch Albom. I HIGHLY recommend it! It's the best I've ever read, made me cry and really gave a perspective check. And such a weird coincidence is, it goes through the guy's life through his birthdays, I don't really give a shit that I didn't do much for mine anymore. It's a day of the year, I was just being immature about it. I think the main reason why I was even mad was because a lot of people forgot, and I wouldnt never forget their's... as if that's even a big deal. By the time I was at the gym I felt a lot better, expectations for what a birthday should be completely diminished. And the confusion with the guy crap lately is gone too, I've gained my independence and don't long or need anyone anymore. I'm just content. The storm is over.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *Happy Birthday to me* ... anyone there? nope.   Thank you Anita! Wasn't stuck at home ~all~ day with your help =)
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Saying no has helped me lose another "friend", gee that's nice. Now I really can't trust guys period, they're ALL the same. I hate that so much! There's something wrong with me in so many ways and I can't even begin to figure it out. Bye Shane. Guess I'm just lame to think of simply as a friend huh? Of course.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I'm not happy, but I don't know why exactly. After writing a really long e-mail to my sister, I think I just don't like the changes over the past month or two. I don't talk to her as much anymore, I'm not fling crazy now-which has revealed many of my guy "friends" in a different light. Tom has taken over my mom's life, which she's really happy, but why couldn't she change for me and James but could change for some guy? She drinks less and acts normal now and everything, the family has noticed that she's happy now. Nothing I did for her made a difference in her happiness though. I feel like the household I'm in has been a nicely filled box, and she's trying to packed him in it now. Next thing you know he'll end up going to San Diego with us...At that point I'd say something. He doesn't compare to Rhonda, basically.  Guy situation has been driving me nuts lately, I don't know what to do- I guess I'll decide eventually.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1250 meters- aka 50 laps, my all time record of non stop swimming. I will beat it someday. Well I think God doesn't want me driving at this point, everything has kept me from getting my damn permit. Matt had called and told me his flight was cancelled so he could take me- (what?! yay!) - he helped me study and everything as we waited (it was sweet), just to eventually find out my birth certificate and social security card were required... of course, long drive for nothing. Thanks for telling me mom, geez. Rachel helped me discover the greatness of frozen capri sun...its really good. But you have to cut it open for the ice, otherwise there's no point. I wish I could write a shitload of stuff here like I used to but nothing happens in the summer, damnit. I guess I might do that community service of serving kids lunch again next week- on my birthday too... I'm happy Anita is willing to hang out with me that day, otherwise I'd be limited to a simple dinner at Bobby McGee's and that would be it- with Tom too..how lovely...
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You would not believe how degrading you can feel from losing intermediate spider solitaire 9 times in a row... Well I finally won a game after all that so I'm ok now. Got a haircut today that looks practically no different than before. Oh well. This weekend has been SO boring. Guess you can tell since I'm talking about spider solitaire right?....Yeah I'll shut up now.   Confirmed: Brandon Chairez is not dead 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I know when I am not understood; there's one particular common trait in all who don't know me- they simply don't understand my love for ice. I went to Manuel's for lunch with the family again (typical Saturday event) and I happen to have brought some ice water with me. I couldn't have just thrown away perfectly good ice, so I kept it and eventually started putting my ice from home in my restaurant ice water. My aunts stared at me as if I were some mental patient in need of serious psychological help. "You know it's bad for your teeth" "I heard eating ice means you're sexually frustrated" "It means you're lacking iron" ... Do you have ANY idea how many times I've heard all of that?! You'd think people would stop asking since I've had the same fetish throughout my childhood. The sound drove them nuts apparently, so I had to restrict myself, which was hard. I'm extremely addicted to it, and I won't die from it so why stop? You don't see me cause chaos when my Grandma or Dad smoke right next to me, or anyone else for that matter- and I hate smoke with a passion. Shit, I don't like smelling like Marlboro, vanilla is perfectly suitable for me. But I think they know now cause I simply leave the room when they do that, and I check the smell of my hair every couple minutes if I can't leave- just making sure I don't smell like smoke. Does anyone else do that or simply not care about it? As for my ice craze, I'm eating it as I type-should I smoke instead? huh???? Eww nasty.      Well something came up lately that bugs me. I honestly do like Matt, I've only just begun to get to know him and I'm enjoying every minute of it, but no matter what, I can't even think to pursue anything (not saying I assumed such a thing would happen - just hoped) because it would bother my brother too much, which I totally understand. Thinking of that in perspective, I wouldn't want him dating Toni all that much- (I wouldn't say anything) but it would be awkward. It does make me sad though, I guess I'll have to simply trust my brother on this one. He goes through enough in life already so... Stifled feelings.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Matt and I went out to lunch at TGI Friday's yesterday-He is such a fun guy to be around. what? why me? That whole situation confuses me, I just don't think he could see me any differently than friends. Guess I just have to hope for otherwise. And then I got to make tombstones, NO!- LAME! "Have some of your 3-D friends help you, it'll be fun" .... hahahahahahaa RIGHT. Well I ran out of paint so I have to wait till all that goes through- and if that doesn't happen then...shit. Went to gym last night to swim again, only 1750, sad. And then I hung out with Shane and others, I'm surprised that my mom has pushed my curfew to 1, strange. Innocent of all charges.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tired! Got to hang out with Matt today and yesterday- So I'm very happy that he calls wanting to hang out with just me- *WHOA*..We went to guitar center and to Zia records, something to do. I've never seen so many keyboards in my LIFE. It was really cool.  GYM mania! I went last night with James and Matt and this morning with Missy, It's a fresh feeling when finishing, accomplished. And after about 8 months of hiding from the sun, I finally sat out to tan today. There's not too much of a difference but a slight burn in some places, yay! Yes, this means I'm still pale white, but there's progress. Something that might end up pretty strange is, I really don't want my face being more tan and whatnot, guess that would look weird with a tan body though (well tan body is something thats far from now, of course but yeah) Yesterday started badly, home can be a boring place if you don't spend your time wisely... TV craze of poker. Yeah, and I gotta wait another week to get my permit.... its been taking forever! angry. oh well, That's life I guess
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WOW...I've been lied to this whole time. I can't even express how angry and betrayed I feel. I guess Amir is far from being a virgin, VERY far. And this whole time I thought he was different, that he wasn't like everyone else and I was special to him. Shit. BULL-FUCKING-SHIT. It's not that I'm upset because theres hidden feelings or something, cause there honestly isn't. I just wish I knew everything beforehand, heh- I would've been able to move on with my life so much sooner! FUCK YOU AMIR.  I hung out with his friend Shane all day today, it was really fun- just random, basically- he's really fun to be around. We went to get his oil changed and then looked at model houses that were AWESOME, and then hung out with another friend Robert at Quizno's. And near the end of the day we visited Amir so Shane could see the damage of his car. Amir just had a whole different form to me, he wasn't even attractive to me anymore. The first thing I noticed was how ape-ish his feet look, and just how stupid he really is. Everything has been a lie. Shit, even his whole story about him being sick of Nick and not wanting to talk to him anymore was a stupid white lie he pulled on me. It was the other way around as Amir was passed on to Robert, who is bothered by Amir now as well. Gee, I wonder why. God... I was SO blind. I don't want to trust people anymore. I thought I could but I can't. Just afraid to be stepped on again. Note to self: Don't trust ANYONE who just wants to be friends with benefits- they don't really give a shit about you and just want to get in your pants.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      P.S. Thanks, Julie
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, recently I was kinda upset and emailed an entry to myself, thinking it was a bit too personal to put on here, but I don't really care now so I'm just going to post it so I have it to remember and look back on when I get weak again:  June 3rd, 9:00PM    I have a confession: I'm a virgin slut. And I'm sick of it, which I say all the time, but I really mean it this time- I'm going to be a femme-bitch and say  FUCK YOU AMIR, DIE AND BURN IN HELL CAUSE IM NOT A HIGH SCHOOL PARTIER LIKE YOU-OK? men disgust me. people disgust me. I make excuses cause I'm in denial of realizing what I'm doing is simply wrong-nothing more to it. I can't handle problems, so I cover them up and that honestly makes me feel perky and bubbly- I'm ignoring my dark side. but now its yelling at me. I look up to my friend Anita in so many ways and tell her everything. And I take her advice- cause she's honest. and she doesn't sugarcoat my actions like I do. just reading this again is aggravating me, cause I can't even count how many times my history is repeating itself: make friends with a guy, become curious, have a fling, and realize its not right afterwards to utterly regret it. The moment arrives and I don't give a shit of who I am or should be. I'm not going to regret anymore, because this fucking-stupid-piece-of-shit repetition of events have combined together to tell me I'm a disfunctional person. I don't like who I am, only I can do anything about it, and I can't let having a boyfriend be my only route to restricting myself. I try to understand why I am the way I am,  and the only thing I can think of is my constant crave for random attention,because I lacked it growing up(James was the favorite confirmably back then)- and remembering what it was like to be rejected and not wanting to do that to people. But that in itself, is bad also. It may piss people off to be rejected but its better than sugarcoating your feelings till push comes to shove and you realize "hey I don't want to go out with you" and make it even worse. But those are just excuses, I know. I'm not perfect, no one is. and in the eyes of the typical partying student, I'm fretting over nothing, but my mind tells me much different. I don't respect my body, I stopped caring when I gave my heart out too soon and gave in to the moment without a title to discover myself as a mistake the next day. I had emotional boundaries of what I would do way back when. But as time has progressed, I act just like the perverted guys do, doing shit with people I don't even have feelings for, its attention.  But now, I don't see myself as someone who deserves anything, I don't think its right for people to like me, I'm boring, flat chested, and a virgin slut with few morals. I can tell myself all I want that my virginity gives me a few brownie points, but thats full of shit. it doesn't matter. thats what helps me sleep at night. I'm not going to promise anything this time-- just want to stop doing shit. I have to remember that saying no doesn't make me miss out on anything, not saying no just fucks everything up. thanks for reading. 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SAT's...hmm... what's the word I'm looking for to describe it...BORING! Woke up at 6 and left at 6:40, not knowing it was a 34 minute drive just as the map quest paper said, so I arrived 5 minutes early...or so I thought. The test didn't start until 8:30... Luckily, my cousin Casey just happened to be there (REALLY  small world) and I got to talk to her and catch up on things. Brevity: conciseness, damn I wish I knew that during the test, I even studied that word, damnit. Well it ended at 11:45, I feel bad that my brother had to do 2 hours worth of driving for the event... He even stopped by McDonald's... can't thank ya enough bro. And then I thought the SAT's were boring... No- they were nothing compared the  next few events of my day. At 4, my mom and I were supposed to go to this one girl's graduation party, but of course she had to stop by some sports bar for a while to conversate with a bunch of old people including her boyfriend, as he gave her a pat on the but hello...eww... You know, I honestly don't want to see that, really. If I had a boyfriend, I wouldn't let him randomly pat my but around my parents like I'm some little girl or something, gross. So yeah, sat there pretending to think and be entertained by the TV's and decorations throughout the bar as people smoked nearby... The owner of castles 'n' Coasters was hanging out with them too, quite a strange guy- reminded me of the guy from The Waterboy that you can't understand mixed with the stapler guy from Office Space... My mom is weird, she's CRAZY for this Tom guy... he's alright I guess, he's kinda growing on me a bit. She just glows with happiness now, which I am superbly happy about, cause I've never really seen her that happy. So uhh, props to ya. Well we finally left the bar, and headed toward 'Ashley's' house. I really didn't think things could get worse but I was totally wrong about that one. I walked in to see Ashley totally bored, acting like one of those snobby bitches too good to conversate with her family who was there for her, I tried to start a conversation but I really didn't know what to say to her, I don't care what's happening in her life, and I don't want to sit there feeling like I'm not wanted there. When going into the kitchen/ adult social scene, people were raving..  "OMG you've gotten so big! I remember when you were this (hand really low) tall!!!, OMG- Do you remember me?" "Ummm...no?" "Oh. well, ok" I was about 6 months old when these people saw me...What kind of psycho person has a memory at 6 months of age? Do I deserve a hidden guilt trip from not knowing who the hell they were?! HELL NO. So they just kept staring at me, like some display at a museum. Oh and then some friends of Ashley's arrived, looking just like her but one was sluttier, great first impression-honest... Of all strange things, Tom was the one to notice I was ready and waiting to leave, gained some brownie points on that one. I don't know if I've ever felt that relieved to leave a social gathering... From there we went to my cousins, which was fine by me cause I talk to them and see them all the time- nothing new. A bunch of us ended up watching the national spelling bee competition, starring Mr.Erickson Jr., Monaswi Gupta and Jackie's boyfriend, who ended up winning. The words were all in other languages, how do 8th graders know all those?! I don't get it! It was really entertaining though, they were so nervous, the Monaswi Gupta guy fainted during the event I guess. My cousin's have such good ice... I was satisfied. As soon as I got home at 10, my mom LET me go out with some friends till 12:30, I did nothing bad, just hung out with a few of Amir's friends, which is kinda weird since he wasn't there... My self respect points have been rising too! I feel so accomplished. Church choir went well with good ol' Mike- he put a lot on me for this one, felt important today, so yeah... That's my weekend.    I want to watch You've Got Mail!!! Brandon Mah rented it and got to watch it while I sit here, bastard. Frank: What about you, is there someone else?  Kathleen Kelly: No. No, but, but there's the dream of someone else. So cute...
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Poor Amir... He came over to show me his new car- a 95 white BMW, it was nice. And then I went over to his house and hung out with him and his sister, and I remembered that he still hadn't met Rachel, so we decided to go to her house. On the way there, we were at about 31st and peoria right by the Wendy's and Blockbuster etc. and there was a lot of traffic. he was driving 5mph and he didnt notice the car in front of him stop and he just crashed into her- at 5mph... I was in total shock, and Amir was PISSED off. He has no insurance, he's basically dead. Well the only good news is that the other car had practically NO damage, just a tiny bit of paint scratched off, but his car has a dent and a headlight fell off, which he wont be able to pay for since he is broke like no other from just buying the car. I honestly don't think its the biggest deal in the world, his car is fine, its just not as pretty as it was before. He should've waited till his insurance went through ya know? I think that's all I did today, I've been at home now debating on when I should start studying for SAT's tomorrow... and its already night-time. Oh well, I dont think there's much I can learn at this point to improve my score. And time has passed where there's only time to sleep now. Darn...
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Its like I saw the light, I'm free. He's just another guy, like anyone else, who just wants a fun time and live high school as society pressures. I just never saw it, I was so blind! Well I went to the gym twice! And I worked on arms and legs in the morning and swam 2500 at night, I'm proud. All the people that were trying to swim at the pool were all impressed wondering if I was ever going to stop, hahahaha 2500 is nothing! Especially when 500 was the most I swam without stopping. So tired... But Matt went too so that was cool! Very cool indeed. And during the day I went with Missy, and then went to David Kwan's to eat steamed rice w/salt..yum...
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well... I got to hang out with Matt Romig last night and talk to him, it was awesome- I had a blast. I need to learn how to play hailo... Other than my pathetic attempt to play that damned game well, things clicked very well- I'm still in a happy mood! I don't get it either, cause I've never had a perky peak last this long- not in a while. And also to where my happiness has no true source, just nothing bad is happening. Rachel stayed the night yesterday also, so many movies... but I spread the wealth of "Requiem for a Dream" to her, wow I LOVE that movie- despite it's cruel and depressing ending. I recommend everyone see it, its a true masterpiece in so many ways. And Matt had seen it too, that was really cool.  In all honesty, I've been extremely single and have been acting unaccordingly, but that stops now- my body is my own and no own else's and I have learned that I need to start respecting that, honest. =) Ever since school has ended I can grow my nails out again, its so weird, and annoying to type! Oh well... And I got a gym membership! So starting tomorrow at 5AM, I will be swimming again, and working out and getting stronger so maybe...JUST MAYBE, I can get a 1:15 in the 100 breastroke next year. Only 4 seconds to get rid of- I can do it.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Did I mention I'm a happy person recently? I've been blessed. Well to start, I think it was a week or so ago but I was at my house and some friends of my brother's came by- usual dog craze of barking at a new visitor, so I peek out of my room to see who it is: Matt Romig is his name, a particular guy I was utterly fond of a few years ago. He was a senior when I was a freshman, and was one of those people you "crush" on from afar, never thinking anything more of it, just that he was a million levels above me and would remain there forever and I would never even say hello (too shy and nervous). Seeing him in my house totally shocked me. I froze in my room- a double glance and I shut the door, hoping he wouldn't know I was staring. Every emotion from 2 years ago overwhelmed me completely. After he left, I wouldn't shut up at my brother. "You talk to him?" "How?" "What?." Go figure, they're good lifting buddies, WOW. And I found out that a week before that I fell asleep in this room and he came in here and used the computer while I was sleeping. I was paranoid as my brother laughed about it, pure torture- thank god I was wearing normal clothes and not my usual mother-like giant T-shirt. It was so pathetic of me, I was a Jr high kid with a crush all over again. But of course, I had still never talked to him before, never thought he would, cause I didn't know I existed in his knowledge- well besides the whole computer room thing as me being his little sister. I guess my brother slipped a sugarcoated version of my "boyband response", saying to him that I merely considered him attractive (thx bro), he was  flattered  - not finding it funny or hilarious, thought it was  "cool".  Well that's where today comes in: My brother, 2 of my cousins and I went to a Dbacks game and whatnot, and he calls James during the game...chitchat yadda yadda...  "Who's at the game with you"  "Oh, just my cousins and my sister"  "Tell her I said hi"  "You wanna tell her yourself?"   And just like that, I got to finally talk to him- I was so dumb! But can I be blamed for that? And he told me he wanted to hang out with  me  and my brother, get something to eat or something after the game was done with...WHAT?! And what was even dumber was the game was extremely loud so I could barely hear him at times, I felt like one of those old ladies with the grandkids yelling at her for saying "I can't hear you!" several times. Well the game took too long, so he says he will make it up to me another day- as if I deserve that. It's been 4 hours since that conversation went on, and I still feel..jittery. Does that make me boy crazy? Does it make me insubstantial to become this excited over a guy I've barely talked to in life? I'd hope not, but if it does- I don't care- because I'm still in total positive shock.
     
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Grapes of Wrath  is slowly draining every ounce of life I have, or had rather. I read  200  pages today (since I love to procrastinate)...  IF ANY OF YOU WANT TO LIVE DO NOT READ  200  PAGES OF A BORING BOOK AT ONCE!!!  It took me 10 hours to do so... and for any other even remotely interesting book it would've taken 3 1/2 hours for me to read that much... PURE TORTURE. I'm going to die... that's all there is to it... Gotta read 100 tomorrow and another 100 the next day. My eyes are already twitching. Where is my head???  IM GOING MAD ! I can't think or anything... just   BLANK  . But I did get a  strawberry cream slush  last night, so that was perky goodness with applesauce...(don't forget that was before the  200 pg marathon). I can't believe school starts a week from Monday, that's horrible. TOO EARLY. oh and by the way,   WHOEVER IS PRANK CALLING ME EVERYDAY NEEDS TO FUCKING STOP     NOW     in which I'm assuming it's Brewer, AJ, and that group of people, its really annoying- along with the egging of my house by Brewer also, just    STOP .     
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        (warning, this is not a sympathy seeking entry, just my own inner observations)   So yeah, I haven't really   slept   all that much as a typical teenager in summertime should... I have no job, nothing to do, and completely confine myself to this computer, and feel   naked   without being here. And its affecting me in so many ways... I   eat   less, I   sleep   less, I dont read anything or draw or write songs or anything really... And my homework is yet to be started. But this just in: Rebecca Jenkins aka queen of AP   is only on page   93   of Grapes of Wrath... So she has set an example for us all, its ok to procrastinate. Wow come to think of it, TV isn't even part of my life that much anymore... I think I should just get rid of the TV in my room.. That's another thing I want to do: totally   spring   clean my room... I dont know, Im sitting here knowing what I should do, and yet this computer is my new   ciggarette  . No No, that's a typo.   Matt is my ciggarette  . Its an addiction I refuse to moderate, which is not like me at all. I know I'll pull through in the end, can't help but walk in a circle now though. I might just be mopey about it because I'm   tired   and   hungry   from getting up to help with registration. That was pure torture, no other way to explain it. I was ok at first but I had trouble finding names etc. after a couple hours, just couldn't focus for the life of me. And a few   *like omg I'm a snob who thinks I'm better than you because I'm a dumbass fully absorbed in the high school life and will have no future!!*   types were there to make me twitch a bit.   Did I mention I'm cranky? I'm really cranky- just totally forget my ramblings right now, I might as well be drunk.      
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        That I am, Matt and I are together now, so I'm almightly perked. We were sitting in one of the caves in papago park for the occasion last night, it was perfect. He makes me so happy. I kinda look back at my past relationships and remember being all like "This guy is different" but they weren't, I had no true comparison to say that you know? Amir wasn't much of a conversationalist and I always felt somewhat nervous about just being myself and not giving a shit (at least when I liked him it was like that), Chris flat out treated me like shit, so yea that was different I guess. There was always something missing. I just feel like I can finally look at a random couple holding hands and not be angrily jealous. Because I have that now. And I dont care if its ridiculous of me to say that so quickly, but throughout life I've always looked at happy couples in envy, even when I was in a relationship, cause I never had that. I might be putting too much trust into this, but you know, I'm risking that. I just feel its mutual both ways, and thats friggin awesome, I'm not asking any questions. And I'm not having any doubts, that has NEVER happened. Inside my little box, everything is perfect- and the best part is, its not a box of denial--- *bonus points*   
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Damn you James .&nbsp;  Well I suppose the vacation was ok , its hard to have fun with a Mom who wants to drink, and a Grandma who wants to sit&nbsp;at the hotel&nbsp;the whole time.  My mom and I did go shopping a few times , but was rushed and got school clothes, which she didnt get any clothes cause she spent a while complaining about her weight,&nbsp;but she is in really good shape for being 47&nbsp;(I was broke so, it wasn't my time to conduct activity). And I went to the ocean once, alone, with a boogie board, waves were weak, and I got burnt. So after that I was pretty much wanting to stay out of the sun. And there was no one to talk to,  except the people online at the internet cafe'. It was cool having Sally's family there, I got to kind of bond with Sally . And when I walked on my own (which was a vacation perk) Mom spazed on me a bit (understandably)... And the family did karaoke tuesday night, wasn't all that perked about it when my mom was being dumb and making me go up all the time after I REALLY didnt want to anymore (5 songs is a lot in my opinion, just gets annoying even to me after a while)... So in my lengthy time of solitude,  I wrote, and listened to music, and walked alone, took a few random pictures,&nbsp;and went to the internet cafe for an hour max, and talked to Matt. And I wrote a total of 24 pages. And I did have fun doing that.  I'm just not a mom/gma conversationalist type, no matter how hard I try. Cause everything I do is not understood to them. And you know, its not really accepted either. Maybe thats why  I liked talking to Sally, she didn't judge me. And she still remembers the worser things she did in high school.   Wow James, that bummed me out hardcore. I wouldn't have complained at all if you were there, but it's lame with just adults and Mindy and Justin of all people, you know how bratty they are... So with no money, no one to talk to besides Sally, a sunburn, and lack of activities combined, I'll rate the vacation 5 out of 10. Its not like I bitched at Mom and Gma about it so get off my back James.  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      By some miracle of God there is an internet cafe' conveniently by my hotel....ahhh the sweetness. Well since I'm here I'm sure its obvious Im not having fun. I want to go home. But the ocean is always nice too look at, its the escape Ive been needing, Ive been antisocial on purpose this whole time, just waiting to call Matt with a godly calling card...it has done wonders. Im also writing him a note, its almost 8 pages now... thats what boredom can do to you I guess...  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Once again, I have stayed up all night with church in the morning, but ooohh smart me, I will be able to sleep in the van all the way over without my strength to remain awake... huh? Yeah I know you're jealous. BOO YAH! Matt, Missy, Sean, James, Brandon... I will miss you all... whole 4 days... *tear* hehe. ta ta! ~SAN DIEGO TIME~&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       "I think it would be funny to get flipped off by an old lady"   -Mani   I agree 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Look up.   Go on the swings.   Laugh  . &nbsp;Smell your shirt.   Take lessons from a glass of water.   
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         I love this song!!!  &nbsp;     I dont know if this happens to anyone else, but usually I listen to songs and they will end up reminding me of places or people, and so far the clips and pictures I see with this song make me perk up. I see the view of papago park, riding a bike in the middle of a rainstorm, just being away from it all with a crystal clear mind. Its the ultimate escape song, in my opinion, as if I'm not really sitting here. Hmm. Almost mental tears of   joy     in a weird way. I highly recommend it to all (it was in the previews of Garden State, which looks like a really good movie)... yea. Makes me think of Matt too, my how things are fitting great this time, so hard to understand. Entertainment is found from practically nothing, talking never stops, just an unusual level of comfort never felt before. And its been 2 weeks... explain that one to me. Well I guess it doesn't need to be looked into, I'll leave it alone. But I'm content.             
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I want to be able to turn my head all the way around, and then have a boyfriend that can do that too&nbsp;and make out back to back. And no, I am not being possessed by a demon right now.    
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I want out.  
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Damn tuesday night was awesome. It hadn't rained here in like 4 months, I just walked out there allowing myself to become totally drenched. It's almost an escape from it all, just listening to the rain. And then I was inside and I realized it was POURING outside, it was totally saying "Holly go outside now" and I did, damnit. And about 20 seconds after I went out there this GIANT bolt of lightning struck really close and scared the SHIT out of me and I even plugged my ears. I guess the people I was hanging out with were inside saying "That would be funny if she started running inside after that" , and sure enough I did so they were laughing at me... oh well. It was crazy and funny. I think my wish in life is just to escape from it all so much more often than I do. I think alone time to breathe outside (most especially in high places)is good for the soul, wonder if I'm alone on that one. It just makes me feel happy, like meditating... 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I hate sounding like a drama queen. But I dont like keeping my anger inside all the time either. Its a no win situation I no longer give a shit about.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Tonight has left me in an ultimately  sour  mood, and I can't get myself out of it. Its not a  "phase",  shit. I just want to fucking scream in my pillow or punch the hell out of something. STOP TALKING TO ME! DONT GIVE ME YOUR  STUPID  COMMENTS ANYMORE BECAUSE I AM HONESTLY SICK OF IT ALL! ... Breathing ... Ok well here's my story, I think it was about 3 weeks ago, Jeff came over and throughout the time I've known him there's always some  dumbass  question out of him or remark, whatever. I think we've argued about me and how I shouldn't be "scared of sex" at least 5 times. Which I think is nice to be left alone since thats not such a bad mindset to have at my age etc. And there's always the want to get drunk and party on weekends, which is typical. I think he bugged me about getting out of my alchohol phobia forever (i did get out of it eventually but its not like Im going to go off and party, ugh hate parties) But when you hear shit like that in constant jokes etc. OMG ITS  ANNOYING . So he came over, and he asked about beer, well his friends weren't with him asking this time so I didn't give a shit. He drank a couple and then I got to the point where I was about to fall asleep and he put his beer can on my forehead, which I instintively flailed around trying to get it off and beer got all over my clothes, hair, the pillow I was on and the couch...and he  laughed  about it... said sorry once or twice and poked fun about it. You can call me  girly  for spazing about it, but I don't prefer to smell like beer, you know? So I got mad about it and he said I was just making a big deal out of it, NO- when you're  stupid  about it, it multiplies the issue by 100. Which is like tonight. I was perfectly content online, didnt want to be some hostess as he watched TV in my living room (I don't even get the concept of that since he has a TV at home.. and umm I'm boring) So we're sitting there watching I love the 90's (good show) and I am at first surprised that he didnt asked for beer, wow. He just had to ask the  STUPIDEST  quesion  "So does your hair still smell like beer?"  ... ... ... 3 weeks= apprx.15 showers=NO. AHHHHHHHHHHH. Well I guess I'm supposed to just face the fact that he's an ass and let it slide. And I got a snack and offered him some, which in return he puts his gum on me. OK, its not a big deal, but who the fuck am I? some fucking trash can to put your GUM on? FUCK NO. I flick it off and I tell him I will never let him come over ever again if he leaves it there, so he tries to be  stupid  about it and put it in my mom's fucking shoe... and then I won when he threw it away and he slammed the door. That was something to  smile  about. So now I'm a psycho spaz for getting pissed about it? no I'm not. I'm just sick of him being so  annoying  and  stupid  about so much shit. And I've told him that, but its shrugged off and ignored. Why do I even talk to him? I'm fully happy to say I dont give a shit about him anymore, and haven't for a WHILE, and get to laugh about it and be at the top of our screwed up friendship for once. I don't want to try and stay friends with him anymore, I don't feel at any loss for throwing 3 years of "friendship" in the trash. And  Jeff , I know I said I wouldn't vent about you on my journal anymore, but I don't give a flying fuck if you hate me or anything anymore. I just don't care, even if I look like the bad person in all of this. Its nothing but stress and aggravation that I don't need. ITS NOT A  PHASE . ITS  ME  FUCKER. Goodbye to you. p.s. my ass isn't " sexy " so shut the fuck up, and don't speak to me that way.    
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've got so many thoughts racing through my head its not even funny.   Who Am I? What's wrong with me? What can I do to fix everything? Is there even a way? I wish I could delete my summer and start over. But I don't even think I'd do anything different with that opportunity. It's not a matter of regret, but guilt. A lot of guilt. I guess it sparked up with reading Ryan's journal. Since he flaked me off a couple weeks ago I figured I might as well just give up on him and remain friends, but he still remembers, and well I still don't plan on going to him, Doesn't that make me a bitch... I tell him I have feelings for him and change my mind~AGAIN, Its just really easy for me to do that when the person removes himself from the world for a while and doesn't call or anything and blows you off and is never home. So NO, I will not feel guilty for that.   So now there's Matt, I've known him for almost 2 weeks but it doesn't feel that way at all. Not really possible to feel that way when talking 12 hours a day. It's so comfortable, the shoe fits great, I'm just looking for the catch. Cause life doesn't like me most of the time, except in music. God I want to write another song so bad, can't bring myself to get out of this chair though. That friggin' Grapes of Wrath book is burning a hole in my mind. Can't bring myself to start reading it. I so should've done what Mr.Mah did, read it for yourself first and then read it for the assignment, what a genius, which I tell him.   Damn I was doing so well about not talking about guys on here, but I guess an update was neccesary.  
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was sitting here and out of the blue, Amir calls. Oh how times have changed. I remember being all giddy from hearing bohemian rhapsody ring on my phone and being nervous and up to see him whenever he wanted to come around. But I don't care anymore. And I was happy to tell him how I've completely moved on from him. He was asking about my guy life (which I know is an intro to tell me his own details). I guess he was in fact lying to his friends about having sex with a bunch of girls a few months ago, since he told me he just lost it a week ago. His life is contained with 3 girls, "a cute one, a really hot one, and a fun one", in which he lost it to the fun one and claims its over-rated, which I'm sure it is. "I was dissappointed cause I didn't lose it to you but I found out its not a big deal, dont know why I waited so long." ok... But I wasn't jealous, I didn't care, damn thats awesome. So now our friendship is right back to the way it was, and I'm completely happy about it.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so filling! its in the freezer (got a certificate from doing the volunteer work so). I noticed they have a bunch of different toppings you can choose, so at first I was like "go individualism!!" But then I looked up at their menu, thinking the only thing on there would be sizes and topping prices and options for waffle bowl or cone or whateva, I was wrong. On the side there was a whole board of possible mixes and special names for them and everything. Damn. Not cool. You think you're creative for thinking of neat mixes but its already there. What's the pride in that? Lucky for me, the mix with french vanilla ice cream, cookie dough and oreos was not on the wall... sweet victory I HAVE BEATEN YOUR STORE AT ITS OWN GAME BIOTCH!  Recording another song, the one called "Wasted time" about Chris that I wrote..I dont know 5 or 6 months ago. THANKS AGAIN CHRIS! haha. Haven't talked to him since school ended, I think he hates me now, that's his fault I guess. I wanted it to be kinda dark sounding song, and have the chorus be in-your-face explosive, there was a vision in my mind--- but Will has totally pop-ped it out with upbeatness etc. Guess I will just have to deal with it. Maybe people will like it. Pop culture for ya. AND NO I DONT WANT RAP!! IS THAT UNDERSTOOD AT ALL? I AM NOT A RAP KIND OF MUSICIAN DAMNIT!  I have been practically living online for the past week and a half basically, just can't seem to stop typing... =) And I have yet to begin my summer homework... and havent gone to the gym in almost 2 weeks, I begin to wonder if this transition in leisure activity is at all helpful...  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Went to my sister's for a couple days, and have now returned home... I dont understand this at all, never happened before, but my house has a smell to it, which I guess has always been there but isn't noticed when you live there---and now that I'm here its all so foreign and its giving me a headache-- has that happened to anyone?   
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *Read this quote extremely carefully and think in literal terms* "I know how hard it is for you to put food on your family." - George W. Bush  *puts a pumpkin pie on Aunt Sally* "Such a hard task, that was fucking heavy, you were right Mr. President" ...   ...   ...   ...   ... ...What is wrong with this country?!?! Couldn't we find a better republican candidate??? Honestly! Not siding toward Kerry either, this will ultimately drive me nuts, government will suck ass regardless at this point...  http://politicalhumor.about.com/library/blbushisms.htm   If you found the quote disturbing, there are much more at that site. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        -Bertrand Russell (1872 - 1970)  Such a great addition to the partriotic festivities aye? =) Should I be stoned to death for agreeing? I think my lack of patriotism makes my mom a bit angry... the world is a corrupt place, can't sugarcoat it, and wearing red white and blue wont make you a better American. Don't get me wrong, I love living here, I have much to learn, but I do not prefer to be arrogant and say "America is the best" "Screw the rest of you." This country is so greedy, Americans are blind.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Got to go swimming and watch fireworks on the roof, and watched fight club for the first time, it was a fun day--- Noticed everyone found their day lame cause they were all trying to find an awesome place to get drunk and failed miserably...haha that's your fault for expecting too much of a day. I think that's how everyday should be: never expect anything from it and never be let down, it honestly works. Or maybe it only does for the easily entertained, in that case I feel sorry for you if you're "Bored"... ugh. *badger* *badger* *badger* *MUSHROOM* *MUSHROOM* hehe, so addicting. Well Missy is in the hospital cause her appendix was about to burst, I really hope she'll be ok, I'm going to see her the second she gets home, somehow. And will pray a shitload, even though I never pray. I miss her so much, we haven't really talked as much as we used to which is both our faults, I must make it up to her. *maow* much love sis. hang in there.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "just realize what do you accomplish by getting upset or sad"-Matt  --- nothing, duh- no point in it. =) made me think.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday was a blast, even with my tiredness. I was actually up all the other night cause I was talking to a newfound internet friend named Matt (damn I know too many Matts) and went off and met him that day since it was his b day, I was laughing the whole trip, its been a while since nothing was so entertaining- watched Spiderman 2, good movie I suppose(tear). Damn, I just had a lot of fun. His friend Brandon wore some red pj pants under khaki shorts, found that pretty funny- he got a lot of stares for it. Yeah I know I'm not supposed to meet people from internet, promised my mom and everything and haven't found anything great in the past and don't even need to look on here, but something seemed really different about him and you know what? I was RIGHT--I have a good judgment of people damnit. =). And I don't consider this being naive, cause I can't even begin to count how many people have randomly IMed me and I've known they're weird or some screws are waay loose and all elements combined against them basically, so yeah! shha to YOU!  Fun friendships, who knows what direction time will take me, don't know yet, which is ok by me.  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      bubblegum...stupid society
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Song finished!!!! It sounds soo awesome! =) proud. Its 5 30 in the morning and I haven't gone to sleep yet-- don't think I will sleep tonight/today.  I JUST DROVE HOME!!! YAY!!! *I didn't crash my mom's car* hahahahahaha, main road ain't so bad at 6am! But thats beside the point... yeah
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm finally recording, thanks Brandon for wanting someone to sing your song with! It sounds really good so far too (well I think it does). And today Anita and I made pasta and some really really good chocolate chip cookies for our friend Daniel, since he's been so busy lately and doesn't eat as much anymore. I can't believe we got up early to do that too, CRAZY. Guess I gotta see what the rest of today brings... School is getting closer =(
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think I've grown in this past month-mentally. And I am so proud of myself. *self-respect* I can say no, I'm not as naive, and through the boy craziness of friends around me, I've realized my similar faults, and how much I don't want to have that in common. Im more mature =) "life is full of knives, watch your back" - me
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       What's tubing? Well I found out today, it was quite fun. Of course, I got somewhat burnt again, but it was worth it, YOU GET TO LAY AROUND AND BE LAZY!!. For 12 bucks (funny how that concept works)... but its ok, there's water... Which I was very disturbed swimming in knowing millions of microscopic organisms live in each drop of water, and that many urinate in it... and seeing people spill beer in it etc. What's in the water? It's lethal, that's the only answer I can find. "Whoa her hair is purple" Stupid people. Well I met Sasha and Dan (two friends of Matt) today in the double date event of tubing, they are very interesting and unique people, and even more unique as an item, but their completely unparalleled personalities mesh in its own strange little way. I was very comfortable around them and had fun, so that is most definitely a bonus. And as each day passes my feelings just grow stronger for my Matt. Just so happy, I get a superbly perked out feeling just thinking about him, and can't help but miss him all the time and talk to him as much as I humanly can. He came to watch me sing in my church choir today... at 7AM, now no other person on this planet would do that for me(besides my mom and gma who got me into the church choir that they go to mass with), he's not even religious. I had to stifle my laughing to extremities when he went for communion and all that jazz, and knowing what he would have to say about the sermons etc., just amused. And I had a solo, finally, great timing, did good I suppose. Hell, I'm not even catholic in mind, but I love to sing. And that is enough for me. I'm at that point where I want to cry because I'm so content and wrapped in the thought of looking into his eyes and knowing exactly what he is thinking. Knowing all the little pigments of olive green and brown and getting lost in the world I find.     *Miracle has just occurred*      First of all, its been a curse every year for quite sometime to where I get a really bad headache the night before school starts, and can't sleep for the life of me. Well I had it again, and after writing about all this, it just disappeared. Completely. Wow. I've got a neverending smile on my face, and its been there a lot ever since meeting him. It's a revolving door of fresh air, and I'm just going to sit and enjoy it.       I love Jazz music.   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      IN YOUR FACE DEVIL BOOK!!! haha!! Yeah, I just finshed reading... and I'm happy about that. 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
             Saw a really awesome movie last night, "What the #$*! Do We Know?", basically a movie questioning reality and giving a clear picture of quantum physics. The main message of the movie is to open your mind and not conform to everyone else's views. It made everything in my mind so clear, I walked around absorbing everything around me, and on Mill avenue thats quite a treat. Highly recommended, its showing only at Valley Art Theatre on Mill avenue.         I've been in a total jazz mood today, I love the vibe I get when listening to it. It reminds me of how I would sit in my room listen to 91.5fm at 7:05PM at night at the beginning of the year last year, so I went and downloaded a few that came to mind and I'm all perked out from it.         And of course, I'm not done reading yet *on page 420* I do intend to finish it today. Overall, its not THAT bad, but its still boring. I dont have to think negatively of it but I choose to.         I've been so content in the past month, its awesome. Yes, there have been a few bumps in the road, but its ok. I don't know if my mind has learned to go by "ignorance is bliss", or if I truly don't get affected by the negative around me. I've just replaced it with "happy" "content" "relaxed" "oh well". Sadness and Anger is a waste of time, in my opinion. I'm sure some consider that absurd or wrong, well that's your view of life, not mine. Right and Wrong is nothing but a standard which is differs with every person. Therefore, you telling me what I'm doing is wrong, is just you pressing your standards on me. Am I supposed to "learn" something is wrong because you say it is? no. If it hurts someone yes, which I realized a few weeks ago and "learned" from. Will it stop? I hope so, but for sure it will stop within your bubble of life.          All i know is I'm not going to press my standards of right and wrong on others or even myself anymore, or talk of who I wish I was either; that ultimately brings dissapointment within myself and aggravates others. I will go on with my life happily, regardless of others trying to bring me down with who they think I should be,and what they think I should be doing. Is that wrong? Makes you think doesn't it?  And I think I did a good job of remembering what I wrote, since pretty much the same thing I just said got deleted entirely from trying to publish it... 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>