<Blog>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Friday the 13th Michael and I are flying out to LA for the weekend. Mike and Sara are going to meet us there and we're going to see that exhibit that uses real human cadavers. This German sciencetist has found a way to to drain the body of fluids and replace it with a silicone plastic solution. By doing this the entire cardiovascular system as well and the muscular system are are in a way preserved, the flesh is then cut away and the skinned bodies are on display for both beauty and science! It looks truly amazing and I can't wait to see it in person. We're going to stay at the Marriott in downtown LA. We had originally planned on staying on the Queen Ann ship which is docked in Long Beach and is now a museum and hotel but they were all booked up for that weekend. Among some of the other things that we would like to do besides the exhibit is a Burlesque show! I guess Larry Flynt has a dinner theatre/Burlesque show. It's affordable too, about $35.00 a person, we may not be able to do this because you have to make the reservations ahead of time. We were thinking about doing it Friday night when we arrive but we are worried that between renting a car, finding the hotel, getting ready and then trying to find this joint we would likely not make it. I guess we'll just have to settle for going to the Hussler store in Hollywood! Which we will definitely be sure to stop at. Michael also found a cool Sushi place that has a Japanamation theme! I would really like to go there too. Speaking of Sushi... I have been craving it so bad lately. It has been so hard not to run down to Happy Sumo on my lunch break just to snag a lil roll. (I don't think Benihanna's is open for lunch but I don't know for sure.) But that would be mean to go with out Michael so I never do, but damn... it's calling my name!  
      
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I can't really explain it but I really feel the "The Fear" lately. It seems like there are a lot of terrible things, lots of tragedy going on around me right now. An unusual amount of sadness and heartache and I have an overwhelming sense of uneasiness. I heard that a friend's Father has retired because he's "not going to make it". His retirement was rushed through. I find this alarming because although I knew that her Father is ill with cancer, she has not spoke of it, nor did she ever allude to the fact that he is so bad. We found out he retired from a co-worker and not from my friends. I wonder if my friend is just in denial and has convinced herself that her Father is not that sick, that he is going to make it. This is the worst frame of mind to have because if he does pass away it's going to make it that much harder for her to deal with his death. My friend has been having medical problems and problems at work. Her daughter's fiance was in a serious accident and is in a coma, if he does make it, he will likely have sever brain damage and have to learn to walk and talk again. Her boyfriend's step mother has been given only months to live, and now her children's grandmother on their father's side has been put on nitro and it doesn't look like she is going to make it either. My supervisor and his wife just had their first child. A healthy 8 pound girl with lots of curly dark hair. We just found out today that the child is having complications now with it's lungs and blood pressure and is at Primary Children's Hospital. I have a very serious suspicion that my job is in danger. This could be my increasing paranoia, but something is up. Something is not right and I really feel as though I could lose my job out of no where. This really perplexes me as I could pass a drug test should I be given one, I do my work and my percentage collected has been excellent. I'm getting my hours in and I know that I'm not doing anything personally that could cause me to lose my job yet somehow I have a weird feeling that it is in fact in jeopardy. It could be that I just don't fit in and I'm not well received or like around the office and the vibe is just getting to me. It could be the new changes that will be implemented soon, they are building new offices over in the warehouse and the rumor is our department will be moving over there. A friend's wife is also sick, she is young and should not be so sick. They really don't seem to know what exactly is wrong with her and I fear with out health insurance it could be too late before she gets properly diagnosed and treated. I can't help but feel scared for some reason. Out of no where I will all of a sudden be paralyzed by fear, terrified that something horrible is going to happen to one of my loved ones. I'm afraid to travel, we are flying to LA Friday the 13th to go to an art exhibit we've been interested in seeing and staying at the Marriott in downtown LA. As I get older flying becomes more difficult for me as with every little bump of turbulence I can't help but picture the plane dropping out of the sky and careening towards the Earth to our death. And no, it doesn't fucking help that we're flying on Friday the 13th. I find myself being worried about my relationships. I worry that my close friends are "mad" at me, I worry that all of a sudden my husband will leave me, I question if my parents really love me or not. I'm so scared, so terrified that my life is all of a sudden going to rip apart at the seams and fall apart. That my luck has run out, that karma is catching up to me, that the feeling I don't deserve all these blessings, all these wonderful friends, family, my loving husband... I feel like it's all going to be taken away from me with a catastrophic event. And you thought you were paranoid. Jesus Christ, is this the beginning of some kind of psychotic episode? Will I soon convenience myself that my neighbors are Alkihda members and be staked out in my back yard with my 9mm and night vision? Will I barricade myself in my home and not leave for fear that "something bad" might happen if I leave the house? Will I hold my husband hostage for the same reason...  my precious .... The fear is strong these days, I will be greatly relieved when this feeling subsides. In the meantime I'm going to be doing a lot of Yoga, hot tub chillin, and heavy meditation. I need to stop assuming the worst and getting strange visions of horrible things happening to my loved ones, it's bad mojo. Fight the Fear! Woo! 
      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's about time I started blogging again damn-it. I took a break for a lot of reasons. For one I just needed some alone time and because I tend to use my bloggie as a journal and many of my friends and family had the address to my old blog I wasn't really getting that alone time. Second, too many of my friends and family had the address to my old blog. I felt pretty censored as to what I could talk about. Okay, okay, and WHO I could talk about. You can't talk smack about someone if they are probably going to read now can you? hahaha! Also, I really didn't like that my Mom was a reader. I use to really want her to know what was going on in my life but now that I understand her more, I see that it's a bad idea. I honestly believe she doesn't want to know that much about my life and it makes our relationship better if I just tell her what she wants to hear.  I am still not sure who all I am going to give this address to. Brian and Kelly for sure. Michael doesn't read the blogs, even though I've told him that it's a really important form of expression to me, he really hates it and would rather me just tell him things in conversation. Which is totally understandable and I think that if I feel a blog entry is good or important, I will read it to him or copy and paste it into an e-mail.  I'm write more here in a little while. I am at work and I need to go and get water and go potty. (I just did a spell check... "potty" is not a word! Ya learn something new everyday I tell ya.) 
      
</post>



</Blog>