<Blog>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hello people! Just a little update. Our wonderful cell group has got a number of members going for the Youth G1 mission trip to Chinagmai, Thailand.  Hui Hui, Marilyn and Shem  are all in the performing arts category. They will be learning  14 dances  within a short period of three and a half days during the boot camp.  Paul and I  are in the mercy ministry category. We will be going to an orphanage over there to help build a building for the Thai orphans. Please remember us in your prayers. Pray that The performers will be able to learn all the dances and that they will be able to use what they have learnt to bless the Thais. Pray also that Paul and I will be able to reach out the the little kids out there who have lost their parents. We all hope to have a wonderful and meaningfull Mission Trip.  God Bless!=)
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      There has been a cluster outing planned for the Sec4-J1 cluster on the 20th June 2004, Sunday. It will start immediately after the service. The outing will be held at Sentosa. You can expect lots of fun, games, and a time to interact with members of other cell groups in our cluster. It will most probably be a half-day thing, time estimated to end is about 4-5pm. Lunch will be provided.   Please inform me or Hui Hui as to whether you are able to turn up. The amount that each person has to pay has not been confirmed yet. You will be informed at a later date. However, i assure you that each person will have to pay no more than $10. We hope to settle everything fast. Please sms  Hui Hui  or  me  ASAP to tell us if you are going. You can also leave a comment. Thank You.  -posted by Jonathan Choy-
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hey people! This blog is here for us to update one another of anything which is happening to us. Post your prayer requests on the blog or also tell us about any church happenings.  Format for posts:  1) No profanities allowed on this blog. Keep them to yourselves.  2) Everyone has the right to update, but please use it discretely. That is, do not post for the fun of it.  3) I (Jonathan Choy), and Ho Hui Hui reserve the right to bar blog-abusers from using this blog. Which means that we have the right to change the password and not inform.  Thank You and God Bless! =)  -posted by Jonathan Choy-
     
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hey guys/gals,sorry for the late post,I was supposed to discuss this with you fellas yesterday on Msn but thanks to the blackout yesterday I think all of you couldn't use the computer except me.Anyway,this is just some of the info Hui Hui wanted me to inform you guys of.  We would have 2 stalls if I'm not wrong,1 would be used to sell drinks and the other food.  For the food stall,we would be selling the following:  Chicken Wings--Jonathan Choy Hash Browns--Timothy Fish/Sotong Balls--Me  For the drinks stall,Hui Hui has suggest that lemonade and lime juice be sold.So the following would be needed:  Ice Containers Cups Lemons Limes  Okay so for the ice,lemons,cups and limes they would have to be bought.So we need people to buy them.Anyone who wants to buy some or all of them can sms Hui Hui or Jonathan Choy,or inform us through Msn or the tagboard here.Containers,if anyone can provide it would be good.  Oh yes,please remember to keep receipts of your purchase i.e receipts for the buying of fishballs,this is to allow us to count the profits easily.  Yup this post is rather vague because I've never planned such stuff,anyway would be updating it later.  -Daniel Loy
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hey people! Thanks for turning up for the cluster outing. Anyway, this is about the the Blokes event on the 3 July. Lumine and Lumina have decided to set up two stalls. Lumine is selling ice-cream floats and other drinks and Lumina is selling fried food, e.g. chicken wings. The 2 stalls will most probably be set up next to each other. If you have any suggestions on what food you wanna sell, you can sms me. yup. If you have any suggestions to what other driknks you wanna sell, sms Hui. Thanks. =)
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yo guys!! =)  Regarding cluster outing this sunday (or tomorrow if you prefer),  Remember to bring...  1. $5 or $10 notes only   2. water bottle 3. change of clothes 4. cap (optional)  More Details...  Transport and lunch provided Meet in open plaza immediately after service  That's all!! (i wonder who will actually read this on time...) Heidi 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hey! I'm sure all you people are going for the outing on the 20 June. Anyway, just a reminder. Please bring a  change of clothes  as you are sure to get WET!!! And also remember to bring about $5 - $6 for payment and a water bottle as it will be quite hot. God bless!=)
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Drinks stall will be selling  Ribena and Lemonade . Food stall will be selling  chicken wings, fish and sotong balls, and hashbrowns . People. Remember to keep your receipts. Thanks.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>