<Blog>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      In a paroxysm of anti-Dubyaism (just kidding, it's job related), my friend Jenny is moving back to Taiwan next week.  Boooo!  BOO, I say.  But really though... what better place to find yourself that gay boyfriend who'll help you disinfect all those filthy door handles encrusted with LP fingerprints?  That was rhetorical.  No need to answer that whatsever.  And don't forget, Jenny... it's Seattle or bust three years from now!  In unrelated news, it's been confirmed by third, fourth, and fifth parties that I have shallow tastes in music.  My favorite venue is a gas-efficient Japanese import.  Lately on the commute, I've been listening to the SCISSOR SISTERS, first track called 'Laura':  "Don't you give me your love/Don't you give me your/Sch-moe, schmoe..."   1) Am I hearing deficient?  2) What the heck is a schmoe?  3) And why am I suddenly singing along?  And then, he goes on to lambaste this Laura: "This could be the last time/I ever do your... hair"  Ouch.  Oh, that's gotta hurt.  The riposte of a scorned gay boyfriend, no doubt.  Finally, witness the lyrical genius of track 7:  "Cuz you're filthy/But I'm gorgeous/You're disgusting/And you're nasty..."  over and over and over and over...  I'd post the link to the SCISSOR SISTER website, but it features a nipple and I don't want any casual internet surfers to be dismayed by the flagrant display of a part of the body that everyone has.  Shocking.  It really is. 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I seem to have misplaced my comment box.  Has anyone seen or come in contact with someone else who has seen my comment box?  And don't tell me you last saw it walking down the street hand-in-hand with Michael Jackson...
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      UPDATE on Smile:  I just read on Pitchfork that Smile's going to be released officially sometime this year in the fall.  Brian Wilson and lyricist Van Dyke Parks revisited the vault tapes and actually FINISHED the record a few months ago!  Previously, I was under the impression that Wilson was just going to release a live version of his UK performances, but this is much,  much  prefered.  I think it would sound totally awesome in 5-speaker surround sound...  Here's the link:  urlLink http://pitchforkmedia.com/news/04-02/24.shtml 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's still raining.  My eyes hurt from driving home tonight.  It's like I can't filter out the visual stimulus of windshield wipers wiping and I pay more attention to them pendualting than I do other cars.  And furthering my pissiness, I neglected to charge my CD player's batteries yesterday and the remaining power seemed to have just leeched out overnight.  Either that, or the power indicator is whack.  I'm currently listening to a few new CDs, but nothing inspiring enough to hammer out a full-fledged review.   DANGER MOUSE, The Grey Album That's the Beatles  White  album meets Jay-Z's  Black  album.  I got it just for the novelty of it.  And now, I think EMI/Sony/Michael Jackson/whoever owns the Beatles catalog is ordering Danger Mouse to cease and desist the distribution of this record.  Pbbt~!  You'd think they had better things to do.   RADIOHEAD, Amnesiac Cuz I never did really listen.  So now I'll really listen.   LLOYD COLE, Music in a Foreign Language He doesn't look like Rob Zombie on the cover of this album...   FEEDER, Comfort in Sound Yesssss, we lovesss Britpop... Bad, wicked hobbitss!   SCISSOR SISTERS, eponymous Apparently that's a slang term for lesbians, but all I hear on this CD is this guy.  And his funny falsetto.  That nasally Barry Gibbs, dance fever, white leisure suits, and John Travolta's paint can sound...   BEACH BOYS, Smile It's never been released officially, but someone collected all the bits and outtakes from various box sets and assembled this playlist of tracks that should have been on Brian Wilson's aborted follow-up to Pet Sounds.  Wilson's on tour in the UK to actually perform the whole thing live.  I'm so jealous that it's exclusive to the UK.  Well, those British music magazines always liked Pet Sounds better than Rubber Soul which is like, the complete opposite to sentiment here in the States.  Speaking of which, I was totally, disgustingly wrong in my Brit Awards predictions.  Which goes to show that I'm just not British enough.  Well, damn.  THE DARKNESS ended up winning every award they were nominated for EXCEPT Breakthrough Artist which instead went to BUSTED who I just couldn't care less for.  And they also like the WHITE STRIPES too much.  Whatever.  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It rained a couple of inches today.  Naturally, Inwood flooded and my tiny gas-effcient Japanese import was splashed silly by bloated beached whales (read: Suburbans) that one day will all suffer the wrath of God when a giant Monty Python foot falls from the sky and crushes all the SUVs like barefoot wine stomping.  Meanwhile, I'm driving through water that reaches the top of my hubcaps, and I see the Ancient Mariner with that damn'd albatross around his neck sail by.  And I'm thinking: Let's get on the tollway!  Yes, let's!    I find it ridiculous how Dallas-ites are woefully underprepared to handle any sort of natural disaster.  A bit of ice and we all think we're in the ice capades.  A bit of rain and we swim to Cuba.  I think the problem might be the erratic nature of Dallas weather patterns.  We get anything from snow flurries to tornadoes but occuring with such low frequency that we hardly remember what we did the last time it happened.  To forget is ultimately a most human quality.  And Texan too...  Remember the Alamo?  Remember Goliad?  Remember San Jacinto?   No?  Me neither.  Ms. Broussard would be appalled.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My thoughts on this year's Brit Awards nominees in select categories.  Does anyone know if it gets aired in the States (however belatedly?)   urlLink British Breakthrough Artist   Nominees: Busted, Darkness, Dizzee Rascal, Jamie Cullum, Lemar.   I'm pretty confident with the assessment that THE DARKNESS will win at least this award.  They're nominated for three others, but in each of the other categories, they're outclassed by established bands like Blur, Stereophonics and Radiohead.  DIZZEE RASCAL, hailed by critics as the savior of hip hop, might present a formidable obstacle, but I wouldn't know because I wasn't aware that hip hop needed saving.  BUSTED may seem like the boy band du jour, the one that got away for Simon Cowell, but I find them a bit uninspired and lightweight.  I'm not very familiar with JAMIE CULLUM and LEMAR, but I don't see the appeal in either case.  The former is lounge jazz and the later is easy-listening R&B, and I've never been a fan of either.     urlLink British Rock Act   Nominees: Darkness, Feeder, Muse, Primal Scream, Stereophonics.   I totally don't know anything about FEEDER or MUSE, and I may have heard the name PRIMAL SCREAM before, but the context eludes me.  Barring a DARKNESS sweep, dare I say that after all this time, I still like Kelly Jones' voice?  Plus, I still think he's kinda cute...   urlLink Mastercard British Album   Nominees: Blur, Coral, Daniel Bedingfield, Darkness, Dido.   Last year's Think Tank was just too awesome for words.  I'm cheering for BLUR.   urlLink British Group   Nominees: Busted, Coral, Darkness, Radiohead, Sugababes.   SUGABABES has that zinger line:  "Won't you miss me like a hole in the head?"   but the rest of that song... icky lame.  (eloquent, I know).  CORAL has a nice sound, cute haircuts... BUSTED and DARKNESS, yadda yadda yadda... How can anyone top RADIOHEAD's sonic masterpiece of 2003?  Even if Hail to the Thief isn't the best Radiohead record (which I think it is), all of these other acts tremble in the shadow of the monolith that is Radiohead.   urlLink British Single   Nominees: Dido, Gareth Gates, Jamelia, Mis-Teeq, Rachel Stevens.   Isn't GARETH GATES one of those Idols?  No comment.  DIDO's "White Flag" was nice.  I think that's the only single in this group of nominees that I've heard.   urlLink International Breakthrough Artist   Nominees: 50-Cent, Evanescence, Kings of Leon, Sean Paul, Thrills.   When EVANESCENCE won the Grammy for Best New Artist, 50-CENT was seen belatedly crossing the stage.  Had he been so certain of his winning that he climbed the stage without waiting for the opening of the envelope?  In any case, I like KINGS OF LEON... the Followills look like Galahads searching for the Holy Grail.  And we all know how I feel about the THRILLS (but "Big Sur" gets catchier each time I hear it...)  As for Sean Paul, reggae's just not my thing.  *shrug*   urlLink International Male Artist   Nominees: 50-Cent, Beck, Damien Rice, Justin Timberlake, Sean Paul.   DAMIEN RICE is in strange company, but I do believe he deserves more recognition for his talent.  His debut album O was absolutely phenomenal.  Funny that he's Irish and they put him in the "international" category...
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've noticed this disturbing trend for quite awhile now, and today, looking back through my archived posts, it's confirmed: I suffer from constipated positivity!  While I can write buckets and buckets about Celine Dion (and the abuse just won't stop), I can't quite express myself adequately when it comes to something I DO like... Case-in-point, this week, I've started listening to JESUS & MARY CHAIN's Darklands album and I become completely flummoxed when asked what I like about it.   It's.. um.. really, really good?  Err, it just sounds SO cool?   Geez.  *rolls eyes*   Other CDs in the changer:    AIR, Talkie Walkie I laughed the first time I saw the title of this album.  That is, until someone told me that "talkie walkie" is just how they say "walkie talkie" in France.  French people are so weird.   ARAB STRAP, Elephant Shoe Naturally, I'd want to check out a band that 1) named themselves after a BELLE & SEBASTIAN song that 2) is common in S&Mish paraphernalia.   FIVE FOR FIGHTING, The Battle For Everything It's true.  John Ondrasik wants to be on Dawson's Creek.  Too bad Dawson's no longer with us.  Fortunately, he has other fine, fine WB programming to choose from such as One Tree Hill and The OC.  *stabs eyes out*   KINGS OF LEON, Youth & Young Manhood Critically labeled the "Southern-fried Strokes"...   NORAH JONES, Feels Like Home It's nice to listen to.  The mice don't mind it either.  Though, they like Josh Groban better.   RYAN ADAMS, Love Is Hell Pt. 1 Ryan Adams is completely schizoid.  Listen to his gorgeous cover of "Wonderwall" in this EP release, then look at that atrocious Rock'n'Roll album and the screaming and the distortion.  I prefer his Wonderwall.   THE WALKMEN, Everyone Who Pretended to Like Me Is Gone And lastly, but not least... I first heard The Walkmen in a Saturn car commercial.  "We've Been Had" was the best single I'd heard all year (that was 2002, I believe).  The rest of this album doesn't sound like that.  I'm bummed.  They have a new one out called Bows and Arrows I think.  Don't know if I'll risk buying it.  If anyone has heard it, email me!
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Whenever I hear new music from bands I like, I inevitably go through the same cycle of emotions: disappointment (that it didn’t sound like the record before), denial, anger, then gradual acceptance and eventual adoration.  So, of course I HATED this album the first time I listened to it.  I’d been waiting well over three months to grasp it in my grubby little hands.  It had been out for quite some time overseas already, and I was impatiently waiting for their US release (as the import version was quite pricey).  I finally found it at Best Buy of all places, two days before it’s announced release date, idiotically shelved behind Elton John.  And naturally, after suffering the long delay and entertaining high expectations, I despised the record.  Gone were the muted blue-gray jungle drums from ASLEEP IN THE BACK.  Gone were the swelling crescendos and provocative imageries.  This was something totally different!  Well, duh.  Eventually, it got through to my nut-enclosed brain (or is that brain-enclosed nut?) that CAST OF THOUSANDS had some intrisic artistic merit despite Elbow’s departure from its predecessor.  And now, as expected, I adore it.  While the first was pretty much a straight-forward affair, the later features more sonic experimentation, an assuredly amateur effort when compared to something like YANKEE HOTEL FOXTROT, but you can definitely hear some weird noise can be in the background texture.  Whereas Wilco moved the noise to the forefront and bludgeon the listener over the head with it, Elbow is much more subtle and it takes a few listens for it to register.  I have but one remaining complaint and it is that the single “Fallen Angels” sounds unappetitzingly like Coldplay.  How embarrassing is it to be derivative of a derivative band…   Favorite tracks:  Except for the hackneyed Coldplay tribute, I like them all, especially the groovier tracks “Snooks (Progress Report)” and “Buttons and Zips”.  Incidentally, they are also the songs with the least meaningful lyrics.  But what meager words they do have sound damn good in the context.  Other Reviews for 2.08.04:   urlLink GUSTER, Keep It Together (2003)  Boston-based ex-bongo act: accomplished songwriters, but aurally conventional.   urlLink WILCO, I Am Trying To Break Your Heart DVD (2003)  Film documenting the recording of Yankee Hotel Foxtrot and the subsequent industry politics that delayed its release.   urlLink EISLEY, Marvelous Things EP (2003)  Second EP release from a brother-sister ensemble from Tyler, TX.  Soaring, amber colored vocals backed by crunchy distortion.   urlLink WHITE STRIPES, Elephant (2003)  Inviting reader opinions on Jack White's performance in Cold Mountain.  Wish that White had a predilection for bluegrass outside of Hollywood.   urlLink SONDRE LERCHE, Faces Down (2002)  One of the discs that endured repeat listenings last year as I endured the sight of unsightly, underwear-less men on the subway.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
         The Thrills sound like they miss California.  I empathize, I really do.  I miss the peaceful contentment of sprawling out on warm grass, listening to the ocean breeze ruffle through the eucalyptus trees.  But this record just doesn't do it for me.  It's catchy and infectious pop, yet ultimately shallow songwriting.  I just can't get anything out of it.  It's completely meaningless.  Only on the opening track and I was already exasperated with them.  How can anyone repeat the words "Santa Cruz" so many times in under 4 minutes?  The lead singer, though terribly adorable in that Micky Dolenz kind of way, insists on singing in a register that he just doesn't have.  But I do appreciate the self-deprecating humor of their videos.  At least they're not afraid of laughing at themselves.  Bottom line: lighthearted lightweights following in the footsteps of the Monkees.  Someone, get them a reality show!
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Advertised as "hot upcoming artists” to watch out for in 2004, I spit coffee the first time I saw pictures of the band in Rolling Stone.  Lead singer Justin Hawks wore these tight leopard print pants and insisted on posing like he was stretching for Jazzercise.  He and his bandmates all have this... big hair 80s metal-ballad vibe going on (well, except for Frankie the bass player who looks like a temporally-displaced Village Person).  I dismissed them immediately, that is, after I mopped up coffee from my magazine.  Fortunately, the band wouldn’t leave me alone.  I caught their video today while channel surfing (oddly enough, MTV was showing music videos… I don’t know what this world is coming to).  The video for “I Believe in a Thing Called Love” starts out with Hawkes – naked – waking up from a very wet cryogenic freezing and gyrating his ass against a headless fuzzy monster.  He’s amazingly hilarious… crooked teeth, squinty eyes, does this comical strut/pout… looks like Thom Yorke, moves like Mick Jagger… and most strikingly, he has this gratuitous falsetto that just sounds SO good.  Then, a giant muppet octopus invaded the space ship they were on, but by that time, I was hooked.  The overwhelming silliness of the video was unable to dissuade me from liking this band.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I was all prepared to dislike this CD – what with the name-calling like “Irish troubadour” and, of course, “sweet-faced, shaggy-haired poet-player” – totally not my thing. But I found out a couple of pretty surprising things about myself whilst listening to this record:   1. I noticed that the repetitiveness of Damien Rice's lyrics didn't even phase me. (And this from a self-described “words” person. I'm ashamed of myself.) Sample lyrics—“I look to my eskimo friend / I look to my eskimo friend / I look to my eskimo friend / When I'm down, down, down…” But each time he sings the line, it sounds different. Just tinged with a slightly transmuted emotional nuance. Like on “Cheers Darling” (a song about being bitterly amused at an ex-lover's wedding), each time he sings.. well.. cheers, darling , he sounds progressively more disillusioned and in denial that she really means to end it with him this time. Another good example is in “The Blower's Daughter”, rapidly becoming my second favorite track, Rice sings I can't take my eyes off of you so many friggin' times and EGADS! It sounds good! I can't understand it.   2. The harmony provided by the female vocalist Lisa Hannigan is just breathtaking and gives me shivers. Now, I can count the number of female voices I like on one hand, so I found this to be a bit surprising indeed. I just really love how her voice lays into his and how they complement each other like an early 70s Stevie Nicks and Lindsey Buckingham (as opposed to early 80s when Stevie had a cocaine-induced hole in her nose the size of Chicago…)   Now the good stuff: 1. Notwithstanding the repetitiveness, there's a bit of lyrical cleverness in places. For example, in “Cannonball”- Stones taught me to fly…/ So it's not hard to fall / When you float like a cannonball . The melody in that one sounds oddly like a Celine Dion song. PK should be aghast right now and shaking his head furiously.   2. Another band with a regular cello player! That's a neat thing. I think it adds a lot of warmth and depth to instrumental arrangements. Belle & Sebastian used to have a cello player, but she left the band. Better off without her, I say. She had this annoying and airy pixie fairy voice.    Favorite tracks  - “Cold Water” wins hands-down with the most enigmatic lyrics and an odd Hawaiian-sounding acappella that had me puzzled for days. “The Blower's Daughter” is a close second with Lisa Hannigan's divine two-liner: Did I say that I loathe you / Did I say that I want to / Just leave it all behind.  Other Reviews for 2.01.04:   urlLink CELINE DION, 1 Fille & 4 Types (2003)  At least it's in French so you can't laugh at the lyrics.  Or can you?   urlLink MY MORNING JACKET, It Still Moves (2003)  Southern indie rockers that scored a place in Pitchfork's top albums of 2003.  Here we see why it put me to sleep, another indication of how refined my musical tastes are.   urlLink ELBOW, Asleep in the Back (2001)  Hauntingly Britpop in the vein of Radiohead.  I've got the newest LP and will review it shortly! 			  urlLink THE SHINS, Chutes Too Narrow (2003)  Still reeling from the downloading debacle.  First the truncated Elbow song, now this.  I'm never buying CDs again.  How can they do this?!? 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Me:  Gee.  The crickets outside are sure loud.  My brother:  Uh huh.  Maybe they're mating.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I unwittingly added an 'r' to it.  The Vogons are an alien race that were sent to bulldoze the planet Earth in the beginning of Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy to make way for an intergalactic freeway.   Far out in the uncharted backwaters of the unfashionable end of the western spiral arm of the galaxy lies a small, unregarded yellow sun. Orbiting this at a distance of roughly 92 million miles is an utterly insignificant little blue-green planet whose ape-descended life forms are so amazingly primitive that they still think digital watches are a really neat idea.  ...And lots of the people were mean, and most of them were miserable, even the ones with digital watches. Many were increasingly of the opinion that they all made a big mistake in coming out of the trees in the first place. And some said that even the trees had been a bad move and that no one should ever have left the oceans.   Our protagonist Arthur Dent is transported up to the Vorgon demolition ship with his somewhat friend, galactical hitchhiker Ford Prefect, and tortured mercilessly by the Vogon commander's poetry recitation:   O Frettled Gruntbuggly, thy micturations are to me / As plurdled gabbleblotchits on a lurgid bee / Groop, I implore thee, my foonting turlingdromes / And hooptiously drangle me with crinkly bindlewurdles / lest I rend thee in the gobberwarts with my blurgle-cruncheon / See if I don't. 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I can ridicule AltaVista's Babelfish French because I know just enough French to understand the monstrous syntax errors (the mistranslation of nouns is unforgivable though...) Also, they render Celine Dion lyrics extremely cogently.  However, I've decided that the Russian is totally useful.  I know less than nothing about Russian grammar... put a smoking gun to my head, I still won't be able to read Cyrillic.  And you might be wondering what exactly I'd need to translate Russian for.  Well, I was flipping through the March issue of MOJO  (God bless British music mags...)  and came across an unreleased solo album by the one and only Robin Gibbs, who I'm sure is everyone's favorite Bee Gee.  The link provided led me to a Russian mp3 site that charges 1-cent per Mb downloaded(!).  Which leads me to my next question: just how legal are these Russian mp3 sites in the States?
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've been at it again, but the categories are getting blurry.  Everything is turning up in 'pop/rock'.  I'm having a hard time telling the difference between 'alternative pop/rock' and 'indie pop/rock' and I don't want to see that unnatural pseudo-word 'pop/rock' anymore.  And for that matter, anything 'post-'... post-rock, post-grunge, post-... Furthermore, what the hell distinguishes experimental post-rock from electronica?  And just because Leaves is an Icelandic band, does it mean it can't be considered Britpop?  They sound the same!  I feel like I'm on Sesame Street.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I spent a good six hours last night filing and re-filing my albums.  In the end, I put it all back the way it was.  To be honest, I was overwhelmed by the complexity.  I had categories like 'post-rock', 'shoegaze', 'lo-fi', and 'noise pop' that would have been lovely if I only had more albums to put under each designation.  On the upside, I found this neat website that traces the development of contemporary music movements and gives you thoughtful reviews on influencial albums:  urlLink http://www.allmusic.com/mus_Styles.html   For example, Jesus and Mary Chain is considered 'noise pop' but are also the progenitors of the later 'shoegaze' movement that somehow, inevitably, spawns 'britpop'.  Also, found an article about Fleetwood Mac being the least influencial great band:  urlLink http://slate.msn.com/id/2097404/.   Remastered versions of their white album, Rumours, and Tusk are hitting shelves next Tuesday, and I still find myself very tempted to at least get the later two.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This just in, from a  urlLink BBC article  Phillip sent me: the face of Doctor Who has changed again.  Paul Gann (the last one) wasn't too bad, but he had this bland aloofness going on in Tom Baker's wardrobe, and the movie was horrendous... in spite of Eric Roberts as an over-the-top Master.  This time around, BBC's going for "edgy" and "eccentric" and the Doctor's got a lean and hungry look in the form of  urlLink Christopher Eccleston  who I've only seen in Gone in 60 Seconds as the cabinet maker baddie, but I'm all for it cuz I remember in the summer of 6th grade when I'd stay up 'til 2 in the morning to catch Doctor Who on PBS, and catching odd bits of Blake's 7 which was on either before or after it.  I took Daytime Sudafed(R) six hours ago and I am so wired it isn't even funny.  And I'm in the mood for organizing my music collection again.  This time, I'm thinking of going with genre.  I've tried by artist, but too cliche... chronological, but it's too hard to remember.  I'll open the floor to suggestions for categories now.   (I just wanted too add an addendum to that: no way will I ever label a category "alternative".  Because that, in itself, is completely nondescriptive.  Furthermore, everything I own would end up falling under that heading... except for the Fleetwood Mac.)   And... my brain's just whizzing and whirling in there.  Saw the season 7 finale of Stargate SG-1 and it was excellent: it showcased Michael Shanks and Richard Dean Anderson's humorous bantering and wicked comic timing and was heartbreaking as well.. not once, but twice, they played the Sam/Jack theme.  This last episode is supposed to set up the Stargate spin-off which looks totally blah to me, but whatever.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Managed to tear myself away from listening to the streaming Rumours bonus disc for the umpteeth time and check out some new stuff:  Stacey's compiled some material from her collection for me, so I've been listening some Morrissey, Death Cab for Cutie, Postal Service...  and Hawksley Workman.  Can't go wrong with a name like 'Hawksley', can ya?  But I still think Apples in Stereo should die a painstakingly slow and ignomious death.    Followed a link from Pitchfork.com for  urlLink Patrick Wolf  and am currently watching one of his sets recorded for  urlLink xFM .  Self-described as folk-electronica, he looks eerily like Elliot Smith reborn, with the idiosyncratic proclivity for accordions, ukuleles, and violas.  A  viola  player...  *shakes head disapprovingly*  According to his website, doubleyoudoubleyoudoubleyoudotpatrickwolfdotcom (I get a kick outta that), he's touring Stateside in May, tbc.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Nice to know the Mac is still a money-making behemoth.  They're re-releasing Rumours and Tusk (and I believe the white Fleetwood Mac album) with bonus discs of unreleased masters.  I've been listening to the  urlLink Rumours Bonus Disc  this morning, and now wiffle waffling over whether to buy the re-release even though we all know I have them already.   F---in' wanker!   According to  urlLink burnish.net , the Fleetwood Mac PBS special is being released on CD  and  DVD May 2nd.  Still no word on Lindsey's Soundstage episode though.  I'm thinking late summer on that one...
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ...when you wake up feeling dumb and nothing makes sense but it's okay because it's Monday.  I had the weirdest dream yesterday.  I was back in the Music Library complaining to my old boss about having to work with Potter the pig and her newly hired mangy dog, who we called The Mangy Dog because I was breaking out in hives having to work in close proximity to dirty animals.  And she broke out into song to sing the many virtues of Potter and the dream slowly devolved into a gay musical and thankfully, I woke up.  It was only 5:05am so I decided to go back to sleep for another half hour or so, but was rudely awakened 12 minutes later by someone whispering "BOO!" really loudly in my ear.  I startled, looked around, but there was no one there...
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      If I had to describe this film in one word, it would be  fragmented .  I wouldn't imagine that it was coherent enough to capture the attention of casual channel surfers.  But fortunately, I'm unabashedly a diehard fan, so I sat through all the whinging and actually got something out of it.  Most of the time, the band is  bickering about whether they could make a double album and whose studio to send their masters to be mixed.  You also get to see some of the recording process, which I always think is neat.  But the movie is not very comprehensive, like they didn't have much of a story to tell.  And Lindsey whines alot, in the name of artistic integrity of course.  In the end, though, you get to see them backstage right before the first Say You Will gig: Lindsey kisses Stevie's knuckles and they walk out on stage hand-in-hand... you just wanna go  awwwww . *grin*   Mick Fleetwood:  I want to say something. John McVie:  You've said enough already!  You should be in the f---ing Senate or something. 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Things I've been listening to recently that lost me after the first track:  1.  SNOW PATROL, Final Straw:  I like the first track.  I really do.  I'm so glad they put it first.  Otherwise, I would've never heard it had they made me wade through the mire to get to it.  2.  THE VINES, Winning Days:  I know it's cliche, but I just have to say this.  They all need to shower.  Badly.  And scrub Comet(R) into their scalp or something.  3.  THE WALKMEN, Bows and Arrows:  I think it's the toy piano... God shall smite the toy piano, Apples in Stereo, and SUVs come Judgement Day.   I repeat, this is not a drill. This is the apocalypse. Please exit the hospital in an orderly fashion. Thank you. 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I neglected to post the last two days of this endeavor (Monday and Tuesday) and then, naturally, the rest of the week was a haywire yo-yo sleep thing.  My internal clock didn't even have the decency to let me sleep in the next morning.  I set my alarm for something like 6 o'clock and wouldn't you know it, I wake up at 3 freakin' 59?  What's new in my head:  1.  Recently, I managed to catch another music video (non-TRL) on MTV... will wonder never f@#!! cease?  I'm amazed by the growth displayed by Blink-182 in their latest video  urlLink "I Miss You" .  What's remarkable is that, by aping The Jesus and Mary Chain, or as I like call them: la cadena de HAY-sus y Maria (sorry, inside joke), the Blink guys and their shallow jackass-itude have somehow become more endearing...  The chorus in this song, albeit catchy and hooky, could have been, in my opinion, repeated just a few times less.  I mean, it's like they ran out of verses and had to fill up the rest of the 3 minutes with something for fear that the entire record would run only 27 minutes long.  2.  I'm slowly gaining appreciation for THE WRENS' Meadowlands.  I think what irked me at first listen were the overly bright, jangly guitars in the first few tracks.  Fortunately for my attention span deficiency, they invested enough elsewhere in the first few tracks to stay my impatience.  3.  Fox's new mid-season replacement WONDERFALL looks quirky and daring.  Too bad it's just going to get canceled like other quirky and daring Fox programs.   Remember Keen Eddie?  Remember Firefly?   I'd say that Fox has abused it's network privledges one too many times.  NO MORE GOOD SHOWS FOR YOU!  Fox just ticks me off...  4.  Last night's JAG was the best episode I've seen in a long time.  It didn't leave me rabidly foaming at the mouth, spouting various nonsensical profanities at the television screen.  On the contrary, for once I was all warm fuzzies over the fact that Harm's going to finally remove that foot lodged permanently in his throat since the beginning of the season because he said  yet ...  5.  Looking forward to the Fleetwood Mac documentary tomorrow night.  Let's hope I get the Central/Eastern time straight for once.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The weather today was so nice, I felt like sitting in the grass and staring at the sun.  Of course, now, I'm awfully itchy everywhere, but it's a small price to pay.  Spent a couple of hours in the park by Schimelpfenig Library this afternoon and took some pictures.  A few turned out quite nice, in my opinion:    My brother.    An microcosm of life embedded in yellow clay.    You must try some of my purple berries / I been eating them for six or seven weeks now / Haven't got sick once...    Some kind of shelf mushroom.  To take this picture, I had to lean against a tree teeming with these strange red ants that crawled around with their asses in the air.  Wish I could've gotten a shot of that. 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Fleetwood Mac... yes, those geriatric cocaine rockers... are back on tour Stateside, hitting Dallas on June 17th at the Smirnoff.  Meanwhile, VH1 is airing, commercial-free, a new documentary of their soap operatic studio life on March 14th, 8PM CST.  Here is a link to the press release:   urlLink http://biz.yahoo.com/prnews/040305/nyf017_1.html   Here's an update on PBS Soundstage where it lists not only a Fleetwood Mac concert, but a LINDSEY solo performance.  Those episodes are scheduled to be aired in the summer.  Though, I think some PBS stations are cheating and airing the Mac one on the 17th.  But of course, naturally, not our belov'd local PBS affiliate, KERA.   urlLink http://www.pbs.org/wttw/soundstage/index.htm   And get this... they're releasing a Live in Boston DVD from the first half of the US tour which PK and I saw live in Vegas last June.  They may be old, but they be LOUD.  It's one of those concerts that you feel the music literally.  A good thing, fortunately, given the nosebleed bleacher seating we had!  And watch for Lindsey B's antics on stage... the rabid gerbil impression in "Come", boxing with Stevie's tambourine in "Tusk"... and who could forget the  tusking ...
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Sorry for not posting recently.  This waking up at 4am thing is really taking its toll on my incentive to blog in the afternoon.  My hard drive installation was successful, by the way.  It's fancy, fancy, and rather empty at the moment.  I also installed an SB Audigy 2 card, and it's probably just my imagination, but oggs have never sounded so good on my Klipschorns...  Had a Mary Poppins moment yesterday morning (and this is pre-tornado).  It was so windy, my umbrella nearly lifted me off the ground.  Being the cheap piece of crap that it was, instead of the Flying Researcher, my umbrella promptly snapped in half instead.  Speaking of flying, driving to work was in itself a unique experience.  In order to maintain an appropriate highway speed, you had to drive behind another car.  It's like those migrating geese were the point flyer takes the brunt of the air shear or something.  In this case, the lead car would inevitably slow down and someone else would take his place.  It definitely wasn't as well coordinated as geese flight, and other drivers had much less altruistic mentalities than I give them credit for, but it was an interesting scenario nonetheless.  These past few days, I've had the lo--   EDIT: For some odd reason, the rest of my post has been truncated.  And I don't remember what I wrote about yesterday, except that I'd wish Fred Durst had been stomped repeated by a giant foot from the sky for attempting sing "Behind Blue Eyes".  It brought tears to my eyes and not in a good way. 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Nothing much new today.  I find that I'm outrageously productive at 6 o'clock in the morning.  If only there were guarantees that I could wake up at 4am every morning past the duration of this experiment...   I cleaned out my glove compartment this afternoon.  Some object kept vibrating against the plastic interior when I was driving home from work today.  In disgust, I threw open the hatch and started pulling items out.  I found a check book (not mine), a ruler, 3 copies of my current insurance card, all my past insurance cards dating back to the year 2000, a nondescript toy rodent that squeaks when molested, two receipts from the dentist, and a reminder to my dad that he has a dentist appointment on August 12th, 2002.  Since I'm home so early, I'm going to take this time to install that new hard drive I bought, oh, two weeks ago?  So, if I'm not blogging tomorrow or the next day, it's safe to say that I've managed to mutilate my computer again.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It took awhile to catch up to me, but I can safely say now, at 3:26pm, I am EXHAUSTED.  Quite nice, though, this ridiculously early work thing, because I'm driving to work at 5 in the morning and everyone is behaving... civilized almost.  Had too much coffee.  Was loopy and wired all morning.  I felt so bad, it felt good.  But not now.  Now... I am ready to just slump over my keyboard and pass out.  But I can't.  My brain is still zooming like that space travel simulating screen saver in Windows.  Britney Spears' "Toxic" is stuck in my head.  I broke my car adaptor for my CD player recently, so I've had to listen to the radio.  They play that song waay too much.  They play Outkast too much.  And John Mayer.  And Sheryl Crow.  Radio programming is assinine.  Currently listening to a few things that don't grate on my ears in the ridiculously early morn:   POLYPHONIC SPREE Cultishly creepy with their flowy white robes and ecstatic choral orgies.  They're playing the Curtain Club in Deep Ellum on March 17th, and I've heard that they're much better live than recorded.   MARC BOLAN AND T.REX Maan, this guy had giganormous hair!   Get it on... Bang a gong... Get it on...    THE WRENS I've been listening to Meadowlands and beginning to see why it's so widely acclaimed.  It's not the most immediately accessible album, in my opinion.  Anyone have a clue on how to get a copy of their first album Seacacus?  And lastly, I went to Circuit City today to check out surround sound speakers, and I must say that I'm severely disappointed in the Infinity TSS-750.  It's tinny, quiet, and altogether too bright for my taste.  I had my heart set on that set, but now I'm definitely not so sure.  So I'm opening the forum to suggestions.  I'm looking for a 5 or 6 speaker system for my living room (which doesn't have a lot of unoccupied nooks and crannies for large speakers).  I'd like something balanced with a clear dialogue coming from the center channel.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      We're on tornado watch right now.  I thought I'd watch the sky for awhile.  It isn't often you get the chance to slow down completely.  If I were really ambitious, I'd turn off my computer and just listen to the rumbling of the thunder.  Not a drop of rain though.  The sky is dry heaving tonight.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      And here's another glimpse of my backyard...    I've decided to buckle up and try to post something new every single day.  I may just end up writing a boatload of crap.  We'll see how this little experiment goes at the end of the week.  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Posts currently floating about in my brain:  1. Why does Bering Strait remind me of Fleetwood Mac?  2. The Wrens review.  It's been there for a month now.  Swirling through the dentate gyrus or something.  3. What is Neo-Psychedelia?  We're gonna hafta skip Post-Rock for now.  I hate that category and I'll tell you why later.  I'd like to sit down sometime this week and hammer those posts out.  In the meantime, I'd suggest everyone to run to the Fleetwood Mac video page on  urlLink RollingStone.com   They've currently got a bunch of live 1975-7 back when Lindsey was still finger-picking steel-string Les Pauls:    Dreams : Stevie Nicks is one hot, sexy mama.  This is the newest addition to this page.  A definite must-see.    Rhiannon : The earliest clip in this collection.    Tusk : Fleetwood Mac recruited the USC Trojan marching band for this track.  Filmed on the football field, you'll see Christine McVie walking around with a martini, Stevie Nicks twirling a baton, those silly band geeks with those stupid, stupid uniforms, and the ever-adorable Lindsey Buckingham minus the 'fro.    You Make Loving Fun : They were right.  Keyboard players never look cool even if they're in a rock band.  Watch towards the end as Stevie plays the wooden fish.  That's right.  You heard me.  The wooden fish.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Link to Picture   Ok, ok, I  might  have fiddled with the color balance a little, but that metallic sheen on the dragonfly just looks too cool.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        The lemon tree.. er, shrub rather.. in the backyard.    Flowering sage.    English ivy creeping poolside.    Formerly potted petunia-related plant.    Oregano that I messed with on Photoshop.  That green just looks... unnatural. 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm so tired.  My body's practically humming with exhaustion.  My brother and his friends stayed up until 3:30 this morning (and probably much later than that but I told them to shut up by then).    I posted this yesterday, changed my mind, but forgot to republish the blog.  So it's back.  Again.  Here's a link to pictures I took at my brother's party:  urlLink http://home.comcast.net/~tina.han/Birthday.html 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Divas Live starts off with a rousing screech fest rendition of “Lady Marmalade” by the original disco space glam diva herself (wait, was there more than one of those?) Patti LaBelle, Starkist almost-spokewoman Jessica Simpson, and the wildly unique Cyndi Lauper.  To borrow the cliché expression, if these three ladies were ice cream flavors, LaBelle would be chocolate, Simpson vanilla, and Cyndi Lauper… rainbow tutti frutti.  I adore her.  Blondie’s Debbie Harry, so painfully out of place with her skin tight homemade camo skirt and bug eyed Yoko Ono shades, performs “Rapture” with Eve rapping an interlude.  Joss Stones sings her latest single, channeling a wholesome, uncomplicated Janis Joplin.  I appreciate the fact that a 16 year old British girl can dig old-fashioned soul music.  She is so comfortable performing, swaying aimlessly barefooted and having little twirly gypsy moments.  Cyndi Lauper performs two numbers: first, a Latinized cover of a really old Motown song “Stay”, which is actually one of my all-time favorite songs so I wasn’t looking forward to hearing someone else butcher it ( aah-Jackson Browne-chooo! ).  But Cyndi Lauper shines live because it showcases her quirky spontaneity, and I was completely distracted by her strange, jerky dancing that I didn’t even notice what the song sounded like.  Best moment:  Oh, won’t you stay / Just a little bit longer / Please, please stay / Say that you will…  No. No? No. Si! No! SI, SI, SI!  (stamps her feet)  She is so cute.  Lauper goes on to sing an acoustic version of "Time After Time" with Patti LaBelle, but those two have rather clashing styles and it sounded too weird.  After this performance, I lost interest in the TV.  I couldn’t tell you what went on afterwards.  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Thursday is the worst day of the week.  I think it has something to do with the fact that I had piano lessons on Thursdays in middle school.  Also, add to that another unfortunate Thursday occurence: I was born on a Thursday.  I hate Thursdays with an incomparable vehemence.  It's infinitely worse than Sunday when you get that trapped feeling that Monday and work is just around the corner.  It's worse than Wednesday when you realize the week's only  half  over.  It's even worse than Monday, when I'm really just walking around half asleep pushing buttons.  Yesterday, while driving home, I had been reflecting on the fact that I'd seen more consecutive traffic accidents this week on the Tollway than I'd ever seen in the past three months put together.  In my work-wearied mind, I took it to be a sign that I should put myself on orange alert for those wicked traffic vibes were bound to be spreading like daycare pink eye.  And then, after being ignored and nearly merged on twice, I had my next not-quite-all-there driving thought: what if I'd  already  been in some horrible accident that was indeed so atrocious, it ravaged my memory, and I was consequently condemned to reliving rush hour Tollway traffic trying to get home not knowing I was already dead.  You see... these SUVs that so thoughtlessly cut me off... they just didn't see my gruesome half-burnt mangled spectral image in my ghostly Japanese import chariot...  The horror of that thought stayed with me for all of.. oh.. five minutes.  Then I got pissed off at some other driver and the fervent cursing kept me focused enough to get home without incident.  Once I got home, I promptly fell asleep for 12 hours.  Turns out, I really did need sleep.  I might've also had some 24 hour hallucinatory thing as well.  Who knows.  I had this odd dream that some people I knew in  high school and I built a concrete plane that we were going to enter in an aeroengineering competition. Trouble was, it just would stay up in the air.  I wonder why.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      On a lark, I followed a link for an album called  urlLink  Plano  .  Just from what I've gleaned from various reviews, this album is "clever gay lounge pop" with "girl-like harmonies", all-in-all, "a distinctive, classy, almost sexual sound".  Gay love in the suburbs.  This has been.. a Gilbert Godfrey.. WHAT THE F*#! moment.  Thanks for tuning in.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Here's an informative post for you folks out there who think I'd hadn't learned a bit from trying to catalog my CD collection awhile back.  Which I didn't.  Catalog my collection that is.  But I did discover a host of heretofore unknown (to me) semi-meaningful alternative/indie rock genre labels.  I figure I'd start a series of entries devoted to the wonderful world of sub-sub-categories.  Chamber Pop.  Not the catchiest of labels.  Not as esoteric sounding as Baroque Pop, infinitely kinder than Twee Pop, yet somehow it all falls under the "heavily informed by the Brian Wilson/Pet Sounds" love fest.  Chamber Pop is defined by the All Music Guide as "inspired in part by the lounge-music revival but with a complete absence of irony or kitsch, chamber pop placed a renewed emphasis on melody and production, as artists layered their baroque, ornate songs with richly textured orchestral strings and horns, all the while virtually denying the very existence of grunge, electronica, and other concurrent musical movements urlLink [AMG]. "  So basically, music that I totally adore and would be absolutely mortified being caught listening to.  A quintessential example of chamber pop is Belle & Sebastian's  urlLink "I'm Waking Up to Us" .  In fact, most of Belle & Sebastian discography probably qualifies under this nomenclature, but I've chosen this track in particular because of the bassoon/English horn duet.  Anyone can use strings.  That's a solid post-production trick founded by the Courvoisier-swigging megalomaniac Phil Spector himself.  Now ask yourself this: how often do you hear a double reed instrument in pop songs?  The only problem I have with B & S is that it is oh so very twee, and after a few hours, one cannot help but wish to vomit.  Other artists who enjoy chamber pop designation include:    Lambchop, a Nashville-based alt-countryish group who just released 2 brilliant albums back-to-back:  Aw, C'mon  and  No You C'mon .  (I own these, if anyone wishes to hit me up for a copy.)   Sigur Ros, who, in my personal opinion, are more chamber than of the post-rock movement, but more on that later...   Polyphonic Spree, the cultish 20-plus member, Dallas-based choral orgy, currently on tour with their flowy white robes opening for Bowie.  and...   Rufus Wainwright, Loudon's wayward son who I never really understood.  If there are any Wainwright fans out there, please enlighten me.  And tune in next week for a couple of sentences on...  Post-Rock/Experimental! 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Actually, this post is not about Sufjan Stevens.  It's really about this random mp3 I downloaded from Pitchfork's free download section.  It's actually really, really about how I hate my own voice.  And, ugh... I hate my own voice.  So, let's start at the beginning... I was casually surfing this morning, casually scrolling down the page when I see this guy holding a banjo.  Okay.  Well, I like banjos.  And his name was cool and unpronounceable, so I'm like, yeah, let's download it.  And ding!  It's finished downloading and I click it to open in Winamp.  Yeah, there are banjos.  It's nice, mellow, unoffensive... and then this vocal.  What the hell.  Is this what Sufjan Stevens sounds like?  He freaking sounds like me!  I'm officially disgusted.  I hate my voice.  Click  urlLink here  to judge for yourself.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm thinking FRANZ FERDINAND and SCISSOR SISTERS.. two buzz-worthy artists of the past few months.. with that pelvic-pivoting bass line.. unavoidably, unabashedly  discotheque  even if critics file them under "dance-rock".  Whatever.  I'm also suddenly reminded that that U2 album released in the late 90s wasn't as bad as I thought it was when I first bought it.  In my old age, I too can be forgiving.   Disco is cool!   If you want it...  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Most of the time, I don't really know why I have a standing subscription to Rolling Stone.  But since I do, and they keep coming, I'm feeling guiltily obligated to at least flip though them.  The last two issues have been rather unpalatable: highlights were Amy Lee (of Evanescence)'s confession that she sings Aguilera in the shower and the Tommy Hilfiger ad featuring a plastic fantastic David Bowie and Iman.  On the other hand, on those rare occasions when RS delivers, they really really do.  (It's that cliche:  when it rains... )  There are just certain things that Rolling Stone does best, namely that kind of morbidly fascinating interview-introspectives that musicians never seem to grant any other publications.  Things I enjoyed in the current issue:  1.  The cover story was excellent: "Goddess and the Geek: Inside Quentin's Obsession With Uma".  Brought to you by the same guy who wrote the excellent Iggy Pop article a couple of issues ago.  I only read the Uma half in this article though.  Reading Quentin Tarantino's dialogue made me want to bite my nails.  2.  "Talking Crazy with Billy Bob"... he's certifiable.   See that label on my beer bottle?  The reason that label is like that is because I turn the bottle a certain way, because there are points, a sharpness to it.  I don't have any sharp or dangerous things facing where my children are.  I always know where northwest is because that's where the kids are from.  So what this label is doing is gathering them up in a semicircle to protect them.   3.  David Fricke's coverage of the 2004 South by Southwest Music and Media Conference in Austin.  Dude, I wish I lived near something like that.  I'd go every year to check out new bands.  I liked his descriptions of this Australian band called ARCHITECTURE IN HELSINKI which he generously writes: "...improves on the artic mystery of Sigur Ros by adding the infectious thrust of the B-52s."  It reminds me of this Scandinavian Studies class I took.  Seriously, that's all there is to study in Finland..  Inuit linguistics and the strange cottages in the countryside.  Unfortunately, what little I've heard by them sound more like Belle & Sebastian if only Isobelle sang all the time... and that's just twee.  4. Economists at Harvard and U. of North Carolina collaborated in a new study that suggests file-sharing is not responsible for the decline of major label CD sales.  I could've told you that.  In fact, it's due to the over-marketing of congealed banana instant oatmeal.  5. Q&A with Debbie Harry who wishes she could rap like Missy Elliot and Ludacris.  She's so cool, yet humble enough to admit that she isn't good at everything.  Wish she'd stop trying to rap though...  If only Rolling Stone would stick to what they're good at.  Leave the classic rock remniscences and Beatles worship to the British music mags and ridiculously irrelevant top whatever lists to VH1.   This post was brought to you by MODEST MOUSE, "Good News for People Who Love Bad News".  I don't think they sound like The Shins.  Why do they keep saying that? 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My brother: A-flat. You're  A-flat , Tina. Me: Bite me.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Me: Bryan, are you stupid or something? My brother: Oui!  Je suis francais.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Me: You have no witty response, because it's true! My brother: ... You're FAT!  Hah!  Witty, witty, me, me, ME!
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      In recent news...  Bob Dylan is in the new Victoria Secret commercials and no one cares.  It amazes me how Dylan can get slammed for licensing his songs to a corporate entity (Bank of Montreal), but applauded for participating in a campaign that objectifies and portrays women as an invading horde of alien entities from another galaxy.  Some faculty member at the U of Ark. (being so poorly paid as it is) is being paid off by anti-abortion flukies to testify that in his opinion, fetuses have feelings too.  This example corroborates the US News article I read yesterday about how science is biased by virtue of nonobjective funding entities, and my opinion as well that the Bush administration is slowly sucking my brains out of my nose like oatmeal.  And also, it's been officially announced on CNN that the world has no sense of humor.  In fact, humor is an flit-fleeting, ephemeral entity that has staying power only when your audience is comprised primarily of middle-aged Japanese businessmen.  Georgian fundamentalists are still having problems with evolution.  What else is new?  And finally, UConn 70, Tennessee 61.  I don't even know what sport that is.  For all I know, it could be an intercollegiate debate.  Yeah, right.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ...and I'm a nail biter.  I fell off the proverbial wagon today, so to speak.  I ravaged the nail of my right index finger.  And after just about 12 years of abstaining (that was when I got braces and, to my horror, my teeth didn't close properly anymore!), this comes as an unwelcomed reminder of what a neurotic person I am.  WILL IT NEVER END?!?
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Remember how I was agonizing over whether to get the remastered Fleetwood Mac albums a few weeks back?  Well, I've decided not to get them.  I've just gotten the chance to hear the Tusk bonus disk... and the songs are not all that different from the album version.  Well, some tracks have really strange drumming.  I hear it's because Lindsey decided to record everything next to the bathroom floor.  The extra tracks on the Rumours edition are pretty cool though.  But Tusk is my favorite record.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ever since I got off work on Friday, I've had this feeling of vague uneasiness permeate my hair follicles... like there's something I needed to do and didn't do, and when I finally remember what it is I didn't do and need to, I'm going to be in deep shit.  What I realized is that apparently I need stress in my life and for the last two weeks, work had been aptly providing that stress.  Friday, however, I managed to solve the mini-crisis... and I felt so relieved, yet strangely disappointed that that was it.  If it hadn't been apparent earlier that I'm neurotic to an extreme, it should be now... *smirk*  So anyway, the absence of this stressor apparently led to the resurfacing of some nameless anxiety (that probably arose evolutionarily when we left trees for open space... dangit,  knew  that was a bad idea!)  To alleviate this, I went on a shopping splurge and bought the following:   2 pairs of DKNY jeans that fit  perfectly  (and also emptied my bank account perfectly)   a face cleanser, body wash, and exfoliator from Bath & Body Works' latest line of products named after kitchen staples (tomato, rice, and salt...)   a birthday present for my grandma's 70th   a stuffed lamb toy with an appropriately vapid facial expression from Kay Bee's because they are still going out of business  and finally,   Reese's white chocolate/peanut butter eggs which I'd been looking for for months... even better, in fact, than the normal "cup" variety: more pb, less choc!  Three things that I wish I could've gotten, but didn't for various reasons:   I'm always looking for camo green cargo pants, but I'm so picky, I never find a pair I like.  For example, I hate those loose strings in front that make them look like karate belts.  I hate buckles.  I hate excessive pocketing... I tried this pair on at Macy's that were simple, but they were waay too loose!  So I tried a size 6, then a size 4, and they were still too loose!  And then, I started getting paranoid that maybe I was in the "larger women" clothing section by mistake...   I found this cute Hamtaro stuffed hamster that were about 2 inches tall at the toy store.  But as it was, KB's going out of business and all, they only had one in stock and it was the Russian diva hamster.  I don't like the Russian diva hamster.   I never found the latest album by TV ON THE RADIO.  Well, I never looked.  I was too tired at this point.  Still, that would've made my day of perfect purchases complete.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My brother had a epic nosebleed last night and by the time it was all over, my bathroom looked like a hastily mopped up crime scene with pinkish water swirling down the drain.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Previously: the face of  urlLink Doctor Who  has changed again. Paul Gann (Doctor #8) wasn't too bad, but he had this bland aloofness going on in Tom Baker's wardrobe, and the movie was horrendous... in spite of Eric Roberts as an over-the-top Master. This time around, BBC's going for "edgy" and "eccentric" and the Doctor #9's got a lean and hungry look in the form of  urlLink Christopher Eccleston  who I've only seen in Gone in 60 Seconds as the cabinet maker baddie, but I'm all for it cuz I remember in the summer of 6th grade when I'd stay up 'til 2 in the morning to catch Doctor Who on PBS, and catching odd bits of Blake's 7 which was on either before or after it.  urlLink [3/20/04]   Some British tabloid reports now that Madame Toussand's creepy celebrity wax dolls will be trying to take over the world in the opening episodes of the new Doctor Who and that David Beckham will play a wax dummy.  I guess the acting won't be much of a stretch. *dodging rotten tomatoes*  Actually, I'm not too clear on that.  Maybe the article was trying to say that the wax dummy was going to play a wax dummy.  *shrug* Aaand... it's good to hear that Doctor Who plots remain as cheesy and uncomplicated as ever.  In my case, familiarity breeds affection, and I eagerly look forward to seeing Christopher Eccleston fend off murderous facsimiles of Madonna and Kylie Minogue.  urlLink [Dark Horizons] 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Gisting "Can the Subaltern Sing? Or Who's Ashamed of William Hung?" / PopMatters Article written by Sharon Mizota   Watching William Hung's determined flailing and flat-pitched delivery of "She Bangs" on his American Idol audition, you've just gotta give this kid credit for getting out here, on stage, and publically humiliate himself in front of the general American public.  Now with a record deal, a music video, merchandising and trinkets, wouldn't you think this infamy has gone a little too far?  Generally accepted good points of William Hung's celebrity:  1. Despite Simon Cowell's scathing remarks and Randy Jackson quivering like a bowl of jelly with uncontrollable laughter, he "took it like a man" so to speak:  I already gave my best.  I have no regrets.   Regardless of whether that's a lack of self-awareness or just plain delusion, we all wish we could sing that badly in public and have no regrets about doing so.  2. Naive or delusional as the case may be, ultimately he's a very real person as opposed to the personalities on "reality" shows (and I use the term loosely).  More average than all the Average Joes combined.  Critics, however, claim that his celebrity is flimsily veiled contempt and ridicule that revolve around the axis of RACE and MASCULINITY:  1. On a Today Show performance, some fans wore photocopies of Hung's face as masks with holes cut out for eyes.  While perhaps unintentional, this "yellowface" roleplaying revives a "long tradition of co-optation and performance of race".  Mizota argues that such a performance is akin to the paradigm of blackface ministry of classic cinema and silent picture shows, an "identification with a source of power and a means to control and contain that power... a sensitive barometer of white racial anxiety, longings, and guilt."  2. Asian American men have a historically emasculated media image as a result of white paranoia over the early "bachelor societies" that formed due to unbalanced immigration.  Ming the Merciless anyone?  William Hung with his awkward, earnest and most unmanly persona fits nicely in this prepackaged category.  Furthermore, as Asian Americans, his weirdness allows the rest of us to feel good about ourselves.  In other words, he represents all that is fobby and unassimilated about Asian Americans, and we should all breathe a sigh of relief that we are not like him.  In the end, Mizota suggests that "Hung embodies a new kind of male ideal".  While agree with many of her points, especially the ones regarding the Asian American attitude towards William Hung, I don't think I would go quite as far to say that Hung is the new paragon of masculinity.  urlLink [PopMatters] 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Morgan Spurlock and his trusty handlebar mustache takes viewers on a expose of the health risks associated with eating at McDonald's every day.  Well, duh.  If it hadn't been self-evident before, it should be by the end of this film.  Using his own body as the template for experimentation, Spurlock embarks on a personalized health crisis by reproducing the eating habits of the general American public.  Within two weeks of starting his new low-veg, all-Mac diet, he gains 17 pounds, suffers a precipitous decline in liver function, and most damaging of all: sexual impotence.  McDonald's is bad for your sex life.  If that isn't the message to take home from this documentary, I'll eat my hat!   urlLink [Stylus] 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      What can I say?  I'm on a Dan Brown kick.  I do believe I have one more of his books to go before I've read 'em all.  They're entertaining, they go fast, and they work wonders on my prematurely stunted attention span.  Deception Point was not as good as the Robert Langdon books (Angels & Demons, The Da Vinci Code).  However formulaic the other two were, this just wasn't my cuppa... It's a high tech thriller, enthused about a NASA satellite or whatnot nonsense.  The protagonists - a dashing made-for-tv oceanographer and a feisty intelligence analyst whose father is a smarmy politician - seem awfully familiar.  Believe it or not, I actually enjoy Dan Brown's writing  because  his characterizations are shallow.  It's nice to once in awhile to read a novel and not have to get so emotionally involved with fictional characters.  I don't necessarily discount that as shoddy writing.  It's written for a 3 hour flight, a weekend at the beach, etc. etc. may the cliches overfloweth.  The only book left to be read is  Digital Fortress: A Thriller , although any book that has to tell its reader that it's supposed to be a thriller is rather suspect...  urlLink [Amazon] 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This is the second post I've written regarding a CD released in 2004.  I feel like I've finally caught up to the new year, and it's not even half over yet.  Go me!  And to top that off, another feather in my cap: initially, I thought the title of this album was in reference to this Lemonheads track called  urlLink "My Hero, Zero"  that Evan Dando did for Schoolhouse Rock.   My hero, Zero / such a funny little hero / But till you came along / We counted on our fingers and toes.   And I was totally down with that.  But then I thought some more about it and decided that it could've also been refering to Disney's Hercules soundtrack:  Hercie, he comes / He sees, he conquers / Honey, the crowds were / Going bonkers / He showed the moxie brains, and spunk / From zero to hero a major hunk / Zero to hero and who'da thunk ... And I find that utterly distressing.   urlLink [Stylus]   urlLink [Pitchfork]  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'd like to see a show of hands of who HASN'T heard of Michael Moore's new anti-Bush documentary.  Slowly, but surely, Fahrenheit 9/11 is gaining publicity especially after Moore's standing ovation at Cannes and despite Disney's adamant refusal to distribute it.  Michael Moore supposedly gets personal in this film, establishing ties between the Bush family and wealthy Saudi clans including the bin Ladins.  Maybe it'll even suggest the possibility of gasoline price conspiracies that Phillip's such a fan of.   urlLink l">[CNN]  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Considering how much TV I DON'T watch anymore, I wasn't sure I'd have any opinions about Fall television...  Apparently, I still care.  Buzzworthy on CBS' fall line-up is CSI: New York, a second generation spin-off of my all-time third favorite show.  The "pilot" episode premiered last week on CSI: Miami when Horatio Caine (David Caruso) followed a suspect up to New York and joined forces with the New York counterparts.  Greg Sinise (Apollo 13, Forrest Gump, the perpetual best supporting actor nominee) leads the New York cast, along with Melina Kanakaredes the doctor from Providence.  Wednesdays, 9pm CST.  JAG, of course, is coming back for a 10th season.  The folks at CBS aren't fools.  *grin*   urlLink [Dark Horizons]   The fact that The Practice has been cancelled doesn't upset me.  I lost interest in that show even before Dylan McDermott and Lara Flynn Boyle were sacked from the show.  But, the fact that it's successor spin-off Fleet Street brings William Shatner back on the small screen in something that is NOT a priceline.com commercial... Fleet Street stars James Spader who apparently impressed TPTB by single-handedly reviving interest the last season of The Practice.  Not that I particularly cared or bothered to watch.  Sundays, 9pm CST.  Also worth mentioning is a new medical drama called Grey's Anatomy which revolves around the lives of first year surgical residents.  So... Scrubs, but not trying to be funny.  Mid-season replacement.  Mondays, 9pm CST.   urlLink [Dark Horizons]   NBC has Joey, of course, and the world is waiting with bated breath... But really what caught my eye is this show called Revelations starring Bill Pullman that has decidedly religious overtones in an epic Science vs. Faith struggle ala Dan Brown.  Also, there's a new Law & Order spin-off.  This fall is not the season for innovative.   urlLink [Dark Horizons]   As for fox, I've made a conscious decision to never watch that network again.  Mention any of the following words to me, and I will scream: Keen. Eddie. Firefly. Veritas. John. Doe. Miracles. Tick. Titus. I don't think I need to go on.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm disappointed to report that instead of finally assembling the fragmented mosaic that is the long awaited SMILE album, Brian Wilson is  re-recording  it with those Wondermint nuts.   urlLink [Pitchfork]   Belle & Sebastian are set to release their next EP which includes tracks: "Wrapped Up In Books", "Your Secrets", and "Your Cover's Blown" which is being touted by NME as "the indie Bohemian Rhapsody" whatever that's supposed to mean.  I do believe this is another one of those landmark events for B&S.  Not only are they out in the real world touring incessantly, giving interviews and releasing singles, this time, they've actually re-used a track from their full-length DEAR CATASTROPHE WAITRESS for an EP.   urlLink [Pitchfork] 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      In the Q review of this band’s debut album, singer Greg Gilbert was compared to both a “post rehab Stevie Nicks” and a “singing dolphin”.  Intrigued, I followed up by getting a copy of this CD.  Gilbert has an effortless and, quite frankly, feminine alto range.  Regarding the Fleetwood Mac references: Christine McVie or perhaps a castrated Lindsey Buckingham at best.  There is no way a post rehab Stevie Nicks could ever reach those notes.   urlLink [Stylus] 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      For me, reading fiction is no casual affair.  It’s a furious enterprise conducted to the exclusion of all else.  These days, it seems I have a bit of an attention deficit, so if I’m not absolutely hooked in a couple of chapters or so, I drop the book like a hot curling iron.  The last book that I can recall finishing is  The Da Vinci Code  by Dan Brown, and that must have been several months ago.  It was an intensely riveting read designed for the attention disabled with cliffhangers after every 2 page chapter.  Therefore, I jumped at the chance to start another Dan Brown novel when a friend at work offered to lend it to me, both of us thinking that there might be a fighting chance that I would finish reading this one as well.    urlLink Angels & Demons   was written, I believe, before  The Da Vinci Code , and not as a afterthough prequel as marketing would have us believe.  As many critics pan on Amazon.com, the two books follow the same formula.  Among other things, it shares a protagonist, the Harvard symbologist Robert Langdon, a feisty foreign female lead who is the daughter of the gruesomely executed murder victim who instigates the investigation of some secret organization plotting to… yeah, you get the picture.  The difference, for me though, between these two books is that reading  Angels & Demons  made me forget how good  The Da Vinci Code  was.  The latter literally pales in comparison.  What’s more, of the two,  Angels & Demons  had the more spectacular climax and, in my opinion, a more fitting ending.  I walked away from that book with that naïve feeling that the balance of justice had been restored and all was right in the world.  Running the risk of spoiling  The Da Vinci Code , I have to say that I was sorely disappointed with its ending.  I felt it should’ve been drawn out a few chapters longer to make the villain’s treachery less glaringly obvious.  Furthermore, to critics of the author’s lack of meaningful character development, this is an action-thriller for God’s sake!  Granted, it’s unconventionally intelligent in its subject matter and depth of historical research, it’s still meant to be a fun, fast-paced read.  Other links of interest:  • I recommend anyone who has read it to visit the official website and read the Dan Brown  urlLink interview of this book .  • Thursday’s the new Saturday, and Dan Brown is the new John Grisham!  The Da Vinci Code is headed for le  urlLink blockbuster movie treatment  (and unlike.. oh I don't know.. #@!!%' TROY maybe? Hollywood can do no wrong in adapting with this type of story).  Russell Crowe and Kate Beckingsale are rumoured to be the leads.  Please, please, please, for all that is holy, NOT Russell Crowe...
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I forgot to mention that I got my hair cut this weekend.  It was time.  I kind of do this seasonally, like sheep shearing or something.  It's at a rather nonfunctional length at the moment.  I'm miffed.  Noticed something about Keane's instrumentation earlier today.  Tim Rice-Oxley plays piano as if he were strumming guitar chords.  This is actually something of a hobby of mine.  Since my guitar playing is rather crap, I'm always trying to adapt some song or another to the piano.  I do it badly though.  Maybe I can learn a few tricks from this band. *shrug*  In preparation for the August 14th CURE concert, I'm putting their discography through rigorous study.  I've never been very interested in 80s music, and now I'll probably have a better idea why that is! *g*
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm terribly behind in posting this week.  I think the silence has partly made up for the incessant prattling of last week's useless blogging.     It was my birthday this past Friday.  Stacey and Jerry kidnapped me from work and forced me to eat too much at the Cheesecake Factory. *g* Fortunately for all parties present, Jerry wasn't able to get our waiter to sing.  I've finally gotten myself a MP3 player!  After months and months of wiffle waffling and serious deliberation, I decided on the 20 gig iRiver iHP-100.  I was hard pressed to even fill it up halfway, but am happy to report that the USB transfer is not as slow as Apple would have you believe.  Currently on my playlist is the UK buzz band of the month: KEANE.  Touted as the second coming of Coldplay, this piano-based trio do indeed share superficial similarities.  Singer Tom Chaplin commands a soaring boy choir vocal, and at a glance, it's much more muscular than Chris Martin's falsetto, but less haunting.  Currently seeking a copy of THE DELAYS, Faded Seaside Glamour.  This quote from the Q review has me completely sold on the band's debut album: "On the opening Wanderlust, [Delays singer] Greg Gilbert sounds like the Cocteau Twins' Liz Fraser in calypso mode, on Bedroom Scene like post rehab Stevie Nicks and Long Time Coming like a singing dolphin."  I went to my brother's end-of-the-year GDYO concert at the Meyerson this afternoon.  Also caught a free performance by a world music group called D'Drum in front of the Asian Art Museum.  Bunch of aging hippies in Birks just rockin' out.  I can see my retirement spent playing the gamelan...  And lastly, adding more youth and zip to my life these days is this new online computer game called FAIRYLAND.  Fairyland is a textbook Tolkienesque role player set in a Grimm fairytale.  Kicker is, it seems that no one my brother's age has ever read the Brothers Grimm.  The little matchstick girl, the red dancing shoes... all foreign concepts to him.  I've just started out in this game, so major NOOB here that sometimes forgets to whisper, but eh.  More on that to come.  I tend to be rather obsessive with these MUDding types of games.. oops, that's right.. no one my brother's age has ever MUDded either. *sigh* Am I dating myself or what?
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's that time again... this irreverent and ever-so whimsical post requires audience participation.  Shift-click this link:  urlLink http://www-personal.umich.edu/~mule/smurfgen.html  to start down the path of enlightenment.  What's your inner smurf?
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I actually did a few interesting things this weekend.  I know, I find it shocking as well.  1.  Actually sat down and had enough attention span to watch an entire DVD on Saturday!  Saw "The Triplets of Belleville", a French-produced animated feature.  It's astonishingly innovative and dripping with sarcasm.  It's barely got any dialogue, just snippets of what I understand is mumbling in French.  Mostly, it's about sounds, how ordinary objects can be music.  Set in a 1920ish jazz culture, there's a comic story as well, but I didn't find it as compelling as the storytelling itself.  The mythical city of Belleville is opened up with a panoramic view of the Statue of Liberty, only the statue is of a Wagnerian soprano hefting a hamburger instead of a torch.  Gee, I wonder who he could be talking about...  2.  Casually watched some of the Dave Matthews and Trey Anastasio going to Africa.  It was a pretty revealing "reality show" type of documentary.  While Dave is engaging and warm in his social interactions with native musicians, he totally freezes when put on stage and is mortified when asked to perform on his own.  Trey, on the other hand, leaves all the socializing responsibilities with Dave and instead stands nonchalant and aloof from his environment.  But when it comes to music, he takes the reins from his petrified partner and bounces around the stage trying to teach the African band an American song.  The dichotomy might just be an artificial construct created by producers as a narrating device, but eh, I can only see so much of the process, so that's my take on it.  3.  Had the opportunity to hear some STONE ROSES this weekend as well.  They're supposedly the vanguard of the "Madchester" scene, which later vomited Oasis and Blur out as well.  The album I'm listening to is one of those that for some reason sound familiar the first time you hear it.  I think I felt the same way about GUSTER, and I don't know if it means that it's so conventional that it sounds normal or that it's so much of an musical influence on later bands that they all borrowed from the original.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      PART I [Updated 5.02.04]  Let’s get one thing straight here.  We’re talking THE WRENS, godfathers of indie pop-punk who took 7 years to release their newest album, the jangly, bittersweet MEADOWLANDS, and not THE WRENS, doo-wop R&B balladeers of the late 1950s who recorded the perennial hits like “I Won’t Come to Your Wedding” and “Come Back My Love”.  Just in case anyone was confused.  :P  So it’s been quite some time since my last full-fledged seriously thought-out album review.  Personally, I think QC started sliding downhill somewhere around the extravagant Celine Dion commentary.  Speaking of which, someone promised to write a vehement rebuttal for that piece, and I haven’t heard anything on that for a really, really long time.  Anyhoo, a quick keyword search through my blog archive reveals that I’ve been listening to this record since at least March, but I’d probably been off-and-on playing it since February.  While all the other critics focus on their initial estrangement from Meadowlands seeing how they were such rabid fans of its predecesor SECAUCUS, I won’t do that here for chiefly since that I’ve never heard Secaucus, I won’t be THAT pretentious (but I can be a little...), and I can’t find it anywhere, 88-cent bargain bins nonwithstanding.  If someone can point me to a quality used CD store in the Dallas area, I’d be there faster than you can say  “Do you.. uh.. Yahoo?” .  In my review, I’d most likely focus on just my initial estrangement.  Perhaps ‘estrangement’ is not the right word to use in this case.  It assumes a kind of long-standing relationship with the band that has suffered a sudden setback due to a new development or realization.  Neither is the case here.  Perhaps the word I’m looking for is ‘distaste’.  You can’t count triplets with it, but it’s infinitely more apt in this context.  After all the promotion Meadowlands got from indie media – namely Magnet and Pitchfork – I was seriously disappointed with the record.  First of all, I have a severe aversion to the jangly, high-pitched guitars.  And next, we have the spitty Sylvester the Cat vocals, no doubt drenching the recording mics.  Drippy.  Slimy.  Eww, yuck.  And after that, what’s with the not posting lyrics in the liner notes?  The Wrens already sing garbled lines which I interpret as “Apartments collide…” in track 6 and “Fum, fum, fum…” in track 9.  I NEED lyrics!  And let’s not even start on track 13 with the 27 seconds of “Baaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaabe…”  But then, I found myself listening to this CD at least once a day in my car.  I usually reserve my hours spent in Tollway traffic as new music time, but when I got tired of the unfamiliar, I’d switch on The Wrens which I always kept on hand.  If I hate this record so much, why am I listening to it everyday?  Riddle me that… 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The usual: gripe about traffic, sleep deprivation, ran out of coffee filters this morning, life is humdrum uneventful and that's the way I like it!  Been listening to Super Furry Animals today.. PHANTOM POWER.  And Gruff Rhys is a paragon of a man, THE most gorgeous guy in indie music.     
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Everyone is trying to kill me on the Tollway, and I'm such a sucker.. paying $80 for that cheap thrill every month.  I thought of a neat post idea this morning, courtesy of looking up vocal ranges for PK: "Baritones and Countertenors in Pop Music".  I'll start that after I finish that blasted Wrens review.  That's what I get for trying to be serious about it.  Don't think I could ever write for a living.. too undisciplined.  Some general observations of the moment: TV on the Radio sounds like an electric toothbrush pressed up against your lip, Godspeed You Black Emperor sounds... Michael Kamen-ish, but indiscriminately noisy like that Beatles hidden track on Sgt. Pepper.  Is that totally sacrilegious?  Am I about to be flamed for it?  Oh well.  And here's an interesting newsbite from Rolling Stone:   LIAM GALLAGHER is planning to team with former STONE ROSES guitarist JOHN SQUIRE and GEORGE HARRISON's son DHANI to record an album later this year.   Who the heck are the Stone Roses?  It seems I've been hearing that name all over the place lately.  Have they broken up already?  What the heck.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Haven't got much to say today.  I'm working on a pretty sizeable review of The Wrens' MEADOWLANDS.  My brother and I rode our bikes to Russell Creek (up north of McDermott near Rice Middle School).  It's nice and spacious up there, and the designated "riparian" habitat zone is promising.  And I've been listening to a bit more of Modest Mouse lately.  Love track 3 - "Float On".  Lately, I've picked up a new hobby.  I've decided to collect !concert posters!  I've found a kickass  urlLink website  that many independent artists post to and sell their limited edition prints.    And lastly, I was wondering why every Jesus and Mary Chain song sounds the same.  That said, I still like DARKLANDS better than the others.  Makes no sense whatsoever.  Here's a funny  urlLink link  to an Australian comedian spoofing Stevie Nicks in a Dolly Parton accent.  Too bad it's so short.  Would've liked to see the whole thing.  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Email I got yesterday from the Sigur Ros mailing list:   kjartan started a joke cover band (featuring orri on drums and his girlfriend marma on violin) a few weeks ago and did alternative country covers of 4 sigur rss songs. the songs can be downloaded  urlLink here    Gee, I wondered what those morphine-addicts were up to after co-orchestrating a ballet soundtrack with Radiohead.  Whereas Thom Yorke won't release his half, Sigur Ros issued the lamentably titled  Ba ba Ti ki Di do.   Actually, these so-called alt country covers don't sound too much different from the non-alt country originals, except for the unmistakable fact that, well, it ain't jonsi singin'...    Well worth checking out, though.  Tell me if I've got it all wrong and ass-backwards. *grin*
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I cribbed the full cabinet speakers from the game room and hooked them up to my cd player via a woefully below average capacity Yamaha receiver.  Right now I'm listening to the train wreck that is Camper van Beethoven's cover of the entire TUSK album.  Sadly, I don't think these giganormous speakers sound even a fraction as good as my belov'd Klipschorns...  I'm planning on getting some kind of A/V switch for the game room TV so my brother can hook up all of his video game consoles and the DVD and the VCR without having to constantly plug and replug.  We have a retarded television unit that has only one set of A/V inputs.  Any suggestions?  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Time for the guilty admission: I bought this book on the heels of the quiet exhilaration (read: relief) that finishing THE NAME OF THE ROSE brought me.  It was happily touted on amazon.com as "The female counterpart to Umberto Eco's  The Name of the Rose ..." Having merited this favorable comparison, how bad could it be?  I was wrong.  I was wrong.  Hail Mary, was I wrong.  Not to say this was a  bad  book, per se.  It was rather readable (unlike FOUCAULT'S PENDULUM that I started and put down, started and put down, started and put into the  Ulysses  stack) and it was enjoyable to a certain extent.  Neville's plot was Dan Brown-esque, really tested the limits of this humble reader's credulity.  The story runs along two parallel tracks, one taking place during the heat and subsequent fallout/critical meltdown of the French Revolution, chronicling the trials and tribulations of a young almost-nun, and the other revolving around "musician, painter, dabbler in mathematics and chess... computer expert", all around superheroine Catherine Velis who works for a corporate auditing firm in the early 70s.  Eventually these two stories come colliding together and not very gracefully either.  You see, as it is gradually revealed after pages and pages of confusion, everyone and their stepsister's mother-in-law is after this mysterious chess set called the Montglane Service.  Apparently, some ancient and heavy curse surrounds the chess service and the Game begins when the abbess of Montglane Abbey (where the chess set had been hidden for thousands of years) decides to exhume the set and disperse the pieces around continental Europe in an attempt to thwart powerhungry forces trying to get their greedy, sticky little paws on this amazing, somehow ultimately powerful, stupid chess set.  A stupid, bloody chess set.  Along the way, Neville hints at more Dan Brown-esque subjects: a) Freemasons, secret order whose members are disguised as scientists and engineers, whose actual goal was to prevent women from ever gaining equality, or God forbid, superiority over the male population.  b) Aliens, but I may (read: most likely) have misinterpreted the author's meaning.  In any case, she never revists that scene and I remain utterly confused.  c) Hashashins (assassins ala  Angels and Demons ) d) Atlantis.  And if Dan Brown hasn't written about it yet, it's because he hasn't gotten to it.  It's cliche enough to be included in his bibliography.  And others, I'm sure, that I've conveniently forgotten.  In this case, the primary reason behind that is not my regrettably transient short term memory, but the fact that unlike Brown who'll use ONE of these concepts as a origin point for the rest of the plot to swing around, Neville mentions these things and never explains or talks about them again.  For example, I would've thought it interesting for the misogynist Freemasons to have played a greater part in the intrigue, especially since the female characters in this story all had stronger personalities than their male counterparts (who were all portrayed as one dimensional rakish cads).  But the Freemasons just come in and out of the storyline as if mere placeholders so the plot could move forward.  Another Brown-esque aspect of this book was the endless exercise in name-dropping the Neville engages in, to an extreme, I might add.  It was not so bad when the abbess traipsed off to Russia to reunite with her long lost childhood friend who also happened to be CATHERINE THE GREAT.  It was not so bad when the young novices from Montglane were sent to live with their godfather in Paris JACQUES-LOUIS DAVID.  And it wasn't even so bad when they met with certain revolutionaries that socially interacted with David: Marat, Robespierre, Danton... But did Mireille really have to sleep with the Bishop of Autun like every other famous Parisian's wife did?  Did she really have to just "bump" into Napoleon on her way to ALGERIA?  Did Tallyrand really need to go the America and on the way "bump" into Benedict Arnold?  And in no particular order, we meet: Euler, Fourier, Voltaire, Cardinal Richelieu's ghost, Rousseau, Wordsworth, Wm. Blake, Boswell (who penned Samuel Johnson's biography), and Napoleon's mom... It's all these inconsequential chance meetings that really drag the narrative down.  The ending, though conclusive, was unsatisfying and so so disappointing.  These are the burning questions I'm left with, though if you've not read this book, you wouldn't really have an answer for me, would you?  1. Why a chess set when it had nothing to do with chess?  2. Whatever happened to Catherine Grand?  If she was the White Queen (the most powerful piece in chess right?), how come she sucked so much?  3. What the hell was that alien thing?  Stupid, bloody chess.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I only recently discovered this band by watching their performance of "Maps" on the MTV Movie Awards.  I found myself oddly captivated by the singer Karen O's awkward and wooden movements.  It's akin to that morbid facination that most people felt when they saw William Hung flail his arms about for the first time.  I also admire the bittersweet Chrissie Hynde quality of Karen O's voice.  I've been playing this album for about a week now in my car.  "Maps" is awesome, an indie love song of sorts, but not exactly reflective of the rest of the album.  I also like "Tick" (track 4) and "Y Control" (track 10).
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The schtick of the newest Magnetic Fields album is that all song titles begin with the most selfish of vowels, the letter I.  And what's more, all the tracks are listed in  alphabetical order!   Okay, whatever.  It's all peripheral inanity.  Not being an extremely detail oriented person myself, I didn't even notice all that crap until I started reading reviews.  Astonishingly, that's all the lightweights harp about.  This album plays like a Broadway songbook.  Stephin Meritt soaring baritone swells and soothes (hey, I too can alliterate!) on tracks like the gorgeous "It's Only Time" that waxes poetic on gay marriage and love at its simplest and most innocent.  The rousing bitterness of "I Thought You Were My Boyfriend" is a delightful "bouncy bitch-slap to a two-timing lover that rides synthesizers and hand claps into disco heaven".  To tell the truth though, this genre of chamber poppiness just isn't my cuppa tea.  It resembles the Rufus Wainwright brand of indulgent melodramatic sentimentality.  It disgusts me.   urlLink [Stylus] 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      After what seemed to be an interminably long (a week and a half) period of self-imposed blog silence, I triumphantly return with news that I have accomplished what the soothsayers and naysayers have deemed well nigh impossible for me:  I finished reading an Umberto Eco novel!   And I cannot how many times I've picked up this book in particular over the course of the last half decade only to guiltily replace it in the ever swelling stack of books that I've bought but never read (of which, illustrious members include: James Joyce's Ullysses, Steven Pinker's The Blank Slate, Arthur Kleinman's Patients and Healers, the modern philosophy textbook from my first year of college, and all the books on the "suggested" reading list for Controlling Processes, Anthro 139).  It was, needless to say, quite a momentous acheivement.  And they were right.  They who crowed about The Name of the Rose from barnyard awnings.  It WAS ultimately an enriching, rewarding experience.  I feel like my brain has expanded two inches in circumferance (which would, I guess, explain this horrible migraine...)
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      OF COURSE I saw this movie the weekend it came out.  It was my favorite Harry Potter book after all.  And the visual textures - the grit and the dust and the worn smooth architecture - I actually found much more stunning than the shiny shiny of the first two movies.  Also, they cut out several chunks of narative, making the first hour hurried and the second hour sail.  All in all, I thought they did a good job with it and I enjoyed it for the most part.  The only problem I have with it, which couldn't be helped, was that if one has read the book, the surprise twist at the end no longer remains so shocking in the movie.  Gary Oldman is excellent, though, in this film, and so is Emma Thompson as Prof. Trelawney.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      What I'm scared of the most: to finish reading a horror novel in the middle of night amidst cacophonous thundering and seeing my reflection through a dark window.  Creepy.  It's like someone's looking in on you, but through a second floor window?   The Bottoms  isn't actually a horror novel.  It's got some gruesome elements and perhaps a slightly supernatural spin, but mostly it's a murder mystery set in East Texas during the Great Depression.  Overarching theme of racial tensions between the "whites" and the "colored".  Interesting read, bit disturbing... not my usual fare.  After some casual googling, I found out that Joe Lansdale is also the one who penned  urlLink BUBBA HO-TEP  which stars Bruce Campbell (love his chin) as an aging Elvis battling a soul-sucking mummy in the bowels of his nursing home.  Want to see that.. sometime.   urlLink [Amazon] 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Reading this novel was a rather draining experience. I hate it when you get emotionally attached to fictional characters. You can't just put the book down and leave it behind.  There are so many things I like about this book, so I’ll just start at the beginning.  This book is about the sweet and dysfunctional relationship between these two characters Henry and Clare.  Henry suffers from Chrono Displacement Disorder that causes him to time travel whenever he's stressed and Clare's known him for all her life when he meets her for the first time.  The rules are these: Henry time travels randomly to important events in his life, times when he felt safe and happy, and he is unable to alter the outcome no matter what he tries.  Free will only occurs in the forward time.  He's also not allowed to bring anything with him on his involuntary time jumps.  Consequently, he's unable to keep tooth fillings in his mouth and his colleagues often find him running around naked as a jaybird in his office.    The storytelling device of Henry's time traveling allows the author to unveil the plot in a Mobius strip fashion.  Events that happen in beginning chapters of the book that are seemingly trivial make greater impact when they happen again, so to speak, later in the book when you see from the opposing perspective.  The narration alternates between Henry and Clare, so you are often presented with two versions of the same event.  For example, Clare meets Henry for the first time when she is six years old and he appears scandalously naked and disappears when she shakes his hand.  She thinks he's an angel for a good portion of her childhood and incessantly asks him questions about God.  Henry, on the other hand, is in his late thirties, early forties and having been married to Clare for almost twenty years, is baffled at how to behave in front of his wife as a precocious child.  In a side story that I found incredibly amusing, Henry's doctor concludes that this disorder is genetic and creates chimeric mice with the time traveling condition.  Easily stressed, the mice would time jump a few minutes before or after present time into the Animal Labs in the basement where they were born.  There is also a bittersweet Odyssean theme in this story of Clare waiting for the wayward Henry to return from time jumping, always the one left behind on his - albeit involuntary - adventures.  But in this case, Odysseus never really makes it back to Penelope and the one unrepentant suitor for her attentions (Clare's best friend's husband) goes unpunished.   urlLink [Amazon]  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's official... I've read 'em all.  And somewhat backwards in publication order.  What a muddy downhill slide it's been.  I was noticeably UN-thrilled after finishing this book.  Plot in a nutshell: brilliant and beautiful scientist (fill-in-name-of-girl) meets athletic and popular liberal arts professor (fill-in-name-of-boy) and who aid/hinder government agency that's working in secrecy on solving/eliminating a problem/academic exercise that has far-reaching consequences to the entire global community.  There.  Fill in a few details, slap Dan Brown's name on that, and I've written another bestselling thriller.  Not only was I mildly offended by the cliche-ridden predictability of  Digital Fortress  (which apparently is the formulaic predecessor of  Deception Point ), I was offended by the final numeric code written on the page following the epilogue.  It's unbreakable.  Really, I tried.  As I later found out, you have to have the hardback edition of the novel in order to solve the puzzle.  This book was passable.  Read only if extreme boredom negates dire risk of cliche overdose.   urlLink [Amazon] 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Sorry for the blog silence lately.&nbsp; I haven't been feeling very literary... and I think it has everything to do with the latest bomb of a novel that I read.&nbsp; Briefly, this book (by the same author as The Flanders Panel) is about murder and intrigue in the dangerous and exciting world of... book collecting.&nbsp; Yep, that's right folks.&nbsp; Books can kill ya.&nbsp; I know this one almost did me in.&nbsp; The protagonist of this story is a mercenary book hunter named Lucas Corso hired to hunt down the last two copies of a rare satanic manuscript that reputedly illustrated how one would be able to communicate with the Devil.&nbsp; And along the way, characters that resemble the cast of The Three Musketeers start popping out of the woodwork.&nbsp; Confused?&nbsp; You, me, and Lucas Corso.&nbsp; Perez-Reverte tries so hard to cram these two narratives together and it was a messy and artificial fit at best.&nbsp; And in the end - I hope you don't mind me spoiling the ending because I'm not recommending reading this - the author goes: Surprise! Did you know the two stories had nothing to do with each other?   Really.&nbsp; Well, you can just bite my ass.   To go along with this poorly constructed narrative is a poorly constructed narrator device.&nbsp; Perez-Reverte ineptly employs a 1st person perspective from a character who is so peripheral to the central story that he nearly falls off the page.&nbsp; How can he tell the story of events that he wasn't present for?&nbsp; Furthermore, this character turns out to be a "villain" of sorts, adding to the awkwardness of an already awkward plot.&nbsp; In summary, I'm so disgusted with this book, I can't express it fully in words.   Next post: nutshell reviews of... New Porn., Sufjan, Devendra, Decemberists, Sleepy J, &amp; Espers   
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Between science and magic, between order and chaos... there is an ancient balance.     And now that balance is unraveling.  You play young April Ryan, frustrated art student by day, reluctant savior of the worlds by night.  Follow April on her "longest journey" to discover the shocking secret of her parentage, the shocking secret of the homeless man who camps out on the bench outside her bohemian slums, the shocking secret of her wardrobe, her agoraphobic landlady, the mechanical contraption next to her apartment, the radioactive looking sewer water, that insistent sparking on the rails...  Whew.  Now that the expositional book jacket cliches are out of the way, I can move on the game itself.  The strongest thing that The Longest Journey (TLJ) really has going for it is its morbid sense of humor.  Sometimes I think you'd have to share that twisted humor in order to solve some of the puzzles.  Constable Guybrush anyone?  April's verbally abusive, drumming toy monkey:   Hey! Hey you! YEAH you!! Put your hands in the air! Spread your legs! ...and do the MON-KAY!!!   Another commendable aspect of TLJ is the fact that the puzzles don't detract from the narrative flow.  It makes the action go so much faster.  Then again, the fact that sometimes you have to make some choices in order to further the storyline and not because you want to bites.  You just accept it and "fulfill your destiny" so to speak.  I keep waiting for the chance to purposely commit a gargantuan error of monumental proportions and die a horrible, tragic (but morbidly funny) death BUT I CANT!  You can't mess up in this game!  That bugs me.  Having said that, I've really enjoyed the game so far.  I feel like I'm actually been absorbed into the narrative.  The supporting character roles are vivid personalities.  April's friends, especially, quite likeable and sympathetic.  Sadly, the epilogue of TLJ doesn't resolve much.  I smell a sequel...   urlLink    www.longestjourney.com
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      After reading the time/space-sprawling soap opera epic that was THE EIGHT, I decided to move on with Perez-Reverte, advertised as intellectual beach reading by the sticker on the cover.  It's totally cliche, I know, to judge a book yadda yadda... but in my defense, it wasn't the cover, but the huge honking sticker that Borders so painstakingly put on each one.  THE FLANDERS PANEL refers to a Van Huys painting (which I have not been able to find online, so I don't know if it's a real painting) called "The Game of Chess" in which the Duke of Flanders and his childhood friend, the knightly Roger of Arras, are engaged in a fiercely absorbing game of... you guessed it... chess, while Beatrice of Burgundy, the Duchess of Flanders, sits reading in the shadows behind the game.  Mighty tiresome of me to choose another book warped around the theme of chess, but at least this time, chess is actually played.  The protagonist of this story, a young art restorer named Julia, uncovers an inscription apparently made by the artist and then subsequently covered up that said "Quis Necavit Equitem" or "Who killed the knight?"  She does a little research into the history of the characters portrayed in the painting, and finds out that the knight - Sir Roger - was indeed assassinated... and all fingers pointed at the Duke, his childhood companion, for likely personal reasons: allegations that his wife Beatrice and Roger were having an affair.   And then real people start dying around her.  People she knows.  And Julia has to race against time to figure out the connection between these new killings and the 500 year old murder of Roger de Arras.   How's that for cliche blurb writing for a suspense novel?  I think I've found a new calling.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Pitchfork's Fiery Furnaces interview  urlLink http://www.pitchforkmedia.com/interviews/f/fiery-furnaces-04/  The Friedberger siblings talk about recording Blueberry Boat.  How they still get compared to the White Stripes and how inept that comparison is.  How Matt wrote most of the lyrics and obsesses about proper nouns.    Snipets-  Matt:...No, I mean, we did want to mention we were brother and sister.  Eleanor: How could we not? Otherwise people would think we were a couple.  Matt: Yeah, that's disgusting.  and  Pitchfork: I've also seen clips where they say you "claim" to be brother and sister.  Matt: Yeah, well, what an achievement that would be. Like, we tricked you by lying. Anyway, we're not The Ramones. The other people in the band, we don't pretend they're [siblings].  Eleanor: We could. We should start saying that, maybe.  Pitchfork: That you just took the name to be in the band together?  Matt: Yeah, "Friedberger." [Laughter]  Eleanor: That would be anyone's first choice.  ---  Pitchfork's Sufjan Stevens interview  urlLink http://www.pitchforkmedia.com/interviews/s/stevens_sufjan-04/  He can use big religious words like "ecumenically" and likes gothic country-folk...
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Has anyone seen the Priceline.com commercial where William Shatner is strutting through some hotel resort and commenting on how since he's the spokesman, he gets to stay in the hotels for free?  He gets to his room and the door won't open so he's shoving that access card like mad until it opens from the other side... AND IT'S LEONARD NIMOY who remarks, "Oh it's you Bill.  I thought you were room service," and closes the door in Shatner's face.  I feel like such the Trekkie at this moment.  And boy does it feel good.  Good times, good times.  *grin*
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      An INSIDE/OUTSIDE poem By Bryan Han  To them I seem quiet, timid To me I seem cheerful, enthusiastic They see a sloth, a willow-wisp tree But I see an active individual, a hyper wildchild They think of me as an anti-social person I think of myself as cautious in new surroundings I am a studious hard worker, to them I am a procrastinator and easily distracted individual, to me They think I regard other people with an air of aloofness But I'm just shy They think of me as a serious young adult I see myself as a playful, mischievous child Emotionless, pessimistic Light-hearted, carefree They see me as a lifeless stone But I am an island, teeming with life
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      JUNE was: discovering the joy of Insound, the cloying sweetness of the neo-folkies, and... Dan Bejar rocks.  NEW PORNOGRAPHERS, Electric Version (2003): I read a interview once where Carl Newman and crew were lamenting the fact that when they first formed the New Pornos, they had difficulty getting labels interested. I find that difficult to believe. In my book, the New Pornos can do no wrong. Dan Bejar's contributions are among my favorite tracks from this album. In particular "Chump Change" and "Testament to Youth in Verse" ...both have mindnumbingly great chorus.  That sparse canon that follows  and the bells ring... ?  SUBLIME.  And I also like any song that Neko Case has more than just harmony vocals.  I think she's fantastic.  SLEEPY JACKSON, Lovers (2003): I like this record.  A lot.  And not even because it's critically acclaimed.  Because it's not.  *grin*  Luke Steele (who is basically the sole survivor of each Sleepy Jackson incarnation) has schizoid musical tastes and this album with its incessant genre hopping shows it.  Which is not to say that's a bad thing.  The Strokes, for example, with that great Strokes sound, will always sound like themselves even on their inevitable White Christmas album featuring duets with Elton John and R. Kelly (just kidding! wouldn't that just be the penultimate sign of the Apocalypse?).  I can't categorize the Sleepy Jackson sound.  It's not innovative by any long stretch of the word, but it's not cookie cutter formulaic.  THE DECEMBERISTS, Her Majesty... (2003): Pirate Rock in the literal sense.  The Decemberists adopt an almost cartoonish approach to songwriting that Pitchfork calls "an aesthetic that's half Dickens, half 1950s adventure comic book".  Singer Colin Meloy plays up the melodrama and escapism remnicent of old Robert Louis Stevenson novels.  With its clever lyrics and unconventional approach, "Her Majesty..." is worth the effort to check out.  .:THE NEO-FOLKIES:. I'm so sick of these discs, I don't really want to discuss them.  I'm sure each has its undiscovered potential, but I don't have the patience to unravel them at the moment.   DEVENDRA BANHART, Rejoicing in the Hands (2004): Quavering old woman voice with billy goat finesse.  Actually, pretty good record... old-fashioned sounding.  ESPERS, Espers (2003): Cloying sweetness really comes together in this album.  High pitched, reed-thin female voices, dulcimers and autoharps.  Clear the way, I need to hurl!  SUFJAN STEVENS, Michigan (2003): Slow-paced, banjo-tinged balladry about Michigan slums.  Not quite bad, really.  Got into Sufjan when I downloaded a track from his "Seven Swans" CD and to my astonishment, heard a slightly out-of-tune and out-of-breath voice that sounded suspiciously... well... like me! 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Hornets vs. Honeybees  I think this clip from a nature documentary is cool, but for some reason, I feel the need to add a disclaimer because it's callow and immature to revel in mass destruction... but I still think it's cool!  When I first surfed onto this link, I had no idea they were real insects.  I thought it was some clever computer mock-up.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>