<Blog>


<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      HTG youth, welcome to  Blog-land   Now I can bring people up to date whenever I want & don't have to worry about forgetting to say something on a Sunday   See ya later 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      WOO script has arrived!!  FanTAStic  Stay tuned  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      IMPORTANT NOTICE!!  When you visit this blogger, click the refresh button after it's loaded. your browser will probably do what most do and bring up what was there on the last visit, & clicking refresh will update it for you  Cher-chiz
     
    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ooh yes, keep an eye on my  urlLink site  to see my life's work in action  If anyone wants to email me about anything on this blogger instead of ringing or texting, feel free:  mg1105@hotmail.com
     
    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      G'day, peeps  been trying to think of anything to put on here that I've not told you already  i've not managed to  So here's some stuff you know already!  The show for this year is Wizard Of Oz, pending getting the license. We can cast it no problems (touch wood), so we just need the final o-k-ya from the license holders... Heh heh... We rock... Show week is October 10th - 17th  Er  Residential weekend has now been booked, which was done last night after theatre group when nearly everyone said they'd want to go  Fantastic  So, to confirm, the dates for that are Friday April 30th, May 1st, May 2nd.  Should be a good one this year, as we're so plentiful in numbers, and we're just great  Lynn's cats haven't said if they want to go yet... ;)  So  anyway, see you next week, i'll post any more news as and when I gets it  cheers  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The script for the "other" version of Wizard of Oz has arrived, & so we can now look @ casting & stuff...  NB: DON'T ASK US ABOUT CASTING ALL THE SAME THO!!!  I'm being devious and putting in a code-word so I know who's been to visit... You can give me the code word when you next see me, or you can text me if you want, or email, or whatever... Up to you...  Code word is  "Sminkey Pinkey"  Heh heh  Keep it to yourself, remember!!  See you Sunday, maybe, depends when Lynn & I get back from our recording studio weekend... Heh heh... I like saying that... Er... anyway, if you can't be there sunday, still let me know, even though I'm not running the session. Jodi and Al will still take pounds & the register  See you later  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well...this is what a new fangled computer does then... Interesting...! Having a good half term I hope. I am. Off to do recording on Friday so you'd better say well done the next time you see me - although not at school, eh Ern! Bored you enough now... Paul... how do I get rid of this?................Oh....that's how....
     
    
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Can't remember if Lynn said about her having secured a rehearsal pianist for WOO...  Heh heh - still no news on casting ;-)  This is the type of thing I do when I'm bored at work, write messages to people...   Whilst  you  lot are on holiday!! Makes ya sick... Ah well  See you... Going now!!
     
    
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      For ease of looking things up, I've added a title setting
     
    
</post>

<date>28,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      An award goes to Eleanor for putting the largest number of comments ever in one go   Heh heh  Great to know people are going finally  And all credit for calling me P Nut goes to Lynn... Bless her  And as for Cromwell's fears about leotards, rest assured we'll try and not put you in a leotard, we want you to be all cuddly and stuff so we're aiming baggy and stuff  Er... Yes...  Keep up with the code words, I've taken note of who's been  Heh heh  See you tomorrow night
     
    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Mmm... Intriguing, Mr Bond...   Re-programming the comments link seems to have retrieved the comments made earlier by those wastrels Ern and Cromwell  Does this mean I can only have one comments thing on my blog? I might have to edit the more pointless comments... Such as "No no no no" or whatever was filling it up earlier, Ernie baby  Right... going to do some work now  traa  
     
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I put up a  urlLink Blog  with a link in for people to post comments... Where's that gone then?!  Ah well, here it is again.  If you want to put any comments, messages or anything to me or anyone in HTG, please click on the link below. I'll try and put a new one in every so often so each one doesn't get too full... Cromwell and Ern did fill the missing one up quite a bit... Pesky kids - grrrr   LinktoComments('MANUAL')    urlLink Comment  
     
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      *sings* Happy birthday to me Happy birthday to me Happy birthday dear meeeee Happy birthday to me  Waiting for my birthday tea right now  Hungry!!
     
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      And we welcome to Blogland Katie, who is the second person to notify me of their visit to my world 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Incidentally... Unfortunately, scripts for Wizard D'Oz are only available to hire, not to buy, so we're not able to give you scripts to keep this year...  Scripts are not here yet, so we'll keep you posted on them!!  Congratulations to Shell who was the first person to give me the code word  "Sminky Pinky"  So come on the rest of you, get your acts together  ;-)
     
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I've announced the cast list, but here it is in black and white... or whatever colours... Make a note of any queries, cause we'll have chats about it Sunday night, we'll run through the plan of action & you can ask us anything then!  DOROTHY - Katie SCARECROW - Ian LION - Michelle TINMAN - Tom WICKED WITCH - Tania WIZARD - Jack (also playing Joe) GOOD WITCH (Glinda) - Georgi AUNT EM - Emily Knight UNCLE HENRY - Stuart E 1ST WITCH - Kat 2ND WITCH - Jade TIBIA - Jeni GLORIA - Claire P LADY GROWLIE - Eleanor MUNCHKIN MAYOR - James B MUNCHKIN FARMER - Hana OZ LADY - Harriet 1ST GENERAL - Beth PRIVATE - Lou OZMAS / SERVANT - Alice "LITTLE WITCH" - Sophie A MUNCHKIN (Referred to in script) - Emma Knight MUNCHKINS / GENERALS / OZ FOLK - Jacqueline; Frances; Charlotte; Hannah; Emily W; Stephanie; Rebecca; Sally; Alexandra; Jacob  There are many single-line parts, the munchkin Barrister, Munchkin Coroner and loads of other parts to dish out, which can only be done as and when we rehearse. Remember that most people will be doing lots of parts, Munchkins, Generals, Emerald City folk. As with Beauty And The Beast last year, those who do not have principal roles will in all probability have more to do than the principals, and I can't stress this enough: THERE ARE NO RUBBISH PARTS in this show, and every single person has to be good, confident, know what they're doing and be with us 100%. WOO is going to be a fantastic show, & it's got last year's show to live up to!!  It's worth saying now, even though it'll be said Sunday, that when we start working on a show, we go through the script and everyone learns what their moves are, where to stand and so on. It can be really dull to sit and watch but it's really important to do that so everyone knows what to do. Remember, the quicker we do it, the quicker things can pick-up and the more we can get done in rehearsals and therefore, you'll have more to do!! If anyone drops out of any of the parts, you may be asked to step in!! So it's really important to watch what's going on & to learn it.   LET'S MAKE A SHOW!!  Sorry, that was corny!!  Anyway, see you Sunday!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
       LinktoComments('MANUAL')    urlLink Comment    really must try and clear it out again but... Thanks to Beth (grrr) it's so massive it'll take forever to do so cause I have to delete them one by one  again I say "grrr"  traa
     
    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I can't view the blog!!!  I hope you're all leaving many messages & that this gets through  I hate being out of touch with the universe  Makes me nervous  KEEP BLOGGING!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I am so computer illiterate!  I have tried to get a message onto the comments things but it didn't seem to go. (Btw - have done an exam in computer stuff recently. I passed - no idea how!)  Anyway, if my comment went on then you'll read this twice but if not...  Thanks for all the congrats. Really don't know why we told you but I suppose its cos we are really excited and it's not going to be for ages. Oh and no, you can't all be bridesmaids etc!  Anyway, in the middle of planning work for tomorrow's lessons. Must get back to it.  Lynn  P.S. If you notice spelling mistakes please don't tell me - I know I'm an english teacher but it doesn't mean I can spell!
     
    
</post>

<date>29,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Now listen, you lot  In view of the MASSIVE amount of comments put in the comments page bit, I'm wondering how you'd feel about me inviting EVERYONE to join the htg youth blogger. Whereas at the moment you click on the link from the blogger and put comments in, you'd put them directly into the blogger like the ones I put in & it'd be simpler to manage for me, it'd be a better system I think  post your thoughts  All we'd have to do if have email addresses off people & I'd send them an invitation  speak up, gimme ya views
     
    
</post>

<date>29,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      For those that weren't @ theatre group last night, or those that had gone by the time we told people,  Lynn and I are now ENGAGED!!  Woo-hoo!!  Heh heh  In other news, many thanks to Cromwell and Ern for their work last night  L and I have had too many weeks off now, we'd better do some work ourselves next week!! :p  We've been working outside drama, by the way, so you don't think we're lazy!! I know you lot, and your conclusions!! ;)  Anyway, plenty of hard work next week, well done to everyone for last night & take care, bye, see you, take care, bye, cheers, thanks, bye, take care, thanks, bye  
     
    
</post>

<date>29,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Here you go, just so as you don't have to keep scrolling down the page  ;-)   LinktoComments('MANUAL')    urlLink Comment  
     
    
</post>

<date>29,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'm going to try and clear the comments thingy out so it doesn't get too big, so I'll put them in here for all to see... The comments might all still be there tho cause last time I tried to delete some it didn't work!!  I presume any links to websites won't work but I'll see if I can revive them!!  Damn I'm good    shell @ 3:09PM | 2004-02-26| permalink  Yeah so ummm whats going on?? Come on peeps support the theater group and get your arses on this site!  email | website      Iain Allsop @ 3:13PM | 2004-02-26| permalink  U Spelt my name wrong :p ...oh well, Well Well Well... 'ope people will be coming to see me play Gavin in "Caught in the net" better hurry up with the buying of tickets... Expecially since they are selling like hot cakes... So Chop Chop!!!!  email | website      shell @ 3:17PM | 2004-02-26| permalink  Yeah yeah yeah..ok Iain we get the pic...im sure that we will all come...to laugh at you only of course! lol you love me reali! ;)  email | website      E @ 3:19PM | 2004-02-26| permalink  Well well well... last time they didnt :p  email | website      shell @ 3:20PM | 2004-02-26| permalink  yeah thats what you think! hehehe  email | website      E @ 3:20PM | 2004-02-26| permalink  no no no no no....  email | website     P-nut @ 3:49PM | 2004-02-26| permalink  You pesky kids  email | website      shell @ 2:01PM | 2004-02-27| permalink  Who you callin pesky?!  email | website      shell @ 2:03PM | 2004-02-27| permalink  HAPPY BIRTHDAY LYN! *MWOAH*  email | website      Passey @ 2:04PM | 2004-02-27| permalink  Woooooo...  email | website      shell @ 2:06PM | 2004-02-27| permalink  Go kt, go kt!  email | website      Passey @ 2:09PM | 2004-02-27| permalink  Go me! Id just like to take this moment to say that i wish everyone the bestest of luck and do i have to wear the blue frock? :oD  'oh lynny you came and you gave me a turkey on my vacation from worky' (note to all i am referring to the bird and not the country.)  email | website      shell @ 2:13PM | 2004-02-27| permalink  well...you may have to wear a blue frock but all im saying is PLEASE DONT MAKE ME WEAR A LEAOTARD (or however it's spelt.. i may be doing english but that doesn't automatically mean my spelling is good....no offence lynn...beautiful lesson today! :D )  email | website      haz @ 5:54PM | 2004-02-27| permalink  Hello!! Sorry i was being blonde!! (not that there is anything worng with blondes) I pressed comment>> without actualli writting anything!! Well i don't know whether it went in owell!! HAPPY BDAY Lyn (when was ur b.day??!!!) sorri owell gtg bye  email | website      Eleanor @ 7:02PM | 2004-02-27| permalink  hiya peeps! happy birthday lynn 4 yesterday. i am so pleased i can go 2 residential! c yall sunday loadsa luv eleanor x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x  email | website      Eleanor @ 7:08PM | 2004-02-27| permalink  soz peeps i am dead excited i dunno y - mayb coz its the WEEKEND finally!!!!! every1 gonna watch FRIENDS tonight? hehehe o well! i am gonna be on t'internet for ages so peeps - tlk 2 me!!  email | website      E @ 7:34PM | 2004-02-27| permalink  Yo Yo Yo Yo ppl... Its jus gunna b the best day ever nxt friday!! i mean, its GOD's b'day... no wait a min, thts jus my b'day Lol Still.. Its gods :D yes yes peeps, i am god!, o well, i feel all famous cuz i was mentiond on the msg bord ... WOW! Lol so happy, its made my day, since it was so rubbish! .. Boo hoo i just wanted to see how long i cuz blabber on for ... cause i just felt like it... RANDOM.... or shud i say Sausage... Sometimes i think im losing the plot, but people reassure me that i alreadi lost it .. so its all gd! workey turkey... Odd.. Lol well i think im gunna go now, my brother onli back 4 a couple of days .. been here for 2 weeks.. onli argued once, im pretty proud of tht! Wew... so i gotta giv him the comp.. dnt want many aruguemtns... Long convo!.. Sooooo TOoooodles!  email | website      Eleanor @ 10:31PM | 2004-02-27| permalink  is ther no1 on at all? i am gettin bored - just watched friends (2 times over) but now bored! nobody is online! i guess most peeps hav betta things 2 do on a friday nite tho - cheeky devils. shame really. o well i hav been blabbin 4 ages so i will jus go now. cyall sunday luv eleanor x x  email | website      Eeeeeeee @ 12:38PM | 2004-02-28| permalink  Yo Yo Yo... "P-nut" >.  Well dun ppl on ur parts in (i keep 4gettin the name of this play) THE WIZARD OF OZ!.. i got it.. Wew u proud of me?.. well yes.. well dun on all ur parts and im sure that this years play is going to b a "Smash it".. or jus basically better than last year! "Big" up Hagley.. Lol  email | website      El @ 12:41PM | 2004-02-28| permalink  i gotta agree that is a rare name P!!! congrats every1 i think this'll b a good show. Pnut, wen u gonna update this again!   email | website      Eeeeeeee @ 12:43PM | 2004-02-28| permalink  Lol Yo El... check out this website.. :D  email |  urlLink website       El @ 12:52PM | 2004-02-28| permalink  tht is a strange site but i like it! strange sense of humour i have, eh? cyall 2moz loads luv eleanor x x x x x    email | website      P Nut @ 4:15PM | 2004-02-28| permalink  Sorry, Eleanor, we were out celebrating Lynn's birthday so we didn't see you comments till today   Ah well   WHO'S HAZ?  email | website      Eleanor @ 6:57PM | 2004-02-28| permalink  thanx paul! wow i am famous! heehee! i think p-nut is quite cute actually! well dun lynn! i am dead excitd again and i dnt know y! o well i will b bak on later 2 see if any1 else is online. where is every1 this weekend? t'internet is deserted! cyall 2moz loadsa luv eleanor x x x   email | website      Eleanor @ 7:00PM | 2004-02-28| permalink  i just realised y i am so xcited, i hav been childmindin for 5 HOURS an i am absolutely shattered but i did make a bit of money and hey, it was fun too! CASUALTY (one of my all-time faves - sad i know, but neway) is on 2nite and then i cn watch movies all nite - and then 2moz i am goin 2 the cinema and doing hwk and then HTG!!!!! cant wait cyall 2moz luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Eleanor @ 7:09PM | 2004-02-28| permalink  i 4got 2 tell u all y there r so many msges from me - coz i am VERY CHATTY wen i want 2 b. ages ago u wuldnt b able 2 shut me up but i hav changed. but on the internet it is different so get used 2 it peeps! anyway i jus wondered wot peeps thought of the eurovision thingy on telly tonite. any1 gonna watch it> i dnt no if i will. o well enuf blabbin 4 now cya luv eleanor   email | website      Eeeeee @ 7:27PM | 2004-02-28| permalink  Lol...  email | website      El @ 8:33PM | 2004-02-28| permalink  i just realised that one of my comments was a bit odd - wen i said 'p-nut is quite cute actually' i was talkin about the name (no offence meant to paul or lynn!) r peeps actually gonna get on the computer 2day or wot? i am the only person on! get a move on peeps. cyall 2moz luv elx x x  email | website      P Nut & Lynn @ 8:43PM | 2004-02-28| permalink  No offense taken re "cute" reference, we took it how it was meant, it;s ok   We've voted for James... Mainly cause of his surname ;)   We have to big this comments page thing up to everyone tomorrow night - could get really massive   Anyway, off to meet one of my old school chums now, leaving L to do school work :(   See you 2moz  email | website      Izzy Quarry @ 8:45PM | 2004-02-28| permalink  Such a fantastic name!!  email | website      Mr. Munch !!! TYPICAL !!! @ 9:23PM | 2004-02-28| permalink  hey crew !!! I cant come 2moz as im in an St john Ambulance county First aid competition!!! Wish me luk  email | website     Eleanor @ 10:03PM | 2004-02-28| permalink  omg * sum1 pick me up off the floor - there IS life in hagley!* good luck brogan 2moz. i didnt vote 4 ne1 i am watchin tho! cyall 2moz luv eleanor x x   email | website      Eleanor @ 10:24PM | 2004-02-28| permalink  james won! i hav 4gotten already wot his song is - o hang on a minute here it comes again. u voted well lynn & p-nut! cyall 2moz luv eleanor x x    email | website     Eeeeeeeeeeeeee @ 10:23AM | 2004-02-29| permalink  Hey ppl, r u all ready for the dance... Muhhahaha, i kno it! well thts cuz i've made sum of it... well, off 2 shell's at one, to sort out the dance, so we actually kno it and can teach it 2 u grubby lot! then going str8 2 drama, we'll b ready 4 u all... Muhahaha   email | website      Eleanor @ 10:25AM | 2004-02-29| permalink  wot dance? this shud b v. fun! hope peeps hav had a gr8 weekend! cyall lata luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Eeeeeeeeeeeeee @ 10:27AM | 2004-02-29| permalink  :o the dance shell was asked to do... Muhahaha, then she asked me 2 help :p so we teachin u all the dance.. Muhahaha  email | website      Eeeeeeeeeeeeee @ 10:29AM | 2004-02-29| permalink  seems like me and El r the onli supports of this comments page.. Wew... Rock on, but El alot more.. (she repeats msgs) Lol  email | website      Eleanor @ 10:31AM | 2004-02-29| permalink  we will hav a lot of fun 2nite eh! cyall luv el x  email | website      Eeeeeeeeeeeeee @ 10:31AM | 2004-02-29| permalink  Hang on Hang on, Wooaa Woooaaa the times rong... i cnt work in these conditions! Lol  email | website      Eeeeeeeeeeeeee @ 10:32AM | 2004-02-29| permalink  Erm, i have a very gd site 4 quizzes if ne1 wants 2 do ne, but b warned... They shud hav an 18 on the front!  email | website      
     
    
</post>

<date>13,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      MY COMMENTS NEVER GO ON!   I was just telling you all that I have decided that there will be no harmonies in Somewhere over the rainbow... only in a slightly more humourous way.. and it's all ruind by the fact that my comment didn't go on!!!!!!!!  AND, yes I do have a CD and I'll let Paul bring it on Sunday for you to hear if you want to... Don't expect everyone to listen to it, I really don't mind, honest!   Going now.. too upset about comment not going on... so I'm going to cry (again - possibly the 7th time today)... beofre I go to sleep COS  I HATE THESE NEW FANGLED COMPUTER THINGS THAT NEVER WORK FOR ME EVER EVER EVER EVER EVER.  (glad I got that off my chest!)  Bye LYNNIEFOXYCHICKENBURGER  p.s. We have our engagement rings now! Woo! v v v v v v v v v v nice! Won't be there Sunday so see y'all at school on monday.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Btw, I've changed the archiving because we've got many huge blogs what with the many comments we've got, so if you wonder where old blogs have gone, try the archive list opposite... Whereas it used to archive monthly, it's now going to do it weekly  Cher-chiz
     
    
</post>

<date>07,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'm off work sick today, so I'm going to make myself busy by spending the  entire  day clearing out the comments... Pesky kids  ;-)  Heh heh - Lynn's cats are looking very cross @ the foreign cat invading their garden... It's the one Izzy fancies so I don't know what her problem is  Heh heh  Anyway, here are the comments... It'll take a while...     Eeeeeeeeeeeeee @ 10:23AM | 2004-02-29| permalink  Hey ppl, r u all ready for the dance... Muhhahaha, i kno it! well thts cuz i've made sum of it... well, off 2 shell's at one, to sort out the dance, so we actually kno it and can teach it 2 u grubby lot! then going str8 2 drama, we'll b ready 4 u all... Muhahaha   email | website      Eleanor @ 10:25AM | 2004-02-29| permalink  wot dance? this shud b v. fun! hope peeps hav had a gr8 weekend! cyall lata luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Eeeeeeeeeeeeee @ 10:27AM | 2004-02-29| permalink  :o the dance shell was asked to do... Muhahaha, then she asked me 2 help :p so we teachin u all the dance.. Muhahaha  email | website      Eeeeeeeeeeeeee @ 10:29AM | 2004-02-29| permalink  seems like me and El r the onli supports of this comments page.. Wew... Rock on, but El alot more.. (she repeats msgs) Lol  email | website      Eleanor @ 10:31AM | 2004-02-29| permalink  we will hav a lot of fun 2nite eh! cyall luv el x  email | website      Eeeeeeeeeeeeee @ 10:31AM | 2004-02-29| permalink  Hang on Hang on, Wooaa Woooaaa the times rong... i cnt work in these conditions! Lol  email | website      Eeeeeeeeeeeeee @ 10:32AM | 2004-02-29| permalink  Erm, i have a very gd site 4 quizzes if ne1 wants 2 do ne, but b warned... They shud hav an 18 on the front!  email | website      P Nut @ 11:18AM | 2004-02-29| permalink  L's marking essays at the mo, so I'm twiddling my thumbs... And blogging... And just editted this comments page as you'll see... The blooming thing only lets you delete one at a time, the delete all button doesn't work proper  Ah well... better go and pester L to hurry up  ;-)  email | website      P Nut @ 12:54PM | 2004-02-29| permalink  Just seen L's parents off on holiday... We're cheering ourselves up by typing out the lyrics for WOO   ... the crazy times we have :p    email | website      Lynn @ 12:56PM | 2004-02-29| permalink  we? we? we typing the lyrics out?   Just so you all know I, yes I, not we, I have been typing the lryics out!!!   Not really bothered... just wanting to make P sweat a bit!   By the way hello to y'all on the comment bit. This is quite a lot of fun isn't it!  email | website      Eleanor @ 1:32PM | 2004-02-29| permalink  hehehe! hi lynn & paul! good to know there is life on this planet after all! :D it is very fun isn't it (even tho waitin 4 a reply isnt) i am glad sum1 else enjoys it too! lynn have fun typing lyrics i am sure Pnut will do sum 4 u (HINT HINT PAUL!) cyall later luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Eleanor @ 1:34PM | 2004-02-29| permalink  oh by the way P the timing is wrong on here! i am sure u guessed that tho. a lil birdie told me that michelle n ern r teachin us a dance 2nite - this shud b gd! cyall lata luv el x  email | website      P Nut @ 5:12PM | 2004-02-29| permalink  Can't seem to change the times although I've not searched very thoroughly through the site   Will keep trying tho  email | website      haz @ 5:12PM | 2004-02-29| permalink  Hello!! "haz" is harriet c!!! soz it is short it is easier to write. I am confused about alll these messages who is Eeeeeeeeee and wot is the code word about??? Do we have to remember this?? I am very confused - well it doesn't take me alot to confuse me!! I don't no wot to write!! gd website by the way!! Very confusing!! I no a code word wot about>>>>very confusing  email | website      haz @ 5:17PM | 2004-02-29| permalink  O mi god!!!! I have neva known u to talk so much eleanor!!! my word I am flabagasted >>>>>>>>>. probably not in the right context  email | website      haz @ 5:18PM | 2004-02-29| permalink  The times of wot???? I am very confused  email | website      Eleanor @ 6:00PM | 2004-02-29| permalink  cyall lata peeps had a gd wkend just been 2 cinema seen 'Somethings Gotta Give' quite good film. cya luv eleanor x  email | website      Eleanor @ 9:44PM | 2004-02-29| permalink  cum on peeps get ur butts online! gr8 session 2nite well dun ern n cromwell. cyall luv eleanor x x x  email | website      haz @ 9:59PM | 2004-02-29| permalink  I am online!!!!!!!! wow!! I no i said i was tired but i had to cum on to print off work!! Yes WELLL DUN ERN AND CROMWELL!!! oops left caps lock on!!!!!!! gtg cya   email | website      haz @ 10:06PM | 2004-02-29| permalink  this comments thing is turning into quite a cht room ( delaye done at that!!!!!!!!) gtg peepes bi bi  email | website      haz @ 10:07PM | 2004-02-29| permalink  i meant to say delayed!!!!!!  email | website      haz @ 10:10PM | 2004-02-29| permalink  v. disappointed that beth isn't on after all it was her idea!!!!!!! - only kidden  email | website      Eleanor @ 10:58PM | 2004-02-29| permalink  i am very disappointed that no1 is on. o well. not all of us are sad enuf 2 leave msges all the time (namely me) so i betta get goin. cyall nxt week loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      shell @ 10:19AM | 2004-03-01| permalink  THANK YOU! phew atleast now i don't have to worry about wearin a leotard thingy thing! Just to say, on behalf of ian and myself, thanks to all of you for participating last night. We hope you enjoyed it and we didn't confuse you tooooo much (and i can tell you now, iain and i got a tad confused quite a few times! lol) Hope you're all still alive today! :p x  email | website      shell @ 10:19AM | 2004-03-01| permalink  THANK YOU! phew atleast now i don't have to worry about wearin a leotard thingy thing! Just to say, on behalf of ian and myself, thanks to all of you for participating last night. We hope you enjoyed it and we didn't confuse you tooooo much (and i can tell you now, iain and i got a tad confused quite a few times! lol) Hope you're all still alive today! :p x  email | website      Katie 'Wheres my turkey?' Passey @ 10:22AM | 2004-03-01| permalink  May I be the first to say CONGRATULATIONS!!!! woooooooooooooooooo   On another note (in deep voice) woooooooooooooooooo ...im so funny  email | website      Katie 'Wheres my turkey?' Passey @ 10:22AM | 2004-03-01| permalink  May I be the first to say CONGRATULATIONS!!!! woooooooooooooooooo   On another note (in deep voice) woooooooooooooooooo ...im so funny  email | website      haz @ 5:13PM | 2004-03-01| permalink  May I be the second one to say  CONGRATULATIONS!!  (sorri i copied wat katy said)   I am very confused about the comments thing owell ok here is my email addy -  hazzie_is_happy@hotmail.com   cya  well dun lyn + paul - i mean congratulations  email | website      haz @ 5:15PM | 2004-03-01| permalink  can i ask lyn -  do u have a rock??? if so is it very big?? -  email | website      Eeee @ 5:37PM | 2004-03-01| permalink  Well Well Well.. Mite b a gd idea... Lol :p  email | website      Eeee @ 5:39PM | 2004-03-01| permalink  Oooo did the thinking hurt ur head Pee ?  email | website      Eleanor @ 5:45PM | 2004-03-01| permalink  yes, a HUGE   CONGRATULATIONS!!!!!   to Lynn and Paul (i guessed last nite but only found out properly 2 day coz i left early last nite)  U 2 r absolutely perfect together and i wish u best wishes and happiness in ur new life 2geva (wen u actually get hitched and now of course). now that the formal bit is over - whooo! i am hyper again everybody but don't worry - i will not b leavin 2 many messages 2nite bcoz i hav 2 go and wear myself out at gymnastics :&)( anyways, hope every1 has a gd week. brogan - how did u do in ur St John's comp? cyall nxt sunday loadsa luv eleanor x x x :-*  email | website      Eleanor @ 5:50PM | 2004-03-01| permalink  i dont think my other msg just now came up so here it is again;   a massive   CONGRATULATIONS!!!!!!!!!   to paul and lynn, i think u r wonderful together and best wishes/happiness in ur new life (wen u get hitched and before then 2, of course!). now that the formal bit is over - - whooooo! i am hyper again but I dont hav a clue y. dont worry tho - i prob wont b leaving so many messages 2nite bcoz i hav 2 go and wear myself out/stretch into impossible positions/build up my 'strength and muscles' at gymnastics. brogan - how was ur St Johns comp? cyall nxt week, loadsa luv, eleanor x x x x :-*  email | website      Lynn @ 5:51PM | 2004-03-01| permalink  Thanks for all your message of congrats. don't know why we told you really - JUST SO EXCITED I SUPPOSE! Oh, and don't go telling everyone at school. Anyway, just to clarify - No you can't all be bridesmaids etc (but I'm sure you'll get an invite)  email | website      Eleanor @ 6:28PM | 2004-03-01| permalink  i dont think my other msg just now came up so here it is again;   a massive   CONGRATULATIONS!!!!!!!!!   to paul and lynn, i think u r wonderful together and best wishes/happiness in ur new life (wen u get hitched and before then 2, of course!). now that the formal bit is over - - whooooo! i am hyper again but I dont hav a clue y. dont worry tho - i prob wont b leaving so many messages 2nite bcoz i hav 2 go and wear myself out/stretch into impossible positions/build up my 'strength and muscles' at gymnastics. brogan - how was ur St Johns comp? cyall nxt week, loadsa luv, eleanor x x x x :-*  email | website      Eleanor @ 6:36PM | 2004-03-01| permalink  ok i only just worked out how 2 view these so i apologise for the massive messages!  email | website      Eeee @ 6:38PM | 2004-03-01| permalink  thts a gr8 idea P... but didnt it hurt u 2 think ?!  email | website      Eleanor @ 6:40PM | 2004-03-01| permalink  wot does harriet mean about a rock? OH! hang on delayed braain reaction i get it now. can we see it if u do> cyall luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Eleanor @ 10:33PM | 2004-03-01| permalink  i think sumfing is wrong wiv my computer but i hav finally managed 2 c the msges from 2day. paul - gd idea but wouldnt u b worried bout me clogging up the whole page? i mean, seriously, i can get mega hyper on the net. anyway keep updating (24/7?) cyall nxt week, loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      P Nut @ 9:08AM | 2004-03-02| permalink  You lot bored with comments already?! C'mon!!  email | website      shell @ 11:22AM | 2004-03-02| permalink  wooooooooooooooooooo woooooooo ok im done! School is sooooo boring...humph! ok random i know!  email | website      P Nut @ 11:50AM | 2004-03-02| permalink  The mouse on this computer is utter rubbish   I'm on one of the puters @ work and it's just rubbish with a capital rub   anyway   Been grilling Shell about a New York accent   Passey, get working on your Kansas accent   and Ern   Just... Start speaking scarecrow  email | website      P Nut @ 11:51AM | 2004-03-02| permalink  The mouse on this computer is utter rubbish   I'm on one of the puters @ work and it's just rubbish with a capital rub   anyway   Been grilling Shell about a New York accent   Passey, get working on your Kansas accent   and Ern   Just... Start speaking scarecrow  email | website      Eeeeeee.... @ 5:38PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  Erm. Yah.. RIiiitteee...! u iz insane man! o.O  email | website      beth @ 5:56PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  just to prrove ive been here  email | website      beth @ 5:59PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  has this worked?  email | website      beth @ 6:00PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  i know how tro work it  email | website      beth @ 6:00PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  i know how tro work it  email | website      beth @ 6:00PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  i know how tro work it  email | website      beth @ 6:00PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  i know how tro work it  email | website      beth @ 6:01PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  i know how to work it!!!  email | website      beth @ 6:01PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  i know how to work it!!!  email | website      beth @ 6:01PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  i know how to work it!!!  email | website      beth @ 6:01PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  i know how to work it!!!  email | website      beth @ 6:01PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  i know how to work it!!!  email | website      beth @ 6:04PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  i know how to work it  email | website      beth @ 6:04PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  i know how to work it  email | website      beth @ 6:04PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  i know how to work it  email | website      beth @ 6:04PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  i know how to work it  email | website      beth @ 6:05PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  what was the dance to???  i know it was micheal jackson but which song????  email | website      beth @ 6:06PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  i know how to work it!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  email | website      beth @ 6:06PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  i know how to work it!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  email | website      beth @ 6:08PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  i know how to work it!!  email | website      beth @ 6:08PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  i know how to work it!!  email | website      beth @ 6:08PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  i know how to work it!!  email | website      beth @ 6:08PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  i know how to work it!!  email | website      beth @ 6:11PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  i know how to work it!!!!  email | website      beth @ 6:11PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  i know how to work it!!!!  email | website      little @ 6:20PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  i know how to use it!!!!  email | website      Eeeeeee.... @ 6:57PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  michael Jackson - Jam ...   and did u REALI need 2 rite tht soooo many times!?  email | website      Eleanor @ 7:07PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  ok that was a lot of messages beth - did u really need 2 do that????  email | website      Eleanor @ 7:23PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  i had the most awful flute lesson in my life today. i played everything wrong and i only hav 3 weeks! i am now v. miserable :( hey, i gotta go. cyall next week, loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      little @ 9:48PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  thankz  email | website      little @ 9:49PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  eeeeeeeee  email | website      little @ 9:49PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  eeeeeeeee  email | website      little @ 9:49PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  yeah  email | website      little @ 9:49PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  eeeeeeeee  email | website      little @ 9:49PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  did  email | website      little @ 9:49PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  i  email | website      little @ 9:49PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  rite  email | website      little @ 9:49PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  have  email | website      little @ 9:49PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  so  email | website      little @ 9:49PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  it  email | website      little @ 9:50PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  !!!!!!!1  email | website      little @ 9:50PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  times  email | website      little @ 9:50PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  yeah i did have to rite it so many times but...  email | website      little @ 9:54PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  itwouldberealyfunnyifacertainsomeonecalledbethlittlewrotearealylongmessagewithnospacesandyouspentagesworkingoutwhatitsaidwhenrealyitdidntsayanythingbecauseimjusttryingtoannouyyouandwasteyourtimesothemoreyoureaderthelongeryouarewastingyourowntimesojustkeeponreadingyouseethethingisthatifyouarestillreadingnowyoumustbeasboaredasiamsokeeponreadingandkeeponwastingyourtimeidontnowwhatelsetosayhopeiwastedyourtime!!!  email | website      little @ 9:54PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  itwouldberealyfunnyifacertainsomeonecalledbethlittlewrotearealylongmessagewithnospacesandyouspentagesworkingoutwhatitsaidwhenrealyitdidntsayanythingbecauseimjusttryingtoannouyyouandwasteyourtimesothemoreyoureaderthelongeryouarewastingyourowntimesojustkeeponreadingyouseethethingisthatifyouarestillreadingnowyoumustbeasboaredasiamsokeeponreadingandkeeponwastingyourtimeidontnowwhatelsetosayhopeiwastedyourtime!!!  email | website      little @ 9:54PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  try and work out what that say  email | website      little @ 10:03PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  what do we vote for and how do we right on the other screen  email | website      Eeeeeeeeeeee.... @ 11:29PM | 2004-03-02| permalink  Odd Child!  email | website      shell @ 11:20AM | 2004-03-03| permalink  We have talked about this already..I DONT KNOW HOW TO DO A NEW YORKIAN ACCENT! so :p you will have to teach me! lol x  email | website      P Nut @ 1:34PM | 2004-03-03| permalink  I KNOW!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!   ;-)  email | website      Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee..... @ 3:09PM | 2004-03-03| permalink  i hav an extended idea off of urs Pee... Well its an even better 1 .. well.. its an idea atleast!  email | website      You can call me dorethy, or Katie, whatevers good for you really @ 3:53PM | 2004-03-03| permalink  'Hi im from kansas' hows that pauly? i cant actually believe i dont wear the shoes... its historically wrong... eww i have some food stuck in my keyboard, i think its toast, where was i? So yeh Paul and Lynn, Lynn and Paul :oD so exciting and there will be a big cake mmmmmm cake... I have now not only the Wizard of oz DVD but also the wizard of oz soundtrack CD arnt i the little bundle of joy wrapped up in one big wizard of oz love nest   Hope everyone is well (by the way its ions birthday on friday woo)   Lave ya and leave ya  Dottyxx  email | website      Eleanor @ 6:16PM | 2004-03-03| permalink  wot is ur idea ern? hiya dotty! i hav a confession 2 make - i have never seen the WOO so PLEASE can i borrow somebody's video before sunday - i guess lynn, u will kill me if i dont c it. i kinda know sum of the songs tho! peeps get in touch quick!!!!! thanx a lot, cyall nxt week, loadsa luv, eleanor x x x  email | website      beth @ 7:42PM | 2004-03-03| permalink  im not odd i was just realy realy boared and im the only one on again !!!!  email | website      beth @ 6:00PM | 2004-03-04| permalink  soz i presssed coment and it didnt work so i kept pressing it then it appeared loads of times!!  ooopppsss  i am blonde  email | website      beth @ 6:03PM | 2004-03-04| permalink  by the way whats the thing with the code word??  email | website      aly @ 7:47PM | 2004-03-04| permalink  hi  CONGRATULATIONS Lynn and Paul  hehehe  :)  c u on sunday  luv aly    email | website      kadt @ 10:41PM | 2004-03-04| permalink  hallu people of this place right here... hope you're good... i'm tired! tum te tum te tum  email | website      kadt @ 10:43PM | 2004-03-04| permalink  hallu people of this place right here! hope you're all good... i'm tired! tum te tum tum te...  email | website      Eeee.... @ 10:47PM | 2004-03-04| permalink  Wew Evrybody.. its 2 hours and 15 mins untill my b'day, and ill b expecting ALOT of Txts!!!! So get texting! and u not having my mobile number is NO Excuse!  email | website      kadt @ 10:49PM | 2004-03-04| permalink  what if people don't see that msg untill after it's your b'day?? huh?? huh?? HUH??   email | website      kadt @ 10:50PM | 2004-03-04| permalink  dammit...now you know i've seen it!  email | website      Eeee.... @ 10:51PM | 2004-03-04| permalink  Well... Then thts their fault, they jus b on this 24/7 (hint to paul) Lol ... :p  email | website      Eeee.... @ 10:52PM | 2004-03-04| permalink  AND even if i see u in the day.. i still want a txt msg!!!!  email | website      kadt @ 10:57PM | 2004-03-04| permalink  in that case maybe you'll receive one... or maybe you won't... somethin for you to look forward to    email | website      Eeee.... @ 10:58PM | 2004-03-04| permalink  Lol well, i better not recieve jus 1, or sum ppl will b .... Ahem...  email | website      kadt @ 11:00PM | 2004-03-04| permalink  ahem???  email | website      Eleanor @ 11:02PM | 2004-03-04| permalink  better switch tat fone on then! happy birthday for tomoz neway. how is every1? its nearly the weekend again!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! whoooo!!!!!! :D :D :D i am excited again but gotta go finish off hwk. cyall on sunday loadsa luv eleanor x xx   email | website      Eeee.... @ 11:02PM | 2004-03-04| permalink  yup yup.. Ahem...!  email | website      Eleanor @ 11:09PM | 2004-03-04| permalink  hehehehe lol i am so excited bout the weekend coz i am goin shoppin again (I think - haz? bef?) and then its CASUALTY on saturday and HTG on sunday!!!!!!!!!!!!!! whooo funfilled weekend. wot we doin on sunday> yes paul, y isnt this site manned 24/7???? (i no u r busy n all but so r we, p, so r we!) :D i am so pleased it is nearly the weekend again. whoooo!!!!!!!!!!!!! soz i am lettin out my energy 4 2nite. sposed 2 b doin hwk - o well :) cyall on sunday loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Eleanor @ 6:26PM | 2004-03-05| permalink  wwwwwhooooooooooooooooooo!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!1 ITS DA WEEKEND AGAIN!!!!!!! happy birthday ern by the way! :D i am excited again so pnut, prepare for a weekend full of msges - but WHERE R U????? cyall sunday loadsa luv eleanor x xx  email | website      Eeeee.... @ 6:35PM | 2004-03-05| permalink  Happy b'day 2 me, Happy b'day 2 me, Happy b'day 2 meeeeee... Happy b'day 2 meee :D:D:D Wew!  email | website      Eleanor @ 8:25PM | 2004-03-05| permalink  ern, hasnt this birthday thing gon 2 ur head a bit??? no offense meant  email | website      Eleanor @ 9:59AM | 2004-03-07| permalink  lookin 4ward 2 c-in every1 2nite. where is everybody? loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Eee @ 2:29PM | 2004-03-07| permalink  Well the day was ruined neway.  email | website      Eleanor @ 6:24PM | 2004-03-08| permalink  why was wot day ruined? ur birthday? aah! i hav a bomb load of hwk to do so i betta go do it - cyall sunday loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      tululah @ 10:35PM | 2004-03-08| permalink  i am sooooo bored, i could eat my...socks??  email | website      scared! @ 10:27AM | 2004-03-09| permalink  Ok thats the one...go and eat your socks! Dont suppose anyone wants to do the improvments on my king lear coursework do they?! x  email | website    
     
    
</post>

<date>07,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Been unable to blog most of the week  now I can't view the comments  Oh well  See you later, you lot
     
    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Paradise... PARADISE!   PARADISE!!    As in the song by Joni Mitchell, cover song from some idiot just recently  They paved paradise to put up a parking lot!!  Come on!!! *sigh*  Ern, cheers for the details re Luke... Got meeting tonight following a rehearsal in which hopefully we'll get the lighting rig plotted, then Saturday morning all being well I'm rigging the front of house lighting bar at the Civic, so if any of my crew were about for that any help gratefully rec'd  Chiz  x
     
    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      You'll never guess what they've gone and done!?!?!  They've only gone and paved paradise!!! I just can't believe it, I really can't... There's a new development there, there's signs and everything... Putting up a parking lot apparently  there's just no justice in the world  Heh heh
     
    
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, sorry for cancelling tonight's theatre group session... As we said to some of you, Lynn & I were back late from rehearsals for Hello Dolly, & we were totally worn out & didn't fancy going and shouting for an evening @ you guys!!   Heh heh  Inceidentally, whilst we're on the subject, Hello Dolly tickets are on sale  Weds March 31st - Saturday April 3rd Note, there are two performances on the Saturday; one at 2.00pm & one at 7.30 pm. We make a point as a theatre group of trying to support each other's work, & so we'd like to see plenty of you there! By the way, some of the older members are running the lighting for this show, so you'd not just be supporting Lynn and me!  And of course there's Ern's play... Sorry, 4got the title :s Tickets available from himself or the Rose Theatre... He'd very much like everyone to come & support him, & would like to say the character he plays in the play is just acting & does in no way resemble his character!!  Ok... Er... Anything else, Lynn??  She says no, so... I guess I trust her  Heh heh  Right, leave me alone then, you lot, I'm going to sit about in the other room  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Here are the codes for smilies. I'm not able to put a preview in unfortunately, you can only view them in the members area of the enetation website... or on the comments bit when using them, obv:  :stun:   :invasion:   :tooth:   :clap:   :clown:   :confused:   :naughty:   :nod:   :nonono:   :sleep:   :sleep2:   :ouch:   :puke:   :D   :-D   :grin:   :)   :-)   :smile:   :(   :-(   :sad:   :o   :-o   :eek:   :-?   :???:   8-)   :cool:   :lol:   :x   :-x   :mad:   :P   :-P   :razz:   :oops:   :cry:   :tear:   :evil:   :roll:   :wink:   ;-)   ;)   :|   Use them wisely, my young friends... Don't use them indiscriminately
     
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Here are your comments immortalised  is that how you spell immortalised? Ah well  The smilies presumably won't show up, so it might read a bit oddly    Pe Pe @ 10:43 | March 9th 2004| permalink  I've cleared out the comments thing as promised...   The delete All button worked this time   Er... Yes, not sure why the Blogger has changed between Bold type and Not Bold type, but never mind   Just want to test something:      Did that work?  email | website      Pe Pe @ 10:47 | March 9th 2004| permalink  Yay!! It worked!!      I've changed the settings now so hopefully the time is right and I tried putting the most recent comments at the top but that just seemed odd...  email | website      Pe Pe @ 11:02 | March 9th 2004| permalink  The time's an hour out!! ARGH!!      Right - back to the settings menu  email | website      Pe Pe @ 10:52 | March 9th 2004| permalink  The timing's all over the place   Because it's an hour ahead when it's set to GMT, I set it to Azores, Cape Verde Island, which we all know is an hour behind us, naturally   And now it's 12 minutes fast!!!!   Wretched thing   So you'll have to make do with that, kay? I'm going to go and watch Judge Judy whilst you lot slave away at school   Heh heh   another smiley coming up.... eeeerrrmm.... This one:     email | website      Pe Pe @ 11:07 | March 9th 2004| permalink  For the love of mike, it's right now   Perhaps it was winding the clock back as I wrote that last message     email | website      Pe Pe @ 10:56 | March 9th 2004| permalink  That wasn't a wink!!!!!   I don't just put boring smiley faces on my comments!!!   The VERY IDEA!!!!!!   I put interesting ones like vomit faces and and and irate faces, I don't put blooming smiles, boring smiles, I mean do I look like the sort of person who puts smiley faces on his comments? Do I? Do I really because tell me now I may as well just give up and go and live in Devon     email | website      Pe Pe @ 10:57 | March 9th 2004| permalink  Ah...   *ahem*   I am quite contrite...   It seems I did a colon instead of a semi-colon...   *ahem*   Look you, tho, it's not that much more like a wink than the other one is it?!  Judge Judy beckons   Traa     email | website      Pe Pe @ 13:00 | March 9th 2004| permalink  ::  email | website      Pe Pe @ 16:19 | March 9th 2004| permalink  C'mon, come and comment on my smilies!!  email | website      Eleanor @ 17:04 | March 9th 2004| permalink  aah! theyr cool! get well soon pnut. i will b bak on lata cyall luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Eee.. @ 17:26 | March 9th 2004| permalink  Erm... seems like u spent a long time on smiles.. but cud u pls hurry and let me kno bout the times on wed!.. Lol Chop Chop!   email | website      Eleanor @ 17:31 | March 9th 2004| permalink  wowee how u do smilees? wot the matter wit u paul? hope u feely betta soon. where is every1? i am v. disappointed there is no1 on xcept me n ern. as per usual!  o well. cyall sunday loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Eee.. @ 17:33 | March 9th 2004| permalink     email | website      Eleanor @ 17:36 | March 9th 2004| permalink  aarrgghh tht is so annoying!    email | website      Eee.. @ 17:59 | March 9th 2004| permalink    email | website      Pe Pe @ 18:09 | March 9th 2004| permalink  I'll do a key of how to do smileys, Eleanor... Then u can get Ern back   I'm ok, just got a heavy cold, can't talk loud or anything, headache, tired, can't be bothered to move kind of thing   Heh heh   Great fun     email | website      Pe Pe @ 18:11 | March 9th 2004| permalink  oh yes, Weds... Er, I'll pick u up about ten to 7... i don't suppose u've seen tania have u... or georgi   not spoken to them  email | website      Eee.. @ 18:24 | March 9th 2004| permalink  my god, dnt u read my txts .. it sed "tania, georgi and i can com"... *mutters* idiot Lol yea .. well.. Lol wher u wanna pik us up from, or u guna com 2 each house in turn ?!  email | website      Eee.. @ 18:35 | March 9th 2004| permalink    email | website      Eee.. @ 18:36 | March 9th 2004| permalink  the  looks all manky!  email | website      Cabbage Patch Kid! @ 19:06 | March 9th 2004| permalink  Kt Passey  Lol...  email | website      Eee... & Georgi @ 18:46 | March 10th 2004| permalink     Hey peeps.  email | website      Eee... @ 18:47 | March 10th 2004| permalink         Muhahaha  email | website      Eee... @ 18:47 | March 10th 2004| permalink    email | website      Eleanor @ 6:43 | March 11th 2004| permalink  i will find out ern! muahahahah to u 2!  oh well. how is every1? had a good week so far?  email | website      Eleanor @ 15:57 | March 11th 2004| permalink  wow that worked! I mite try out sum more . . . lynn, a lil birdie told me that u hav got a cd! so r we gonna hear it or wot? o, i hav been tryin 2 remember SOTR alto part but not doin very well! o well, i am sure i will get betta wiv practice! i hav 2 go now but xpect more msges lata on peeps! cyall sunday loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Eleanor @ 15:58 | March 11th 2004| permalink   is this gonna work! if so - yay! if not - :$  email | website      Eleanor @ 15:59 | March 11th 2004| permalink   is this gonna work! if so - yay! if not - :$  email | website      Eleanor @ 15:59 | March 11th 2004| permalink  ooh! one of them worked! paul or ern can u tell me how to make better ones?  email | website      Eee.. @ 19:06 | March 11th 2004| permalink   Moo-Hahaa  email | website      Eleanor @ 19:08 | March 11th 2004| permalink  heelloooo!!!!!!!  i dont know y i am jst smilee! jst incase ne1 is interested - i had a practice with the accompaniest for my flute exam (2 weeks yesterday) and it went great so i am feelin betta than on tuesday. o - brogan, did u tell every1 your team WON St John's comp 2 sundays ago?  i g2g but cyall sunday loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Eleanor @ 17:16 | March 12th 2004| permalink  um. wot r we doin on sunday? wuld i b allowed 2 b late or not? youth service @ st. saviours half past six - half hour prob. i culd miss it if u want me to - pls either post on here or txt me paul or lynn thanx eleanor x x x  email | website      El @ 19:25 | March 12th 2004| permalink  http://www.smiliegenerator.de/s22/smilies-41542.png i hav done it! hahahahahaha! i worked it out! so pleased! http://www.click-smilies.de/sammlung0903/grinser/grinning-smiley-002.gif hehehe! http://www.click-smilies.de/sammlung0903/lachen/laughing-smiley-003.gif http://www.click-smilies.de/sammlung0903/lachen/laughing-smiley-008.gif http://www.click-smilies.de/sammlung0903/lachen/laughing-smiley-014.gif lol  i did it!  email | website      El @ 19:26 | March 12th 2004| permalink  oh! it didnt work!   email | website      ME @ 22:21 | March 13th 2004| permalink  I want one of my cooments to go on here!  email | website      ME @ 22:33 | March 13th 2004| permalink  IT WORKED   email | website      ME @ 22:22 | March 13th 2004| permalink  when the clap is on freeze frame it looks like it's got ears!  email | website      ME @ 22:35 | March 13th 2004| permalink  Me is lynn by the way... oh and did paul tell you that we NEARLY have our own house... just the fact that we now need a mortgage... no problem there then!   email | website      LYNNIEFOXYCHICKENBURGER @ 22:27 | March 13th 2004| permalink  THIS IS FUN WHEN IT WORKS.   Must go to bed though now. Very long day tomorrow. Oh and you should all be in bed too - spect though you're all out partying somewhere.. in a field... in the cold... in stupid shoes (girls that is)... and Ian! Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha  Didn't mean it Ian, Promise! Please don't hate me... Ever wondered why I ramble on... I have... have no conclusions though... umph... poo... tigger... nothing else... bye.... I bet you've all read this far waiting for me to say something useful and I haven't... finished now!  email | website      LYNNIEFOXYCHICKENBURGER @ 22:29 | March 13th 2004| permalink  I'm quite funny sometimes... only quiet tho!   Really am going this time  email | website      Pe of Pe-land @ 22:33 | March 13th 2004| permalink  My word that girl goes on, doesn't she?!   Heh heh   She's tired I think   We've just been typing out script for tomorrow night... As that Lynn's not around to do music, we're going to set some movement, and as we've not been sent the scripts yet we've had to type them out   So BRING PENCILS WITH YOU   Or you'll all be shot   Had a dream about the residential the other night; it was in my back garden... Ferry odd... Not as odd as the dream I had in which I met Vicky's parents in a cinema car park and pretended I was Vicky so they wouldn't shout at me for some reason... I don't know, ask my analyst... My mind - a dangerous place to be... Heh heh  email | website      Eleanor @ 0:16 | March 14th 2004| permalink  i dont hav a clue wot all that was about! i am v upset my smilies didnt work P - PLEASE tell me how 2 do it! lynnie i am not in bed bcoz i hav been babysittin now absolutely shattered - paul please dont shout at me 2moro if i am sleepy! congrats re: engagement rings and house! yay! i want to hear the cd! wot u mean no more harmonies? cyall 2moro (part from lynn) loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      ... @ 9:51 | March 14th 2004| permalink    email | website      Eleanor @ 12:12 | March 14th 2004| permalink  well well well well well i am annoyed and bored and . . . . . . . . generally under par. its raining and grey and cloudy and i will just shut up now ok cyall lata luv eleanor      email | website      Stu @ 12:39 | March 14th 2004| permalink                                                                          ops:                    thought id try the emoticons  lol  email | website      :invasion: @ 12:56 | March 14th 2004| permalink  Jus wanna c if it works in ur names...  email | website      Eee... @ 13:00 | March 14th 2004| permalink  Obviously didnt work them! Meh!     email | website      Eleanor @ 16:14 | March 14th 2004| permalink  thanx paul - re: smilies  re: aly, becky, charlotte & me late - possibly not! not quite sure yet so sorry. cya  email | website      Eleanor @ 20:05 | March 14th 2004| permalink  well i missed my weekly fix of fun wit every1! o well cyall next sunday loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      P nut & Lynniefoxychickenburger @ 20:13 | March 14th 2004| permalink  Hi, Eleanor... We're on the same time as you at last   Er...   Trying to think of something to write   Not able to...  email | website      Eleanor @ 22:07 | March 14th 2004| permalink  sorry i went offline! only just got that message! hope u had a fun rehearsal anyway. cyall next sunday loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      P Nut @ 10:37 | March 15th 2004| permalink  C'mon you lot, don't dry up comments-wise   get commentin, stop leaving it to us over-worked ones     email | website      Eee... @ 14:49 | March 15th 2004| permalink  Luke's "Busy Week Scedule":   The following times are wen he is busy   Monday: 5 - 5.30  Tuesday: 6.45 - 7:15  Wednesday: 7 - 9  Thursday: Free  Friday: Free  Saturday: Day Time  Sunday: Day time   He can cancel sum of these times if he is needed.  email | website      Eee... @ 14:51 | March 15th 2004| permalink  Oh.. And thanx 4 advertising my play   email | website      Eleanor @ 16:47 | March 15th 2004| permalink  paradise???  email | website      Eleanor @ 19:22 | March 15th 2004| permalink  hallo peeps! i tried 2 leave a msg earlier but it obviously didnt work, paul wot u mean paradise??? i will try and cum 2 peeps' plays but i cant promise nethin! lol i just thought wot is peeps doin over easter? i am goin wit my friends to butlins at skegness!  o well it shuld b fun! gotta go - gymnastics  cyall sunday loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Eleanor @ 19:23 | March 15th 2004| permalink  hallo peeps! i tried 2 leave a msg earlier but it obviously didnt work, paul wot u mean paradise??? i will try and cum 2 peeps' plays but i cant promise nethin! lol i just thought wot is peeps doin over easter? i am goin wit my friends to butlins at skegness!  o well it shuld b fun! gotta go - gymnastics  cyall sunday loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Eleanor @ 22:20 | March 15th 2004| permalink  ok it did nitenite every1 luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Eleanor @ 17:52 | March 16th 2004| permalink  halloo!!!! where is everybody? i am feelin hyper again 2nite - wot u mean peeps dryin up on comments? i not dryin up! i am floodin them out! (well not quite but u get wot i mean!) lookin forward 2 residential now!  everybody smile cyall sunday loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Eleanor @ 15:56 | March 18th 2004| permalink  where is everybody? peeps leave a message! luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Dot @ 15:02 | March 19th 2004| permalink  I apologise for not posting a comment on here for such a long time, although im sure its not missed as eleanor seems to talk to herself anyway...  To Mr. Pee I no the song your on about... its called yellow taxi isnt it? meh...   Im sat in the school 'independant learning centre' at the moment (iain is behind me woop) and i just looked up to find inspiration for something to write and you no what i saw? no not books, well yes book, but not that... flowers!? why is there flowers in here...to make it more 'homely' i expect heh...   FOLLOW THAT YELLOW BRICK ROAD   email | website      Dot @ 15:02 | March 19th 2004| permalink  I apologise for not posting a comment on here for such a long time, although im sure its not missed as eleanor seems to talk to herself anyway...  To Mr. Pee I no the song your on about... its called yellow taxi isnt it? meh...   Im sat in the school 'independant learning centre' at the moment (iain is behind me woop) and i just looked up to find inspiration for something to write and you no what i saw? no not books, well yes book, but not that... flowers!? why is there flowers in here...to make it more 'homely' i expect heh...   FOLLOW THAT YELLOW BRICK ROAD   email | website      Dot @ 15:04 | March 19th 2004| permalink  *books   p.s JESUS THERES A TREE ASWELL... (well spotted ion)  email | website      Eleanor @ 21:57 | March 19th 2004| permalink  my comments wont go on!!!!! i am annoyd now! did ne1 watch friends? its the WEEKEND!!!!!!!!! AGAIN!!!!!!!!! WWWHHHOOOO!!!!!!!!! cyall sunday loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Eleanor @ 20:01 | March 20th 2004| permalink  howdee peeps! where r u all? i am ramblin 2 myself again!!!!!!!! cant wait 2 c u all 2moz loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Eleanor @ 21:43 | March 20th 2004| permalink  omg i cant believe there is still no1 on!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! will peeps please let me know that there is still life in hagley (& kiddi & other . . .) will sumbody please cum online i am rambling again . . . cyall 2moz loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Eleanor @ 20:55 | March 21st 2004| permalink  paul or lynn or anybody where r u? lynn i think ur ring is absolutely GORGEOUS so extra congrats 4 that! hope every1 has a gr8 week nd cant wait 2 cyall in 2 weeks! (when, bytheway, we will be shattered coz its Duke of Edinburgh practise! o well!) cyall then loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Eleanor @ 17:15 | March 22nd 2004| permalink  halloo!!!!!!!!! peeps where r u all???? not that i mind talkin 2 myself or nethin but it does help if i get reminded that there is still life outside of my room!!!! cyall soon loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Eleanor @ 16:59 | March 23rd 2004| permalink  omg omg omg where is every1? wish me luck 4 my flute exam 2moz - well done alice 2day! cyall soon loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Eleanor @ 18:21 | March 24th 2004| permalink  ok ok this is jus beginnin 2 get the teensiest bit annoyin . . . WHERE R U ALL???????? hallohallohallohallohallo???? i am gettin bored wit no1 2 talk 2!!!!! cyall soon loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      guess who @ 21:54 | March 24th 2004| permalink  more than a week has passed and no1 has been on! o, kt was on but paul it has been ages! where is every1???? nitynight luv eleanor x x x  email | website      i dont think i need 2 tell u @ 15:56 | March 25th 2004| permalink  ggrrr!!!! :@  email | website      E @ 17:16 | March 25th 2004| permalink  ppl havent been on, cuz they busy gettin GCSE c/w in and sum ppl hav been busy with lighting, and L and P r busy with their play, and im busy with my play!... hope tht answers ur question as 2 y we aint been on.  email | website      Eleanor @ 18:30 | March 26th 2004| permalink  oooh! so sorry!  lol at least now i know there is still life on earth and t'internet! soz if i offended ne1! its the WEEKEND again!!!!!!!!!!! WWHHHHOOOOO!!!!!!! i am pleased coz i can sleep for ages and ages! lol cyall soon loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Eleanor @ 8:12 | March 28th 2004| permalink  well da weekend is nearly over n i havnt dun nethin! no HTG 2 cheer me up! lol cyall soon loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      beth @ 19:32 | March 31st 2004| permalink  i havent been on 4 ages.  it took me 10 mins to find the button to say add comments.  im realy boared.  good luck in ur play!!!!!  see u all on sunday ill probably be tired cause im doing d of e  email | website      Spotty Dotty @ 13:45 | April 2nd 2004| permalink  Congratulations to lynny for passing her teachers thang Yayyy...  That is all.  email | website      Eleanor @ 17:06 | April 2nd 2004| permalink  wot teachers thang? i am cumin 2 c u 2nite good luck! cyall soon loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Eleanor @ 17:00 | April 4th 2004| permalink  howdee all. now that hello dolly is finished PLEASE will P or L write bak 2 me! i loved the play btw it was cool! american accents!! hehehe  *she grins widely* c u all really soon loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website    
     
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Now my breaktimes at work aren't taken up with Hello Dolly stuff, I can Blog-on  Yay!!  Erm  Right... going to have a look at the comments section... Either everyone will have given up or it'll be REALLY huge!!!  See ya later, guys  Good work last night... Sorry I disappeared half way through   
     
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      There is  NO DRAMA  Sunday April 18th  Had two people ask already ( grrrrrr ), so despite having said a myriad times it's not on this week,   PLUS   it being on the rummin' rehearsal schedules yer  STILL  didn't take it in, yer pesky kids  Right  I'm off to have me haddock and chips  Tra   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Could Walter Moers have been talking about anyone in HTG, when he said  "It was amazing how many obnoxious qualities could be accomodated in such a small body"    ???    Heh heh  Sorry, HTG...  Couldn't resist  Traa til Sunday
     
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I, dear children - and young adults ;-) have just passed my driving test  Heh heh  My driving instructor's test that is... One hour fifteen minutes of nerve-wracking hell well spent, I think... Had to do all the manoeueoaeuvres except for reverse round a left hand corner... Had to do a reverse to the right tho... I actually stalled the car!!! I NEVER stall the car... But I did today... Had to go on the motorway and all that... Gert fun  I have an application form for a license to be a trainee instructor... Heh heh - I could be teaching very soon  Waaayy  Right  I'm going to look at what messages there are in the comments bit  Better be loads *grrrrrrrr*  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       DON'T FORGETS THE OPEN EVENING!!!!!!!!  TELL EVERY HTG YOUTHER YOU SEE & MAKE SURE  EVERYONE  KNOWS & HAS INVITED THEIR PARENTS, THEIR FRIENDS, THEIR FAMILIES, THEIR FAMILIES' FRIENDS, THEIR FAMILIES' FRIENDS' TENNIS PARTNERS   And so forth
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Awwwwwwwww  The comments thing ISN'T working now  What the catapult is wrong with it?!!?!?!?!?????!?!?!!!!!?!?!?!?!?!?! ?!?!?!?!  I'm going to look for an alternative  ive
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Did anyone see the small horse called p-nut on GMTV this morning?  Heh heh  Class in a glass
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I've just had to delete 103 comments one by one!!  Blooming delete all button just would not work  It's worked like once in the whole tme we've been blogging  wretched thing  I really hate the fact that I can't put a new comments link in!  *Grrrrrrrrrrrr*
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Eleanor @ 21:26 | April 5th 2004| permalink  hehehehe dairy milk tasters??? i dunno . . well i am v. v. annoyed that we r still @ school when EVERY1 has broken up. o well. we only hav 3 days left and its nearly a WEEK to spring harvest!!!! wwwhhhoooo!!!!!!! hehehe lol cyall soon loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Eleanor @ 15:50 | April 6th 2004| permalink  howdee! it is exactly une semaine until SPRING HARVEST!!!!! whooo! cyall soon loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      P Nut @ 9:21 | April 7th 2004| permalink  Just thought I'd drop in and say hello   Having Buttons today, didn't fancy Tasters   If anyone sees Lynn, smile at her for me     email | website      The one called Katie @ 14:18 | April 8th 2004| permalink  Holiday woop woop... bout bladdy time too  email | website      Eleanor @ 15:22 | April 8th 2004| permalink  i know wot u mean kt! LOL WWWHHHOOOOOOO!!!!!!! its FINALLY the HOLIDAYS! wwwhhhhhhhooooooo!!!!!!!  *she grins excitedly*  is anybody goin away? lynn i am goin away wit the mottersheads 2 spring harvest hehehe shud b fun - i am in a chalet wit Hannah, Kirsty, their friend Sarah, Janet Lewis and Harriet Webb! lol i am dead excited. hope every1 has a great holiday and gets their butts online 2 leave a msg! cyall soon loadsa luv eleanor x x x  **H@ppy E@$ter!**  email | website      Eleanor @ 20:29 | April 10th 2004| permalink  happy easter 4 2moz every1! hope u hav a gr8 day n eat loadsa chox! i am pleased i can finally eat chocolate again! i am so proud of myself 4 lastin all of lent! whhooo! neway hav a gr8 day loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Ern... @ 9:18 | April 14th 2004| permalink  Well 1 easter egg this year, and tht wasnt even of my family... well well well, im sooooo tired  email | website      Pe Pe @ 18:01 | April 16th 2004| permalink  Really should get back int othe habit of leaving messages here   But keep *not* leaving messages here   We're looking @ some options for lighting WOO as the chap who lit us last year can't help us this year with our new date   Ah well   Been shopping today to buy food for residential... Got some more still to get but it's mostly done. Sunday there is NO DRAMA as we're having a production meeting for WOO & also about the residential   Going to be good this year - lots of surprises and stuff   Spread the word   Heh heh   Tra  email | website      Eleanor @ 17:01 | April 18th 2004| permalink  i tried 2 leave a MASSIVE message on Easter day but it didn't work and i couldnt b bothered 2 type it all again . . so u were deprived of my messages! lol! i got back from Spring Harvest 2day - incase nebody wanted 2 know it was very fun and inspiring and I went 2 the beach  and i even went in the SEA at SKEGNESS because it was SUNNY!!!!!!!!! hahahahahaha i heard that it was v bad weather here. hohoho. lol i cant wait 2 c everybody again but not quite lookin 4ward to school again. hope everyone had a great holiday and good to see that P has finally managed 2 get back onto the net! hahaha cyall soon loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Eleanor @ 7:42 | April 20th 2004| permalink  i just remembered - how was ur play Ern?  email | website      Eleanor @ 8:00 | April 21st 2004| permalink  hahaha my sis had 2 go back 2 school 2day! but she broke up 4 days before us! how does that work? lookin forward 2 c-ing every1 again, loadsa luv Eleanor x x x  email | website      Eleanor @ 20:40 | April 21st 2004| permalink  hehehe cyall @ school 2moro loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Eleanor @ 18:00 | April 26th 2004| permalink  cant wait till residential!  cyall v v soon loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Eleanor @ 14:50 | April 29th 2004| permalink  STILL lookin 4ward 2 residential - if anybody finds this message in the next 50 yrs pls reply . . .  SATs nxt week aarrgghh hehehe lol need 2 do sum revisin!  good luck 2 peeps doin GCSEs and other exams! lol cyall 2moro loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Eleanor @ 17:13 | April 30th 2004| permalink  whoo! leavin in half an hour - waitin 4 becky  so c u all soon - if i survive bein in a car with aly, becky and charlotte 4 ages!!!!!   email | website      Eleanor @ 19:38 | May 2nd 2004| permalink  well i survived 2 car journeys wit them . . .  hehehe lol what a hysterical weekend - last nite i laughed more than i hav in ages - thanx bef 4 ur hilarious family (particularly ur grandad) lol  thanx 2 lynn and paul and corinne and bob and paula !!!!!!  hope 2 cyall really soon, loadsa luv eleanor x x x  wish every1 luck in sats, gcses and year 10 exams and everythin else in the next few weeks! whoo  ??? WIN ???  email | website      p-nut and lynn @ 20:27 | May 2nd 2004| permalink  to all,  hope you had an enjoyale weekend. seems strange not to be shouting!  would love to hear both positive and negative (if any!) feedback. we will take note of any comments with a view to next years residential!   see you next week!   thanks a lot for not behaving toooooooooooooooooooooooooo badly,    email | website      lynn @ 20:29 | May 2nd 2004| permalink  how tired am i exactly! how do you spell enjoyable? oh that's how and not how i spelt it before! got it!  email | website      Pe Pe @ 9:12 | May 5th 2004| permalink  Thought I'd log in to a mass of comments after our fantastic weekend   But er...   but I haven't...   Er...   Mmm...   I'll go and have my sandwich... Hope exams etc go well   C u all Sunday for s'more blocking and roitous fun-up-the-c'munity-centre  email | website      Eleanor @ 14:49 | May 5th 2004| permalink  what u mean no masses of comments? wasnt mine long enuf?? heheh loved the weekend - bad thing was the weather but cant be helped. love that centre! its so cool! lol  glad 2 c lynn and p-nut bak on the web at long last! i am no longer the only person on . . . .  exams r nearly ok! lol cyall sunday loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Ern @ 14:53 | May 5th 2004| permalink  Hello people, im ok, for those who are wandering...   did you hav a nice sandwhich P ? Lol   Hope y'all are well   Toodles.  email | website      Eleanor @ 14:55 | May 6th 2004| permalink  hiyaaa!! im hyper coz 2moro is our last exam! whoo! until next week that is . . .2 year 10 maths exams! gr8! o well .. need 2 do sum revision 4 that . . .  just 2 say thanx lynn coz u made me understand shakespeare's macbeth better so heres hopin i do well in that paper 2moro . . .! thanz  thanx also 4 a gr8 weekend! i did post a different message but the comp broke (rite after residential). g2g buy some choc so cyall soon loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Pe Pe @ 16:45 | May 6th 2004| permalink  Heh heh - sandwich was great, Ernald...   Juat celebrated my massive success @ driving by having a battered sausage   Tell yer - I know how to live, me    Er... Yes   I notice we're all doing exams and that at the moment - interesting   Mine am done now tho - till my part 3, obviously...   I'm rambling... Going to go and be "Charmed" by the telly   c u Sun   PS  Glad you're ok, Ern... Get back to exercising those leg muscles for Passey so er doesn't damager herself - you're a bit more expendable than she is...   lol  email | website      Eleanor @ 19:12 | May 7th 2004| permalink  whoo! exams r over!!!!!!!! wwhhoo!!!!!!!! lol in case u cant tell i am dead pleased! lol well done P 4 passin ur test or woteva - hehehe its funny 2 think of u teachin peeps 2 drive! (no offence! heheheeeeeeeeeeeeeeee) sorry i am so pleased!!!!! heheheheheheheheh  lol i need 2 calm down nd do sum revision 4 the year 10 maths exams next week bcoz mr richards is being SO nice and letting our group do them - 2 x 2hour exams! aarrgghh! good luck every1 in GCSEs etc. coz my exams are FINISHED!!!!!!!! WHOOO!!  lol i g2g now cyall sunday loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Eleanor @ 19:15 | May 7th 2004| permalink  ok soz that was a bit hyper but WHOO!!!!!!!! i 4got 2 tell peeps - i hav arranged my work experience 4 next year (at BIRMINGHAM CHILDREN'S HOSPITAL!!!!!) wahey! and bcoz they only offered me 4 days i mite b doin my other day at Birmingham Maternity Hospital! yay!! lol i am so pleased coz i love babies etc. and want to work in neonatal intensive care so this is excellent news! eheheheh  off 2 watch friends later *sob, nearly over!* cyall sunday loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Eleanor @ 6:50 | May 8th 2004| permalink  i just re-read those msges! perhaps i was a lil bit 2 excited yesterday. o well. lol. cyall 2moz loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      ern @ 15:33 | May 11th 2004| permalink  Random random... tum te tum tum... Lol well well well... la la laaa... tra la la laaa... ahem... yes well... rambleness... how r y'all * we are family* yeaa... welll... bye all Lol  email | website      ern @ 15:33 | May 11th 2004| permalink  Random random... tum te tum tum... Lol well well well... la la laaa... tra la la laaa... ahem... yes well... rambleness... how r y'all * we are family* yeaa... welll... bye all Lol  email | website      Ern @ 21:59 | May 11th 2004| permalink  Wow i posted it twice!!   email | website      Eleanor @ 15:33 | May 13th 2004| permalink  likin the new layout! btw - wwwwwwwwhhhhhoooooo!!!!!!!!! exams r finally over! properly! wahey! gd luck 2 peeps in their exams soon - no more icky uniform 4 u!! damnit! lol cyall soon loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Oooooooooooookkkkkkkkkkkaaaaaayyyy  The comments link IS working, despite it telling me that this bit of code was not allowed  Interesting... ah well, enjoy still further, kids ;-)
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Thought I had the comments link thing sorted... I had to insert a line of code between the header tags, you see... It's worked up to a point, in that we can use the old comments links but I can't put in any new ones...  Darn  It'll get sorted, but for now you'll have to use the old link
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It's not allowing the comments link to go in  Darn  I'll think of something!  My members won't be silenced!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The link for comments seems to have disappeared in the move to the new layout  I'll get hold of it asap
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      blogger.com has updated its site layout, so I've followed suit & changed our layout  Sinnerbit
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      There's no theatre group remember for 2 weeks!!  Starting today  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Here's the comments from the last few months:  Edit Delete Block IP : (213.122.181.77)   Eleanor @ 20:59 | May 13th 2004| permalink  wahey! i am going to b the first person to comment on the new block and clog it all up! well done Pnut 4 deletin msges - most of which i suspect were mine. my exams are officially OVER!!!! WHOOOO!!!! lol i am so pleased - just nervous bout results. and jealous of yr 11s coz they get 2 hav a PROM and get 2 dress up and . . . blabberblabberblabber better shut up now cyall soon loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Edit Delete Block IP : (81.131.193.183)   Eleanor @ 20:41 | May 14th 2004| permalink  no dont watch GMTV! o well. cyall sunday loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Edit Delete Block IP : (213.122.142.132)   Eleanor @ 21:00 | May 15th 2004| permalink  wot is the POINT of the eurovision song contest?? all the songs r the same!!!! bored out of my mind watchin it will hav 2 go do summink else like tidy my room  cyall 2moz loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Edit Delete Block IP : (195.188.152.14)   Pe Pe @ 22:12 | May 16th 2004| permalink  There was a cd left @ theatre group tonight... anyone leave a cd? Keane or something?   It's in the car, safe and sound   Lets me know  email | website      Edit Delete Block IP : (82.37.56.118)   P-Nut @ 7:20 | May 17th 2004| permalink  I don't like this new layout, I prefered the old new layout, the one before this... This one's too... rubbish   Any thoughts, peeps?  email | website      Edit Delete Block IP : (82.37.81.167)   Ern @ 9:12 | May 17th 2004| permalink  Yes.. tht CD is kats, i sed i put it on side 4 her but she obviously wasnt listening.. Silly kat! Lol  email | website      Edit Delete Block IP : (82.37.81.167)   Ern @ 9:13 | May 17th 2004| permalink  this layout if gd!!!   email | website      Edit Delete Block IP : (213.122.175.73)   Eleanor @ 16:08 | May 18th 2004| permalink  quite like the layout its good colours . . . i am shattered 2day! think it was coz i did loadsa athletcis yesterday  hows peeps? well done pnut u got bak online! finally! whoo!  ok i gotta go now cyall sunday loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Edit Delete Block IP : (82.37.81.167)   Ern @ 10:48 | May 21st 2004| permalink  Well.. im sitting at home, while all u ppl r at school or work.. Aww shame  LOL .. well... drama shud b fun... o btw... 2 ppl from drama r going out.. can u all guess hu ? 1st person 2 com up 2 me and tell me wins.. Hmm.. a sweet ?!  email | website      Edit Delete Block IP : (195.188.152.16)   Pe Pe @ 18:04 | May 22nd 2004| permalink  Er... Me and Lynn   ( ? )   Idiot boy...  email | website      Edit Delete Block IP : (82.37.81.167)   Ern @ 21:13 | May 22nd 2004| permalink  Lol nope... haha u rong.. well u 2 r going out .. but guess hu jus started going out last week  AAahhahahaa   email | website      Edit Delete Block IP : (213.122.130.46)   Eleanor @ 14:19 | May 23rd 2004| permalink  Kat and Tom - started goin out last week! haha i know! just finished D of E absolutely shattered! MASSIVE whopoff blisters on my heels and soles of feet! gotta go cyall later loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Edit Delete Block IP : (217.33.74.20)   Shellmi @ 9:33 | May 25th 2004| permalink  It was obvious it was going to happen...what a sweet couple they make! Any who, hello! I'm soooo bored..anyone want to do my exams for me this week? I've only got 2 sociology tomorrow and 3 psychology on thursday..not many so come one, someone be nice and do them for me??? Please? :s  email | website      Edit Delete Block IP : (81.131.229.133)   Eleanor @ 16:19 | May 25th 2004| permalink  sorry shell don't think anyone would WANT to volunteer 2 do ur exams! Good luck anyway! hows every1? i still hav several blisters including one whopoff one but it will have to get better soon! coz we r goin 2 france in 2 WEEKS (or somethin like that) hehehe cant wait. cyall soon loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Edit Delete Block IP : (82.37.81.167)   Ern @ 9:40 | May 26th 2004| permalink  well well well.. thts 1 exam down.. and i feel i did gr8 (think and hope) didnt miss 1 question neway! so all i need 2 do is Relax until the 8th june  aaaaaah ... Wew!.. o btw.. hi all   email | website      Edit Delete Block IP : (81.131.210.103)   Eleanor @ 18:01 | May 26th 2004| permalink  hiya peeps! hope u do well in ur exams ern n shell n kt an every1 else 2. hehehe goin 2 france v v soon! lol cyall soon loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Edit Delete Block IP : (213.122.6.92)   Eleanor @ 15:18 | May 27th 2004| permalink  lynnie were u in tescos on wednesday night? i think i saw u in the alcohol section  hehe hows peeps? cant w8 till half term!? whoo! last ever friends 2moro  but big brother starts again  wahey cyall soon loadsa luv eleanor x x   email | website      Edit Delete Block IP : (213.122.1.40)   Eleanor @ 20:19 | May 31st 2004| permalink  where the blob is every1? cmon peeps get online or i mite b forced 2 leave hundreds of messages of . . me talkin 2 myself basically. come on!!!!!!!! hope every1 has good holidays . . luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Edit Delete Block IP : (213.122.1.40)   Eleanor @ 20:22 | May 31st 2004| permalink  OMG CaSuAlTy this weekend!!!!!! how scary but how GOOD? i know i know i am sad but I love that programme. . .. on another note I went 2 c The Day After Tomorrow on Saturday . . .  awesome film but HORRIBLE (i enjoyed it but it was SCARY ) o well i would c it again tho . shows how mad my brain is  there i go again, blabbering  hope u hav fun . . . this week . . . cyall soon loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Edit Delete Block IP : (213.122.214.157)   Eleanor @ 13:31 | June 6th 2004| permalink  where the blob is every1? i know it is half term an all but hey, i managed 2 get on here! cant wait 2 c every1 (well most peeps) 2nite . . . gonna miss u next week  casualty last night . . . not as good as last weekend but i still cried hehehe  incase u cant guess casualty is my faveist programme in the world. apart from friends. and neighbours. but hey . . . . moving on going to france next saturday!! whoo! cant wait. gotta go now but hope 2 cyall soon laodsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Edit Delete Block IP : (82.37.81.252)   Ern @ 6:49 | June 9th 2004| permalink  Who on earth in their right mind is up @ this hour... Lol Most ppl ? :S Eurgh, going in 2 school 2day exam  (dt) BORING Lol Mer  email | website      Edit Delete Block IP : (213.122.6.109)   Eleanor @ 13:24 | June 11th 2004| permalink  wwwwwhhhhhhhoooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  email | website      Edit Delete Block IP : (213.122.6.109)   Eleanor @ 13:24 | June 11th 2004| permalink  hiya peeps in case u couldnt tell i am excited! wahey! we are off 2 france 2moro so good luck peeps in exams an all ...cyall really soon loadsa luv eleanor x x x  email | website      Edit Delete Block IP : (213.122.123.227)   Eleanor @ 9:17 | June 12th 2004| permalink  hehehe 4 hours 2 go! Cyall next week loadsa luv eleanor x x xx  email | website      Edit Delete Block IP : (213.122.38.212)   Eleanor @ 15:18 | June 20th 2004| permalink  i cant believe no1 has been on since AGES! bak from france, cyall lata luv ele x  email | website      
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Blogger.com have finally seen sense and allow comments to be made as part of a Blog, as opposed to making us link to a separate site  fantastic  There should be a comments bit at the bottom of posts from now on, so I shall delete the off-site comments thing  From Lonely Paul Cause Lynn's on holiday in Yorkshire without him :-( 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        I've deleted lots of the old comments links to the pop-up, off-site comments thing we've used for ages... Just to re-iterate, you can now use the comments link built in to the Blog, found at the bottom of each post     GET COMMENTING!!! honestly, give em a holiday, they go all lazy on you *sigh*     Lynn's back from holiday today... "Woo hoo!" as Eleanor would say!     Anyways I'm off now 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>