<Blog>




<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       1. Name? Devin Nicole 2. Are you named after anyone? Yes, but I don't know who 3. Do you wish on stars? Sometimes.. rarely seriously..  4. Which finger is your favorite? Um.. none.. 5. When did you last cry? Few days ago.. 6. Do you like your handwriting? Sure.. not to bad 7. What is your favorite lunchmeat? Um.. I likes lots..  8. Any bad habits! Yesh.. 9. What is your most embarrassing CD on the shelf. No clue.. 10. If you were another person, would you be friends with YOU? Sure.. 11. Are you a daredevil? Depends 12. Have you ever told a secret you swore not to tell? I'm sure I have I don't remember though.. 13. Do looks matter? Yes, and no 14. Have you ever misused a word and it sounded absolutely stupid? most likely.. 15. You think there is a pot of gold at the end of the rainbow? Always, if you know which rainbow to follow 16. Do fish have feelings? Fishy fish? 17. Are you trendy? No, and it doesn't bother me one bit ^.^ 18. How do you release? Writing, crying, climbing on my roof 19. Where are your second homes? Di, Truley, and Mahdis' house.. the stables ANY stable! 20. Do you trust others easily? No. Definetly not..  21. What was your favorite toy as a child? Um.. I dunno..  22. What class in school do you think is totally useless? Hm.. Communications was stupid.. Newspaper was good though 23. Do you have a journal? Yep 24. Do you use sarcasm a lot? Who me? Why.. I never.. 25. Have you ever been in a mosh pit? No.. 26. What do you look for in a boy/girl? Like Dap said, someone I can be myself around and that can be themselves around me. 27. What are your nicknames? ... 28 Ever bungee jump? Not yet! 29. Do You untie your shoes when you take them off? Rarely 30. Do you think that you are strong? Physically or mentally?  31. Whats your favorite Ice Cream Flavor? Hm.. chocolate! 32. What's your favorite color? Two.. midnight blue and silver! 33. What is your least favorite food? Um.. 34. How many wisdom teeth do you have? I don't know..  35. Are you in love with anyone? Love is silly.. 36. How many people have a crush on you right now? Psh.. I don't know.. one? 37. Who do you miss most right now? I miss a few people.. 38. Do you want everyone you send this to, to send it back? Journal.. 39. What color pants are you wearing? Black 40. What are you listening to right now? *listens* crickets.. the keyboard  41. What are the last four digits of your phone number? 8897  42. What was the last thing you ate? um.. a cookie!  43. If you were a crayon, what color would you be? I wouldn't be a crayon.. I'd be a marker!  44. How is the weather right now? cloudy bwee! 45. Who is the last person you talked to on the phone? Otis 46. First thing you notice about the opposite sex? Eyes..   47. Do you like the person who sent this to you? Stole it from Daph.. she's my friend! *hugs Dap* 48. How are you today? Okay.. 49. Favorite drink? Dr. Pepper 50. Favorite alcoholic? I want to try Death by Chocolate. sounds delicous! 51. Favorite sports? Horseback riding! Which is a sport.. *glare* 52. Hair color? Blonde-ish  53. Eye color? Green-ish  54. Do you wear contacts? Nopers  55. What would you change about you? Um.. I dunno..  56. Would you like to be rich and have no friends or the opposite? Friends and have no rich? That makes no sense.. 57. Favorite food? Food is yummy.  58. Last movies you watched? Spiderman  59. Fave song at the moment? No clue.. 60. Are you too shy to ask someone out? No comment.  61. Scary movies or happy endings? Oooh.. hard one..  62. Summer or winter? Winter!  63. Hugs or kisses? Both! ~.^ 64. Relationships or one-night stands? Relationships 65. Do you fancy anyone at the moment? Yesh! 66. Who is most likely to respond? Um.. I don't know.. 67. Who is least likely to respond? Don't know that either  68. What books are you reading? I finished Star Scrolls 69. Girls: thongs or pants? ... 70. guys: boxers or briefs? ...  71. Favorite board game? Don't really have one.. 72. What did you watch on TV last night? the weather.. it was rainy..  73. What are your favourite smells? Mmm.. cookies.. 74. What is the first thing you think of when you wake up in da morning? Why can't I go back to sleep.. 75. Wouldn't it be nice if whenever we messed up our lives we could simply press 'Ctrl Alt Delete' and start all over? No! That takes all the fun out of it.. 76. Ever do one night stands? No.. that's bad.. 77. Whats your fav choccie? Choccie?   78. If you were famous who would you be? Myself! 79. DO NOT WRITE IN THIS BOX [ *poke* bawhawhawhaw!]   
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Bwee! 
    
    
</post>




</Blog>