<Blog>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      CLASS OF LOST KIDS...  Melanie Barnes La Trobe Secondary College, Macleod  February 23rd 2004  To the representative for the SRC Dear sir/madam,  Hello my name is Melanie Barnes and I am a currently a student at La Trobe Secondary College. I am writing to you to address the issue of increased absenteeism within our school. After recently reading an article published by the Herald Sun I think it is about time we do something to tackle this growing problem. Although I do believe truancy and absenteeism is a fairly global issue I do believe that there are a few things that we can do in this school to try and improve the situation.  As a student myself, I understand the struggle it can be sometimes to get out of bed in the morning and come to a place that you don’t want to be at. Because a vast majority of the students don’t enjoy being here I think that a few major changes need to be made to class curriculum. Certain classes I’m sure are attended more frequently than others. This is because they capture that child’s interests. I believe that if we make the other classes catch the child’s interests they will attend these regularly as well.  Seems students are young they don’t understand how important these years are and if they can find something better to do than go to school they will.  That’s why I believe we need to add some variety to the curriculum and make it more interesting. It becomes a problem because we constantly do the same thing “year in year out”. We go to school sit in a classroom and half the time our subject matters overlap and it appears useless to be at school, as well as boring so hopefully adding some variety will lower truancy numbers and help improve attendance but it might just be the wake up call that parents need.  As the Herald Sun Article suggests, parent's disciplinary actions are softening. They are putting petty things such as family shopping trips in front of their child’s schooling, not knowing the impact it is having. The softening attitudes are leading to the children taking more “sickies” than truly necessary. This also comes under parents letting their children sleep in then giving them the day off because of this. I think that maybe for the parents to realise what they are doing as Shadow Education Minister Victor Parton suggests, maybe their child welfare payments need to be reduced for those that cannot get their child to school frequently enough.  To take another angle on in maybe our recording mechanisms need to be looked at as well. Our current systems record the absenteeism rate of our students but it doesn’t look at why. I think that the reasons for the child being away needs to be categorised and then recorded to enable a calculation at the end of each term and/or semester. After this a decision needs to be made to whether parents need to be contacted or the child requires special provision.  Well I thank you for taking the time to read my opinions and I hope that for future refrences for problems in this area you will take my ideas into consideration.  Respectfully, Melanie Banes 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      STOLEN   Anne was a very young child when she was stolen. She is put into a children’s home but doesn’t remain there long as she is “chosen” and adopted into a white family. Anne grows up not remembering her past before her new family until one day as a teen she is told by her white parents that she is aboriginal. This sends Anne into a confused struggle for her identity. Is she black or is he white?  	Unlike the other characters in stolen Anne has grown up being educated and well looked after. In all the scenes where the others are standing reminiscing their losses and troubles Anne exclaims on her material benefits. Anne is left very confused in the line up scenes as she doesn’t remember the home and is frequently ignored in her questions of reason “But why?”  	Anne’s good fortune for being chosen is represented in the book by a white doll that she receives from her white adoptive parents. The doll symbolises a new beginning, a new life with a sense of security, a good education and a good “white” upbringing.  	Although Anne doesn’t suffer from the loss of her family throughout her childhood after discovering that her true heritage is aboriginal she becomes confused with who she is and she loses the identity that she had become.  	In scenes such as “ to tan or not to tan” and “ Am I black or white” we see her struggle with the concepts of being both black and white. In “to tan or not to tan” her troubles are portrayed more as a joke. As she pulls at her milky white skin laughing at the fact she lays there smothered in coconut oil attempting to tan when she is black. That is until the end where the reality of her situation sets in.  	Both families escalate her problems as the pressure of making a decision between the two in “ Am I black or white”. In this scene it also shows her lack of understanding of her aboriginal family. She expects them to be more “at one with the land” as she puts it and is rather disappointed to find that they are all crowded in to a commission flat.  	“Am I black or white” is a scene that truly documents the pressures she is emplaced with as both families lay a guilt trip on her. Both want he to be with them and both make her feel that she has to earn her place as a part of the family,. It also gives off the impression that she is surrounded with people that want her love but she is somehow left feeling alone as the two families trap her both screaming the exact same thing at her.  	 All throughout Anne’s life her white adoptive parents have told her that she is special because they chose her, however in this she is frequently reminded that she should feel privileged as she is and should feel lucky and grateful to them for all that they have done for her  Again in “Am I black or white” we get the feeling that the white family feels she should be appreciative as the mother bellows that she’s given Anne everything and to leave would be breaking their hearts, The father is much more straightforward, questioning Anne’s appreciation and telling her that if she goes to her aboriginal family he wont take her back in. 	            The whites also bring shame to Anne for being Aboriginal in “Anne’s told she is aboriginal” It is clear that they kept it from her but in saying that no one need ever know and that she only has to see her mum once they show that they are ashamed of her being aboriginal and they treat it as if it can easily be ignored.   Although Anne is deeply affected by all of this her hopes seem to rely on the chance that two families will learn to get along and she can live being both black and white. However deep down she knows this cannot ever happen. We see this directly as she addresses the audience in Anne’s scene and maturely tackles the problem. She is left still not quite knowing who she is, still struggling for her identity but she has grown enough to realise that she is lucky enough to have two families, and smart enough to love them both. And to live as Anne, whether that is being black or white.    
     

    
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hi peoples I'm going to be posting bits n peices of my english work here so...  RED DEATH  From the moment the keys were thrown away, one shy woman began to feel intimidated, a cold shiver ran up the inside of her spine. As this awkwardness grew inside her, she tried to tell others only to have them sneer at her pathetic insecurities… after. All what was there to worry about when Red Death was outside… 	As they all rejoiced in escaping red deaths wrath, the celebrations continued long into the nights. As Prince Prospero and his thousand-man army enjoyed their women, wine and entertainment the shy woman wondered through the crowd, and as she watched everyones joy and sense of victory, a smirk emerged on her face. 	During these parties, she kept a close eye on the Prince. Her passion towards him growing by the day. As much as she loathed his confidence and sureness, she was drawn in by the power of his handsomeness and his courage. Shy envied the object of his affections Lady Amelia,  she watched her as she ever so gracefully flirted with him, but pulled away drawing him in more every time and kept thinking that it should be her. 	Weeks passed and the celebrations continued, incessant laughter spread through the castle. With the prince as their leader, they had all survived and red death was all but forgotten in their drunken nightly escapades.  The shy girl had remained unheard and unseen especially by the prince. Nightly as everyone slept, she would sit in her room gazing out at the night sky and wait. 	One morning everyone in the castle all awoke to quite a scuffle. And like a little herd of school children everyone including the shy girl followed the crowd to this magnificent elegant ballroom. There stood Prince Prospero on top of the main feasting table with a massive smile upon his face. He took a deep breath and the enormous crowd did with him. “In three weeks it is the anniversary of my great mother Queen Sylvias death and since no one had entered this castle before us after the devastating tragedy in three weeks we will have her wake and celebrate my mother’s term as queen. On this day I will also officially take my seat in the royal throne and become King Prospero” bellowed Prince prospero  Shouts and cheers of glory came flooding through the crowd the excitement began to stir. Prince Prospero continued “To celebrate we are going to have a masked ball in this very ballroom” Ooooohs and aaaaaaaahs emerged from the guests as their eyes circulated the ever-elegant ballroom. Chandeliers filled with crystal and gold encrusted hung from the rafters. 	As the prince dismissed the eager crowd conversations about what they were going to wear, shoes make up and hair began amongst the females. There were two that were looking forward to it most of all though. Lady Amelia and the very shy woman, both in the back of their minds thinking that it was the night they were going to make the Prince theirs.  PART 2 RED DEATH PART 2- THE MASKED BALL  Anticipations were growing, the ball was to be tomorrow night. In his room the prince was trying on his custom made outfit and enjoying a glass of chardonnay when he heard a shriek from down the corridor. 	 The prince sent a few of his men to investigate and as the men neared the area which the scream was coming from they gasped in shock and hurriedly ran back to the prince. Trying to explain the men couldn’t speak, as they stuttered and fell over their words the prince became frustrated “worthless fools” he exclaimed and went to see for himself. As he approached the room he slowed his footsteps, creeping the door open he turned to see a blood covered wall engraved in which was his name. The Prince fainted. Aware that what he saw could not possibly be true, was the Red Death here? 	When the Prince came to the blood on the wall was gone without a trace, the men tried to comfort him but they thought him a little delusional because the name they saw engraved in the wall was not the Princes but the deceased Queen Sylvia. After hearing this news the Prince started to panic. He tossed and turned in his four post bed all night. Could his dead mother still be here? Is the castle really haunted or is she here only to plague revenge on her assassinator? He rested his eyes but slept with one eye open all night. 	 	 In a midst of all the confusion in the middle of the night the shy girl had began wondering around the castle in search of something special. The Queens Old room. As she crept around she finally found two massive big doors that she hadn’t noticed before, she had found it, the room the Queen was assassinated in. Marvelled by the beauty the shy girl found the room just as it had been left, beautiful covered in jewels, but as she wandered near the Queens bed she gasped. Here on the bed lie the most magnificent ruby she had ever seen. Set in a heart shaped necklace she picked it up and placed it around her neck. “He’s sure to notice me now” she exclaimed as she looked at her reflection in the mirror. Just as she placed it around her neck she heard a shriek from down the corridor, she ignored it and continued marvelling at her reflection in the mirror. Hurriedly she scurried back to her room with a brilliant glowing smile upon her face. 	The next morning the castle was a buzz with the news of the night before. Many were worried it signalled the return of their all but forgotten red death  but both the shy girl and Lady Amelia had other things on their mind and were laughing and joking in their anticipation for the ball. Both had devised plans to capture the Prince’s heart. The shy girl only hoping that the red gem, as she had appropriately named it the hope ruby would help her in her endeavours.  RED DEATH – PART 3  The night was approaching quickly, and everyone was getting done up in their elegant gowns. The shy girl had an elegant crimson and black number, just perfect to match the beautiful gem she was wearing around her neck. Lady Amelia was covered by diamonds and wearing a gorgeous gold dress to suit the occasion.  	Everyone gathered in the dining room. Lady Amelia determined to have all the attention wandered in fashionably late. As she entered the room everyone’s head turned, including the prince. She was surrounded by a circle of admirers, the shy girl who had been ignored up until this point decided to remake her entrance, full of confidence. With the hope ruby on display she gracefully entered the ballroom. This time however she did get a reaction, gasps of shock and amazement at her beauty arose from the crowd and the Prince. Who was this young beauty and why had he never noticed her before.  	Well Amelia didn’t like this, how dare this unknown character take away her limelight, she pushed through the crowd eager to see who it was. When she got to the front she stopped dead in her tracks for this beautiful girl was none other than her little sister, Jacinta. And as Jacinta noticed the look of surprised the very same smirk come about her face as did the very first night in the castle. 	Amelia was the really jealous type, she noticed the red ruby around her sister’s neck and recognised it as the one she saw lying on the queen’s bed. Knowing that she could not say that she two had been in the queen’s room to see this she ever so sarcastically asked Jacinta where she could have got such a gorgeous piece of jewellery.  With an ease of confidence about her she said that it had belonged to her mother, their mother and she had found it beside her after she died of the Red Death. 	Amelia without thinking questioned this, accusing Jacinta of stealing it from the queen’s room. At this remark everyone stopped and turned to face the bickering siblings. The prince stepped forward to try and sort out this dilemma between the two only to be knocked out of the way as Amelia flew at her little sister. “You were always the ugly one how dare you try and ruin my night” Amelia screamed. As she got nearer to her sister she flung out her arms in hope of stealing the hope ruby. Jacinta full of rage screamed, it was a scream that could have trembled the castle walls and as she did this the crowd gasped, as a ray of light shone from the ruby placing the entire kingdom in a trance it directed itself towards Amelia. Amelia began to laugh, louder and louder “you don’t know what your doing Sis you have no idea” She chuckled as Jacinta continued to scream.  They collapsed. Slowly but surely Jacinta again began to rise. Amelia was left on the floor, drowning in her own blood just as red death had left so many others. The frightened crowd new nothing to what was going on. Suddenly still with the ruby around her neck Sylvia raised off the ground. “you don’t deserve him skank’ she seemed to scream in her own voice but her eyes began to turn red and the next time she spoke it was loud, it was furious and her eyes lit up like they were on fire. “I’m back” said the voice with a giggle the prince immediately knew what was going on. “You thought you had gotten rid of me didn’t you son” and there was another giggle. At these words the prince himself became furious. His mother, in Jacinta’s body was trying to reap revenge on him as she had tried to on the whole prospero kingdom. Grabbing the nearest thing he could find, a candelabra. Jacinta / Sylvia looked up at him rather oddly and in this brief moment he took a chance and threw it at her, aiming at the necklace.  	Time almost seemed to freeze as it travelled along in the air, everyone sat there mouths open and as it connected they all gasped. But it didn’t connect with the ruby, He missed, it hit the possessed Jacinta straight in the head. The prince saw the opportunity and took it lunging at her. The two tackled on the ground for a while until the ruby began dislodged and slid across the dining room floor. No- one knew what to do. The queen began to scream out “ it is me your queen my son here murdered me to take the throne please protect that stone it is all that keeps me here today”  The prince counteracted this screaming back “ don’t you see that she is the red death, the stone is anyway haven’t you noticed it had not taken any lives until my mother and this stone re-emerged” the crowd stood there bewildered until a third plea, one that they had not expected emerged. It was the voice of young Jacinta pleading for help.  As both the crowd and Jacinta, well the Queen   seemed to be paralysed the prince dived towards the ruby and swung at it. He smashed that beautiful gem into thousands of little pieces. Releasing the spell on Jacinta and destroying what was left on both his mother and the Red Death. He ran up to Jacinta who was lying on the floor, drained checking to see if she was fine. But as he looked at her, and gradually at everyone else in the room he saw blood leaking out of ears, eyes and noses of everyone, and as the fear began to run through him he reached up and touched his nose. It was bleeding.    
     

    
</post>

<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      DESCANSOS – THE ROBBERY 	 Never shall I forget that cold shiver that ran down my spine the moment we pulled in the drive or the absolute fear of what was to come. I will never forget my innocence and young confusion. Why would anyone do this?  Still in my head I can picture the house.I can clearly remember my first steps inside and how it all felt like a movie. I guess it hasn’t been until almost this moment that I have forced myself to look upon this in any other way than how it is in my memory. I can now see the dramatic impact that this event had on not only me but my entire family’s life. 	 A lot of questions arose that day. How could you be robbed in broad daylight in the middle of the afternoon on a main street? What reasons did they have not to take our main appliances the Nintendo the TV? Why had they targeted my mums one – off jewellery? That day influenced a lot of change. It was the first time I had heard slanderous comments from my father towards my mother, the first time I had understood secrets may lie beneath my family’s surface and it was probably among one of the first times I questioned the way the world worked. But the irony lies in my original reaction. “Shit my CD players gone”  That year was a fairly miserable one. Two days after Christmas all my presents were stolen, along with my sense of security. My first CD player was a big deal. My friend since birth, god sister, and best mate and I had received the same one. I had played with hers but was not yet to put a CD in mine, and it was gone. I was devastated, shattered as all my jewellery and my expensive materialistic items were gone. I was too young and naïve to see the big picture though, my real loss. My sense of security.  I can still remember how cold that first night was. A chilly breeze glided through the house as our front door was broken and refused not only to lock but to even shut. I remember not being able to sleep properly. I remember awakening only to the screeching of angry adult voices …my parents, well my mum and stepfather they were angry, but not at the fact we had been robbed. They were angry with each other!  The screaming and yelling I heard during these nights will stay in my memories forever. I honestly thought that they were going to break up and I would be left again with my mother.  The time was odd. The police believed that it was the arrival of my father and I that had warned the burglars away. But I myself didn’t like that idea, for it meant that they were there when I was a very chilling thought.  The absence of my logical thinking was clearly present at the time. I couldn’t even remember the police phone number. And yet it was on the damn phone, as a big sticker. I remember searching through my room, happy that most of my stuff remained. My TV was there, my “treasures of the earth gem collection” remained but more importantly my new CD’S. Only now I had nothing to play them in.  Although at the time it was a fairly traumatic experience, a lot of good things did arise from the situation. Over the following few months it appeared that  Mum and Dad resolved some issued that they had seemingly been hiding from each other for quite some time. My sister and I became closer as we were forced to move house and share a room. Even though we were at each others throats all the time I know that our bond grew. 	 And I guess I was forced to grow up. I had to be strong as it seemed everything and everyone around me was falling apart. But maybe the most relevant thing to me at the time that changed was that I filled my ever since birth, kind of god sister and really good friend with absolute envy. I had received a new CD player. It had a three disc spin and it was better than hers. And I could play with it whenever I wanted. 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ok i understand that for alot of people this will not make much sense, it is afterall my memories but anyway here you are.  I REMEMBER  I remember the very first day I came to school with last years year 12’s gone. Our spot felt so empty. After a few shed tears I took a look around at the graffiti they left behind and thought the year through. I remember when Leigh and Gene wrote a song about Muniur to the tune of an old Tupac song and how we made them sing it over and over till we were almost in tears of laughter. I remember the day me & john were trying to light our cigarettes. It was windy and the flame wouldn’t light. Everyone was screaming our name, we were ignoring them because we just wanted to get them lit. We ended up looking up, just to see Mr McMahon’s face glaring at us.  No- one would let it go. We were picked on for weeks. I remember all the birthdays and the time it took us to the money for all of the presents, not to even mention the parties. But there was a new pain in the arse every month. I remember each and every one of us chucking our guts up at one time or another. The pats on the back and holding each others hair back. I remember those evil passion pop bottles and us doing somersaults in Kayla’s spa. I remember Kimbo almost falling asleep on the pool cue, Kayla’s exorcist style chunder, Beck almost electrocuting all of us, Brizzy always thinking she knows best, Sideshow beck, sophisticated mama, enemy, fresh and the list goes on. They are all classic people and classic moments.  I remember everyone at my debutante ball in the middle of the dance floor jumping up and down to Khe Sahn only to have the clips on my dress undo and the whole front of my dress to fall down. I remember all of us in our drunken glory and some of the surprising hook-ups.  I remember Inverloch , I’m not even going to go into that one but I remember that no matter what we were doing it was always a blast. I remember how much fun school was each and everyday.  I remember the good times, I try to forget the bad but I do know that life goes on. It almost feels like the end of an era, but it’s ok. I don’t see them all as much and school sucks now but I will always have my memories and I will never forget. 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      As part of our year 12 coursework we are required to analyse a current issue in the world. our teacher Mrs Blakey has chosen the GBH issue for us to tackle. This is an analysis of a few articles we had to tackle.  ARTICLE ANALYSIS - GBH MELANIE BARNES  The issue of whether rave parties should be banned has been in circulating in the media because of recent overdoses on the illicit drug GBH at Two Tribes. Three articles that directly address this issue are “ We can’t rant about Raves “,  “ call for dance party ban rejected and “one in five try killer drug GBH” which were all published in the herald Sun the week following two tribes. In an article entitled “ We can’t rant about raves.” Jim Stynes argues that banning these major rave parties will only earn the Government a pat on the back and will stop us even prevent this problem from happening. He believes to attack the problem we need to focus on the reason people take these drugs, and what they need to gain motivation to live in their lives. To support this view Stynes points out that at rave parties there is medical care but at other smaller parties in which these people will be forced to attend in substitution of raves there is not, and time is everything with overdoses the medical attention provided could be a matter of life and death.  Stynes clearly supports rave parties. He says that he witnessed 20,000 people escaping their lives to come together and enjoy the music saying that raves are an almost tribal experience where people of varying backgrounds can feel a part of something greater, like they belong.  In separating the GBH problem from the rave party scent Jim Stynes does Stynes does not deny the problem of GBH needs to be dealt with. He makes it clear that the government needs to identify the real reasons young people are taking these drugs and take actions to tackle these problems. Stynes effectively argues that understanding the underlying issues in our young peoples lives is key. Saying that to adopt the approach of harm minimalisation, it is vital to understand what our young are thinking and feeling. He backs this up saying that it is inevitable that many young people will experiment with drugs but that those who do it on a regular basis must be missing something in their lives and that this is where we need to put our focus.  He states that it is not the time to hide from the problem. Stynes as the co-founder of the Reach Foundation has worked a lot with young people and obviously cares for their well-being. He has insight into the problems these young people have that cause them to resort to drugs. Thus resulting in him believing that we need to make sure young people healthy enough to make the right choices. In another contrasting article “ Call for dance party ban rejected” Christine Caulfield takes quite an apposing view. She presents the argument that rave parties encourage young people to take drugs. Caulfield uses the example of Mr Brooker who lost his best friend to drugs to demonstrate that there is a case to shut down these rave parties. What Caulfield fails to mention is that the people that suffer from drug overdose are a vast minority. Only 10 out of a massive 20,000 ravers suffered overdoses while the rest went about having a great night. In another article entitled “one in five try killer drug GHB” Patrick O’Neil and Christine Caulfield once again tackle this hotly debated issue. Despite the misleading headline the duo make a solid argument that shutting down rave parties would harbour devastating consequences as it would only drive the problem underground. To support these views they spoke to earth core coordinator Pip Darvall and the director of the harrowing dance drug movie “One Perfect day” Paul Currie. Pip darvall questions what happened to a draft version of “A Guide to running safe rave Parties” stating that running safe rave parties is a better solution is a better solution to shutting them down entirely. This article also aims to raise awareness in young people in the dangers of GBH, as does Paul Currie’s movie “One Perfect Day” Mr Currie said that the recent two tribes Speculation affirmed the films importance and he hoped it lifted the lid on what was really going on. The article also distributed some useful information about GBH. Although most people do know that GBH is a clear odourless liquid not many know that it is often distributed in clear sachets in a variety of bright colours to increase its appeal among young users. Paul Currie believes we need to bring all the facts into the limelight. Overall all the articles present strong views against the problems of drug use and concern about the impact of GBH. However they do have different views against what action needs to be taken to prevent further drug overdoses. I strongly believe that demonizing rave culture is not the answer and that no matter who may be right or wrong action needs to be taken.  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      FEELING POEMS - THE THINGS THEY CARRIED  TIM O’BRIEN ON THE RAINY RIVER – SHAME  Shame  Sounds like a silent howl Smells like blood soiled pig flesh Tastes like greasy pig stink in my throat. Feels like fear spreading inside me like weeds Feels like the whole worlds squeezing in tight It’s my smouldering self pity I don’t want to fight Shame  LT JIMMY CROSS THE THINGS THEY CARRIED - GUILT  Guilt Sounds like absolute silence, then wind, then sunlight, then voices Smells like ashes of a burnt photograph Tastes like a dead mans dope Feels like dead weight Feels like hating someone you love Feels like a story with no moral Guilt  LT JIMMY CROSS LOVE – LOVE   Love Sounds like a gunshot that killed Bonnie & Clyde Smells like a burnt photograph Tastes like lingering memories Feels like that legs of a virgin Feels like hope that’s never going to die Feels like he still loves her Love  TIM O’BRIEN  FEAR   Fear  Sounds like ridicule and sensor Smells like blood and hog stink Tastes like greasy pig stink in my throat Feels like a kind of schizophrenia Feels like losing the respect of my parents Feels like physical Rapture Fear MARK FOSSIE LOVE – SWEETHEART OF THE SONG TRA BONG  Love  Sounds like it’s not crazy, it really happens Smells like Darvon dreams Tastes like nothing Feels like I’ve never been better in my whole life Feels like I cant find her Feels like I cant let her go like that Love  TIM O’BRIEN TERROR   Terror Sounds like my mothers voice calling out "Run!" (p44) Smells like vomit (p44) Tastes bitter (p45) Feels like loosing the respect of my parents (p43) Feels like walking away from my own life (p43) Feels like weeds spreading inside of me (p45) Terror   KATHLEEN O’BRIEN INNOCENCE   Innocence Sounds like "did you ever kill anybody?" Smells like "...God I don't know what. It smells rotten" Tastes like the exotic foods Feels like "what did you want?" Feels like "you’re pretty weird" Feels like "I hope you’re having fun" Innocence   RAT KILEY LONGING  Longing Sounds like the sound. You need to get a consistent sound  Smells like one more animal Tastes like nothing a war Feels like he’d slept with four girls, one night Feels like I saw it man Feels like no lie Longing   MARK FOSSIE LOSS – SWEETHEART OF THE SONG TRA BONG  Loss Sounds Like “Please not a word” Smells like freshly shampooed hair Tastes like a bittersweet kiss Feels like she’s here but so far away Feels like something tentative and false Feels like she’s lost Loss 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      QUEEN OF THE CATTLE MARKET   Q1) Explain the impact of the headline on and photograph on the reader. How is this meant to influence our view of pageants?   The headline is one that automatically gets us intrigued. I think it is meant so as we see Ms Hawkins as a rather animal on show, purely a piece of meat.    Q2) What is Robin Riley’s main contention?  To argue that beauty pageants send a bad message out to the public that you have to be beautiful to be successful. And that beauty pageant are a sexually driven waste of time.   Q3) List the words and phrases that she uses to support her anti-pageant view?  -	“That’s basically all they are, window dressing” -	 Cattle markets -	 Meaningless title and a useless crown -	“It was all about looks” -	 Exploitative -	“Heretical display of exploitation and decadence”  	 Q4) Explain how the words and phrases help her convey her view. What is the tone? What issues does she highlight?  The tone of the article is rather satirical. With comments relating to other peoples opinions being rather sarcastic and the overall put downs towards these people she seems rather argumentative with her view She highlights the past contestants and winners and some of their pathetically ditsy answers to a few of the questions asked. Opposing the view that pageant are not just about looks she laughs at the statement by rival contest Miss World’s in that they promised a contest about beauty with purpose. She is being critical of everything to do with beauty pageants.        Q5) Write a short response to riley supporting pageants.  Dear Ms Riley, 	After recently reading your article entitled “Queen of the cattle market” I am really disappointed with your pessimistic view towards beauty pageants.  Although I do appreciate your personal opinion I found that you actually shot yourself before you began. Stating that some people see it as harmless fun was reasonable. And you effectively argued about that but when you stepped towards freedom of choice you lost it. Freedom of choice is something as Australians that we have and you are right, she was just exercising her right. Although I do agree with you in the term that beauty pageants are pointless there are many people in the world that disagree. Some of these people even dream about winning these “cattle markets” as you like to call them. And who are we, who are you to shut these people’s dreams down. There are many other worse occupations in this world. I find that quite a few other accepted jobs in the community could be easily scoffed at too. Yours for example. You are getting paid to criticise other people in the world, criticise their decisions. Just as Donald Trump has no right to judge a woman’s beauty, I don’t believe you have the right to question their intellectual integrity. So as much as I do respect you opinion I think that laughing at these people’s dreams is not the answer.  	Melanie Barnes 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      LETTERS HOME	 TIM O’BRIEN THE THINGS THEY CARRIED  FROM THE RAINY RIVER  Dear mum and dad, 	I am sorry to be writing to you in this way. It is almost a struggle to be writing this letter and although I don’t know how you are right now I do hope everything is ok. I am staying at the tip top lodge at the moment with an old man Elroy Berdahl. He is good to me and I am fed, clothed and well.  	Before I begin I need to apologise the wrath my cowardess actions may be causing you. But I had to go. If not to run from the war to run from my life and the confined space I felt like I was trapped in. Being drafted from the war frightened me. I know it seems kind of obvious but please acknowledge the fact that this is difficult to admit to myself let alone admitting it to a few of the only people in this world that I admire. Because of this I am sorry if I have disappointed you.  	I do not understand the war at all. Infact I consider it to be rather useless. I laugh at the fact these people think they are fighting for freedom. It is all political lies and a huge cover up, for what I do not know but my beliefs lie firmly against the war. When I sleep at night I do think of those men. Fighting for their lives with no clue what they are fighting for. It saddens me and knowing that I may soon be one of these men leaves me paralysed.  	I do not know what I will do. Please do not try to contact me. I wrote this letter to you to assure you of my safety I hope you can respect me to give me my space for I need some more time. I again apologise to you for my actions and any actions that I may take in advance. I wish I could reassure you but I do not know what I will do. I may or may not write you soon. Goodbye   			Kind regards 			You son Tim O’Brien 
     

    
</post>


<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When days just dont seem right this is my peice to cheer me up. I dont qiute know why. The theme for a modern day romeo and juliet arose from a writing assignment in year 10. And hey this is what i come up with. Inspired my an ex love at the time love really sucked  A MODERN DAY ROMEO AND JULIET  A modern day Romeo and Juliet, what a joke. There will never be such a thing for is anyone in today’s “modern” selfish world, selfless enough to believe in a love that will precede life in itself and give up	all future years of aspiration for the off chance that nothing great will ever happen again because their so called “true love” is not by their side? If you ask me, or anyone else around me not caught up in the dream themselves. NO CHANCE. Love is simply overrated… just like sex. You spend you’re the  whole of your younger years looking forward to some fairytale, get to where you begin thinking about it and find yourself  in the unfortunate situation too early… then arising with the wisdom that you could only dream that you had a minor part beforehand. And before too long its all your life is revolved around… what a drag.   Yet another fairytale from your childhood that can and will be shattered in an instant. Then in less than a year your life could feel destroyed. Not knowing what direction your life is heading in, what corners will confront you or whether you make the right decision in the forks lying ahead in the road. Throughout it all in later years it is all but too depressing to reminisce those teenage years because in the years you are destined to make some of the biggest and hardest decisions of your life. You are also persuaded by the pressure that these will be your last few years of freedom. To be free from restrictions, for being either too young or too old, Too young to comprehend anything which in some form has a major significance in the world or too old with too many responsibilities. Over the phase where the world is “at your feet” And apparently by the way they react over the little things, having the weight of the world on their shoulders. Yet in theory and practice, the time of tender kisses, arising maturity and the apparently carefree and joyous times of experimentation seems to be the hardest to get through, but in the same context the most enjoyable. Which brings me back to Romeo and Juliet. Why? Why is it that in the midst of everything else going on do we have to love? To fall in love with someone who may or may not love you as deeply as they claim, but if it is, not understanding when and how you would like it placed. Again this refers back to the selfish views we, as modern civilians have today. But ask yourself are there  any other perks to “love”, is their any point in it if the only gratification we get is knowing that we love and are loved in return? I ask myself sometimes why that isn’t enough, or even sometimes why it is. But really there is no possible answer for there is no logical, mathematical, or even rational explanation to love. The only conclusion I can make is that I wish the world was all it seemed that short year ago. Happy, carefree and even in love with nature and the manufactured demise of the heavens. The world is forever changing…wish in my mind I could decide whether I like love, what love is and even if in any way I would ever want to be as stupid as  Romeo and Juliet.   
     

    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      To anyone reading all of this i warn you i am not the best writer but i do use writing to express my emotions at the time. So although sometimes i may sound like a suicidal maniac i promise you I'm am not and there is no need to stress for my wellbeing  PAIN  pain is evil,  pain is death pain is in my every breath  pain is wicked, pain is sin pain is eating me within pain is consuming it doesnt 4give  its taken away my will 2 live so leave me here & watch me rot cos then all my pain will be 4got 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      IT JUST IS  Emotionless with meaning My scars you cannot see Forever Hiding Truths Forever Hiding Me  It’s a shattered Mirror Princess without a Prince It’s a fractured fairytale It’s my Life, It’s bent  Is there any Truths Are there any lies It’s all do fucked up I'm left with no surprise  All the bruises you left I emplaced on others But is it your fault Is my life just a cover?  I wish you could fell  Really empathise But if you said you did It would be all lies  Is there an escape I don’t think so I can’t take cover  I've got nowhere to go  It’s a shattered form of life But it just is It’s where I’m at  KIDS  
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yeah hi guys thanks to adam im doing all of these weird arse test things so here it is i have a heart of gold...Thats right.oh who cares. I dont think anyone elae actually comes in here but anyways if you wanna check out adams blog it's http://jobe314.blogspot.com/    Heart of Gold    urlLink   What is Your Heart REALLY Made of?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     

    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Protector    urlLink   The ULTIMATE personality test     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     

    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i found this on a site...its really cool. Blogger is called what is simple is true... Check it out at jeff83882.blogspot.com Anyways the quote live by it Dream as if you'll live forever. Live like you'll die 2day Jeff u rock
     

    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys not much to write actually just a quick hello i do have stuff at home though that i will add here soon . So i dont know hi 2 everyone that both loves and hates this world. Love ya Melby xxx
     

    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi...um I'm just writing to give you something to write to me on. I was just reading someone else's blogger and wanted to send them a note or something and realized I couldn't. S neways I have two emails you can write to me on but I don't know which one I check more frequently. 1. melby_2@hotmail.com but beware it might take me a while. This stupid nerdy jerk we have at school has blocked all of our hotmail things so I only check this one at my boyfriends house. 2. melby@eudoramail.com Again beware I get alot of shitty spam so if u write to me here please in your topic write blogger or something cos if not I will just delete your message along with the rest of my junk. By the way if the angry guy Aaron Allen is reading this send me one you bastard. That is so I can be acknowledged as another person you can hate in this world. Well catch all love ye Melby xxx
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i know i havent added a post for ages so sorry guys. Um I guess VCE has kind of got me down um life is good and i guess i"ll write soon i have nothing new,. Dude ... i suck. Well catcha later i guess im off Luv ya all
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      MY SELFISH LOVE  I know all relationships have their ups and downs But baby I want to be sky high In the short time we have here on earth  I’m not wasting my time 2 cry If my tears shed too many times You’ll taste your own blood If you love me like you say you do  You’d do it to yourself This may seem harsh But boy it’s true It’s for our own good Cos I love you  Were struggling now It’s not okay I can feel my love Beginning to decay Times are tough It’s in your court Time 2 see what life lessons  You have been taught I wont get hurt  I refuse to cry My tears dare not be wasted You’re only a guy More people in the world Plenty more fish in the sea I’m sure ill find one  More deserving of me. 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      GONE  Yet again your gone  when i need you here My love 4 u  is full of fear fear that next time your gone its gone for good why cant i leave you when i know i should? 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I know, more quizilla crap but this stuff is reasonably accurate. I'm a cancer 2 so the whole emotional stuff is really true. Um if u do decide to visit Quizilla please see what kind of shit you are. I didnt post mine it semed kind of embarrasing. Oh Well life's good hope everyones ok 2. catcha later dude.      You are an Elementalist. Your magic stems from the forces of nature. You might be a forest nuturing Druid, a storm-creating Weather-Wizard or any of the many Elementals, but one thing is sure-- your bond with nature is strong. You can rely heavily on nature to support yourself aesthetically or physically for it lends you both comfort and strength. Your instincts rarely fail you. You are vibrantly passionate but are sometimes carried away by your own emotions.    urlLink   Which Magical Order Are You In?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey ppl ive got nothing really interesting to write but if you visit an you pleeeeeeeeeeease leave a comment i love feedback even though i already know im crap. Well luv ya all life's great. Melby xxx 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>