<Blog>

<date>28,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Elvin and I cuddled last night. It was quite nice, and we did kiss. Such a wonderful kiss it was, it made me rather hard. But, as with all things, it ended.  I am still very horny though, and I know Elvin isn't. I don't know if it is his meds or something else, but it is quite irritating.  I don't close tonight, which is rather unusual (kind of). I used to close every Saturday, and then Liz took it over, and then I got it back. And now I seem to be losing it again. I don't think it matters, Kim is giving me thirty or more hours a week.  We had a meeting today, and during it she announced the yearly bonuses. Guess what?! I got one! It was only $85 (after tax), but I can use every cent I can get.  I am continuing my research into Rihannsu (Romulan) religion. I find it very interesting, and better than most religions I have researched. I do mush prefer Rihannsu to Romulan. Romulan just sounds unflattering to me, and Rihannsu has a bit of an exotic feel. It also feels more natural and fluid. Too bad it is fictional. 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm not all that depressed anymore. I am tired, and last night I was rather pissed (bullshit at work). But, not all that depressed. That isn't to say I don't still feel depressed, I'm just not as bad as I was.  I'm really starting to wonder why Elvin isn't even slightly horny any more. He says he is still attracted to me, but I'm beginning to wonder. He was reading a book the other day, and I started to 'massage' his cock through his pants and he got moderately hard. However, he shot me this look that said 'leave me alone.' Yes, he was reading a book... but one would think somethings are more important.  We have been trying to get a church of the ground, but haven't meet with much (any) success so far. One of our stumbling blocks has been trying to find a place to meet. We may have found somewhere, though. The local YMCA has a multi-purpose room that they rent out. So, we may try that.  Well, I have to run off and get ready for work. 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm not feeling quite so depressed anymore. I'm not out of it, but I am better. I just wish Elvin wanted to cuddle more (or even at all). I know his last relationship hurt him, but I do so love to cuddle (and it cheers me up).  I am doing some research online into Shinto, and I find it very interesting. A religion without gods, as we westerners know them. I also looked up Rihannsu (Romulan) religion. I know it is fictional, but I like the way it is set up. It kind of blends with Shinto, and I may explore a combination of the two. It will probably look something like Wicca, although I really don't want that to happen.  My hours were cut a little at work, and I was first off last night. It won't mean much overall (I do close two days this week, instead of the usual three). But, every little bit counts. I have enough bills to make things hard. 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm feeling depressed. It started with closing last night, and oh was that fun. It was a really bad night, where nothing (and yes, I do mean NOTHING) went right. We got incredibly busy, but instead of being on deliveries I was fixing problems. Two deliveries got mixed up, and I spent half an hour fixing them and answering phones. I lost four or five deliveries (at least) to that. Then, almost no one was tipping (and those that were tipping only tipped ten or fifteen cense). The whole night I was hearing how I needed to go faster, how I wasn't going fast enough, how I would have to do everything on my own (i.e. they would send all my help home) if I didn't speed up. Well, hard to do my work when we are so busy I'm only in the store for a minute or two at a time.  I also don't think Elvin finds me all that attractive anymore. I will admit it could be the medication he is on, as it could have side effects like that, but I'm not sure. All I know is he doesn't want sex, and doesn't look that happy if I bring up the subject. Now, it isn't that I think sex is the most important part of the relationship, but it does make me wonder when he suddenly doesn't want it that much.  We went out yesterday to a neighboring town, called Galesburg. We went to the mall there and spent pretty much the whole time shopping. I know Elvin LOVES to shop, but I had wanted to spend the day with him (as in just the two of us). Instead we were looking for new fish, replacing a tank, getting new equipment, checking out a store or two, and going to the library. Quite frankly, we didn't get any 'us time.' That probably didn't help my current mood, as I had been looking forward to that.   I really am fighting to maintain my emotional equilibrium today. I find it hard to either not cry, or not to think very depressing thoughts. Hell, I actually thought about suicide last night. Luckily, there is something about my hardwiring that won't ever let me go through on such a thing. But, I thought it nonetheless. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I edited an old post, and discovered that it changed the date to today's. I will have to remember that in the future, and carefully read the post before I publish it.  Not much happened today. I went to work, took a nap, went online, and went back to work.   Elvin has evidently been going around and doing chores for people for money. He hadn't told me this, and didn't tell me until he had too. I trust him, but it made me wonder just how much he tells me. 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It has been four days since I last wrote, yet it seems like it was only yesterday or the day before. My sense of time is different than most peoples.  I have closed the last two days in a row, as well as working a split shift on both days. I'm tired, worn out, and feel darn near dead. But, I still can't go to sleep. They did make Megan the new Assistant Manager. Ben, my brother in-law, doesn't think it was a good decision, but I'm going to wait and see. I have only closed with her a couple of times, and I really haven't worked with her that much.  Well, Elvin read my blog and freaked out when he read the part about the guy wanting to meet me. He was so worked up that he woke me up at 5 AM, which was shortly after he read it. I can't say I remember a whole lot of our conversation, as I wasn't awake quite yet. But, he does jump to conclusions a little too much. His first reaction was that I was cheating on him, then he thought about it and changed his mind (after waking me up and yelling at me). Now, he just wants to beat up the guy. He is very protective of me. And, now he feels he must reclaim me, which involves sex evidently. Not necessarily a bad thing, but I'm not sure that is a good reason for sex. 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Even though he is mad at me, I still love him (how could I not?). I wanted to cuddle earlier, as we were both going to sleep. And, because I know he is mad at me, I'm fighting insomnia. That, and I could already tell that the caffeine from the Diet Coke I drank was going to keep me up anyway, and it helps me to go to sleep if we cuddle. He wouldn't do that, he just gave me his 'hell no' grunt and went to sleep.  He is just so cute sleeping though. Right now he is staying right on the edge of the bed, trying to keep as far away from my side as possible. He is snoring, yet he is still so cute and handsome. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I can't quite say Elvin and I had an argument, it is a bit simpler. He got mad at me. He thought I wanted to go online, and, at the time, I was only thinking about it. Instead, I changed my mind and decided to watch TV with Elvin. Well, that pissed him off. That meant he couldn't only watch what he wanted (our tastes are not exactly the same in certain areas). I tried to explain that I didn't want to use the net, but he only got more pissed. Eventually, I said I would just read a book and he could watch TV. Then he got up and said he would go downstairs. I followed him, tried to talk to him, and he just said: "Don't follow me and bitch." I asked him to come upstairs and watch TV (I haven't seen him much, and I did want to spend time with him), but he just told me (rather meanly) to leave him alone. I swear, men can be as bad as women.  I think I'm going to stay away from Excite Private Messenger for a while. I have been talking to someone, and we have occasionally cybered. But, it wasn't anything serious. Well, tonight he asks if we could meet in person. This surprised the hell out of me! He knows I'm with someone, but he still asked. I think, looking back on it, that he may have feelings for me. Quite frankly this isn't something I want to deal with right now. Hell, I only chat with him a couple of times a week as it is. Life is simply too complex sometimes.  Work is fun. I am working split shifts just about every day of the week (except for Tuesday, and that is only because I'm not available that night). I close two nights during the week, and once on the weekend.  It kind of burns me out, but I do get hours. And I also need the money. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       There isn't much to write about today. I need to go pay my computer bill, but I will do that later (in an hour or so). I was online chatting, mostly running across people wanting to cyber (which I did do a little of, I'm not going to lie). My imagination is good, and it works me up so that when Elvin does want sex, I'm ready.  Later today we are suppose to do something special. Have dinner, watch a video, I'm not sure what yet. I'm low on cash, as is he. I do have to work later, but I don't close (I switched hours with someone).  What matters is that it is Valentine's day and I'm with Him!  He is lying asleep right now, everything covered by the blanket except for his feet. He is just so cute when he sleeps, I love to watch him. I love to watch him even when he is awake. He says he isn't handsome, but he is most definitely wrong there. I just love him. I love the way he looks, the way he smells, the way he thinks. Ya, he may be hard (damn near impossible) to get to stop talking sometimes, but I love him nonetheless. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, this is my first post. Frankly, I don't have anything to write yet. In the future I will, until then... well, this is what you get. Enjoy! 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, we have spent a good amount of time cleaning the apartment. (It was part of our agreement with our landlord. We clean the apartment, and we don't pay the security deposit. It helps that we know him.) It looks so much better than before Tom (our landlord) started on it. He repainted every room, fixed problems, and all that. Then, we came in and finished by cleaning. I still need to clean the toilet, and use bleach on the bath tub, but that isn't for today.  But, that does mean we have to find furniture. That will be the fun part, considering that money is very tight right now.  I'm feeling a bit sick, it is probably (hopefully) just sinus stuff. My throat was a bit soar, and my nose is running a bit. I'm also dreadfully worn out. I'm almost kind of glad we can't make it to the dinner group tonight, I don't know if I really have the energy for it, even though Elvin won't be happy we aren't going. 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, we have an appartment now. An ex-coworker of mine owns a few buildings, and he has several openings so when he heard we were looking he told us to call him. And, long story short, we got an appartment. Money will be tight for a while, and I'm not sure just how I'm going to get all of the bills paid, but we will find a way. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I woke up with a migraine this morning, and I had to go to work today. I'm out of my medication, but it doesn't work that well anymore. It has stayed low level (well, low level to me, others who aren't use to intense pain might disagree), but it is still having a Chinese water torture effect. I just wish I wasn't getting light sensitive, and it leaves me feeling dead tired. All I want to do is take excedrine (sp?) PM and sleep for about a year.  I think Elvin and I are doing better. Yesterday he work up me, stripped me, and then we had sex. A very nice surprise.  I do wonder if there is something bothering him, though. I know his past relationship problems are still haunting him, and I wish there was something I could do. About the only thing I can do is to be there for him when he needs me, but I wish I could take a more active approach. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm not that happy with Elvin right now. I mentioned sex yesterday, and he got pissed. Well, what does he expect. A little over a month ago he just stops putting out, and shows no interest at all. I'm not supposed to wonder what is going on?! He mentions that it has to do with problems from his past relationships, but I have to wonder. We were together for one year before he suddenly stopped wanting sex. And, after one month he still doesn't want to talk about it. I can understand having a problem, but when the problem effects both of us I would like to know what is going on. He admitted that he is subconsciously trying to sabotage our relationship, but does nothing to stop from doing it. I love him, but I'm really starting to wonder what the hell is going on.  I read his blog (I have permission) and he says that I need to understand that he doesn't want to deal with this issue right now. Well, one has to wonder when he will want to. He has had one month, and still doesn't want to do anything about it. Just how long will it be until he decides it is time to do something? He needs to realize that this problem (which he won't tell me anything about) is effecting more than just him.  He also says that I talked about sex every chance I got. Well, he was wrong there. Some conversations were about sex, but not with us. (One was about a conversation I had with someone online that I found interesting.) One time I asked if anything was wrong (he was acting strange), and tells me to drop it and that he doesn't want to talk about sex. Well, I wasn't even talking about sex! I was asking if anything was wrong! He says I have sex on the brain, yet even when I'm not talking about it he thinks I am. I damned if I do, and damned if I don't.  I really do love him, but he isn't making anything easy for me. He says I need to understand his point of view, but how am I supposed to do that when he won't tell me anything? A relationship requires communication. I love him, and I want to help him. But, he won't let me. He won't even tell me what is wrong. I'm just supposed to be there and deal with the consequnces. I can understand that he wants to work this out on his own, but I would at least like to know what is going on. 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, we borrowed a DVD player from a friend of ours, and she is going to let us keep it until she moves. It was rather nice to actually watch the movies that we rent, instead of waiting for my sister and her husband to finish watching their movies.  I chickened out, and I didn't confront Kim about working tonight. Hopefully, I will get off in time to make it to our dinner group. I know Elvin will be very pissed if we miss it, and I won't be that happy either. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, for the last two nights we have tried to have a quiet movie night, and for the past two nights my sister and/or her husband ruined it. (We share a house with them, a rather bad idea.) Ben, her husband, came home yesterday with two of his friends, and they got loud, took over the living room, and invited one other person to show up. So, we got to put up with them all night. What pissed me off was that we had movies sitting out, had an empty pizza box, and it was rather obvious we had plans. But, they just took over. Then, it was darn near the same thing yesterday. Jen and Ben came home, and took over the living room. We had food coming (they were there when we ordered), and we had movies sitting out. When they got home we were watching a movie, and when it was finished they popped in a wresting tape... without asking if we were done! My sister is a rude spoiled little bitch. What really pisses me off is that they would, literally, throw a fit if we did the same thing to them. They are children in adult bodies.  I so wish we could afford to move out. But, I don't have any money saved up. Bills soak up everything. We are trying to find Elvin a job, but we haven't succeeded. So, he is thinking of reapplying for disability from social security.  Quite frankly, I don't know why they turned him down in the first place. He isn't an invalid, yet. He has rhumatoid arthritis, bipolar disorder, and probably one or two other problems. However, it is the rhumatiod that is a problem. He is still mobile, but his doctors told him he won't be in a few years. I know he hurts a lot of the time, but won't say anything. He likes to walk, but can't do it that often, because he hurts from it later.  Sometimes I just wish life were a lot easier. 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, I have just changed all of the settings so that this blog is now available to the public. I'm still not completely sure I really want to do this, but I'm sure enough to go through with it. That, and I doubt that anyone will actually read any of this. (Or, at least, not many people will.)  Someone named Danny called and left a message on the answering machine yesterday. The weird thing is, I don't know anyone named Danny. I might think it was a tele-marketer, but they don't leave local numbers. (The phone number was from a neighboring town.) I haven't called him back yet, but I'm am really curious as to who this Danny person is. The only possibility I can think of is the minister of our church gave him my number. The reason being I told him my car is dieing, and my minister said he would keep an eye out for any good deals. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Elvin wrote a letter to me last night, and left it on the computers desktop so I could read it. I wasn't sure what to expect when he told me he left something on the computer for me, but this was a good surprise. He explained that because of his previous relationships he has been expecting, and preparing, for the worst. He is used to being treated badly by his ex-boyfriends, and he is used to the idea that the relationship won't last that long. He admitted that he is starting to feel like he is sabotaging the relationship, which is partly true. But, I won't let that happen. I love him, and I know about his past problems.  He did say that I am sweet and kind to him, and I can't express how great hearing that makes me feel. HE IS THE MAN I LOVE, and I want him to know that. However, he added that he knows that he has been neglecting my needs and wants (and, that he knows that he shouldn't have). He is worried that I will get tired of him, because of his problems, and 'trade him in for a better model.' Well, I know he isn't perfect (I mean, who is?). But, to me, there is no 'better model.' 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am chatty today, although I don't know why.  I do forgive Elvin, and I will trust him. As to whether he lied, I'm going to believe him when he says he didn't. Although, a small part of me worries about all that has happened.  I read a couple of other weblogs, they are rather interesting. It has caused me to wonder if I should make mine available to the public. I will have to ask Elvin though. I have written about him, and will continue to do so as he is a major part of my life. I wouldn't feel right if I didn't get his permission. On the down side, that means I will have to let him read everything I have written. But, if I do go public, he would have access anyway.  I don't know, I just feel the need to write today. I don't have anything in particular to write about, I just want to write about something... anything.  I read Wil Wheatons blog, and I liked what I saw.  I think I may join the Green Party. I don't like the Republicans, and while I'm liberal (and typically vote for them) I'm not really a Democrat. I'm a bit of a socialist, but I have read their sites and they have no hope of ever winning office in the US. (In fact, quite a few don't even go for any of the good positions anyway. Way too defeatist of an attitude.) The Greens though are trying to get into all the 'right' places, even though they don't (currently) have that much of a chance. The thing is, they are trying. And, more importantly, I like most of their positions. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Elvin said he didn't lie to me. But, all his statements do not agree with each other. However, I do love him. And, I hope he loves me. And, since I know this won't get resolved, I will have to forgive him and try to trust Elvin again. (I'm not going to say forget, as that would be stupid.) It isn't that I don't trust him, it is just that he has been knocked down a couple of levels because of all that has happened so that I don't quite trust him as much as I did. I will have to try to trust him that much again, but I don't think it will be easy.  I took a look at next weeks schedule, and Kim (the store manager) has me working Tuesday night. Granted, she has scheduled me to get off at 6 PM, but that isn't set in stone. I'm going to have to talk to her and let her know not to do this again, and to let her know that I won't stay past 6 PM. She isn't going to like it, but she doesn't have a choice. Now, I just need to tell Elvin that she did this. He will be pissed! (That is the evening we have the dinner group.)  I have also lost some more hours. I had asked Kim if I could keep two closing day, and she said she was fine with that. Well, she scheduled me for one closing day. I think people have complained because I am not as fast as everyone else at closing (mainly because I actually do the job the right way, and don't cut anywhere near as many corners as everyone else does). If she keeps cutting my hours I will have to find another job.  I got curious, and explored the Green party website. It turns out there are a couple of different groups, both claiming to be The Green Party. (Although, because of legalities, their names are slightly different.) I found it rather interesting, and I rather liked what I read. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I have discovered that Elvin has been masturbating at night, when I'm asleep. I found out because we are out of lube. I find this rather disturbing. He has lied to me about not being in the mood, and made me feel very unattractive. Frankly, I don't know how to react to this. I know he loves me (or, at least, I hope he does), yet this lie hurt me quite a bit. His saying he wasn't in the mood made me rather depressed. It did help when he said that it might be the meds, now I find out he lied. And this isn't some small little while lie, this is a biggie.  My refund check came today. It wasn't much this year. I went to H&R Block, and they charge out the ass. I should have gotten $200 back, but after they took out enough to cover the bill, I only got $72. Elvin is the one who wanted to go there, I just wanted to do it myself (like I have done for the last few years). I would have saved quite a bit of money by doing that.  A while back Elvin "accidentally" read my blog. He happened to bring it up yesterday, and his excuse wasn't that good. He said he accidentally clicked on my internet favorites and went to my blog thinking it was his. That doesn't hold water. My blog is listed under Astennu's Tower, and does not have blog in its name. The name is not close to his, so just how am I suppose to believe he accidentally did this? 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am, to say the least, worried. I don't think Elvin is that happy with our relationship right now, and I know he regrets having even moved down here. Plus, I forgot to say Happy Birthday yesterday (see previous posts). I know he doesn't like it down here, but I wouldn't stop him if he left. That isn't to say I would want him to leave. (Quite the opposite, as he is the one bright spot in my world right now.) I just understand his not wanting to be here. 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Have you ever wished that you could just rewind time and change stuff you regretted. I wish I could do that with yesterday. Not to change what happened at work, that wasn't even under my control. It would be to change how I treated Elvin. On his Birthday no less!  I shouldn't have yelled at him, no matter what reason I had.  I should have said Happy Birthday to him! God, I regret that more than anything else. I know what it is like for people, family included, to miss your birthday. I didn't miss it, I knew it was his birthday, I just forgot to say "Happy Birthday." It may seem like a small thing to some, but to me it is a big thing. A big think I fucked up. 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today was not a good day. I was treated very badly at work. I was ordered to do stuff other than my job, and then got in trouble because I wasn't able to do that and my job at the same time. Megan was a bitch for a while tonight, and I got some of it from her. If she hadn't perked up and started acting somewhat more civilly, I would have quit. I know Elvin wouldn't have liked that, but she was treating me very very badly.  Today was also Elvin's birthday. Oh lord, how I wish it had been another day. I yelled at him, which I greatly regret. He smoked all of his cigarettes again, and we couldn't afford to get more. (I wish we could, but as quickly as he goes through them we would be completely broke very soon.) I also didn't tell him Happy Birthday, something else I greatly regret. With all that was going on, I forgot to say it.  One last note, Kim still hasn't talked to me about an interview. She approached Josh, and I believe she has Chris as well, but me she hasn't said word one about the shift manager job. In truth, I know I wouldn't enjoy the job, but we need the money. What pisses me off is that she really doesn't know me that well, but has already decided that I won't get it. Well, fuck you Kim. She is the last person who should be making judgments on anyone. 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Kim has started to interview people for the shift manager position, and even though she has more access to me she has decided to interview other people first. Knowing Kim as I do, I do not take this as a good sign. 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I read a blurb today about the US government intelligence agencies (oxymoron?) reading blogs as part of the war on terror. Well, huh? I don't really mind anyone reading my blog, that's why it's public. It when the government reads it to try to find terrorists that I wonder just what kind of idiots thought this up. I mean, if I were a terrorist I wouldn't create a blog and tell everyone my plans. Yet, the US government seems to think so. We don't have money for social security, and all that, but we can pay people to surf blogs and find people who might be terrorists.  I look at Mr. Bush (el Presidente) and see an idiot. Granted, Sept. 11 gave him some great PR, but that is all it was for him. His actions after that haven't made me think any better of him, and, quite frankly, quite a few of his actions have lowered my opinion of him. Yet, we do now know that a lot of people at Nascar back him (I remember seeing that on the TV news). Wow, a bunch of people who watch cars make a lot of left turns back Bush! (As you can tell, I don't get the point of it.) Then, there are his "Free Speech Zones" that he has the Secret Service (SS!) create whenever he goes in public. Those are far away from him, and the only place the SS will allow protestors. That gives him even better PR, as there is no one in sight on TV who disagrees with him. And, if you do slip out of one of these zones and get closer they arrest you. Gee, makes me think of certain WW2 fascists.  Well, moving on...  Elvin told me yesterday about this bigot at his job. As it turns out he works with someone who is one of those "I hate faggots" people. It was funny, because someone there has a brother who is gay and even goes with his brother to gay bars sometimes. I feel sorry for this guy, as he will never open his mind to truly new experiences. He will only see what he wants to see, and never any more than that. The thing is, if heaven truly exists I doubt people like him would have a good chance of getting in. (And no, I'm not saying that I'm a saint or anything, or that I would go straight to heaven. I have no better chance than the average person.) 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The day is over now, a long day it was. I told you about work, and about a few other things, but that still leaves a little bit of the story untold.  We went to the dinner group, and there were more people there than I have ever seen. I really had not expected that many people, and it is probably a good thing that we met at Cherry Street tonight. (I don't think any of the other places we go would have easily held all of us, not that we weren't kind of scrunched.) The meal was good, and there was some good conversation. But, I didn't get involved with it. I didn't know some of the people we were sitting with, as I am shy, and I'm quiet anyway. I thought it went well enough, and I hope Elvin enjoyed himself.  After that we came back, switched back vehicles, dropped some movies off, and came home. Then, we watched Big Fish. I have to say I enjoyed the movie more than I thought I would.  That takes us to now, with me typing. There isn't much left to say, except that I Love Elvin. We have our ups and our downs, but at the end of the day I still love him. Nothing will change that. I love him with my heart and with my soul. 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm am so bored right now. I worked earlier, and now I'm off for the day. (On Tuesdays I don't work at night, as Elvin and I have a dinner group we go to.) Normally I would watch TV, or something like that, with Elvin. But, he is at work and the appartment just feels so empty without him here. And I have nothing to do!  Since I was bored, I decided to go online (duh! I'm writing this online). I did a search of blogs, just looking for good gay ones. I went through five pages of them, checking out those that caught my eye (usually three or four per page) and found just one that I decided to keep checking periodically.  Work was "fun." Instead of doing my job, my boss had me do a favor for her. (This translates as: "Shawn clean this" or "Shawn, go out in the company truck and see if you can find ____ at any of the local stores.") I spent about an hour and a half doing her "favor" and didn't get any of my stuff done. Now, I know when people come in tonight they are going to bitch about it and blame me for all the extra stuff they get to do. Thanks Kim!  I'm trying out Gmail, and so far so good. Elvin says he won't try it as it looks for keywords in your mail and targets you with ads. Well, duh! Like no one else is doing that now? Yes, they are. They just aren't being up front about it. Besides, I get to help beta test it. Yay! 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Nothing much is happening right now. I talked to Mark (the guy from Ireland) yesterday morning, and I hope everything went well. His bf had given him an ultimatum, I think, to have made a choice by a certain time. Quite frankly, ending the relationship seems like it would be a good decision. However, I'm not Mark and I'm not in his situation right now. Only he knows what the "right" decision is.  Things are a bit fun at work right now, as some people are not happy with my boss. She has not been working with them. Liz has a last minute problem, and can't work this Friday. She apologized for it, but she really can't make it. Kim, however, isn't going to be nice about it. Then, there is Joey. He is finally graduating from College, and is working on getting a job somewhere else (besides currently having another job). So, he can't work as much. Well, according to him, Kim hasn't been acting the same towards him since he told him he could only work certain hours. They are both unhappy, and if Kim pushes them they may quit. We really can't afford it, but I won't hold it against them if they do. One bright spot is that they both said they would try to not to just quit on the spot, and would try to give a week or two notice. Those are just two examples, there are quite a few people unhappy at work. I would say that I hope that Kim wakes up and realizes that people are not happy, but this has been going on for a long while now. Normally, people just quit and move onto another job. I really do wonder though, why hasn't corporate noticed our high turnover rate? Especially with as many people that have quit in the last two weeks.  I did apply for the shift manager position, even though I don't have high hopes as to getting it. Liz did say she thought I deserved it, and I have had one or two other people say the same thing. I just hope that whoever gets it is good at the job. (Well, I should use plural as all the shift manager positions are open right now.)  Elvin isn't all that happy with is new job, and he wants to find another one as soon as possible. He did accidentally hit one of the stones when mowing yesterday, and I hope he doesn't get in too much trouble for it. 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Met a cool guy online tonight. He is having boyfriend trouble, and I happened to be in the chat room when he was talking about it. He turned out to be a good guy. On the cool side, he is from Ireland. (I can trace some of my family to Ireland.) I just hope things work out for him. From the sound of things, it may be best for him to just end the relationship. He loves him though, which makes things hard.  I didn't work today, and it was great to have a day off!  Elvin and I had sex this morning, and I thought it was rather good. It has just been so very long since we have had sex. But, considering his ex, I should be happy he even still wants sex at all.  I think I should start an exercise routine. I know, as an American I was brought up to constantly believe I weight too much, but I could stand to loose a few pounds. The only problem is, I just don't have the time. I get up, go to work, come home and rest as I am completely worn out. 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am so tired. I didn't get off from work until almost one PM last night, and I had to be up early this morning to take Elvin to work.  Oh, and Elvin has found a job. He went to an interview yesterday morning, and they called him back in the early afternoon. He now works for the city mowing their various properties. It isn't the greatest job, but it is one of the few that was hiring. Oh, how I'm am coming to hate living in a small town. 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I don't know why Elvin seems to think I'm trying to keep him away from his family. I'm not, I just don't have a way to get him up there. For one, I have to borrow a vehicle. And second, I don't have the gas money to even get up there. But, he seems to think I don't want him to see his family. Actually, it is much the opposite. I very much want to be able to find a way to get him up there. There just isn't a way to do that right now.  Elvin also thinks I want him to be dependent on me, and again he is wrong. When he gets a job, I want us to be inter-dependent. Meaning, we both pay the bills and all that. When he has his own money, I don't mind his paying for his own stuff. My problem is that he seems to want to be completely dependent. Well, if he were single and living on his own I would have no problem with that. But, that isn't the case.  I just don't know what the problem is. I talk to Elvin and tell him one thing, but he mistranslates what I say. He translates it by what he has heard other people say. Well, as I have repeatedly told him: I'M NOT OTHER PEOPLE. We have been together for about a year and a half now, but he still doesn't seem to understand me. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Elvin has been annoying today. We are going to Galesburg later, and that trip will suck up most (if not all) of our money. However, he wants to rent a movie. So, he keeps saying we need to go the the movie place. I keep telling him we can't afford it, and he just pouts at me. I really wish he would understand that I can barely pay the bills as it is. Taking these trips does not help, and I can't afford to take a trip and rent movies. (The trips aren't cheap when you drive a gas gussler, and you belong to a dinner group that doesn't go to cheap places.)  I understand that he spends most of his time in the appartment and doesn't have a job (I won't touch on the subject quite yet). But, he needs to understand that we are poor. I can't afford to go to Galesburg on a daily basis, I can't affort to go to Chicago or Juliet even once a month. The bills take just about all my money, and leave very little. I know what Cabin Fever is like, but we can't afford to do the things he wants to do. I wish we could, but we can't. I try to come up with alternatives, and he shoots them down. But no, nothing I come up with is good enough. He HAS to go to Chicago and Joliet, and constantly reminds me about it. I know he wants/needs to, but, as I keep telling him, we can't afford it.  I'm tired and stressed out. I'm working a lot more hours at work, and I really don't have much time to relax. When I finally got home today, Elvin wants to go to my sisters (we needed to use her phone, she has long distance and we don't, and he wants to see Zak, my nephew). I asked for just a little bit to relax, and he acts like I just asked from some impossible thing. I NEED some rest and relaxation damn it. I really can't take this. I can't watch my TV shows, because Elvin doesn't like them and we have one TV. (Although, he put it on wrestling last night, and I was expected to either watch it or find something else to do.) All I can do is use the computer when Elvin doesn't want it. I'm really starting to think this is a one way thing. Hell, he put most of the utilities in HIS name. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It is nice to have a day off, although Elvin is getting on my nerves a bit. He is doing his "I'm so very bored I could die" bit, and spends most of his time channel surfing. I wouldn't mind it if we had more than one TV, but I'm getting tired of him staying on a channel long enough to get me interested in it just to start channel surfing again. I'm finding it very annoying.  I find most religions to be hypocritical. Do not kill, but killing in the name of god is okay. Hello?! How stupid can one be. Do unto others as you want them to do unto you, unless God says you can do otherwise (with the voice of god being played by some tele-evangelist). I have no problem with money, so long as one does not see money as god. We need money to survive, that is it.  I just went to google and looked through the religious section at the the religions, and their sects. There are so many of them. Each one  usually  says that they are the "true way" and that all the others are wrong.  I guess I'm just in a bit of a bad mood today. Elvin getting on my nerves, plus I am very tired. (I woke up early and couldn't go back to sleep.) 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I sometimes go to sites and read stories of people coming out, and how hard it was. It makes me feel lucky. It was hard for me to tell people I'm gay, but no one I have told has had a problem. My mother just told me it made sense, once she thought about it. My sister wasn't surprised either, and the rest of my family is just fine with it. (Surprising since a good portion are conservative Christian.) The only family members I'm close to that I haven't told are my grandparents on my dad's side. That is partly because I don't see them too often anymore, and because they are so old and frail. Grandpa has been in the hospital several times this last year, and Grandma has had some major surgery herself. I just get this picture in my head of me telling them, and then them having a hear attack or something. I'm even out at work, witch wasn't easy for me. I just showed up at the Christmas party with Elvin. Since Kim had been explicit about bringing only the person you are dating, the point got across. I was very nervous, but that was the best way I could think of doing it while not having to actually tell everyone personally. Surprisingly, no one at work has had a problem with it (or, they haven't let me know if they do). Either way, when Elvin calls me at work I get told my boyfriend called. I was just so surprised at how easy it was. It didn't happen all that quickly, but it happened. As for friends, those I'm still in contact with know and have no problem with it. I guess I'm just surprised at how easy it was. No one told me they hated me, no one tried to hurt me, they just accepted it and me.  The only problem was telling my grandma on my mom's side. I had to actually explain what gay, homosexual and all that mean. It was not the most comfortable situation, talking to my grandma about that topic (one just doesn't discuss sex and the like in my family). But, once she understood she accepted it. I don't think she, or grandpa, quite like it, but they accept that I'm happy. She just asked if I still loved them, and when I said yes she said that was all that mattered.  I guess that is how everyone else in my family sees it. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm not updating all that often anymore, mostly because I'm low on time. Of course, it doesn't help that I could really use some help on the procrastination thing.  I have gotten a lot of hours at work (and a lot of overtime), as several people have quit and one person is now working two jobs so he can't work as much. It does mean that I'm really tired now, and could really stand to use that vacation time I have coming. But, that would require someone to work for me while I'm gone, and that can't happen until Kim hires some more people. Speaking of which, I applied for a shift manager position. I don't think I have much of a chance of getting it, but one never knows. I do have a lot of experience with bad managers, so I do know what not to do.  Other than that, there really isn't much happening. I work, spend time with Elvin, read, watch TV, and sleep. I don't have much time for anything else right now, plus I live in a small town so there isn't much to do anyway. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, so far so good. We have at least paid the rent, but I don't know how we are going to pay for everything else. Well, I guess we will just have to take care of that when it comes time.   I put my Church of Mithra webpage back online. I thought I had returned to it fully, but I am not sure. I have been searching for my true spiritual home, yet I do not know if I really need to. I read in a book that we all search, and continue to search even after we find what we want. That reminded me of how I first felt when I discovered Mithraism, I felt like I had come home. But, is that because I had found the right place for me or because I possibly was a follower of Mithra in a past life? The odd thing, I have a book title stuck in my head. It is about Antinous and the religion Hadrian founded around him. I find this odd because I always have to write everything down or I WILL forget it. So, why is it I can't get this title out of my head?  Needless to say I have a lot on my mind. I am so unsure of what to do. I think I may go to the library and request the book through inter-library loan. I think I am meant to read it, although I do not know why.  I did come across this guy called Tony Subia, who claims to be a priest of Antinous. What I read is disturbing. He reminds me of come cult leader, in the worst sense of the word. The sad thing is, he has people who follow him. How can they not see through him? I look at him, and I do not see a priest. A see a dangerous person. I worry for those who decide to follow him.  I think he focus's too much on the appearance of Antinous for one. When I was reading what he wrote, it felt like I was reading a badly written love letter. What truly worries me is that he was brought up Catholic, and seems to have tried to combine that with the religion of Antinous (or something like that, anyway). He is totally confusing, because he seems to still consider himself catholic. What is scary is that on one of his websites (they seem to go on and offline on a daily or weekly basis) there is a picture of him dressed up in one of the Catholic churches many Holy outfits (reminiscent of one of the popes garments). He seems to want to be some great religious leader, but I think he has a very long way to go before he is even an OK one. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       We, or at least I, have been busy. When I haven't been at work, we have tried to clean the apartment. We have also moved in furniture. I had some in storage, and got some more from family. The mattress was ruined when storage got flooded, but Grandma and Grandpa will let me borrow a mattress and box spring.  I am worried about paying the bills. The rent will take up most of my pay check, and paying the other bills will be hard. There are some assistance programs I can probably get on, but I'm not sure if they will accept me. 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Work went rather badly tonight. Someone (I think I know who, but I'm not sure... and actually two someone's) made a mess at work with the food release (oil in spray form, like you buy at the store). They had some kind of "fight" with it, evidently spraying it at each other. Well, from the looks of it, most of it ended up on the floor. I had to mop it three times, scrub it twice, and change the water each time. I lost of a lot of time doing that. Then, the drain in the dishroom got clogged up, so we had dirty water from the dishwasher flood the room and leak out into the hallway. I had to use sanitizer to lesson the smell of the dirty water, and I will have to do the same tomorrow. That cost me even more time to clean up.  I haven't wanted Elvin to touch me lately. Part of it is probably because he hasn't wanted to for so long, and it made me feel rather ugly. It probably doesn't help that this is the time of year I stop wanting sex (my sex drive usually turns off, or shifts into ultra low gear). Last year (around this time) we did have sex, but there were times when I didn't want it, but we did it anyway. (I'm not saying he forced me, I didn't tell him I wasn't in the mood.)  I Love Elvin. I love him with all of my heart, and all of my soul. If there was a way to move the heavens and the earth to make him happy, I would gladly do it.  I sometimes wonder about my past. I have blocked out portions, rather large ones, of my childhood. I know I could tear down those walls, but I'm not sure I want to. I can guess at some of what I blocked out, but there are portions that scare me. Things which I'm not sure I want to know about.  Van Go (sp?), our cat, is currently sitting next to my chair. He is looking up at me, rather expectantly, and purring. I should give him some attention, and he has been after me for it. It is just so late, and I am so tired. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I know Elvin doesn't want sex, and it is killing me. It's not that I'm a nympho, it's just that we almost never have sex anymore, when I'm lucky I get it once a month. I will be the first to admit I don't have much of a sex drive, but even I need it more than once a month. Elvin should be happy I have a lot of self control.  Not much is going on with work. I'm training someone again tonight, not that she really needs it. (She had to close on her own last night - someone called in sick - and she did a great job.)  I have joined Nova Roma, and have created a Roman name (a requirement to join). However, my name will be changing, as it evidently shouldn't have passed as it is. I will post it when the change is finalized. I joined because of their reconstructing of the Religio Romana. I feel pulled to it, and I think I will try it out. I find it interesting. Right now I'm still researching it. I will build an Lararium (altar) when I have the time and materials. 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I changed the template and added a comment option. I just wanted to change the look a bit, and I'm not sure why I added the comment option. Sometimes, ya just do things.  Elvin lost his job on Wednesday. He was working for the city as a grounds keeper, and he evidently hit one of the cemetery stones with the lawn mower. So, they decided to fire him, as they think he has had too many accidents (two, to be precise). This will make paying bills fun, but he does have one more check coming.  Work has been interesting, as Liz quit. I can't say I blame her, as she did have incentive. While we did hire two people, they are still new and make more than a few mistakes. One of the new people is a manager at a local fast food place, and evidently doesn't like to be bossed around. As an example, I was correcting her as she kept spraying the dough pans wrong. She didn't like that, but she did apologize (sort of). She needs to get used to the fact that she isn't a manager at Pizza Hut.  We had a grease fire on the stove today, and it really scared me. I saw a weird light from the bedroom, called Elvin by name and he yelled "Shawn help." I walked in, saw the flames, and he asked me what to do. (He had been trying to put them out with a towel, but wasn't having success.) Well, my first reaction was to use water. After pouring the water on the fire we then learned it was a grease fire, as the flames shot up - almost to the ceiling. Surprisingly it went out on its own shortly after that. I don't know why it just died like that, but I'm glad it did. If it hadn't we would have had to call the fire department, and (considering I was wearing a towel, having just gotten out of the shower) I really didn't want to do that.  Later, while I was on delivery, I saw the fire trucks out with their lights and sirens going. My heart stopped beating for a second, as they headed in the direction of the apartment. I wanted to tell Dan (the manager at the time) that I had to run home, but I knew it couldn't be our apartment. However, it took a lot of self control not to run home and make sure Elvin was okay. It reminded me how much I love him, and made me think. I mean, I wouldn't know what to do without him. I just can't imagine my life without him in it. Yes, we do fight, but I really, truly love that man. 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Nothing much happened yesterday, I worked and argued with Elvin. Not a while lot different than how today is looking, actually.  I do close tonight, and I'm not looking forward to that. The only upside is that I am training this girl to close, so I at least know I'm not going to be doing it alone. It is nice to have an extra set of hands.  That's about all I have to say for today. I close for the next two days, so I may not have time to log on and write anything. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Not a whole bunch to write about today, but here it goes...  I didn't do much except for work yesterday. Not a really exciting day. We did have a waitress quit on Sunday, we had a drive call in (also on Sunday), and our all day wait called in yesterday. Needless to say, Kim was in a bad mood. On the flip side, she didn't take any of it out on me. She did talk to me about it, which is how I know about all of that.  I do find it weird, that sometimes people just seem to open up to me. It is one of the reasons I keep my friendships to a minimum, as I usually end up being the person they talk when they need it. It isn't that I mind it, I just can only take so much of it at one time. However, I have learned to keep my help to a minimum. (I have been burned.)  Elvin did clog up the toilet yesterday, and then the sink today. I told him to stop doing certain things, and he didn't seem to take it well. I know I repeated myself, but he should have listened to me when I told him to stop doing it the first time. Oil doesn't go down the drain, cigarette butts go in the trash, that sort of thing.  We aren't going to be able to make it to the dinner group tonight, we just don't have the money. I wish we could, as I rather enjoy it. Although, we will need to start showing up earlier. Last time we ended up sitting with some people from out of town, and I would have preferred to sit next to some other people. That was an odd night though, a lot of people showed up and they showed up early.  That's all for now, maybe I will have more to write about later. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today was my only day off for the week (not unusual).  To start off with, we didn't make it to church. We needed to borrow my mothers van, and she was nowhere to be found yesterday and when I called today she wasn't home yet (and probably didn't get home until after 11 AM). I doubt Elvin was all that happy with it, but there wasn't anything I could do. Surprisingly, I missed going to church.  I did wake up with a migraine today, which stuck with me for most of the day. It only went away an hour or two ago. However, the exedrin kept it to a low level pain with few side effects.  I not feeling all that depressed today. What probably helped with that was that I didn't work today. I really am working too much, as I'm now starting to dream about closing (and getting bitched at by my boss). That isn't a good sign. Also, it was nice to just spend time with Elvin (even though he was probably bored all day, but he is always bored).  I didn't go to my Uncle's birthday party. I know Grandma won't be happy about that, but life doesn't always give us what we want. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I got to thinking a little bit ago, while I was taking a shower, and I wondered why I was writing all of this in a public blog. To be truthful, I'm not completely sure. Some of what I write is mundane, and not that important. Other bits, though, are important (to me, anyway). I could say that I'm doing this so that others can read this and say, "Well, I'm not the only one with a screwed up family... work... or whatever else." But, I'm not really sure why I made this public.  I'm not writing this for pity, instead I'm writing all of this for myself. It helps me vent, it helps me de-stress, and there is a need to write it all. I don't understand it, but the need is there. On the flip side, I guess someone would read it eventually, anyway. Ya, it would probably have been decades down the road, but it would have been read.  I also got to thinking about my screwed up family. After all they did to me, they still want me in their lives. But, they want it on their terms. They don't want Elvin there, they don't want this or that or something else. Well, guess what... this isn't just about them. It is about me too. I don't want to pretend nothing has happened, or that everything is perfectly fine. (It isn't. And, what makes it worse, is that what they did to me went against everything they ever taught me.) I'm tired of pretending, well... I'm just plain tired of it all. If they want me in their lives, they have to take the whole package. I'm gay (which the seem to accept), and that Elvin won't just fade into the background when they want him to. I'm not going to just cut Elvin out of parts of my life because they don't want to deal with reality.  Also, these posts have been getting longer and longer (plus miltiple posts per day). I guess it is just that there is so much going on right now. I have a lot to think about, and it helps me to write it down. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm feeling quite a bit better now. The main reason for this is probably sleeping for 7 or 8 hours. I'm still tired, but I got enough to tide me over. Tonight, after I get off work, I have hopes of sleeping for another 7 or 8 hours.  I talked to Grandma McBride today, and she asked me to come to my uncles birthday party (which is tomorrow, he turns 50). Quite frankly, I don't want to go. Why should I go to his b-day party, when he won't come to mine? Last year I didn't even get a card from him, and I don't think he sent me one the year before that. My family doesn't treat me all that well, and I'm supposed to just show up and pretend everything is perfectly fine? I really don't like the man that much. He had a mid-life crisis, divorced his wife, and married someone else. Plus, his new wives daughter happens to look a lot like his dead daughter (she died in 1984 from cancer). One of his excuses was that he didn't like how his family turned out, so he wanted a second chance. Well, why not try to fix things in your own family? I can't blame my cousin for not liking his new step-mom. By all accounts she is only after his money. God, my family is so screwed up. I kind of wish I had an excuse like my cousin, who said he has a marriage to attend. He probably does, but even if he didn't I doubt he would have attended.  Grandma did ask about Elvin, even if she wouldn't say his name. That didn't make me happy. Grandpa has a low opinion of Elvin, and it seems grandma is picking up on it. If only grandpa would sit down and listen to the truth, rather than listen to my insane mother (druggie... oh, did I say that?) who wouldn't know reality if it hit her in the face.  I know, I'm going on and on about my family. I'm just so tired of all the shit. If it were not for my nephew (cute little darling that he can be) and Grandma McBride (with her it is mainly that she virtually raised me), I would sever all my ties with them. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Elvin has his annoying moments, and tonight is one of them.  Right now he is sitting in the living room constantly changing channels, and it is driving me batty. I sat down to watch TV with him, but he doesn't stay on one channel for more than a minute or two. If he has seen the show even once, he has no interest in it. He really has no interest in most TV shows. To make things worse, he won't even settle on putting it on any channel, whether he likes the show or not.  This is one of the reasons I don't get to see my shows anymore. Elvin is always sitting in front of the TV, and won't share the damn thing. All he does, most of the time anyway, is channel surf. I don't mind it sometimes, but after about half an hour of it I'm ready to kill him. I would just like to sit down and watch one TV show, just one would be nice. Not see three minutes of it, and then start channel surfing again. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I got off of work about half an hour ago, and I am extremely tired. However, I can't get to sleep yet. For some reason it takes me an hour or two to unwind first.  I didn't get to see Elvin much yesterday. I wish I had been able to spend more time with him, it would have helped my depression. Plus, it would just be nice to spend time with him.  Which leads me to the next bit. I'm feeling a bit depressed again, it's kind of a cycle I guess. But, with all of the stuff that has happened to me in the last one and a half, or two, years, who wouldn't be? To have my family treat me the way they did, plus work, and some other stuff... blah!  I checked out a site on depression, as well as a couple on suicide. I hit damn near rock bottom tonight, and it took everything I had to continue on and not just break down. (I'm still working on maintaining an emotional equilibrium.) Oh lord, how I need a vacation. I just need to get away for a while, relax, and de-stress. It isn't going to happen, no matter how much I may need it.  One good bit of news though, no matter how depressed I get suicide isn't an option. That isn't to say I don't think about it when I hit rock bottom (like tonight), but there is a psychological block that won't let me do anything other than think about it. Maybe it is because I know that it doesn't really end the pain, or, at best, ends it temporarily.  Van Goh (sp?), our cat, is doing everything he can to get my attention. He is moving around me while I sit here purring and meowing (or, at least, trying to meow... we need to take him to the vet and all that). 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, we can't go to Chicago. We had plans to go up tomorrow (technically today, as it is after midnight) to visit Elvin's family, and then go to the Gay Pride Parade. Then, Mom does a 180 and says we can't have the van (which we need to make the trip). Needless to say, I'm not happy.  We do have plans to go see the new Harry Potter movie, though. Now we just need to borrow the van for a while.  I ended up closing cook tonight, I was supposed to close drive. The good news is, I was a drive for most of the night. (I was only a cook for two hours, one of which was after we closed.) So, I made a nice little bit in tips. (The closing cook cut himself, and had to go get stiches. He should have known better than to cut a sandwich while holding it like he was.) 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I was looking at the dashboard settings, and I saw that I have a little under sixty posts. I'm slowly climbing up there.  I have been a little depressed today. I feel a bit like I have failed, as I cannot support Elvin. No matter how hard I try, my paycheck just can't cover everything. I have even started to wonder if he wouldn't be better off if we hadn't gotten together, or just been friends. I know he isn't happy down here, and I really don't know what to do anymore. Don't misunderstand me, I Love him with all my heart. I just have to wonder if he wouldn't be better off without me. That is the contradiction. I can no longer imagine life without him, yet I wonder if he would be better off with someone else.  I watched a strange movie that Elvin said he liked. I missed the very beginning, and that might have helped to explain it a bit more. This guy startes dating this good looking young man, who seems to be mixed up with the gangs and all that. (Oh, and this happens in Columbia.) He gets killed, and the guy hooks up with the kid who killed the kid he was with (after a period of morning). (By kid, I don't mean underage. Just young.) So, he starts morning all over again. There it ends. A good example of life actually. Nothing really ends, it just goes in cycles. Even though the movie was a bit depressing, or so I thought, and really didn't help my mood. 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm still not sure as to my religious path. I have tried several, and looked at so many. The teachings of Jesus appeal to me, but so do parts of other religions. I did once try to create my own path, but it didn't work right. I'm just a bit confused right now. I get that way sometimes. I have moments of great faith, followed by doubt and confusion.  Work is fun. But, Kim will be away for the rest of the week.  I have thought of trying to write a story, but I'm not sure what to write. There are so many possibilities, it is just so hard to choose. (And, anyone who knows my family will know that it takes us forever to decide on anything.)  I LOVE ELVIN. What more need I say? He is the center of my existence, the part of my life that seems to make everything worth it. I would move the heaven and the earth for him, if I only could. (I know, I have written this before. But, I mean it and I repeat it to remind myself that it is real and not a dream.) 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am just so tired today, and I'm not sure why. It might be that I haven't really slept that well, and keep having really weird (and I mean REALLY WEIRD!) dreams. Last nights was truly f*cked up. My teddy bear was seducing me (no idea what the hell that means, and I'm not sure I want to know), and then Elvin and I are in some kind of summer camp. It's in a park somewhere, but everything is child size and recently built. There is more to it, but it is just too weird. Someday, I would like to have a "normal" dream.  My sex drive has started to kick back in, which is rather unusual. (Winter is my time of the year.) Several times during the night I woke up rock hard, and when Elvin got up (and woke me up in the process, not his fault though) I was also rock hard. Rather weird, as this time of year my sex drive is usually winding down.  Speaking of which, I walked into the living room a little bit ago, and accidentally discovered he (Elvin) was hard. But, he wouldn't let me touch it and play with it! He wants sex, but only when he wants it. If I want it, or just want to play a bit, and he isn't in the mood I'm just suppose to keep it inside. ARG! 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       As usual, work was "fun" tonight. We started off slow, so we had all of the panning (dough) done. Then, after they had sent almost everyone home, we got hit. We had a lot of deliveries, as well as a full dining room. I was helping in the kitchen, and my trainee was helping in the dining room. I felt sorry for some of our customers, as they had to wait a while to be seated. But, that happens when we only have two waits (who are trying to take care of more than a dozen tables who got there rather recently).  My trainee was okay, she really only needs to work on her speed (and that will improve in time). She is an ex-housewife who is currently getting divorced. (I think she is now working at two jobs, and has two kids to take care of. Not to mention a dead-beat dad). The only problem I can see is that she is a conservative Christian. I discovered that when I mentioned I was a member of a couple of interfaith yahoo groups. She said (in a tone most people use to talk about alcohol or drug abuse, or something really REALLY bad), "Oh, I don't mess with that." So, I asked her what she believes, and she gave me the classic the bible is the literal word and all that. She didn't ask what I believe, and I didn't tell her. I doubt she wants to know, and there shouldn't be a problem unless she does ask. I am wondering what her reaction will be when she discovers I'm gay. (Which is something most people at work know about. It can't be hidden as I do play flirt with a couple of people there. Besides, I won't hide what I am.) 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       When I went to bed last night I could feel the beginning of a migraine, and I knew today was going to be fun. However, I shouldn't have shrugged off my nautiousness last night. Now, I have a low level migraine and my stomach is upset. Work will be fun tonight.  Speaking of work, I'm training someone again. She is nice, although she doesn't catch on too quickly on some things (no one is perfect). The only major thing is that she needs to speed up a little, as it takes her too long just to wash and put away dishes.  My hours were cut a little at work, but not enough to make too big of a difference. I only lost one night, and it isn't one of my closing nights. Plus, I could use another night off. I'm overworked, and can't afford a vacation. So, a night off is as close as I come.  Well, that is all for now. I will probably have more to write when I get off work. However, I may not have a change to post anything for a day or so. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am feeling so tired today. I could take a nap, but that never solves the problem. It takes me forever and a day to actually "wake up", and I really don't have enough time.  Elvin ran out of cigarettes yesterday (although he didn't tell me until today), so I went out and bought some for him. On the down side, I only have one or two dollars left. I do work tonight, so I can hopefully make enough in tips to eat supper on Friday (since I close I get a break, and I won't have a chance to eat before I go back from my day shift).  I have am the owner/moderator of a local Freecycle Yahoo group, and I have recently implemented some changes. Prospective members have to tell me where they live (not an exact address, just their general location and their zip code). I didn't originally want to do that, but we had our first spammer, and I don't want to take anymore chances. I have seen too many lists get hit by them to believe that there won't be any more of them. I also created some files that are sent to prospective and new members, so that they know how Freecycle works. I also have a couple of files that are set to be sent out every couple of weeks, and one that goes out once a month. I also need to get a disclaimer for the group, which will either have to be sent out once a month or every too weeks. I hadn't planned on it, but it would probably be best. (If only because too many Americans are law suit happy.) 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I got home, and tried to relax and spend some Me time reading (alone in the bed room). But, Elvin has to come in and start talking to me. I know he has been alone in the apartment for most of the day, but he doesn't seem to understand that I don't get much time alone. I go to work, and spend almost all of my day around people. The only time I'm not around someone is when I'm out on delivery, and that is very short. I certainly don't have enough time to relax, speeding (not going too far over the limit, mind you) to the delivery and trying to keep focused on what I am doing. I come home and then Elvin wants to spend time with me. I don't always mind, but lately I have just needed some time alone to myself. I had that when he was working, but now that he got fired I don't. I have to shut the door, and hope that Elvin gets the hint. The thing is, he doesn't.  Elvin was complaining about being hungry tonight, like he does every other night. Well, there isn't anything I can do about it. He wants to go over to my moms place and raid their kitchen, but he won't eat anything they have. First, they are meat eaters. Second, they have mostly canned food. (Elvin doesn't like to eat canned food. I know, as we have some and he hasn't touched it.)  Every time he complains about being hungry, there is a thought that momentarily pops into my head. The same thought that pops into my head when he says he wants to go visit his family, or just wants to get out of town for a while. We can't afford it, but we could if you could keep a job longer than a month. I know that Beck's over hired, but he didn't help himself when he mouthed off about the boss. And, he says it was an accident that he hit the grave stone, but he also could have been paying more attention (I do know how hard it can be for him to focus). I just wish he hadn't lost his jobs. I'm not saying he is completely to blame for it, but I have listened to him talk about his job history. Maybe I misunderstood, but he can't seem to stay at one place for very long.  Don't get my wrong, I love Elvin with all my heart. And, I know that all probably sounded rather negative. I didn't mean it to come across overly negative. The problem is that I'm frustrated. Mine is the only source of income right now, and that doesn't make things easy. 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I know, it's four in the morning and I should be in bed. I'm not tired though, and the battle with insomnia is not going well.  The cat just fell off the window sill, which just about scared the sh*t out of me. I was just sitting here surfing the net, and all of sudden I hear this racket from the living room window. I just about freaked, thinking someone was breaking in or something. But no, it was the cat falling off the sill. I'm still a bit freaked out though, as I wonder what caused him to fall. He often sits there, and he never fell before. It makes me wonder just what could cause him to fall, what might scare him. It could have been the neighbor kids, but even they generally aren't out this late/early. There was this weird noise that seemed to be coming from out side. I did look out the window when the cat fell, but with the living room light on I couldn't see anything. I should have looked again, but just why the hell should I see what is making a such scary/weird noise. It sounded a bit like very loud breathing, or maybe someone messing with the window. Either way, I moved around, messed with the drapes, and made sure anyone that might be outside would know there was someone awake. Anyway, it REALLY freaked me out.  Well, now I'm definetaly going to have problems going to sleep. Going online generally helps me relax, and I was going to read a book and/or take a shower. But, now I just want to stay up and make sure nothing happens. God, it doesn't take much to freak me out when it is late at night. I guess that comes from once living in a house with at least one ghost. I have been trained to be freaked out by weird and unusual noises.  Yes, I know, someone is going to say ghosts don't exist. Well, you explain how you could hear foot steps on the stairs when no one else was home and you were looking straight at the stairs and could see no one was there. Or, how could you hear the nintendo being played in the basement game room, even though no one was downstairs and it was turned off. Or, explain loud crashes from the basement storage room, but when you check it everything is exactly where it is suppose to be.  Oh, this is going to help me sleep. I need to think about something that will help me relax, not work me up even more!  This is good, now there are weird tapping/knocking noises coming from the storage room. It only happened twice, and then stopped. That doesn't mean it didn't freak me out.  Yes, there are occasional weird noises from that room anyway. And I am going to keep telling myself that it is nothing. It is late at night, and I need sleep badly. Nothing at all.  Oh f*ck, the tapping/knocking noise happened again! I'm never going to get any sleep at this rate. AH! It just happened again, damnit. No one could be in there, as it is locked. Plus, just to get where that noise is coming from would cause a lot of noise as the land lord has all sorts of stuff stacked in front of the door.  I'm sure there is a logical explanation for it all. I just need to relax and try to work myself into sleep mode. There is no one there, everything is perfectly fine. Now, I just have to believe it. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Earlier I tried I tried to post a blog, and lost everything I wrote. So, here's to hoping it works this time. It is very frustrating to lose everything.  My dad sent me an e-mail, and he really wants me to come visit him. I wish I could, but there really isn't any time for it. No one can fill in for me at work, and I can't afford to lose even one pay check.  Elvin and I had sex Tuesday, it was great. It had been so long, that I was beginning to worry.  I am in doubt as to me religious beliefs right now. I have been a Pagan, Wiccan, Neo-Christian (NOT NEW AGE), Christo-Pagan, Mithraic, and one or two other things. Throughout it all I have remembered the teachings of Jesus (and they have been a part of my moral compass). I was brought up with them, and it is inevitable that they stay with me. (To clarify, I mean what Jesus supposedly said, not what some Preacher says he said.) I feel pulled to those teachings, and by extension to Christianity. If I were to return, I would still be a rather liberal one (by the conservative/fundamentalist standard).  I am reminded of a "discussion" I had with a literalist Christian on a message board. It was whether the bible was the literal word of god, I said no and he said yes. I explained that I consider the bible to be written by the hand of man, and therefore suspect. He just started quoting the bible, or I should say the Old Testament (quotations directed at the OT, as the NT did not yet exist when the quotation was written). I told him that quoting a book to prove that book is valid as the literal word of god wasn't a good argument with me, but he just kicked it into heigh gear and sent me pages of quotations. (The vast majority of them were random, and really didn't have anything to do with our argument.) I tried asking why he thought the bible is the literal word of god, but the only answer I got was quotations and being told I was a child/minion of Satan. He never once said anything original, or acted like he knew how to think for himself. Sadly, this man called himself a minister. After a while I told him that I was ending the argument, as neither of us were winning. He wouldn't listen to anything I said, and he just kept quoting the bible and calling me a minion/child of Satan. I did check that thread every so often, but he was the only one who posted. Sadly, he continued to post quotes. They didn't have any common subject, and were rather random.  I really don't understand some people. All he had to do was answer my question, but instead he just started quoting the bible. When I pointed out that wouldn't work with me, he called me a child/minion of Satan. He seemed to think I was just supposed to believe whatever he said without questioning it. People like him worry me, as they eventually do find people who will follow them. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Go damn it! I wrote out this long blog entry, and then there was some problem while publishing it and it is all gone! GOD DAMN IT! 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I got an e-mail from dad, and he really wants me to visit him. But, it just isn't possible right now. There isn't anyone available to work for me, and I can't afford to lose any pay.  Elvin and I had sex yesterday! I'm not sure why he wanted it, but it was great.  My sex drive is still slightly active, at least more so than it usually is. Usually, I'm not that interested in sex this time of year. But, it still pops into my head every so often. It is slowly moving towards the low position, though.  I'm in doubt as to my religious beliefs. I have been a pagan, wiccan, Mithraist, neo-Christian, christo-pagan, and one or two other things. Through it all though, the teachings of Jesus have stuck in my head. They were what I was brought up with, and they remain important to me (and a part of my moral compass). This isn't to say a particular churches teaching, but actually reading what Jesus supposedly said and learning from it. I feel pulled to his teachings, and I feel a pull towards Christianity as a result (albeit a very liberal version of it).  I am reminded of a discussion I had with a literalist Christian on a message board. It was whether the bible was the literal work of god. I said no, he said yes. I tried to explain my position, and he blasted me with old testament quotations (which were themselves directed at the OT) and said they proved the bible (as a whole) is the literal word of god. I pointed out that quoting a book I believed was written by the hand of man didn't prove it is the literal work of god, and he just kept sending different quotes. (Surprisingly, most of them really didn't seem to fit with the argument. It really seemed as if he was going for volume, and picked most of them by random.) Eventually I just told him I wasn't interesting in talking with him anymore, as neither of use were budging from out positions. (He wouldn't listen to anything I said, and he just blasted me with quotations and called me a minion of Satan.) After that, I didn't post anything. But, I checked the thread periodically, hoping someone who used their head would post. But, he was the only one who did and he just kept posting bible quotations directed at me (never read any of his posts after a while).  I don't know why that popped into my head, but it did. I just wonder what kind of logic people like him use, as I can't see the logic in their thinking. Quoting a book proves that book is what you say it is? 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I wanted to kill Elvin earlier, but let me explain a bit first.&nbsp; Right now I can only afford to eat once, maybe twice a day.&nbsp; However, Elvin has a Link card so he eats whenever he wants.&nbsp; Well, I'm starving and wishing I had something to eat, and he just sits down and starts munching on snacks.&nbsp; I was already starving, but he had to sit right in front of me and eat.&nbsp; That is on par with Chinese water torture, or, at the very least, just plain torture.&nbsp; He hates it if I even talk about food when he is out of money, but it is okay for him to do even worse to me.&nbsp; I really wish he could think about more than just his own wants and needs sometimes.   I wonder if he thinks I eat all the time, if he thinks when I go to work I eat all I want.&nbsp; If he does, he is sorely wrong.&nbsp; I might eat lunch, but that is only if I make enough in tips.   Which reminds me, I gave Elvin permission to take a dollar.&nbsp; Well, I only had a five dollar bill so he took it.&nbsp; I figured I would get change back, well I didn't.&nbsp; That was my money for food, now he spent it.&nbsp; So if I want to eat anything tomorrow, I will have to take it out of my checking account.&nbsp; And I already had to spend part of that on car insurance.&nbsp; All of it needed to go to rent.     
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Have you ever had that one moment where you just suddently ask: what am I doing?&nbsp; I don't mean: why am I doing this?&nbsp; Just simply, what am I doing?&nbsp; Which, for me, leads to: where am I going?  &nbsp;  Today I just wondered where I am going with my life.&nbsp; Ya, right now I'm working to be a shift manager.&nbsp; But, that isn't what I want to do with my life.&nbsp; I want to own a restaurant, travel, just DO something.&nbsp; But, what?&nbsp; My options are limited, and that frustrates me.&nbsp; I feel the NEED to go do SOMETHING, anything.&nbsp;&nbsp; Yet, I'm stuck where I am.&nbsp; If I were single I would contemplate just selling everything and taking off somewhere.&nbsp; However, I'm not single and I doubt Elvin would want to do that.&nbsp; Even if he did, we have our future to think about.  &nbsp;  That just leaves me sitting here thinking: why?&nbsp; It leaves me frustrated, and rather unhappy.&nbsp; I feel a desperate need to go DO something with my life.&nbsp; Yet, here I sit.   
    
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        I got a rather bad migraine last night, and I'm out of excedrin. So, I&nbsp;took some non-aspirin PM. It really didn't do much for me, and I threw up my dinner at one point.&nbsp;I'm just glad I didn't wake up with it. (Usually when I wake up with a migraine they last all day.)  &nbsp;  Elvin was concerned for me, and came to the bathroom when he heard me throw up. He also grabbed the fan and moved it into the bedroom so it could blow on me. I was glad he did that, as I was sweating quite a bit at that point.  &nbsp;  The one bright side is that I slept from the evening yesterday to 7:30 this morning. So, I did get plenty of sleep.        
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The Amendment to ban Gay Marriage failed! 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I got the Shift Manager position. Now I get to do all that "fun" training. I also have to watch all of the training videos, whether or not I have seen them already. (As I was told: "To make sure that I had seen each and every one of them.")  I went to my first manager meeting today. It was basically a bitch out session, as our customer complaints are getting too high. I can't say it was fun, but thankfully most of it wasn't my fault. (There were a couple of things that were mentioned that I do, which I should change. Although, one of them that was mentioned I was under orders to do at that time. Even though I really should have been doing something else.)  I rather agree with everything that was said. We have to focus on the customer. Without them, we wouldn't have a job. If they aren't happy, even if it isn't our fault, we have to apologize and find a way to make things better. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today was long and hard. I worked from 11 to 2, and then went back in at 5 and closed. It wasn't that we were busy, the problem is that my body is complaining. My back and my hip hurt, not a fun combo. I'm trying not to walk funny, but it isn't easy.  I wasn't scheduled to close, but one of my co-workers got beat up by her ex-husband. I agreed with Kim, she needs some time off. (She had a broken nose, a concussion, and bruises.) The bastard should be happy I'm a pacifist.  Some good news, though, I did get a password today. Now, I can work the cahs register. Yay! I'm glad to know that Kim trusts me.  Money is tight, but we should be able to pay the bills. Although, it may take some creative book keeping to do it.  Elvin's tooth has been hurting him. I have told him to call a dentist, but he won't do it. I keep telling him that he  NEEDS  to go, but he won't listen to me. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today was rather long, and not all that good. I worked this afternoon, and the tips sucked most royal. Then, tonight I made just enough to cover the computer. With any luck, I can make enough to grab a bite to eat tomorrow/today (I work all day).  I did go to the Monmouth College Library, although it was Elvin who wanted to go. However, I have been wanting to but hadn't felt the push to do it. Well, Elvin was the push. I found several books that will be useful. On the down side, I evidently have a book out and they will charge me $50 if I don't find it and return it.  I sometimes wonder what Elvin does when I am not here. When I ask him, he just says "nothing." If I ask a specific questions, I do get a specific answer. But, no more than that. Now, consider that I have problems trusting people and then someone doesn't answer my questions unless I push the issue. That equals fears I have to try to control. (i.e. I wonder if he isn't cheating on me). Now, I know he isn't cheating, but my mind is simply too good at seeing the possibilities. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I set up an account with geocities, but I don't like their site builders. One takes forever and a day to load (and I haven't completely figured it out yet), and the other is complete crap. Sometimes, I just wish there was a good free site builder program out there.  I woke up early, and I couldn't go back to sleep. I laid there for about twently minutes before I finally decided to get up. I'm hoping that if I go lay down again I can go back to sleep. 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       We tell ourselves that we can do anything we want anytime we want, but can we really? Every time we make a decision we limit future decisions. I decided to stay in a small town, which has limited quite a few things and I am now stuck here (can't afford to move now). Maybe it is because I have a gift to see the possibilities rather easily, but I don't think we are as free as we like to think. Yes, we have free will. But, only to a point. Everyone makes decisions which impact on others. Sometimes the only thing we can control is our reactions to things. And sometimes, we can only hope to influence our surroundings... control is not usually an option.  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I was watching a show on social classes in America on PBS. I very much agree with them, while most Americans say we don't have class structures and conflicts - they are just plain wrong. There are social classes here, whether we like it or not. It made me think of some of the local kids who like to say they (as in their parents) are rich (by their standards anyway). However, I was once related to old money. I once knew people who were rich (although they were not as rich as they had once been). My former step-father grew up with maids, butlers, drivers, and all that. People who actually have money and class wouldn't give these local "rich" kids the time of day. Quite frankly, I feel sorry for the kids. One day they are going to find out they are moderate sized fish in a small pond, and won't like it when they move to a bigger pond. Quite frankly, I don't see all the hoopla about trying to act like some of the upper class people. I was watching the show, and this rich WASP was going on and on about how more people were getting rich and how it used to be. One example he used was when he went to a charity dinner, and their were actually ugly people there. He was surprised, and wondered how  THEY  had gotten in. Then he said, he wasn't trying to act like a typical WASP, and wasn't acting like a snob. Yet, in the previous sentence he had bashed all who were not like him (as in rich and a WASP). God, some people only see what they want to see.  
    
    
</post>


</Blog>