<Blog>

<date>28,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Look, its Phil!    and Phil's anatomically correct self-portrait:  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Steve got a virus on my other computer. What a whore. Lacrosse starts in a week. Holy way for half the team to quit batman..... My mom is an idiot, my dad is leaving (supposedly only for a week or something, but who really knows for sure?) Extreme makeover doesnt make people look better. It makes them look different. Completely different, but still just as ugly as before. James started calling again...strange... I have mucho confusion these days. I dont know what im doing, what I want. Ok Steve is a stupid asshole piece of shit bitch. and so is my mom. i hate my "family." And when i say this, people say, "no, you're just pissed off and its probably your fault anyway, yaddy fuckin yaddah, you have to love them." Well fuck that. Thats not how my life works. And at this very moment I am getting yelled at...for what? absofuckinglutely nothing. Its always nothing and i hate everything. sigh. hold please, im in need of a tissue....ah screw it. not getting up. sleeves dry up tears just as well. I need to get away.... i remember back when i used to never go home after school... i'd always go to chris's house or mike's house or something and just waste time because I hated to be here. Then I started getting caught. Allllll thanks to my wonderful loving sisters. I cant get away. Even if I could, I'd have nowhere to go. Cant really go to Chris's too much anymore... in fact I havent been there in a looooooooong time. I have no where to go anymore. No escape. Nothing. And now my mom is fucking up the whole lacrosse thing for me too. The only thing that matters to me. The only thing I have, and shes trying to take that away too. I dont know what to do anymore.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I guess I should elaborate... theres not much to say about it, but I just sort of realized that I'm sad again. Everything makes me sad and I'm really not as content with life as I keep saying I am. I convinced myself that I was really ok this time and nothing mattered that much and being sad is pointless and such... and part of me still believes that... but lying to myself isnt making things hurt any less. I don't know why its like this. I just wish it would go away.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm sad.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Holy shit that was a long ass update.   PS- Fuck you rob, I am not a midget. And your eating midgets theory is all wrong. Small people taste bad. Also, In my case, if you tried to eat me, you'd pretty much be gnawing on bone, because in case you havent noticed, I'm not fat.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alright the first time I started this post, my computer flipped out and restarted itself so everything died. If it does it again, its getting shot in the face. That's a warning to you, you piece of crap pile of metal and plastic they call technology.  This whole Me and Nick not hanging out thing is getting slightly retarded. Sort of like this blog. Yesterday we didn't hang out because I got home way later than expected, and now today his parents have dragged him off to the mall. It sucks. Hardcore. Oh well. Friday night was movie night at Amy's. We had a whole bunch of movies picked out to watch and Courtney was supposed to come join us but she had to stay home and babysit her brothers. So me and Amy made some Jello Jigglers and watched half of "The Shining" before falling asleep. It wasn't the original Jack Nicholson version of "The Shining." It was the remake from the 90's, where the guy uses a croquet mallet instead of an ax. It was sort of funny actually. Except for that whole bunny topiary thing. That was friggin creepy. I would be scared shitless if a bush shaped like a bunny came after me. I really would.  Saturday, we woke up way to early at like 7 am. Then we had waffles and finished watching the movie, then we watched the Muppet Movie. Then we got ready to go shopping and I made my hair all gross and curly and wore weird shiny bluish greenish eyeshadow. It was awesome. I looked all girly and whatnot. Then I went through Amy's closet and found a random belt and her old school Euclid School t-shirt. Then we found her old Euclid School sweatshirt from when she was in like kindergarten that doesn't fit her anymore but of course fits tiny Danielle. So w00t, I have this awesome sweatshirt now.  Later on, we were sitting downstairs and listening to random ska music and shitty hip hop waiting for her mom to come home from work, when the doorbell rings. Its my sister Steve. I told her to go home. So she got back in the car where my mom was waiting and I followed her and asked why they were there and they said they didn't know so they left. It was strange.  Finally Amy's mom came home and we left. We listened to some random 90's music on the way to Middletown, and suddenly, Hootie comes on the radio. We have decided that Hootie is due for a comeback. All these other crappy artists are making comebacks, but only Hootie is worthy. We'd so buy all the new albums if the Blowfish came back.    The Shopping Experience with Amy and Danielle:   *I made Amy buy a skirt. *I got a belt. Its green and orange and blue. It was on these shorts but we didn't want the shorts so we just switched the belt with the really weird ugly one that was on the skirt. *I tried on this obnoxious skirt that looked like it wanted to eat my body. It was so disgustingly awesomely ugly. It was all purple and pink with random black spots on it. It was great. *People looked at us weird. This is not unusual. People always look at us weird when we go out in public.   Good times. On the way home we could find nothing but Linkin Park on the radio. It was horrible. We made it good though by singing crazy 2-part harmonies, and making up our own awesomely bad lyrics, because well, we're awesomely bad like that.  Oh yeah I also borrowed Amy's Brave Little Toaster movies because they are the greatest things ever. And now I am going to watch them. Goodbye. 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had a lot to post from yesterday.... But you know what? I'm really not in the mood to write all about that, because it was really not fun. But today, I realized, a lot of people really piss me off. I hate slutty girls. I hate wishy-washy people. I hate stupid people. I hate hypocrites......  Ok so I was in the middle of typing this when Amy called... We discussed how much we hate everyone, especially Paul. Then Steve took over the computer while held back from stabbing her in the neck with a pen because she's being a dick. And the fashionable thing to do when dicks are unpleasant is to stab them with pens..... That statement was wrong on so many levels....  And now I hate everyone so much that I don't even want to tell you about hating everyone. So instead, I'm going to pack for movie night at Amy's, and even though I really don't want to, I guess I need to shower... Then I will wait for my mom to come home, and I will leave. Then I will come home sometime tomorrow, so can watch Lilo and Stitch with Nick. You see, Nick and Amy are part of a very small group of people that I actually don't hate. They hate everyone too, so we get along well. Did I mention that everyone hates us back? 'Cause yeah, they do.    I hate people who hate things that they don't understand.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok Nick was demanding a new post so here it is.  Dominos for breakfast, goooooooooood shit. Let me tell you, its the breakfast of champions.... or well... breakfast of lazy fat ass kids like me and Steve. So, spent the whole freaking day cleaning, doing my mom's laundry, cleaning my mom's bathroom, cleaning my mom's bedroom, etc. The things I do for her and what do I get in return? Nothing. She wouldn't even let Nick come over to watch Lilo and Stitch with me. Stupid bitch. The only other thing I did today was listen to some nice loud music to piss off my stupid whorebag of an older sister, because well, she's a stupid whorebag. So the listening of music went as follows: Story of the Year (Page Avenue) something like 2-4 times, Alkaline Trio (Good Morning) once, Incubus (Morning View) once, Brand New (Deja Entendu) twice, and now its on AFI (Sing the Sorrow) which I haven't listened to in quite a long time. I would have included the fabulous Motion City Soundtrack somewhere in that playlist except that Amy STILL HAS MY CD! But its ok, I can deal with it, because I love that crazy kid...("He's SO MEXICAN!!!!") Oh isn't this lovely? My mother is now yelling at me to turn my music off. My response, turn it up so I can't hear her telling me to turn it off, then when she comes upstairs screaming, I sit there looking downright confused and yell back "What??? I cant hear you!!!" at which point she proceeds to shut off the music herself by throwing the stereo at the wall. Then she continues yelling while I sit here singing to myself as though the music was still playing, while my mom, overwhelmed by frustration, storms out of the room, cursing to herself...... or I could just turn the music down....NAH.... haha If my kids were as obnoxious as me, I'd be just as insane as my mommy.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday was quite an interesting day. Most interesting one I've had in a long time... That's probably because its the second time I've left my house in a month, other than to go to school. It started out with me being woken up at the ridiculously early hour of 11 am by my wonderful, loving mother (cough cough bitch cough). I ate breakfast, got dressed and whatnot, then was dragged to my great aunt or something's house in Belleville for her 85th birthday... and that's quite sad considering she has outlived everyone on my mother's side of the family. You know what this means. I'm going to die soon. But anyway, there was a bunch of random people that I've either never met, or haven't seen since I was in diapers. However it was quite strange how I was the only one of my sisters that anyone recognized. I don't really look the same as I used to. They say its because I look exactly like my mom (shoot me in the face) and because I have the same personality that I had when I was little: Shy super-ADHD kid. Hey, if it makes a mark in people's memories, then I'll keep it. Its the only thing I'll ever stand out for. So this little family gathering, it was as boring as could be expected, a few verbal fights between my aunts, and me being attacked by a gang of 5-year olds. I pretty much spent the entire time sitting in the living room watching Spongebob Squarepants all day. Finally around 5 or so my mom decided it was time to leave. So after a round of hugs and kisses, we headed out only to be driven around in circles through Nutley for an hour. My mom decided to take a nice trip down memory lane. Literally. We drove passed run-down houses and abandoned factories (hey this is starting to sound like an Ataris song...) as she told us all the fantabulous things she used to do. Like sneak out and get drunk with her friends. Now why is it that I get in trouble for these things? I don't understand it. Not one bit.   Eventually the tour ended and we started out for my other aunt's house in Denville. We stayed there for an hour-ish while my mom and aunt discussed some random thing, and I entertained myself with an entire bag of chips. Then we left my aunt's house and somehow ended up at the mall. Somehow I found myself wearing a prom dress. Oh the prom shopping experience, my tulle and taffeta nightmare... I'm not a big fan of that whole thing. Oh well, after saving myself from the wrath of this long itchy tangle of fabric, I waited anxiously for my mom to do whatever it was she was doing so I could go home.   On the way home, my mom kept irritatingly turn of the radio every time she said something that no one listened to anyway, so in the most annoying voice possible I just sat there repeating "RADIO" over and over again until she turned it back on. This process was repeated every time she turned it off, and believe me, it happened a lot. I am obnoxious. I love it.   Anywho, we eventually arrived at my house, which automatically ended the chance of anything interesting from possibly occurring. End of story.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Its official. I suck at life. I can't even cook a grilled cheese sandwich. I will never survive in the world.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ahh the day after V-day. I hope all you love birds have happiness hangovers. My evening went as expected. Spent it completely alone, playing Emogame 2 all night. Things went well for most of the day anyway, at least until my parents got home. They did the fighting thing, yelling and whatnot. I mean come on it was Valentine's Day, you'd think they could at least pretend to care for one day. But they can't. So I didn't eat dinner, not wanting to listen to all of that. I stayed upstairs on the computer and sustained myself with mini chocolate bars all evening. Last night I also decided I should move into Steve's room. We'll be sharing a room on a temporary basis to see how long it takes before we kill each other, then my room will just be my escape room and the band room. So last night we dragged my mattress into Steve's room, and we stayed up and watched MadTV. Then after MadTV, this random black comedy show or something comes on, so we started watching that too. HOLY CRAP it was the stupidest, most pointless thing I have ever seen in my entire frickin life! Worse than this blog, so obviously it was pretty bad. I mean, these people weren't even funny! They made jokes about gas stations and mountains and J.Lo's ass... It was bad. And this coming from one of the most easily entertained kids ever born. I fell asleep after the second act. After that I slept like a rock, except for when I started feeling things crawling on my face. I woke up like 8 times, thinking there were bugs crawling on me or something, then I realized, it was my hair. As for today, I'll probably be stuck in the house all day again, cleaning or something, so I might as well get an early start on that, so I can have absolutely nothing to do later on. Adios... (yeah that's about as far as my Spanish comprehension goes)  Oh well, later on yo.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, so I was reading Phil's blog and I thought to myself, "Hey, I should have my own blog." Why, I'm not too sure, but hey, I'm bored, I have no life, why the hell not? It seemed like a good thing to do at the time. We'll just have to see how well this thing actually turns out.  So anywho, today is Valentine's Day. A more suitable name for it, at least for me, is Singles Awareness Day. Its just another pointless holiday to remind you how much of a loser you really are. Now don't get me wrong, its pretty hard to forget how much of a loser I am. Just take this blog for example. Considering no one will read it anyway, its a sure sign of my uncoolness. Oh well, I am perfectly content with being a loser. Its really not so bad. (Riiiiight) But anyway, this whole valentine's thing... I don't understand it. Wasn't that whole thing just a big massacre somewhere in Europe? I really don't know. History's not really my thing.  Well, I just went downstairs to get a drink and I saw my sister in the kitchen. She was disgustingly giddy with Valentine's Day cheer... I just wanted to throw something at her. Instead I just said, "Sack" and continued on my not-so-merry little way.  Everyone has their wonderful little plans for this evening... me? I'll probably just be sitting here alone all night. I had plans to go to Rob's with Nick and Amy and Erica for "Sad Movie Night/ Anti-Vday party" however these plans were shot to hell, due to Rob forgetting to mention that HE'LL BE IN FLORIDA. Lucky for him, no one could go anyway, so we'll let him live... for now. So since my parents and Nick's parents wont be around, and Amy's parents are being stupid and imprisoning her in her house, and Erica... well... I'm not sure what happened with Erica, but because of all of that, we have been forced to cancel our sad movie night, and will all be spending tonight alone. Great isn't it? Yeah I though so.... or not.   Well my sister Steve (formerly known as Michelle, but James and I decided her name should be changed to Steve) has decided to cook something so I better go supervise and make sure she doesn't catch the microwave on fire again. tah-tah for now kids. Hope you enjoyed the randomness stupidness of my brain.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh I forgot, we watched Spice World last night too. It was crazy awesome.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey there, long time, no blog, eh? Yeah strange. Oh well, I have been in quite an excellent mood aside from my parental issues. So Friday, we had a scrimmage in Pingry and lets put it this way. We got metaphorically raped in the ass and beaten. It was crazy. Some chick elbowed me in the back and then I couldn't breathe and I died. I'm not quite sure of the score but it was something like 2(us)-7ish(them). Then we got back at like 8 and a few of us randomly went to the really lame-ass Spring Fling dance crap at the HS, and hour and a half late of course. I just stayed with Nick the whole time... man we were so out of place. Oh well, it was ok anyway... There was that part where this "special-ed"-ish kid started dancing with me and then he did a split and it was scary. After that, Amy and I went to Burger King then we went home and I passed out at like 11:30. Saturday, we were supposed to have another scrimmage but it got cancelled and I was woken up at 9:30 when someone called to inform me that I had practice at 10. So I rolled out of bed, threw on my practice clothes, and left to pick up Amy. I had no time to shower and I was quite filthy from the previous day. Oh well. I'm a skankified child. After practice, I came home and cleaned and such, then Nick and Amy came over and we made another cooter cookie. This one was quite grandma-like though... Anywho, then we watched some random movie, then played Twister for like .002 seconds, then Amy disappeared for a few minutes, so me and Nick played Twister by ourselves....ahem yeah. Then Amy came back and we sat on the couch and watched "I love the 80's" and such, then I was playing Pokemon on Gameboy and I named the one guy "Ur Mom" and the other one "Cooter" and it was funny because it would say stuff like "Ur Mom defeated Cooter!" then Amy took it and played while me and Nick watched TV.....and such.... and she named this one Pokemon "Penis". Then there was this one part where we were watching TV... and such... and Amy yells out "Go Penis!" I thought it was funny... but hey I guess you just had to be there at the time... haha. It was an awesome night :-):-):-):-):-):-):-):-):-)
     

    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So here I am in first period history, being bored, sitting here in the library. I was all getting in trouble for not doing the research paper thing. Oh well. There's nothing to do... blah blah... Adam is weird. He's my morning buddy. Me and Chris are going to sing in English today. He brought his guitar to school so we're gonna jam (and before practice too). I'm hungry. Well, the bell is going to ring soon, so I'm gonna go and find my awesome boyfriend. :) Goodbye!
     

    
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My mood has significantly improved. Well, except for a few minor details, but still. Its all good. I think I'm going to change my cat's name from Huckleberry to Rip Van Kitten. What do you think? I think I should.  Wow. During the time period that I was writing this, my wonderful fucking life has been completely shat on. I love it. Friends are so fucking overrated.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sunday... I hate Sundays. Me and Sam Hoyt used to love Sundays. Those were the good old days. Anywhom, its been an interesting weekend. Friday we had another snow day, so Amy came over that evening as well as my Nick, and Chris-ko (who smelled awesome, which Amy couldn't get over for like 3 days). We decided to make a giant cookie, like we usually do when Nick and Amy and I are all standing around in my kitchen. (Except that one time when we made cupcakes instead and Rob thought we should make one giant cupcake, like we do with the cookie. Think about it. Picture a giant cupcake. Yes that's right ladies and gentleman. Its called a "cake.") Anyway, we decided to make an "Amy's Asshole" themed cookie so they put a big hole in the middle of it, but then when we cooked it, it came out looking like a vagina. So we ate our nice, large, gooey cooter cookie, then I had some mac and cheese which is permanently ruined for me because of the chlamydia. We'll leave it at that. But yeah, so we sort of but not really watched Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles 3. That was pretty much it, besides the usual trampoline wrestling and some other stuff... ;-) (-: What a good night... (:  Saturday was generally boring but still good, 'cause I'm happy most of the time these days, except where my parents are involved.  Today was also quite boring because I just cleaned all day and then there was this thing... that made me all sad.... but its all good now... I think.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Holy snow day, lampshade! Haha that was strange. Oh well. I hate snow, and its been snowing for quite a long time and you know what else? I am sick. So here I am, sitting on my mom's bed, updating the blog and talking to Nick. Its fun. And my mom will be home soon. And I don't know what else to say.  Peace, love, and pink elephants to you. Good day :-D.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Woot, Its snowing, so we got sent home from school all early and whatnot. And you know what else this means? No lacrosse practice! Sweet! So I'm going to sit around and drink apple juice out of a champagne glass and eat some chips. I'm just so amazingly cool like that. *Rolls eyes* Yeah I think I shall also revisit that old love of mine known as the EmoGame.   So here's how my day went so far...Well.. I'm going to start from yesterday... Yesterday I went to school, then practice, yaddy yaddah, I was being lazy so I played defense in the drill we were doing and Mr. C was like, "You were doing good on D, maybe we should move you from 1st home to cover point." and I was like, "Um... I don't know about that..." because I hate playing defense in games. Then varsity had to run hills, so I'm quite grateful for being on JV just for that. Oh yeah I got hit in the head again. Leave it to me to find a way to get hit in the head, even with those retarded cages/ masks/ goggles/ whatever you want to call them that we have to wear. After practice we were taking the bus home and it was me and Courtney and Amy and Daniel Roth and some other random girl that was just kind of there, and we were pretty much sharing my extremely exaggerated sex life with the whole bus. It was awesome, because really, we weren't talking about my sex life. Somehow it just seemed like we were. But its all good. It was some quality entertainment. After that, I went home, ate mac and cheese, then went to bed, even though it was only like 6:30. Then Nick called and we talked till like 10, then I passed out.   This morning, I woke up late, showered, then my sister starting yelling that I had to leave in 2 minutes, so I got out of the shower and got dressed and whatnot as quickly as possible, then went to school, did pretty much nothing all day, then found out we were going home early so then in lunch I found out Erica was not there which kind of made things boring but I was all talking to Jen and Nicole, then Nick came to visit me, and we looked at pictures he drew in his notebook of people dying. It was fun. Then we went home and we were all on the bus and Nick had my leg and he kept hitting my knee... ya know, that whole reflex thing, so then everyone was hitting my knee. Then Nick and Natch were pretending to be Fitty-cent and then I left and stood on my deck in the snow till my sister came home, then I watched Saved By The Bell. And that is all. I was all going to go over to Nick's with Rob but my mom is a waste of life and decided to fall off the face of the earth.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      UGH! I hate post-traumatic fish syndrome.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So here it is, Sunday morning/ afternoon-ish... I'm still sleepy, so its close enough to being morning. Oh well, I already forget where I was going with this.  Oh here's some news:   So Friday, I walk into the locker room after school to get ready for practice, and there is a crowd of girls standing around 2 pieces of paper taped to the wall. All of these girls are lacrosse players, and some of them are crying, so we know what these papers were. THE LIST. So I mosey on over to find out what's going on. The first page had a list of names under  Varsity  and a second list of names under  JV Regular . Then the second page was entitled  "JV Foaters"  (we figured out it was supposed to say "Floaters") then under this was Group A and B. Under Group A was about 6 names, and then a different list of names under Group B. We were/are really confused about this. So anyway, I look on the regular JV list first just to be safe. And holy ball sack, guess what the first name on the list is! Yeah it looked something like this (with my added little side comments):   JV Regulars  1. Danielle Enman (Yes that's right, me... starting JV... bleh) 2. Nicole Gagliostro (What the gay? That upsets me more than seeing my own name on this list.) .blah .blah .blah .some random names including Hilary, Cole, and others 11. Kristen Oyen (crazy sometimes-goalie-kid) 12. Amy Spoer (my Spoergasmo! yay! Damn goalie bitch :-D) 13>Elaine Kubik (yes with that exact typo) The End. I forget who was 3-10. No biggy.  It was slightly retarded. So then I looked on the Varsity list, which had 20 people on it. It was Kendahl (obviously), Lauren Brierly (yay), Noel, Shell Promnitz (yay), Taren, Marissa (whhhhaaaat???? Ouch.), Allie ( :( My bench bitch wont be sharing the bench with me anymore:( ), and Kelly (yeeeahhh....). Then there's some other random people that I really don't care about. And then there's Linda. It comes as no surprise that Linda's on varsity, because, well, Linda's awesome. The rest of this list was bullshit. Oh well.  Then this Floaters list. Apparently, its mostly just the people that would have gotten cut but since someone's a pushover and didn't want to make cuts, we ended up with this floater list. The people in these group alternate between games. Group A plays one game and Group B plays in the next. The JV Regulars will play/ start in every JV game, and some will be moved up to varsity. And honestly? I think this system sucks.  Oh yeah so Friday, Phil was allowed to come back to school, which made me very happy. So happy, in fact, that I jumped on him in the hall after lunch and gave him quite a dramatic kiss on the cheek, and people looked at me weird. :-D  Oh well. Friday night, I was waiting around for Nick to come over, and Chris Korwan decided to stop by, and ended up staying the whole night. So it was me, Nick, Chris, and Steve, eating frozen french fries, wrestling on the trampoline, and watching Ferngully. Chris was all with Steve, which was... creepy... to say the least. So then blah blah blah, random things went on, blah blah blah. The end. :-D Oh yeah Steve kicked me really hard it the back and it still hurts a lot.  Yesterday I had to get up and go to my lacrosse scrimmage in Millburn. It sucked. But me and Amy ate mac and cheese on the way there, because we're awesome like that. It was really cold out. It sucked. On the way home I saw a house with a lot of lawn flamingos in the backyard. I'm jealous.  So then I went home and slept, and then at 7-something, Meagan's all like "Hey, lets go to the movies." So we did. We wandered around the mall for a while before the movie (50 First Dates) started. We went to Hot Topic and bought shoelaces, and there was all Family Guy stuff everywhere and I was like, I should get something for James, seeing how he's obsessed with Family Guy. But I didn't. So then we wandered into H&M... why I'm not sure, but it was fun. I tried on this crazy ugly poofy black and red skirt with a red and white striped shirt. It was great. Then I made Meag buy a blue plaid skirt. We got in this big music discussion with the cashier guy. It was strange. On the way back to the movie theater, we ran into Britt, Adam, and Stasha. That was strange too. So then we went and saw the movie and it was ok, then we drove home blasting various random punk. It was fun. Then I got home at like 12:30, and started watching "Pieces of April" (which kind of sucked by the way) before passing out.   As for today, I have not accomplished a single thing other than cutting up my Finch shirt and digging an old shirt out of the back of my closet and cutting fuzzies off of it for like an hour.   Good times.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm so tired. I'm friggin beat, but I figured, its not even 7:00. I don't want to go to sleep yet, so what better thing to do than update the blog?   So yesterday I had to do a timed 2-mile run, at the very beginning of a double lacrosse practice. Me and Jen finished in 18:45, not too bad... not great though. Then there's Kendahl who finished the whole thing in like 10 minutes. And by the way, it was also snowing... a lot. I wasn't a big fan of this. Then during our fantabulous hour-long break between double practice, we kidnapped some food from Kelly's mom.... Poptarts and Girl Scout cookies and such. Anyone who went near my cookies had their eyeballs ripped out. I was also getting a lot of weird looks from people as we walked around eating because I was definitely making some sexified sound effects the whole time I was eating. Honestly, I quite enjoyed it. Then practice #2 went something like this: passing/ catching drills ("quicksticks" and such), then some sprinting/ throwing/ catching weird sort of shuttle drills for a loooooong time. Then we played some keep-away type game things then did a normal game-ish sort of thing... 5 on 5's or something like that. Of course I ended up covering Linda in the first round, who is ridiculously good, and I also suck crazy bad at anything defensive. Put me on offense, and I'm good to go, but defense, its not my thing. Then after that we ran a few laps, died, went home, did some random stuff (talked on the phone with Nick for like .002 seconds before I flipped out on my dad and told him to shut the fuck up, then was no longer allowed to use the phone, almost got in a fight with Rob, and probably Nick too, then just gave up on everything and went to bed.... and cried through pretty much all of that), then passed out.  As for today, I was pretty obnoxious today, but that's really ok because it put me in a good mood. Faber and Lasher took quite a bit of abuse from me, and I will not apologize for it because I enjoyed every second of it, but they are cool kids anyway for taking my shit. As far as lacrosse went, we did a lot of circuit training type stuff, but it wasn't too horrible. Except for the background music. Some of it was ok, but seriously... Really slow techno shit doesn't work for me. Its supposed to motivate us to play, not motivate us to cut off our ears. But anyway, after that, we did random rotations, 15 minutes each of running, stick work, and... basketball??? . Yeah. My little group consisting of Amy, Allie, Kelly, Alyson and Rose did our nice little half-assed 15 minute run... We jogged mad slow around the upstairs of the school and took like 5 breaks. Normally we have to run for at least 30 minutes, without stopping, and with coaches watching our every move, so it was some well-deserved nothingness. Then there was the whole basketball thing which I really do not understand at all. But I have no say in these things so whatever. So out of 3 hours of lacrosse practice, we used our sticks and did something actually somewhat related to the sport for a grand total of 15 minutes. THE LIST is being posted supposedly on Friday, so I take it we are also getting uniforms Friday considering we have a scrimmage the next day. Allie and I are definitely looking forward to the game against Jefferson on the 7th because we have acquired quite a few enemies over there in J-town. Could it be because we kicked their asses twice? Or just because we're assholes? Hmmm... w()()t.... I'm so looking forward to running a timed mile tomorrow.... yeeeah not. But hey, its nothing compared to yesterday.   Oh well.... I'm in a strangely good mood. I don't know why. I think I'm bipolar or something haha.... Yesterday I was in a really really bad mood and today I'm in a good one. I have weird random mood swings. Oh wellllll, it doesn't matter. At the moment, its all good in the neighborhood.  Now I think I will attempt to work on my history research thing a little bit and wait for the kid to come home from where ever he is, 'cause at the moment, I have no one to talk to, which is why I am continuing to ramble in this thing. But now I'm done.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Rob made me an awesome logo. This stupid thing won't let me put it as my title thing though so its just going in here.     Yep, those are Rob's fingers. Its great isn't it? It kind of reminds me of that time... oh wait... that wasn't Rob.... I mean... that never happened... arg SHUT UP. Haha, good times... Sort of...
     

    
</post>

<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I love lacrosse, especially that whole practicing and running thing. *shoots self in foot*. I also like how Nick keeps trying to find every little excuse for me to quit though.... Its like "What? You got a paper cut? Oh damn, it looks like you're going to have to quit lacrosse..." Its not going to happen, but it makes me laugh a little anyway. Its only the second day and I'm already getting a bad vibe from this deal. But if its even half as good as last year, it will be worth it I guess, plus now I can just cause myself intense pain every day! Woohoo. Oh well.   So last night, Nick and Rob and Kelly came over and we sort of but not really watched "Freaky Friday." Then we watched "The Brave Little Toaster Goes to Mars" which was crrrrazy awesome. And of course Sir Nicholas was used as my pillow (my very boney pillow) and I fell asleep several times. My hair was a great source of entertainment as well... yeeeeeah... And it was like the first time ever that Rob was somewhat quiet... all thanks to the loss of his voice. It was insane. And I think I was also sort of sick. But still, it was good times.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today kind of sucked. It was ok in the morning until about 7-ish. Then there was some confusion and sadness slash anger between one of my bestest friends and I. I'd sort of like to blame Rob for this, but I can't because it was my fault and I did some stupid stuff. It was something like this: I did something bad-ish and stupid that I guess I shouldn't have done... Then when Rob told Nick about it he got all mad that I did it in the first place, but mostly mad because I lied. So he was pissed off all day and ignoring me and I didn't really understand what was going on, and then Rob sort of filled me in but I was still pretty confused about it, so the day continued with me being sad and unable to concentrate on the stupid HSPA test bullshit, and with Nick all ignoring me and wanting me to die and such. All because of one stupid little thing I did. So later, I got on the bus to go home (for the last time till June), and normally I sit with Nick, but he was being all Danielle-hating, so I sat down in the seat behind him and talked to my awesome tiny twin/ B.U.S. buddy, Erica. Then Amy got on and we discussed how much we hate certain conniving (yeah, I just learned how to spell that word properly all thanks to the spell checker thing that they have on here.)athletic equipment stealing bitches. Then something strange happened. James sat down next to Rob. Now, the whole James sitting down next to Rob thing wasn't really strange. What was strange was just the fact that he was there, since he doesn't actually go to school very often. Anyway, I decided to just be an asshole the whole time, because somehow, when I'm pissed off, being an asshole just makes it amusing. So we were all sitting there looking at this little book thing that James had and there was all this stuff about sex and drugs and such, then Rob turns to the page entitled "Mental Health," which had all.....  Holy ADD subject change interruption thing, Batman!: I love how my grandma just called and told me I'm boring.  Anywho, as I was saying:                                                                                                                    ...stuff about depression and self mutilation and suicide and he hands it to me. Then I looked at it, didn't read a word of it other than those subtitles and threw it at him, and it was kind of funny because both Rob and James looked like they were going to dive out of the way.. but really it was just kind of like James leaned one way and Rob went the other way...Yeah nevermind... But it was fun (or something). Then I sat there being all sad and every once in a while threw in some asshole comment just to be... well... an asshole. Not that it mattered anyway because Nick probably couldn't hear me since he was sitting there listening to music and hating me. Although the asshole comments weren't even specifically directed towards him. They were really just general asshole-isms. Yeah, I'm stupid, I know. So then when I got home, I actually did something somewhat smart. For once I tried to fix what I fucked up. So I called Nick. He was still pissed for a while, but something, I'm not sure what, but something made him change his mind. So everything is ok now.... I hope....   Other than that, today was quite uneventful, unless I was just completely oblivious to anything that might have happened. Lacrosse starts tomorrow. Ugh... That kind of sucks. Oh well. My family members are assholes. Goodbye.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow I just realized that my blog has pretty much just become indirect conversation between me and Phil. Its cool how hes the only person that reads this besides Nick (nothing against either of them because they're cooler than an eskimo in a whip cream bikini....or something....) You know I enjoy being a big loser waste of life kid. I love it like I love bleeding out my mouth after being hit in the face by Amy's water bottle. Really. Its quite fun. You should try it sometime.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bad day. Sort of. Sorry for these shitty ass updates, but this is just the way its been lately. Shitty.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow i have had nothing to say lately. But now i do. and here it is:  1. Phil is awesome. 2.  urlLink This is why Phil is awesome.  3. If i had a cock, the school administration would so be sucking it right now for not letting me see the crazy awesome Philly-fro. 4. I forget where i was going with this. 5. I suck at life. 6. Oh well. 7. Lacrosse starts in 3 days. 8. Amy and I have been running 2 miles everyday. 9. My legs hurt. 10. James just called. 11. Steve is making me leave so.... 12. To be continued....
     

    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I hate fighting.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, yesterday was some good times. I had a lax game against Hanover. We won... By a lot... I got my first yellow card (woot woot)! Then I went to Nick's house, and a bunch of his relatives were there for his confirmation thing. His 2 cousins were like in awe of me... It was crazy. Crazy little kids... They were all like playing with my hair and telling Nicky to kiss me haha, it was great. Then Rob said he was going to ride his bike over, so we decided to walk to his road to meet him, so we sat on this big rock on a hill across from a lake (so poetic-ish, haha). We were waiting for like 20 minutes, and Rob never showed, so we went back to Nick's house and it turns out, Rob walked in the front door at the exact same time we walked out the back door. How nuts is that? So Rob was all like on the computer playing games and I fell asleep on the floor, then we had food and watched "My Cousin Vinny." Then Rob left as well as Nick's family members and I went back to sleep on the floor with my pillow/ Nick and then I went home at 11 and went to sleep in my bed.  Then today, Nick came over and we watched "Malibu's Most Wanted" and "Viva La Bam" and he beat me up (mwahaha) and such then he went home (sad face). Then I ate star soup and learned 110 SAT words then got all crazy confused. It was an enjoyable time. Now I'm going to go converse with el chico and eat veggie lasagna, all gangsta-retarded Garfield style.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yo dawgs and dawgettes, long time no blog, eh? Yeah so..... Nick is standing behind me. Well he was, but he just walked away. And now he's back. Um yeah I'm done. I will improve the updatage later.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I need to learn how to make my posts colorful.   And no one comments in here anymore! ... although Phil and Nick are the only people that ever read it anyway...
     

    
</post>

<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok Phil just explained Easter to me:   lamY mclAme laMe:  today is the day christ rose from the grave  lamY mclAme laMe:  ...and then layed pretty colored eggs around  James and I have also come to the conclusion that Steve ate the Easter Bunny.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My cat isn't responding too well to the name change. Everytime I call him Rip Van Kitten, he just looks at me funny and walks away. Cats, man.  Today is Easter, the day that some religious thing happened so now we celebrate. I don't understand, probably never will, and honestly don't really care to know.  My favoritest aunt is here. She keeps beating me over the head with questions about the love life.  I flung a pig at my dad's head with a spoon. Now that is what I call "Holiday Entertainment."  The Easter Bunny didn't visit my house this year... but hey, Santa never showed either, so why should I expect some faggy bunny to give me candy and such?   Sigh... 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *Sigh*...... :) Nick is awesome :)   In other news, today we had a game in Wayne Hills. We lost. Varsity was 13-4 or something, I don't really know because I was sleeping on the ground through that whole game. JV was 6-4. I scored 2 of those 4. w00t. After that we had lunch with their team because last year we threw a lunch party thing for them, so they repaid the favor and we ate a lot. We met this girl who lives in Highland Lakes during the summer and is going to our junior prom so we're going to see her there. She was nice. I don't remember her name though. Oh well.  Last night Nick came over then we went out for pizza and we made him drink stuff because he has a fear of liquids then we went back to my house and watched Matilda and Dude, Where's My Car? It was good times. Very good times.  Oh yeah and I got my prom dress motha fuckas. Now I'm one of the loser cool kids.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Blah.. I saw Marky Sweet Cheeks today!! I saw him at Chrispy's v-ball game, and let me tell you, it made me oh so happy. I went from seeing Marko every day in like August and September, then boom, shit happened, and I didn't see Marky anymore due to this shit's happening. Oh well. Tis all good now I guess. I have my first game tomorrow, which was supposed to be Friday but was rescheduled due the the ickness of the field and such.   Friday I got hit in the face with a basketball in gym class and most likely got a concussion, although we'll never really know for sure due to the lack of going to the doctor-ness. I didn't practice lax that day because my head was throbbing. Lights still hurt my head, so I just sit in the dark a lot.  I spent the whole weekend at Amy's, post head injury, since my family went off somewhere and left me behind. We went to the mall Saturday, spent $30 of my mom's money on underwear, a belt and 2 shirts, then we went to the school play (Sweeney Todd) which sucked by the way. Except that one... nevermind... All I have to say is this: Kermit the Frog + a bus = ??? You know.   Oh yeah, we watched "Gothika". It was FUCKED UP to say the least.  I hate school, yaddy yadda, Chrispy hates being penetrated in the ear.   Goodnight and Happy Chickens to you all.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yo, I'm in Photo, 8th period, doing nothing. Jared's not here, and even though its April Fool's day, I'm too lazy for the prankage. So today, 6th period, in Trig with Trivento, I was proposed to. By John the Polish kid. We're going to Vegas to elope. Or not, because then what about my Nicholas? I hate my English teacher. She's a stupid bitch. I'm so obnoxious in that class now just because I hate her. She acts all fakely nice, but she's really all stupid and conniving. People in my class are talking about how some girl shat in a tanning bed. Strange. I think my game is going to be canceled tomorrow, which kind of sucks because the hour I have to kill before my game is the only time I have to spend with Nick this weekend (insert sad face here).  Ok, Jared just walked in and put on the Yeah Yeah Yeah's. I'm going to shoot myself. Or him. Someone. I fucking can't stand the Yeah Yeah Yeah's. I hate them so much. Seriously I'm cringing right now listening to this shit. I want to take something sharp and shove it into my eyeballs or something.  Happy April Fool's Day, Assholes :-D
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sick, it's Skit Day. English blows. Good day.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wowee what a weekend... Went prom shopping for Nicholas and there was this Nazi lady and yeah.... And then we went to the Outback for my padre's birthday. They ran out of mother fucking pork chops which is the only thing I eat from the Outback. Those Aussie bastards.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So there's this thing called a family.... Can someone PLEASE tell me what that is? Because I really don't know.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Holy cow, I haven't blogged it up in a long ass time. So here's the game plan. I'm going to get blogified.  So what has happened since my last post? *shrugs* Prom mayhaps... That was fun. We hung about with Allie and Donnie and Matt and Elaine and such. It was good times.  Other news, Nick and I broke up temporarily, but we don't like to remember that. It was bad times.  I got a job!! I started working at Dairy Queen last week. I like it. Its fun. I just don't think I ever want to eat ice cream again though.  I think I'm dying, but I don't know. I may have to go get blood tests and junk to find out what's wrong with me. Ick.  I went to that show the other day. It was super. Did I just say super?.... No.....  Oh here's some huge news. I recently made amends with some very good friends of mine with whom I had what we'll call a "falling out", but it is all well and wonderful now. I love those crazy kids.  I don't know what else there is to tell. Not much else has happened lately. Oh well. Time to pretend to be doing research in Espanol.
     

    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I forgot something.  You are NOT an asshole, no matter what I ever said before. No matter what anyone else says, no matter what you think. You did everything for me and I threw it all away. I hate myself for this. I hate myself for making you believe in me then fucking it all up. You were the only one who ever believed me or cared about me at all. I hate myself for letting this fall apart. I hate myself for every stupid thing I did and every mistake I made that led to this. And I know nothing I can say will ever change your mind. And its not ok, its not ok at all. But the only thing I can do is let you know how sorry I am, whether or not you believe me. I just needed you to know. There's nothing else I can do.   I know you're ok, I know you'll be happy, but I'm not you, and I'm not happy. I won't be ok at all after this.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Remember when I said "I love you"? .... Well I still do. But thank you, for making me worthless.   Now with those Alkaline Trio and Funeral for a Friend references successfully and meaningfully enstated, we move on to other....stuff.   Today I woke up at about 1. I missed a phone call that I've been waiting for forever. Actually I've seemed to miss the only calls that matter lately. But I guess it doesn't matter because nothing is going to change and nothing is going to be ok, no matter what is said. The main reason for that is that, well, I suck at life. Its as simple as that.  I'm still sad. But my day went ok anyway. I did absolutely nothing all day which is ok I guess, but I'd rather not have done nothing alone. There is absolutely nothing I want more than to do nothing at all, as long as Nick is there. But he's not. And I can't fix it. And there's nothing I wouldn't give to fix it. I'd give up everything. I know I'm not worth much, but that has to mean something...  Anyway, after a long lonely day, I had to go to work at 6. This evening I was working with Christine and Nicole... It was good times. Nick's cousin came in 3 times. And of course he came to my window every time so I could get all nice and sad. Then Nicole dropped an entire cone into the chocolate dip. And we laughed for like 20 minutes straight even though it wasn't really that funny... Ok yeah it was. haha. And our boss guy was being a dickface all night, especially after I jokingly called Christine a bitch. :-) Well later on Christine left, an hour before we closed and me and Nicole couldn't finish cleaning anything, especially when Phil and Eustace and Gary came in and harassed us excessively. Eustace attempted to fit his entire body through the window and I wanted to close it on his neck and decapitate him, that bastard. Then they tried to perform a strip tease and such, and Eustace stole all of my lids, which I almost got bitched at for, but I just denied any knowledge of the noise and the fact that there were plastic lids strewn throughout the lobby. Gah I want to kill them. But I can't stay mad at those stupid motherfuckers. Haha. Then as soon as it was 11, Nicole and I busted a fuckin move out of that joint. I think my mom was completely wasted too. Good frickin times.   Things are crazy right now. I don't even know what's going on anymore.  Screw it. I'm tired. And sad.  I fucked up, big time. And I no longer believe in second chances, at least not for myself.  Goodnight. Only minus the good part. So I guess just, Night.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      All I can think of to say is I'm sorry. More than you will ever know...   But I will never be ok with this.    
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So... where do I start now? I've gone and convinced myself that everything is grand. Hah, who am I kidding? Well I just spent some time reminiscing with one of my best friends the way we did all the time last summer, staying up late and bullshitting about how everything is, was, or will be. I missed that. A lot. More than anyone will probably understand, and more than anyone could possibly care about. After everything, I'm glad we could just pick up right where we left off.   Besides that, I guess its ok to just spill all of this crap right here, right now since no one will probably ever read it anyway so I don't think it could do that much harm. I never thought that talking about ice cream could piss someone off so much, but leave it to me to succeed in doing that. Maybe I've just been doing a whole bunch of little things to piss him off and I didn't realize it till it, I just made him crack, or maybe there's just some hidden crime in simply saying you want ice cream. I don't really know. All I know is that my very own frigging boyfriend completely flipped out on me, entirely out of nowhere when I said that. I really don't fucking understand it. Part of me is convinced that for whatever reason, I completely deserved that. And part of me resents the part of me that thinks that ( I dont want to become someone else that I know so well).... I'm sure I did something to provoke the flipping out-age... I just dont exactly have any idea what it was that I did wrong. And after this happens all I get is a repetition of "I'm sorry I'm such an asshole, go ahead and say it." Yeah I'm sorry you're an asshole too. No attempts to even make me feel better... you hand me a phone and tell me to go home. Then you call me this morning to say you get off work at 8 and that  I  can call you then if  I  want to talk. Its not my move. Hence the fact that I didn't call. You pushed me away. You flipped out on me. You can fix it if its worth it to you. The way I see it, if you don't try, its not worth it to me, because I didn't deserve that.... or did I? I don't know. Maybe if you explain it to me....  There's more bullshit, but I no longer feel like sharing.  Cool. My life is grand. Here we fucking go again.   
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Thats an awesome line. Silly Thursday. Anywho. Not sleeping and not eating is making me really sick. Its not good.   I drove solo today. First I went to the high school to drop off my senior picture junk and fix my schedule. Its so random: 1. English- Kaicher 2. Calculus- Freifelder 3. Gym (with the love of my life, Amy.) 4. Human Bio- Kuplin (Again with Amy.) 5. Lunch (With Erica, Natch, Dan Rist, and Nicoley Oley Bonilly. Excellent I say.) 6. Italian- Haddeland (was physics but fuck that) 7. Photo Major- Roppolo 8. Spanish AP- Galati (with Alyson, and such.)  Pretty decent senior year, I'd say. I'm not slacking off or anything this time around.  So anywho, then I drove to Dairy Queen so my boss could make me some lunch and to get some ice cream for Steve. And a Coke because I needed caffiene, hardcore. I should have just gotten some Bawls, dammit.   After that I delivered ice cream to Steve, then went to Mike's house to drop off his sunglasses. :( They'll come back to me someday, mwahaha. Then I found James' house and then almost hit a dog. Then I wont home and then decided I needed to get gas to cover up all of the aimless driving I did. Then I talked to Amy on the telephono, and I just remembered I was supposed to call her back, and then I looked at the time and realized, fuck I have to shower and get ready for work now.  So goodbye for now, blog viewers.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey, you know, I've been a real fuckbag lately. I'm sure all of my friends and even people who can't stand me have noticed. Well, I'm sorry. I'm sorry for being an ass all the time. But I'm not sorry to fake people who act like they're something they're not and lie and say something that means a lot to someone then condradict it to someone else, who it also means a lot too. Just because everyone likes you, it doesn't give you the right to fuck with other people. So fuck you. And thats it for today. I flipped a shit earlier which I really needed to get out of my system, but that probably didn't help the situation I'm in.  So anyway, forgive me. I'm pathetic. I'm a fuckbag. It happens.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Random survey nonsense so you can learn all sorts of useless information about me:  Full Name: Danielle Lauren Enman  Nicknames: Yella, Daniyeller, Daniyella, Tiny Twin (with Erica), Devil Grill, Biz, some other random ones.  Hometown: Originally Rockaway, but been in Vernon most of the time.  Croutons or Bacon Bits: Hmm probably bacon bits.  Favorite Salad Dressing: Greek vinagerette  Have you ever gone skinny dipping? Of course.  Do you make fun of people: Not in a mean way usually, not people who don't really deserve it.  Have you ever been convicted of a crime?: Psh, nope.  Best online friends: Mike, I suppose, and probably Roberto/ Natch even though we haven't talked in a while. Used to be Nick but now we just fight.  One pillow or two?: Two... speaking of pillows... :(  Pets: a whole random bunch  Favorite Type of Music: hmm as long as its not country, rap, pop, or well really anything other than rock, I'm not that picky (haha)  Hobbies: Guitar, sleep, music, lacrosse, is it bad that if I consider my job a hobby too?  Dream Car: A viper maybe.. red or blue. The 1992 model.  Type of Car you drive now: White 1991 Pontiac Firebird with t-tops 8-)  Words or Phrases you overuse: Bud, Fuck, Kid, like, I don't know, and probably a lot of others  Toothpaste: Anything that cleans my mouth.  Favorite Food: Tacos and chicken.  Online Crush: Psh, thats silly.  Current Boyfriend/Girlfriend: None :( I miss him though.  Piercing or tattoos?: Just my ears currently, but soon there will be more in the ears and 2 tattoos, one of this APO logo thing, and this other one with a bunch of stars.  Most romantic thing that ever happened to you: There's been a few. I don't want to think about it though, even though they were the happiest moments of my life, I'm still sad. :(  Do you get along with your parents: Not in the slightest. On rare occasions, maybe, but for the most part, its a not a happy relationship.  Favorite town to chill in: Hmmm. I really don't know. But Mike just very intelligently suggested Sun Valley, even though its not really a town, but its the best little section to hang about in, with the best kids ever. :)  Favorite Ice Cream: Cookie dough  Favorite Soft Drink: Coke or Sprite... or orange soda... well ok really anything thats not Root Beer.  What's your bed time: N/A  Adidas, Nike, or Reebok: Do I look like a silly little jock to you? Well if i had to choose, for shoes, Nike, but for like sweatpants and stuff Adidas is godly. Reebok blows.  Favorite Perfume/Cologne: Cologne, Adidas Adrenaline (another thing Adidas is good for) Perfume, anything that smells nice, really. I'm not picky.  Favorite Song at the moment: I don't know, there's a lot. But one of the most favoritests I guess would be "Logan to Government Center" by BrandNew.  Favorite Website: www.emogame.com (Its the best thing ever.)  Least Favorite Subject in School: English  Favorite Sport to Watch: Volleyball or lax  Most humiliating moment: Hmm lets not remember all of those.  Loudest person you know: Oh man, I don't know... I'm pretty loud sometimes... Wow I really can't think of anyone. Oh yes I can... Shannon Roth.  Craziest person you know (or silliest): Well, theres the whole man clan, plus maybe Oyen, and Ryan Eustace.   Favorite Holiday: Halloween or Christmas  What do you look for in the opposite sex?: sense of humor, honesty, eyes and smile. :) I miss that too... :(  Things I've learned from life: I fuck things up. A lot.  Favorite number: 27  Favorite color: gray. It covers all the angles.  Greatest experience in your lifetime: The past 4 months, well at least before 2 weeks ago.  Why are you here on earth?: I honestly don't know.  Who means the most to you?: Nick  Have you ever been in love?: I'm pretty sure I was, but it doesn't matter now...  Who makes you laugh the most?: There's a few... Mike, Eustace, Mark, some random others  Who do you go to for advice?: Mike or Erica.  Who knows the most about you?: I dont know, I guess Amy.  When was your last hospital check in?: September of my freshman year I think, when I broke my arm. The last time I went to the hospital was a few months ago for some psych. apppointments but I wasn't technically checked in.  Do You Drink?: Not anymore.  How many times did you fail your permit and Drivers License Test?: Written, twice, road test, none.  What do you do most often when you are bored?: read and listen to music.  PREFERENCES (would you rather/ do you prefer...) 1. Pierce your nose or tongue? Neither but I suppose the nose (and kill me for rhyming...) 2. Boxers or briefs? Boxers of course 3. Whole or skim milk? Ew. 4. Law or anarchy? Whichever. 5. Flowers or angels? what the hell do the 2 have to do with each other? 6. Grey or gray? grAy. not grey. GRAY. 7. Read or write? Both 8. Color or black-and-white photos? Black and white 9. Sunrise or sunset? Sunset. I hate mornings anyway. 10. M&M's or Skittles? Skittles 11. Rap or rock? Rap, fo' shizzle. Ok I was kidding. Rock. Nothing else. 12. Stay up late or wake up late? They go hand in hand, ya stay up late, ya wake up late, like I do quite often. 13. TV or Radio? Radio, I suppose but both suck. 14. Is it POP or SODA? Soda, you POP drinking fucks. 15. X or O in Tic-tac-toe? X 16. Eat an apple or an orange? depends on the day, but more often, apple. 17. Purple or green? green 18. Corduroy or plaid? Cords. 19. Singing or dancing? Singing. 20. Blonde or brunette? Brunette 21. What came first the chicken or the egg? Your mom. Then she fornicated with a bird-like creature and out pops this egg, and the chicken is invented. Or something, you sick fuckbag. 22. Hot or Cold? Hot. 24. Tall members of the opposite sex or short? Short 25. Sun or moon? Sun. 26. Emerald or ruby? Ruby. 28. Left or right? Left. Just because. But I'm right-handed. 29. 10 acquaintances or 1 best friend? 1 best friend 30. Vanilla ice cream or chocolate ice cream? I'm sick of any type of ice cream. 31. High or Drunk? Ew, neither. 32. Green beans or carrots? Carrots give me hiccups, but I don't have a preference. 33. Low fat or fat free? Does it really matter? 34. What is your biggest fear in the world? Well one already happened 2 weeks and 2 days ago. 36. Kids or no kids? Kids. 37. Cat or dog? Cat... but dogs are ok too but not stupid prissy dogs. 38. Half empty or half full? depends what it is. Unopened bags of chips are half empty usually. A glass of some sort of beverage is probably half full. 39. Mustard or ketchup? Ketchup. But only on hamburgers and french fries. 40. Hard cover books or soft cover books? The cover doesn't matter. Its what's inside that counts. 41. Newspaper or magazine? Magazine 42. Sandals or sneakers? Sandals 43. Wonder or amazement? Either one.  44. Red car or white car? Depends on the car. I mean, my white Firebird is one sexy piece of automobile. But most other cars are better red. 45. Happy and poor or sad and rich? Happy and poor. 46. Hugging or Kissing? Hugging I think, but kissing is awesome too. Hugging is more of a comfort thing though. I need that. 47. A year of hot sex or a lifetime of friendship? a lifetime of hot sex with your best friend. hahaha    Ok I'm bored with this now because its long and whatnot. Be cool and copy and paste it and fill yours out in the comments. I'm betting 2 people, max, actually even consider doing it. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Mr Shrubs69: im reading your thingy  Mr Shrubs69: i dont know what it isoh its a blog  Mr Shrubs69: but alot of the things you write sound like songs  Mr Shrubs69: its sick   James is a fan. This is crazy.   In other news, my parents forgot to pick me up from work again... and I swore I wouldn't cry today. I almost destroyed that. I hate them so much.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am not going to cry today. No matter what.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm miserable... how can you being doing this to me? 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Its about time you finish forgetting about me. I know you started and I've been trying to keep it from happening, but I'm not going to stop you anymore. Just erase me from your memory.    I'll erase myself entirely soon anyway.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Once that something is gone it might never reappear."  "And I stay up all night walking through these houses I have grown to hate."  "And I don't know on which side his heart falls  But I know where mine is buried  And it's so far from any wanting  Yeah, it needs this to keep beating  It won't go on without it."  "But now there is no way to change this  So I just photographed and framed it  And its hanging in a hallway  That we have no right to walk back down"    I wish I never felt this way.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I forgot something again, and how I could possibly forget this, I don't really know. I guess I was just pretending I didnt believe it. But I found out something from my best friend last night and even after all the fun I had, to be quite honest, I went home and cried. Not even the best night ever can save you from the truth.  You pretended to be some other girl's boyfriend. While we were still together. Not just "Hey I'm her boyfriend." You put your arms around her and everything. Then you blame me for keeping shit from you, shit that wasn't even my fault, it wasn't stuff that I did out of free will, but what you did was. You blamed me for everything. You just needed an excuse, it sounds better than saying "hey I don't give a fuck about you anymore." You blamed me for everything so I would come out looking worse than you. So you wouldn't have to hurt nearly as much as I do.  Just when I thought it couldn't possibly hurt any worse, here I am.  I want nothing more than to be completely motionless.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night was a fucking excellent night. My beloved Shannon Roth invites me and Amy over to hang out with her and Nicole, so we go and we sit around doing nothing for a while. Then Mike, Mark, Chris, and Gary show up to pick up Dan to go do stuff for Mark's birthday. So being the crazy bored kids that we were, we decided to tag along. Then some whores showed up and whatnot, but they weren't important. We went to the movies to see The Village (which sucked my nonexistant penis, by the way) and Chris drove all of us gals and we talked about silly things such as uteruses and bad things that I accidentally say, and such (mwahahaha) and weirded him out in the car. It was excellent-ay. So after the movie it was like 12 and we went to the Taco Bell drive-thru shindig and got some mexican pubes and such. Then we met up with Gary, Mark, Mike and Dan in the back parking lot of the nearby Wal-Mart. We had a nice little taco picnic (wink wink, it was a beautiful little taco/sausage party). Then we played car tag around the parking lot and threw beverages and garbage and other nonsensical objects at each other, and then we drove home and Chris drove on the wrong side of the road halfway there. It was gorgeous. Then Marky Sweet Cheeks puked all over Gary's vehicle. That was also gorgeous. Then... I don't know, it was kind of over after that. But, honestly, that was the most fun I've had in a while. :-)    ....aaaaaand stuff.   The End.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>