<Blog>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      by Ernie Kerns
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Story of Aan
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is my test... my dilema. I am just one man.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
                               
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Aan looked at the man. He could smell his terror and his betrayal. There was no hiding it from Aan's keen senses.  "What is your name?" Aan demanded. "Ensign Toby Pierce, my lord." He bowed his head as he said this. In respect or some other emotion? "Well, Toby Pierce. Why? I'm curious... Why did you bring that apparition to me and then cover it up?" I leaned towards him and opened my mouth a bit to show my teeth. I found his gasp rewarding. His knees literally went weak and he started to swoon. I was amused but satisfied that I had the right man but were there others and what was this all about... I wanted to know. I pulled back from him so he could catch his breath and I might learn more from him. "Stand at attention when I'm speaking with you. I don't care if you are a traitor you will respect me." I snarled. He righted himself then and managed to get something close to an attention stance.  "I'm sorry, my Lord. I did not mean to offend. I am not guilty of any crime of treason." He looked at me with pleading eyes then. "I did try to cover up the visit but it wasn't for treason." "Then why?" I stood up and moved towards him. "The only explanation I could find for the energy anomaly would cause a worse problem. It was Shiraz energy." He stammered. "Shiraz energy? I demand to know where it came from. I am aware of the type of energy already." I grabbed him by the uniform. "Are you a practitioner of the Shiraz ceremony?" I shook him a little while lifting his feet from the ground an inch or so. "I am a believer." He squeaked. "I had nothing to do with that visit though. I just practice for my own benefit." "Your benefit? Even you should know the consequence of being a practitioner of that banned religion? You see a benefit here?" I set him down for the moment but then I moved in a bit closer. "I cannot help believing. It has set me free and saved me." He said bravely. He had to know my reputation. He was very brave. I had to watch this one and yet I respected him much more now. I could not let him know I had been a member of that banned sect so many years ago. Usually I killed those who were discovered in a quick and painless way. "Who is your Shiraz partner? Did they entice you into this practice? I will punish them and release you if that is the case." I moved back to my consol then to give him a feeling of safety and to provide myself with the same- he could have been booby-trapped. "You know I cannot divulge that to you. I would protect him till the day I die. Even if that day and moment were now and your terrible claws were the means of death." He stood there looking much more calm now. Sweet. He's so noble and young and foolish. It seemed a shame to kill such people but there is a good side to doing so. If someone must die for what he believes and he sticks with that choice to the end then you have given him or her knowledge of his or her own power. If anyone could practice the Shiraz and there was no down side to it then the up side, that self-knowledge, would be reduced. I was doing them a huge favor by killing them when they were discovered and it was a crime to split up a pair since the survivor would be damaged for all time. I know since I was the survivor in my pair and look at what I had become. I looked at my reflection now and I shivered inside. My body was fierce and firm with huge teeth and a long claw used to rip the living flesh off of my living meals. The rest of my hand was human but I had to have the claw to assist in eating. That was the downside I had chosen with this body- I had to eat live creatures and watch them die in the process. I could eat dead things if I had too but my senses were too good for my own good. I could taste the rot in flesh that's been dead for even a few minutes so I now feasted on living creatures exclusively. Why would you choose to live in a body like this? The brain was better thanks to our scientist?s modifications and it lived a very long time. Our main enemy was in this same body, which was the deciding factor. We had to have someone who was as ruthless and brilliant as he but without his desire to destroy our civilization. I made the ultimate sacrifice for my people. I turned my attention back to my prisoner. "Letting your partner live on without you is not being kind to them. You must realize the pain they will endure without you around. Most Shiraz partners expose themselves anyway when they mourn so why not make it easy on both of you? I promise to make your death wonderful and painless. If you don't tell then I will have to make it really hurt for you and it will be worse for the other." Now I waited. We stood staring at one another. He kept his mouth shut. "Time's up. What is your decision?"  "I choose the most painful and terrible death that you can possibly arrange for me." He said in defiance. I smiled with my teeth at him. "Good for you." I jumped to him and my right claw extended. It sunk into the flesh of his right buttocks and it pulled him to me. He involuntarily gasped at the pain. My claw moved up tearing flesh for half an inch or so. "You still feel that way?" I asked him. He closed his eyes and gasped a word. I assume it was yes. He fainted then and slumped towards me. I pulled my claw from him and let him drop to the floor. What was I to do with him?
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I decided to do some investigating myself. It isn't much good having an intellect superior than the best human genius if you weren't going to use it for anything. I stepped into my console again and started probing both the ship and my memory. I guess that gave me an advantage since only I had access to my memory of the incident and of the past that it reminded me of now. I scanned for metaphysical energy readings. We had learned to detect this type energy during The Purge when I was just a child. The sensors had a reading but the source was not obvious. What was obvious to me was that someone was not on my side and was attempting to cover up the tracks of this energy trace. It could be the captain or any of the crew assigned to help him. I was furious. My rage grew up within me and turned cold. I would find this traitor and then I would learn the truth. Humans could not hide their feeling from me. Their nervous systems were incapable of lying to me and getting away with it, which is why I knew the Captain himself probably, wasn’t my culprit. I hadn’t asked specific questions though so I could not rule him out completely yet. I would know shortly. I waved my right hand over the 3d console and pulled up the roster of those crewmen assigned to find my visitor. I called them all to an emergency meeting in my chamber. They would all get the point. I gave them ten minutes to report to me.  I made them wait an extra 20 minutes on me as I observed them from my cubicle. I was looking for the telltale signs- the heart rate that betrays its body. I had a couple possibilities so I would have to take time in person to discover my traitor. I wasn’t using voodoo or any mystical powers- just simple bodily reactions that all humans displayed when they lied or when they knew they had done something bad. I could see that the Captain was not experiencing any symptoms. I had him come to me first. I turned in my console to face him. He entered and I bid him come to me. He hesitated but I urged him come all the way to me. He did and kneeled before me.  “Captain. Look at me.” I ordered and he obeyed. “I have placed my trust in you. Is that trust well placed?” “Yes, my lord. I have never betrayed you nor our purpose.” He stated. I stared at him for a long moment, measuring his heart rate and breathing.  “I believe you and I’m glad.” I said and I meant it. “Go and start sending the others to me one at a time. I will let you know when the time for each man’s visit has come.” “Is there something I should know, my Lord?” He looked concerned. “I suspect that one of these men is working against us. I found evidence of tampering in the log files.” I pulled the files up to show him on the console next to me and highlighted the forged area.  “This is out of your area, Captain. I do not hold you responsible for this treason. Go now and send in the first man.”  “As you wish, my Lord.” He bowed and walked from me into the chamber.   A few minutes later, the door opened and in stepped the man I suspected of actually being involved with this plot. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I spent the day meditating in my cabin. My breath was under my complete control. My mind was clear of all distractions. I began to go over the conversation with my visitor in my head. I wasn't concentrating on the words but on the voice and body movements. It bothered me greatly that I couldn't discern where he had come from yet he seemed so familiar to me. It was a memory of him but not of him that I was trying to find. It was from very long ago when I was just a human boy working on growing up- no real cares in my thoughts. I felt my mind slip back to that childhood. I was nine years old. My best friend and I were sitting on the floor together. My Mother was there. She encouraged us to hold hands. We were in the midst of the Shiraz Ceremony. It was an ancient practice from my Mothers religion. We sat on an elaborate carpet in dark cool room. My hands joined with his. We both began to chant slowly over and over. The warmth of his palms on mine was comforting. I didn't really believe in any of this but it was important to my Mother so I pretended for her sake. That changed when I felt my friends thoughts inside my own mind. He and I had joined mentally just as had been promised! It frightened me and I pulled my hands away from him. The contact broken we both stared into one anothers eyes. Mother wasn't angry but she was sad that I had not finished with the ceremony. The joining was the most sacred of practices and had to be done before puberty. "You still have time" she said. My visitors eyes were so much like his. It was improbable but I couldn't shake the feeling that my Shiraz mate had been the one who had visited me but he'd been dead and gone for an eternity. There was a knock at the door. I left my trance state. "Come in."   The Captain was back and he looked uncomfortable. He stood at the far end of the room not wanting to get too close. I guess I had let my anger get out of control before and he was hoping to avoid that. "Security could find no intruder, My Lord." He bowed his head at the end of his statement.  "Really. Did they check for energy fluctuations?" "Yes, my Lord. There was nothing out of the ordinary but it may have been missed by the start of the battle." "I want this cabin torn apart Captain. I want every reading from every instrument that has ever been created used on this place. I am not satisfied. Do you understand me? I don't care if there is on one millionth of a percent diference in a reading in this room I want to know about it. I want you to find this. Prepare new quarters for me and get those scientist in here." "Yes, my Lord. They will find it if it is at all possible." "They'll find something. I'm sure of it."
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I ordered my flagship and a small contingent of it's battlegroup to return to our home world. It was many weeks flight and may keep the enemy guessing as to where I would be. I didn't feel like handling a direct conflict with my foe right now. He tended to wait to attack where he knew I was going to be. The trick I learned was to keep moving and force him to find me. His fleet was strong and brutal in it's tactics but it did not grow any bigger or stronger so each battle depleted his options more. Time, then was on my side in this war and I refused to surrender to him- ever. I got a message in my comm unit. I entered it and watched the information unfold. One of our explorer class battle units had discovered another useful planet that had a moderate population and materials for our fleet. I dispatched an ambassador class to see if they would be willing to sign on to our side. It pays to just go and ask nicely- offering many privileges of membership that are not seen if you are one of the conquered races. Then if they say no you have all rights to wipe them from the face of their own planet without a disturbed thought. I had wiped more than a couple planets of intelligent life- those that would never surrender to us. You cannot afford the time to put down such a rebellion and the knowledge of other enemies that you will actually carry out your threat and obliterate them can have an effect.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You don’t know the why yet so don’t judge me. I have little choice but to take this sector and all sectors under our direct supervision to keep them from the hands of the enemy. He is ruthless and would destroy us all for his own pleasure. I sometimes wonder if I have also become what I detest in him but there seems little wiggle room here.  I have now enhanced my forces with the materials available from these people. I lost little to gain much and that’s what you look to do in a war of this caliber.  I dispatched our embassy ships to begin the occupation. They would handle the details with their stunning efficiency. I could actually turn my thoughts to bigger fish now.  What was that damned dream all about? I never have dreams- not since I changed bodies some time ago. It was one of the things I thought I’d sacrificed. I called the Captain of this flagship to my quarters. I didn’t worry that he might think me insane since even if I were so he would have to serve me without question.  I heard the slight nock at the door. I bid him enter. He is a striking fellow with his dark hair and blue eyes. Human still. I could smell his nervousness as he approached me and I noticed that he kept a good distance back as he always did.  “Captain. Good of you to join me.” I attempted to be cordial. “Please relax. I congratulate you and the others on our victory.” I found it is usually good to stroke your help some. He bowed his head towards me. “Thank you, my lord. It was your victory.”  “It is not possible without the loyal work of men like you.” I countered. “ I didn’t ask you here to get into a debate about who is to be congratulated though. I need your help.” I paused to make certain he had heard me. He remained silent and thoughtful. “I had a visitor right before the battle. If I were capable of dreaming then I would be inclined to dismiss this as a simple dream. I am not blaming you for this visit but I need you to find out who was in my quarters and how he got in here. Is that clear, Captain?” He appeared to turn white like a ghost then. I felt his heart rate increase. “I will get to the bottom of this immediately.”  “Excellent. Then I won’t spend another moment worrying about it happening again. Thank you, Captain. I look forward to your report in the morning.” I dismissed him with a wave of my hand.  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The generals seemed divided about whether to attack full out or just a small probe. I felt the enemies weakness and made the decision for them. I lifted my right claw to the controls and grabbed the center. Thirty ships in unision accelerated and slammed into the center of the enemy line of ships from 3 different directions. The enemy was unprepared for such a coordinated attack. Debris littered the space as the enemy was blasted by my attack. I felt the five ships die that had been under my control. We lost 5 ships but they lost much, much more. This seemed too easy. I had broken the defense in the center and these ships were now headed on to assault the planet itself. I raised my hand and grabbed another squad of ships to follow the first through the whole- knocking out any surviving and injured ships in the way. The enemy ships attempted to out-flank my two squads. My ships were faster. I knew This would cause the enemy to change their positions to attempt to stop the coming destruction. I was not known for my mercy to my enemies but you can't count on reputation in space- they may have never heard of me before. I ordered another wave of drone attack pods to follow the lead of the manned squads. The drones were not good at actual combat but they were great at the repetitive search and destroy and decoy functions. They did not feel remorse nor hesitate to carry out their orders. I like their obediance and often wish I could get the same from my human followers. As expected, the enemy lines completely collapsed as they rushed to stop the incoming death. I had them and nothing would stop it. Now should I wipe out all life on the planet or just damage them? I wondered to myself. I was feeling generous for the moment and ordered a straffing action only. My ships fired a volley and pulled up. I saw several cities on the planet light up briefly and then go dark. The drones swarmed by the planet keeping the enemy fighters busy. I had my image projected to their leaders and on every enemy fighter. "I order you to surender and submit to me. Lay down your arms and your planet will be spared. Resist and all will die. I have shown that we can destroy you now if we wished. What is your answer?"  I ordered my squads of ships both human and drone to move back to the main line. I could see their leaders distraut reactions. The main one bowed his head and offered me their surrender. It was finished except for the hard part- occupation.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Could the dream have been about this battle? I moved to a view pod. The battle was all around me now in 3d. My generals and tacticians would be sitting in similar pods on secure rooms on their ships. I felt my nervous system engage with the others. I could feel and hear their thoughts now as they gave orders and moved ships at great speeds. I have to laugh at the early programs dealing with space battles where the ships line up and attack from in front or behind. The problem with space is that they can come from any direction and they do if they plan on having a chance on winning. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I thought it was a dream. You know the feeling- when you have to pinch yourself to be certain that you are actually awake and even with the pain you are still not convinced. It may have been a dream though my body ached where my flesh was pulled together tightly. It seems real but then many dreams do. I am leaning towards the idea that  it was a dream because no one could have survived getting to me like he managed to do. I would have seen, heard, or smelled him coming. Yet, there he was. I saw him standing there in my room as plain as day in his white robe and gold sandals; his dark hair blew in the breeze from the air circulator. He smiled at me with a big, toothy, and friendly grin. I wasn't worried about him killing me since if that had been his purpose I'd have already been dead. He had the surprise factor on his side at that moment. I am quiet capable of defending myself in combat but if you don't know that they are there then it's a mute point. His clothing struck me as odd and reinforced the idea that I was indeed dreaming this figure. I searched through my many memories for some recognition of his face but I drew a blank. Do you dream of people you've never met before?  We were in my cabin on the ship. I could feel the engines throbbing through the floor. That's what made me think it wasn't a dream at that moment. I could never remember ever feeling the floor in a dream before. He slowly raised his right hand in a symbol of greeting. I nodded at him but I'm sure my instincts had taken over and my eyelids shuttered to half mast. My heart rate increased ready for action. I raised my right hand in response to his greeting.  "I am Tyre", he said. "Do not be concerned for you safety. I am not here to harm you." I couldn't help but bark out a small laugh then. He sounded so calm and sweet that you couldn't imagine him harming anyone. Most men would be trembling in my presence for their lives- this was one very brave person. I sniffed but no odor of him came to me- very odd.  I then decided to find out what he wanted without calling on the guards first. "I imagine you know who I am." I stated. "I am curious of how you managed to get into these rooms without being stopped." He stared at me with the greatest of interest on his face. "Stopped? Killed you mean? It wasn't hard. I didn't bother to use the door though. I am here to make a request of you." I knew that. They always want something from me. I grow so tired of being the noble lord for so many but it was the job I took for myself. I assumed the character for him then. It is a role I have been used to playing for some time. I summoned up my aura of power and slowly moved to my favorite seat. I then lowered myself into this seat that was specially designed for me without taking my eyes from him. I wanted him to be sure that I was in charge of this conversation now. It is important to maintain dominance over those who come to you, even the ones who surprise you like this one. "Ah. What is it that you need?" He moved closer to me. I couldn't hear any footsteps- not a dream but perhaps a vision? My hearing is one of my best senses. I could not feel him walking on the floor. I couldn't smell him still. I wondered if he was really there at all. He stooped into a kneeling position before me- one knee to the ground in respect. "I am not here for anything for myself but it's really for you and for all living things." He managed to surprise me again! No one ever came to me wanting things for me or for anyone else. "Go on.", I encouraged him. "May I touch your hand?" he asked. I could see no point in denying him. He wasn't armed and I would be able to then judge if he was actually there or not. I moved my right hand towards him offering it to him. He then took it with his own hand- first one and then the other clasping my hand. I could feel the warmth coming from him. Then I felt a wind rushing through me- like in a sudden storm within my body. It was unsettling but not frightening. I wondered if my very soul would be ripped from my body. I looked at him now. He seemed to glow with a radiance of the sun. Then I heard his voice in my head. 'We miss you and need you to come home to us. Make this journey of yours end and find your way, my brother. Your very existence is damaging the fabric of life and your own soul. You must find a way.' He was gone. I was sitting in my chair. My hand was stretched before me. The door to the room opened and one of my guards walked in. He looked curiously at me but said nothing. "What?" I demanded. "The battle has begun, my Lord. You asked to be informed when we had engaged them." He bowed to me and then backed out of the room. 
     

    
</post>




</Blog>