<Blog>


<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      okay everyone must  SERIOUSLY  get their own accounts soon because it is  SO CONFUSING  trying to read and find out who is who! okay anyway softball today was fun man x) i must talk about the stupid bus incident we had while leaving NUS. okay so the NUS bus stop we were at had only 95, 96 and 151. so 151 was the bus me, nana and some other people wanted to take. however i was taking it simply because i wanted to drop outside NUS for my mummy to pick me up. well nana they all wanted to take it to go home. so well since we were tired, we just plopped on the grass and waited while the guys kept a look out for the bus. so as time passes, 95 and 96 comes but still NO 151. we get impatient and start complaining then some of the guys suddenly said 'eh 151 here already!' then we all scramble up and rush to the bus stop. BUT all we see is the stupid road. so basically they were fooling around with us. o_0 then when they did it the 2nd and 3rd time nana still fell for it!! haha i didn't! clever me =] well then the stupid thing was that i wanted to take bus out of NUS so it's easier for my mummy to pick me up. however my mum ended up driving in to pick me up because the stupid bus just didn't appear for close to 40 mins. heh wonder how long more they waited after i left. oh well looking back up to what i wrote it doesn't sound as funny as i thought it was, but i think it is one of those things that you must be there to be able to understand. heh so anyway this is my entry of the day. do your homework people. =]
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Heyhey, this blog's getting interesting. So many poets actually publish their work here. Think sooner or later muz buy copyrights for them le. hee, hope anyone of u ppl would be famous for ur talents, so that i could sell this link to publishers. $$$  Just to let the class know: i'm holding a post in the band. So, any interested classmate can take over my post as CIP rep le. unless there isn't anyone, den i have to do the job, k? Basically, being CIP rep is good. You get to learn to organise activities with  STRANGERS.  (funny rite? mum actually taught me not to tok to strangers. so this job is highly dangerous)  juz for u all to kaypoh. The way i got this exco post is god damn  dramatic .  Nobody knows their positioning in terms  of the number of votes except for me!!! i'm 9th. Why? i was selected after one of the 8 new excos decide not to take up the job! it was DRAMATIC. i cant tahan my life animore. I HATE  DRAMAS ! Why make it so special that i must be given a "solo" timeslot to be introduced? Making me a surprise to everyone, even the year 2s also don't know it prior to the announcment.   By the way, i wanna formally thank everyone from 04S08 who have made contributions to this class blog. Without me, there wouldn't be a blog. Without your support, there wouldn't be a  class blog .
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       yet another weak attempt at being william wordsworth   Some amatuer poets' haven  Has become of this blog with poems laden That I find myself compelled to pen A poem now and then.  A disturbing matter I see arise Absolutely vicious and teeming with lies. A little note to those out there  PRETENSE  and  IGNORANCE  Should be distinguished with care  Isn't it how very embarrassing How immature you all are being? Blame of all things,exam blues I haven't got the vaguest clue  But if you want the tiger to spite then go on, continue to bite.  Girls,i conclude,are not sugar and spice And most definitely far from nice.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I HAVE DONE IT! just testing my new username! ke ai aren't you proud of me! x) well i don't care cause i am proud of myself. heh and i just realised that nana wrote like the LONGEST entry on the blog. anyway did junkai really tumble down the stairs cause he was looking and tending to CCA? MY GOODNESS that would be hilarious! oh and who is the person who wrote the entry  this is sad  i wanted to say something but i think it isn't suitable right now.  ?? 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this SJ. the blog thingy is so popular.... everyone types so much..i'm glad about that...but then ...pls post msg using own account hor. (this is juz to test my new username)  ALAMAK!!!! this is chaos. can blogspot pls be more user-friendly? we r all confused, not knowing how to link nor invite.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ppl, pls sign up ur own account n link to 04s08 instead. it's easier like that. it's up to u to leave ur blog empty but fill in 04s08's   shujun
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Shujun , it's ok Elsa has been kind and sporty enuff to allow this poem to be viewed :D  Well here we go:   The Elsa Song!   Hey let's all make Elsa a nick-name,  The way she's playing this match-making game,   How about mean gal number one?  I don't like her teasing me about eventually having a son!   Elsa what u said made my heart simply torn,  You must realise i'm just like Jimmy Neutron!   Understand that i'm not a love-seeking bird,  The way you say stuff proclaims me as a desperate.  !@^$*$%#$@   Lyrics by: Janet the Mighty 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hi pple  you know what? poor junkai injured his ankle today! wonder how he is now..hope he is alright. this goes to show tt thinking of yr cca all the time can b quite disastrous..haha..so pple, pls take care. dont keep thinking about the cute guy/girl you just saw if not you may just tumble down the stairs..  today is quite a good day..just tt my arm ache badly..i suspect i got rhemeutisn(dunno how to spell)..it kinda ache when it gets cold...sad ah..im an old lady now..i think you guys need to call me lao nana. oh ya..n pe just now was quite fun..we won! cheer! haha. my not so best fren, mindy and i are really slack. we kinda "rolled" to the back of the goal post thingy to hide so that we can run 1 round less. i think we looked stupid infront of the other classes pple running past us..haha..but i had a good laugh..  i really think elsa is going mad over softball.. gosh..she actually saw tt ball hiding at the tree. seriously, how did you do tt. its so..so..well hidden. haha. i am really amazed you manz...nv get bored of throwing or batting over and over again.  i nv realise tt ian is so....poetic? and elsa too. competing to come up with the sweetest poem for my dear best fren? hey..dun steal me best fren frm me! she is MINE! HAHA. i can just imagine the funny look on nus face when she reads this..i think she thinks im some pyschopath or something..haha...actually im............not la  i just realise that my english is the worse among all you guys...how can you guys possibly type proper sentences? gosh..i think i will take years to type proper sentences and spell all my words correctly..no wonder i failed the language part of my gp paper.  just realise tt the pple blogging is all gurls except ian..must get the rest to blog too!! love ya all!  nana aka baozhu(happy elsa? haha..ps. y do u call me tt anyway? its weird..y would pple want to name their daughters "precious pig"?..haha)       
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      by CLAY Aiken (originally from dunnoe who)  Tomorrow morning If you wake up And the sun does not appear I will be here  If in the dark We lose sight of love Hold my hand and have no fear I will be here  I will be here When you feel like being quiet When you need to speak your mind I will listen And I will be here When the laughter turns to cryin' Through the winning, losing, and trying I will be here  
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Safe With Me   As the clouds darken above your head, When you suddenly feel down and out, As you remember everything people said, When you just want to scream and shout.  But as you feel lost and alone, But as you just break down and cry, Remember nothing can be done by an idle stone, Remember nothing can be done unless you try.  Lay down your sweet and weary head, Rest upon my shoulder, Let nothing be said, Drift off quietly into silent slumbler.  Take a soft glance around, What do you see? Shelter from violence and sound, Safe with Me.  Safe with Me.  Author: Janet the Kind  Note: Dedicated to someone, you know who you are. Just want this poem to cheer you guys up. Please leave comments. Thanks!         
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey elsa!!   y am i called desperate! its not me who wanted to take the pic with the cute hongkie its SJ!! but he is really cute...its nice to have hi pic..haha... anyway.. i am pissed..i type such a long n nice msg n i dunno where it went to..i click publish then it said something which i din bother reading n i click yes n wala! its gone now..so annoying..decided not to type again  oh ya manda, haha..i found it! n its not tt difficult..what can i say..im good!  nana
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Heez . . .i heard from manda that ian is gonna write a poem bout me. WOW! So touching! Can't wait! That's why i decided to do him a favour and help him snag a mean girl . . .  Ergo, here you have, a poem from Ian to nus:  I've been watching your world from afar,  I've been trying to be where you are,  And I've been secretly falling apart,  I'll see.  To me, you're strange and you're beautiful,  You'd be so perfect with me but you just can't see,  You turn every head but you don't see me.   I'll put a spell on you,  You'll fall asleep and I'll put a spell on you.  And when I wake you,  I'll be the first thing you see,  And you'll realise that you love me.   Yeah...   HAHAHAHA!!!! Can u imagine? Picture this: 1 day during mths lecture, nus falls asleep on the chair table, then suddenly ian wakes her up . . .and grins. HAHAHAHA!! wonder wat happened the day both were left alone in chinese class to practice oral?  -Elsa  
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      IT IS A FRIDAY! hi all! i don't really have any idea about what to write so pardon me if this entry is filled with nonsense. NOTE: i am updating simply to show that i have visited! =] so anyway to start of this entry, a big big THANK YOU to ke ai for taking bus back with me! always my favourite ke ai man x) well today was lecture day so talked a whole bunch of crap and copied notes with my favourite canoeist/cook! had a really good time laughing and talking rubbish with her. our class girls are seriously the best man. can hold a decent conversation with every one of them! (class guys also very nice la) then today during pe we had captains ball AGAIN and as usual the girls outnumbered the boys and we win. well we have to at least or it would be extremely embarrassing. wouldn't it? then we had economics and math tutorial which were basically like every other tutorial just that i would like to say that our new economics tutor is not bad and i actually don't find her boring! yay thank God she is staying with us till the year end. so i have managed to squeeze out a few paragraphs about my day at school which sounds really similar to ke ai's and should be for the obvious reasons. so i shall end here in case it becomes to repetitive and i'll spare you people the boredom! x)
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Hi everybody! This is  elsa , ringleader of the mean girls ( im ringleader cos i started this whole mean girls thingy but we know the real mean girl is manda lah hor? ). this is my first time writing in a blog, or actually typing on the computer for non-hmwk stuff.Anyway, the main point is . . ."Mean Girls Movie" alert! All mean girls  MUST  watch after school next friday. Special attention to Nuria, shujun ( i treat u lah :), anyway u refused my $1 ice-cream b'dae prez, jus come OK? pls . . .),mindy (must pon ur cooking lesson like u promise kay?),wai teng (instead of giggling everytime i ask u to watch mean girls, why dun u ans me yes or no?).Manda, christina and elsa all can make it already so the rest must show support and loyalty when we plan mean girls rampages.     Oh, guys u can also come and join the mean girls and become mean  boys  (actually more like mean gays after u watch the movie, but nvr mind lah hor? as long as u accompany us and chaperone the mean girls).      Finally, pe today was actually  EXCITING  cos the gals won(!) and the guys lost.Yay! Sweet revenge! Future captain's ball sessions shid be played w these same rules but we can add some more such as girls can dribble and all "out" balls belong to girls no matter who touch last.  p.s. i got idea about (some of the) mean girls nicknames for blogspot. i know u guys already have ur own but anyway . . . CHRISTINA - Bao Zhu or Desperate MINDY     - Elephant or "Ah Sao" for chao fan NURIA     - Mrs Goh    Eh, shujun wat's the cheez joke bout ian? How come i said it but i dun noe? N who is nus?    
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I really dun have much to say lor, except...  CURSE YOU JUSTIN TIMBERLAKE, u're just made of wood, CURSE YOU JUSTIN TIMBERLAKE, u just had to be in the mood...  CURSE YOU JUSTIN TIMBERLAKE, for passing down that "joke" CURSE YOU JUSTIN TIMBERLAKE, wish i could wash ur mouth with soap...  CURSE YOU JUSTIN TIMBERLAKE, it spread like wildfire without control, CURSE YOU JUSTIN TIMBERLAKE, i hope the other party din get to know...  CURSE YOU JUSTIN TIMBERLAKE, my reputation has flown the coop, CURSE YOU JUSTIN TIMBERLAKE, for revealing my b**bs!  !#!$!@#^&@#$@    Lyrics by: Janet the Great  P.S For those of you who have absolutely no idea what the heck I just said...good. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yoz, this has nothing to to do with spiderman. the above title would be my own blog's title.  Friday, (not the black in the story of robinson Cru???). hm...i forgo brkfst in the morning. but was still late for band. utterly disappointed with myself.  chem n math lec: sit beside "Best Frends", was toking abt "periods".giggle pls.   PE:  Nus changing the pe T using MGS method taught by best frend. so damn funny. she struggled for so long to get her clothes changed. fancy to think that Yt could change faster using the same mtd. captains' ball AGAIN. battle of the sexes AGAIN.gal won marginally AGAIN. but this time round, there's improvement. the ratio of gals: guys was 2:1 rather than the usual 3:1. one comment: guys r MCP! will u die making ladies happy by losing the game??  econ lec: not worth mentioning  math: KO SZE!!! i've let u down!!! i din bring my hmwk!! haha, den there's an "IAN" joke.  econ: I LOVE MS NG! she's a powerful ladies!! she really eased phobia for tutorial!!! "Charismatic" speaker..... every1 listen n din tok..... i really hate tutors who r slow, unclear of wad they r doing, n not able to grasp pupils' attention. gd time management.... we were dismissed promptly.  quite happy that our class are getting along well after june hols. think those pools n movie really can forge bonds. and the gals hor, they discovered their gossipy nature. now that the "mean" gals get together, they would maximise their potential ....n CRAP!  
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this entry was created so that shujun would not feel like as if she's rambling on to  HERSELF ,gratitude accepted:)this is my first time using blogspot too..amanda,u're not alone.i haven't the vaguest idea what i just did..i think i created a new blog using this account.ya well,just a note to u people..pls refrain from splashing my name everywhere in this blog(i know it's quite irresistable) as due to the unique(ahem..UNIQUE) nature of my name,it would be very easy for people to find our blog if they type my name in the search engine.that is,if u want to keep this blog confidential.but i prefer not to have people whom i know come up to me and mention that i "suck" in class.oh yes,also if any teacher should be so bored as to type in his/her own name in the search engine(i think science teachers would probably face this boredom problem more than the art teachers bcos listening to chemistry jokes do get stupid after a while),it would be VERY,i repeat VERY easy to link to our blog.of course b*tching about teachers will perhaps be the main activity happening in many entries to come,but we all have to take precautions not to write our real names.if your aim is to suck up,by all means,use  BOLD  letterings for your name. that's all folks..adios. nus
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      b4 we tok abt the interesting list of suckiest things, let's go thru roughly wad had happened in class (or rather to me).  GP joke: topic: computer technology story goes like this: Ms Wan tried to show the whole class how we human rely on CT. She used the example of type writer and computer printer and how production of reading materials n information can be conveyed on rapidly.  Ms Wan: (holding on to my june 7th n 14th Newsweek magazine) look at the words...everyone of them of the million copies sold world-wide, used to be typed one by one using the type-writer....wad would this become without printers' duplicating technology?? tell me, wad would this become... (still flippin the pages)  SJ: News"year"  k, suckiest list .....u may wanna add on, pls comment.  1) the white board - sucks the ink from the markers.  2) notice board - sucks the pins n paper n notice onto itself  3) the ceiling - sucks the lightbulbs n fans to it  4) floor - sucks us ppl n all objects on the ground to it  5) cheez - sucks ppl ard her to herself eg, "Best Frend" ( can u control ur "best frend" - tan poh gek?? she's haunting me with monotonous "where's my best frend" )  6) best frend's sucker toy/thingy (i dunno wad that call, for baby use)  good nite everyone, i'm not finishing my maths tonite, shall copy tml.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      HELLO! this is my first time using blogspot! hahah so i have betrayed my beloved diaryland! oh well. anyway this is AMANDA in case you ignorant people have yet to realise. in other words, shujun's xingan, nuria's bestest friend and nana's unbest friend. x) waa applause for ke ai man! so efficient! we only suggested a blog for the class during lunch and she gets it done within the day! in response to ke ai's post about our 7th chem tutor! i think she looks like an elf. very legolas like. hmmm. does anyone want to replace me as a chem rep? i will  GLADLY  give it up :) anyway back to the thing about this new blog thingy. i still have no idea how to use blogspot but it does look quite user friendly. okay so now the job is to tell the WHOLE class about it. so WHO should we push this job to? or should we just do open advertising and put it on our MSN nicks? oh yeah before i forget, qj, richard, ke ai and i have  cool  MSN nicks man! [If the Earth doesn't suck, we won't be here.] shall sign off now. by the way,  CHRISTINA TAN POH GEK  IF YOU READ THIS, have fun finding my diary! mandy
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      if earth doesn't suck, we wouldn't be here!  lousy day in sch, without PW in the afternoon. there's a new chem tutor in our class - mrs Ng. tok damn fast. super efficient to the extent of becoming dictative. No doubt i haf faith in her that i'll do beta in promo (i almost type "porno") with her ard, but life seems more tedious as well cos of her higher expectations. but i think i haf qt good impression of her.. she's dynamic n "power"! shit her, onli me has no wksht to do. AM I PART OF THIS CLASS???  haha great joke of the day contributed by elsa : one word to describe janet- "cheez"   ko Sze ROx man, bt he's leaving for Sponge Bob land!! life's great without chong mong teaching me!   love, Ke ai 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this is our blog! pls post anything interesting n comments on the post! however, do take note that if u need to post anithing impt, eg cip notice, pls put [impt] as the 1st word of ur title.   have fun blogging!   * pls get password from me if u wanna sign in. (oya!, pls state ur name for the post/comments!)  Ke Ai (SJ)
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Recently i was very very very BZ. Getting sick (ill i mean)&nbsp;too, so 04S08 rockers, do show concern to your classmate pls! And one effective way is to keep hold of my "tap" card and help me tap it on the scanning machine when i'm not in sch =P . &nbsp; There seems to be nothin for me to write on a&nbsp;saturday morning when school (or rather band pra)begins later. ok, let's tok about ydae. Crazy me actually left the hos 40min after i arrived there (after almost 30 min's travel) juz to play pool with the guys @ mambo (hooray! i spent less than 1hour to get there from hos) . HAHA. I WAS SCOLDED BY MY MUM FOR MY IRRESPONSIBLE BEHAVIOUR! haiz.... despite that, i trashed ivan + janet with 3 or 4 balls in a row, finally with justin hitting the black ball into the corner hole. yoyoz. well, sorry to justin, i wasn't performing after that game. =P &nbsp; Ha, all of us were discussing why nus din wanna come to pool. I was told that she wanna stay home to do PW.&nbsp; janet was told that she wanna ZZZ and log on to MSN. (both of us were screamed by her into our ears). ok, wadeva the case i wouldn't noe nor bother to find out the truth. Using my PW's analysis technique and skill, i drew conclusion that nus's a good liar (note: she's not the best) Opps, i shdn't haf leaked out the fact that i forgo mean gal outing for pooling! &nbsp; racial harmony day's mon? seriously, will anione wear ethnic costume? i think i'll look silly lor! see, I LOVE NJ GREY -_-"' 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       hi pple of   04s08,    would like to ask if any of u would be so sporting as to wear costumes on monday?wouldn't it be so  cool  if all of us wore nice colourful traditional costumes and be the "most enthu class"??hehehhe ...let's create NJ history together!!(saris are beautiful!)    -nus    
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Faith   Raindrops falling from the night sky, You stand in the open staring up with a sigh.  The rain mixes with tears down your sweet face, Don't let a single drop go to waste...  Your heart may seem broken and torn, But wait, because a rainbow comes after a storm.  Even if your world grows darker with each passing day, Remember that there are people around guiding you all the way.  The path before you may rise or plummel, Yet know that hope lies at the end of every tunnel.  So endure this cold winters' night, Because one day, just one day, your face will feel the warm summer sunlight.  Have Faith.  Lyrics By: Janet the Concerned  Note: This poem is dedicated to any friends who happen to be feeling down. Cheer up people :D  
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      eh what happened to the entry left by 'wee^2' which i assume is from wee siang? i just realised that no one updated yesterday! my goodness! don't know if to talk about the silly toilet incident that happened yesterday with christina and nuria. hahah quite old stuff already ma. ok maybe i will type about that later. anyway i shall talk about the   NICE and PRETTY   henna design that nuria drew for me during chinese/physics lect/after school. it's so pretty! thank you   bestESTestEST   friend! however when silly lionel saw it, he called it a dead vine la. we can just go whack him la right? and then nana drew another nice henna design for me on my other hand! yay. one happy event of the day. we should do this for racial harmony day man! going to watch tv now. hopefully someone updates later on today. =]
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dear Lion-head's MSN nick... it's so offensive!!!  "Women are nothing but trouble, and men are nothing but trouble seekers"  I dun mind if he admitted that men are trouble-seekers, but please,women are no trouble, k!   [edited] ok, now i saw another Lion head's nick :  "Menstrual blues, menstrual syndromes, menses, menstrual cramps....have u realised that women's problems begin with "men".
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hi all. as you all know we got back our cmath CT today. and  YAY  we got like the highest in level for the number of As, As and Bs and As - Es.   GO 04S08!   although i want to add that i do not belong to the band of As and Bs. =[ oh well. ANYWAY we did super well for chem too! more than 50% of us got A! and well nana, elane and jasmine did us proud to by scoring 80+++ marks la. 0_o from now on, we shall ALL approach nana for chemistry tuition ok! or better still during chem promos, we just sit next to her. x) okay anyway the real reason why i updated was to highlight the funniest thing that happened during PE today. heh mr mennon wasn't around, so we had captains ball again. yes again. it should be made our class game man. so yes, elsa was on the opposite team with wei jian and wee siang while nana, sj and i were on the other team with a few others obviously. so well halfway through the game, wei jian intercepts one of our teams passes and so yes the ball is in his hand. then suddenly elsa starts shouting  'WEE SIANG WEE SIANG HERE!' . and then she repeats herself again. now isn't that funny? here is elsa screaming wee siangs name while the ball is in  wei jians  hand! at first no one seemed to notice the mistake and suddenly it all hit us and we got all confused and couldn't stop laughing. while well of course elsa felt very embarrassed. heh. okay that's all. and one last note. WE HAVE A NEW SOFTBALLER IN THE HOUSE.    NURIA!    let's welcome here with a round of applause! x)
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i dun get u guys..this is like the  BEST  cip i've ever come across and people are not fighting for it.ANYWAY,only 5 places are reserved for 5 special,dedicated zoo lovers.it's throughout the first week of december(6 days)from 9am to 4pm everyday and commitment is compulsory.[elephant shit can be fun to clean up,depends on how u look at it]so....any of u wanna join me? :) -nus ps playing softball today has made me realise that photog has SO much more potential..SO i've decided to be SUPER enthu frm now on,borrow the sch's SLR and snap away!!
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey! First time blogg here. :) Guess who's blogg. Ip kids are amusing. Haha. Esp my squash junior. She's so crappy you can fall off the chair just talking to her. Anw, it's my first time home so early since a long long while. Feeling on top of the world! :) Pardon me for my short form and all. Finally settled d dance item for installation -- all thnx to Ros! It's like wow! I went one whole big round trying to get ppl to help choreograph, but I'm just thankful that d dance's kinda ready now. :) And we've got the cheque from our rotarian advisor! So mayb now u all can expect better food at the installation. Haha. [elsa you've heard it?] o yar. manda sighted at ac spyg on ac tennis. haha. reported by clara. :)  wt
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       IT IS NOT PINK ANYMORE!  it is now  GREEN . goodness.    i hope the guys are happy now.. hahahah    =)
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The fOlLoWiNG PeoPlE ARe ImVolVeD in ThE FollOwinG CIP:  National Street sale 2004 in conjunction with Singapore Fireworks 2004 @ marina Bay. Time 4-8pm. date: 1st n 8th Aug.   Chow Lee Yee Ling Xinyi Nuria Luen Wai Teng Luo Shuhui Elane Tan Poh Gek Christina Tan Shujun Tan Yan Ying Amanda Tay Huiling Zeng Jiamin Jasmine Goh Hsien Jun Ian Lim Wei Jian Loh Kai Hui Low Wen Yan Richard Andrew Ong Junkai Poh Shin Sng Wee Siang Tan Kim Ong (8th)Yeo Chee Keong Ivan (8th)Hermawan Wijaya  Class: i really need u ppl's cooperation to remind one another of this CIP events. I forsee that i might be busy and tend to forget to remind the class. T-shirt size cant be changed now
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hello all. as you all know (if you are in 04S08) we had TWO practicals today. PHYSICS and CHEMISTRY. how very interesting. well basically today was slack just that special mention goes to chemistry prac where i supposedly 'bossed' around the class to their respective groups. oih la i am chemistry rep and if you people don't get there on time i am the one in trouble la. o_0 silly shu jun. nvm i forgive my mean girl x) okay so anyway for chemistry prac my group went to CM44 which happened to be where s5I was at. well basically chemistry prac was fun for us because, we finished earlier than the class there because we cheated. so we spent half the time 'gossiping' and trying to make the teacher let us off early. well we succeeded la but not before we sat through 45 mins worth of going through the entire experiment calculations. heh then mindy, sj and i sat at one corner and ostracised elsa because she was MEAN to mindy! hahah we basically acted like stupid kids till we were let off. i think we are one crazy but united class man. props to us ;) oh and special mention goes to mindy leow for filling up her burette with HCl till it overflowed from her burette onto my chair and shoes simply because she just placed the filter funnel on top of the opening without leaving a gap in between to let it go down faster. her look on her face was h i l a r i o u s. but nvm we still love our canoe babe for doing these kinda funny things don't we? oh and qian jin!! we will miss you!! come back soon! preferrably with lotsa chocolates and goodies x)
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm so pissed off by a flyer distributor yesterday. She handed to me a flyer that goes like this:    "PLSE STRESSED? ARE U PRIMARY 6? PSLE Preparatory Course available...."  Halo! I'm wearing the NJC IGNIS HOUSE T-shirt.  Ultimate PRA day, i was slacking at noon, playing caram (dunno how to spell) with nus. She was FANTASTIC! I bet she only has the "No way i would lose" look for such petty games. Come on, challenge me with the same attiude for mugging. HUH! Stare at me during Econ for wad??!!?? HUH??!!! I reckon if I wanna ignite a fight from a staring incident with someone, this person would most probably be nus. Juz kidding.  Sianz.... i was so "suay" to be in the chem 41 class. The 5I people are so slow lor. All the 5As spent at least 30 minutes to idle around, if not, gossiping before the 5Is finished their work. Cant tahan the teacher, pathetically slow in her teaching pace. Lucky we protested to be released earlier, if not we would be trapped there till 5pm.  -When a dermentor approach you, what must you say?-  ===  Expecto Patronum ===  this is the WRONG answer. Correct answer:  "No Smint, no kiss"
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      im flying off people! DO YOUR HOMEWORK! STAY AWAKE DURING LECTURES! DON'T LET SILENCE OVER TAKE THE CLASS ONCE IM GONE! please please please take care and dun fall sick. keep the teachers happy so that i dun get the bad side of them when i come back =D haha i might get stuff for you guys.. i think jun kai and myself will combine lah! whee! germs here we come!   once we were in a few groups, never united... always clique-ish.  after the wearing of burdensome njc,  we have smoothened out friction, white merged with black to form grey.  04s08 is really united and stuff =D that roxxors!!!!!! lets kick butt.   taataa~ qian jin. =D
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Boobs, do not make a woman   Hardly a day goes by without one coming across bust-enhancement advertisements.....  Pictures of well-endowed scantily-clad models whoclaim to be satisfied customers ....... create a need, in both female reader who are "unhappy with their bust" and, possibly, their partners.  * As a woman, I would like to address the salons' definition of sexiness, attractiveness and the other "-nesses" that have to do with beauty.   The worth and value of a woman are not and should not be measured by the size of her breasts  or any other part of her anatomy.  A woman has much beauty to celebrate : her life and identity, the vital roles she plays in the domestic setting and the workplace, the contributions she has made in various arenas through the years. her creative energies manifested in her writing, and the power in her voice which can still be both a crying baby and a raging sea, among other.  Therefore,  every woman is beautiful and worthy , with or without bigger and firmer breasts. Beauty salons should not try to define us by relegating us to the rank of mere sexual visuals.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      last night at great world city i saw TWO ang moh guys in SPECS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!the honkie didn't even come CLOSE to being that hot. -nus
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Vocal Bananas   Listen to the yellow ones sing, Harmoniously in perfect melding.  Singing as if to a yellow moon, Pondering if their lives would suddenly end soon.  Crying out that life is unfair, Wondering "Why or why had I not been a pear?"  In doubt and worry they sighed, Until the final day when they became acidified.  The lesson learnt is one shouldn't worry about the following hour, For that will simply make you taste damn sour...  Lyrics: Janet the Lost  Note: Dedicated to Qian Jin and Nana!  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      was really boring.. i hope that we will never have listening again.  you'll never know when the time will come.  the time where God decides to take you to his side. a time where you can only watch your kins from afar,  a time where you can only regret not doing the things that mattered.  sorry... this may be a short poem, but im feeling morbid now.   qian jin.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      (with regards to previous entry and the comment by "mr yong")  seriously, is that Mr Yong?? 'Cause i'm about to comment that he's a tough guy, i saw him running in the rain one morning. Nus also expressed that he's a "muscle man".  Basically, todae's damn boring even though qianjin and junkai's back from germany. However, that was not the highlight of my entry. i would like to stress that we had 5 absentees today and all of them are.....                     SCORPIOS!!!  ALL our SCORPIOS in 04S08 were GONE!!! except for elane. but even elane was not spared. indeed, she's first in line for the scorpio downfall. She was sick ydae too. IT'S phenomenal!!!!  o dear!!! which sign would be the next??!!!??? the second populous signs after scorpio is.....  AQUARIUS N CANCER!!!!! ( shit!, the whole back row might be gone except for me, yteng, kim and kaihui) 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hello dearest fellow comrades please study hard and pay attention in class. no more time for laughter and jokes, be serious! copying of work is bad and so is eating in class, we need a clean environment to study. support and not make fun of fellow muggers, a school is a place for mugging. lastly, do not follow our mean girl elsa comrade and make fun of canoeists. that is bad and mean. thank you, and have a nice day -professor leow. 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      my goodness. today was one crazy day man!  &nbsp;  three really silly/stupid/insane things happened today! heh ok first one. MINDY has MORPHED INTO   MUGGER/PROFESSOR LEOW  ! oh the HORROR man. the slacker/non-muggerish/don'tdohomework mindy has CHANGED. oh no where have they taken my favourite old mindy to? for example, during physics tutorial this insane woman started answering all of miss ong's questions and even offering to go to the whiteboard and write down her answers! NOT GOOD. however this did keep me and elsa in constant hysterics with her stupid antics la. so it's good for our abs. heh  &nbsp;  next silly thing is my discovery that i have... *DRUMROLL*  &nbsp;      BIONIC EARS!        &nbsp;   woohoo cool me. right so during chemistry lecture today, i was seating one row behind nana and bestestest friend. well i was technically like 5 - 6 seats away from them in the row behind. so suddenly i hear 'amanda blahblahblah' then i am like 'eh who called me?' apparently it was nana BACKSTABBING (just kidding)&nbsp;me!! nana HOW could you betray me? hahha my ears are so sharp man! then during physics tutorial i was seating at the second row left corner and ke ai was at the last row right corner when i heard her say 'amanda blahblahblah' and AGAIN i heard it and turned around saying 'hey what did u say about me?' HAHAH i have such sharp ears man! all you people gossiping and talking rubbish about me better not do it within a 10 metre radius of me because MY EARS ARE LISTENING! x) 
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ..who by the way is SLACKING at home somewhere in  MALAYSIA  eating D24 durians and having an itch.wahhh get chicken pox and get sent to m'sia?!that's what i call good life man.when i had chicken pox by the way,I  did not  go m'sia for one,  nor  did i get sent to cdc.i was  at home  applying lots of calamine lotion and looking like a ghost all in white.hey,u noe what..u should share the joy with your lovely classmates in 04s08 who are mugging so hard and being trashed by all the teachers.and u noe  HOW  u can do that??by popping up in our class for just ONE chem tutorial :) this will not only benefit YOU,the individual,but ALSO has FAR REACHING benefits for US,the society at large.(that line was in my GP essay,couldn't help it.haha)  #1. You might infect half the class..meaning we'll have a empty class,which means teachers might cut us some slack and we can give the excuse that "half the class is not here",which means our workload might be lessoned,which means we have more time to write in the blog,which means we'll have a life,which means...... (u get the picture) #2. (this is the  best  part) You might infect the chem teacher!!  H  O  O  R  A  Y !! she hasn't got immunity yet,she told us during chem prac.so u are actually doing her some good by GIVING her immunity by infecting her...good eh?2 in one. yup,u know what u have to do ;) -nus 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      nus, u r angry ar??? kk, i'll stop the nosense about 1) TyPinG ThIS wAY 2) adding at least one paragraph to&nbsp;"suan" u. &nbsp; however, i dun think typing in those fonts are completely bad though.&nbsp; remember what the PW lecturer once said: the survey with usually font and letters jumping around attract more attention from readers. =) 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       just a   note to everyone, WrITiNG lIkE tHiS is SO NoT cUtE.pls stop it before this whole blog looks like it belongs to some broken-english,boliao,brainless ah lian.thank u.    &nbsp;  the more i listen to our chem teacher talking,the more i find myself irritated by that shrill,piercing,mechanical voice with this particularly disturbing&nbsp;phrase thrown in every so often: "You think to yourself..HEY!what if i could do it this way.." i mean, think about this..does any  NORMAL  person say  HEY  to themselves??i'd think that person&nbsp;would be&nbsp;a little bonkus.sometimes i wonder if she really memorises all her lines before a lesson.the way she goes on and on without catching her breath seems  pretty scary  to me.    &nbsp;  btw,thanks amanda for mr spongebob!!! it shall forever have a reserved place on my bag :)   -nus  &nbsp;  p.s pple,i DO have a personal account but if i use it,access to my blog will be open to public.hah..so too bad folks!    &nbsp; 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      HAHA, i suffered insommia last night.&nbsp; Now very tired.&nbsp; moreover i din bring my lecture notes for physics, so might as well rest on the desk and Zzz. HAHA, but that's not me! i'm efficient!!! i did ECON meanwhile!!!  &nbsp;  now that i read the blog, was surprised to see irene posting something. heeehee, it's all abt the 1st 3 mths' recap. Ya, that time was fun during GP. It's always Carrom, Carrom and CARROM!!! But didn't matter lah, Mrs Nair usually tok crap.  &nbsp;  Ha, irene, i dun rmb the part on me singing on a table???!!!??  &nbsp;  k, todae there's racial harmony day celebration. We gals signed up to take part in some designing competition. haha, shame on us, din bring any&nbsp;material at all. So,&nbsp;&nbsp;since the theme was sth to do with flowers, i went ard the school to pluck them. hee, i think it was fun. PLUCK-AND-RUN! heehee,&nbsp;Best frends were like the creative directors, seeking ways to improvise. haha. but come to think about it, the whole competition was stupid and purely a WASTE OF TIME, PrEcIOUS TIME!&nbsp;the chem pra was fun ( of cos not the part when she held back the class to go thru chem paper) cos we got the chance to deal with SiMplE ExpErimeNtaL PrOceDuREs.  &nbsp;  Manda, i truly stand on ur side that&nbsp; Nus needs occassional sCoLding. Like todae, she PurposEly held me back to wait for her to complEte Physics Pra.&nbsp; Haha, i Know, i Muz HaF the sPirIT of thE&nbsp;156-gals, but SureLY noT aT tHe exPenSE of Mi$$ing @ leAST 3 154 buses, rite? U SHD hAF COMPENSATE ME WITH ALMOND SNICKERS BAR, nuriA!!!&nbsp;Y r u so OFF-beAt??? Didn't i Say u, me and manda Muz peel the wrapper&nbsp; TOGETHER  and munch the chocolate  TOGETHER?? &nbsp; AnD wHAt DiD U DO???&nbsp;Coldly&nbsp;SaiD ThAt iT's  SILLY? AND&nbsp;WHAT"S MORE?? TURN&nbsp;Ur BACK ON US&nbsp;2??  &nbsp;  manda, i think it's fun, y not every entry say sth bad about Nus?   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Anonymous said...   hey guys Irene here. mandy has been trying to get me to come to ur blog, n i haven't had the time till today, so here i am!! shujun, sorry for posting this under comment to ur post, but i dunno how else to do it leh =P forgive forgive me... haha..so hey guys! how's every1 doing? i miss da class a lot, but since i see a lot of new faces i'm kinda reluctant to come over n hang out wif u guys for fear of being called thick skin or sumthing lidat.. (i noe u guys won't la, but i'm jus paranoid, haha).. heard u guys did very well for CT! great job ya! look at me la.. suffering man.. aih..janet, great poem, n yea, i AM kinda depressed, so reading it helped a little. thanx yo!hope ur doing a gr8 job as da math rep.. r u very close to b-ball lee now? hahamandy! miss all dos talks we had.. hope ur happier now. if u need anything, u noe where to find me la k? remember i'll always pray for u!!wai teng, miss u lots! ur so cheery, n happy, n u always manage to make my day brighter! thanx a lot! frens forever yo!   11:34 PM       Anonymous said...   oops, i haven't finished, haha...anyway, shujun! super smarty pants! super carrom player! will never forget our gp class! (or was dat our no-mrs-nair-carrom-sessions?? haha)..elsa! yo man! ur so cool! n so smart!! always so practical.. keep it up ya!! =)erm,... let's c.. putih! miss u lots! always happy, always singing! remember the time when u climbed onto da table to clean da windows n u started singing? haha, so hilarious! =Ppoh shin! my grand daughter! oops, is no one supposed to noe dat? haha, neway... beloved CT rep.. always bickering wif auntie kim bout hantus.. i wonder who's da real hantu la..jun kai.. hmm, looks very naive.. still wondering if u r.. but i saw u being notti da other day.. shall not say it out here la.. hahajustin! chun peng! u think i listen to yes 933?? haiyo! nvm.. u cheeky little thing! miss ur antiques wif our tutors la.. especially wif ms ang.. still remember once when da whole c=back row slept during a class.. haha.. n listening to c-phyllis talking bout da 'LOUD' fan..richard! mushroom double! be careful ya, next time u play 'sai kang tai ti' don fall off da chair u noe? or else da money u stole from council will fall out of ur pocket ar!! oops.. paiseh ;)lee yee! octave SL! great job in harmoc n oso in class! still as cute as ever! don laugh too much alrd k? hav to concentrate in class ya!elane, still as quiet as ever.. all da best yo!jas.. very fair.. pretty, but won compare wif lee yee...aft she kills me..my lap top low batt d.. i'll continue nother day ya!! tata11   11:46 PM  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       WHY DOESN'T ANYONE UPDATE ANYMORE!   &nbsp;    anyway nuria please get your own account soon! nana YOU TOO!      now it only seems like me and sj updating with the occasional nuria. =I     anyway today was crazy cause sj, ian, justin and i went to mambo to play pool. my goodness sj was   ON FIRE   man. everything all go in and she and ian had at least 7 tyco shots. while me and justin must have been having super unlucky days as scorpios cause we lost 3 outta 4 games and  FINALLY  managed to win the last one. thank God. if not we can just go hide our faces.. i think i was the main course of justin's downfall simply because i was too busy eating my kfc. heh. well what a nice class outing this was man! FOUR people only!    do you know who i am angling this at?         NURIA!     
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      One question to myself: why did i always have the urge to blog yet couldn't type out anything? Does that mean that i do have inner thoughts which i desire to share yet i'm always hold back for some reasons? blah...blah...blah...i dun wanna sound like a problem kid.  &nbsp; i decide not to scare off my classmates. [STOP RIGHT NOW, thank you very much] &nbsp; Anyway, many a time, things are getting out of hand. that is why something call "friend" or "assistant" or "partner" are invented. Nus, pls propose to Daniel Wong the national street sale by the end of the coming week. if you wanna me to go with u, do let me know wad time. afterall, i have more FREE period than you do.heehee. 
     
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       When It's Time For  Sex , She Knows   Byline: David Bjerklie Women are more likely to have sex during the most fertile  six  days of their menstrual cycle, even if they don't want to get pregnant, according to a study published in the journal Human Reproduction. Scientists studying sexually active women who had been sterilized or were using an IUD found that intercourse was  24%  more frequent during what would have been the fertile part of their cycle--although these women were clearly not looking to procreate. So why the urge? Researchers speculate that a woman's libido may rise during ovulation or that her sexual attractiveness to partners may increase. It could also be that intercourse accelerates ovulation. There aren't any definitive answers yet, but women who have unprotected sex and do not want to get pregnant should know that nature appears to be subtly working against them.  *remember the statistic, it's helpful. =P 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey, people, i'm doing my work again, making full use of this site for reading magazine. Then u read this article which dates back to 2003. topic: homosexuality. below are the ASTOUNISHING CONCLUSIONS drawn by researchers.  1)when males and females are exposed to a loud noise, they blink in somewhat different ways -- except that   lesbians   appear to  blink like    men  , not like women.  2)An  identical twin  of a   gay person   is about   twice as likely   to be   gay   as a fraternal twin would be.  3)50 to 60 percent of   sexual orientation   might be  genetic .  4)some studies show    most gay    men have a larger isthmus of the corpus callosum -- which may also be true of   left-handed people  . And that's intriguing because gays are    39    percent more likely to be left-handed than straight people.  5) a male is more likely to be gay if he has older brothers; for each    older brother    he is about   33   percent more likely to be gay.  Then, i saw a paragraph that goes like this : O.K., these theories are potentially junk science until the studies are replicated with much larger numbers. ( i felt cheated)  BUT THEN, the next line .....  "we also SHOULD NOT ignore the accumulating EVIDENCE."  What shall we do?!!!?? is there anyone in our class who fits in the description??? 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      &nbsp;YO ppl attention! I jus realized that our cip so happens to fall on the day when the S'pore food fest got exhibitions at Suntec City expo hall. So we can go there to  "sell"  collar pins and try out all the great food (we'll be mtg at esplanade so will be very near) .  &nbsp; Anyway, sigh . . .&nbsp;today was a bad day for me :( First, the stupid, dammanable seed crystal screwed itself up and became so blurry. But nvm other grps also the same so they are also all screwed  *evil grin*  .  &nbsp; Then, came back late for Mr lee's maths class and he knew i nvr do my work AGAIN. So 1st thing when i step in he ask me to go up to the board AGAIN. Then of course i did all wrong AGAIN and he had to correct me, resulting in some very awkward moments of him trying to be nice and me looking as  meek  and  studious  as possible. ( I think i grinned/cringed a bit too much, look perverty) &nbsp; Later, went ar East to collect the printed underwear and got "violated " by the se lang ( fellow mean gal manda would know :)) AGAIN.  &nbsp; Lastly(and worst of all), got bad news from dearest canoeist mindy. And that was the last straw on MY back. Hence, total shit in school today + bad news= sad day&nbsp;  p.s. eh, who going for hc college dayt tml huh? 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      To qns posted for my last entry: the first line in fact has nothing to do with the rest of the entry. it's juz an evidence that i had done my work and effectively utilise the webpage subscribed by our school.  I dun understand why u ppl are&nbsp;commenting on janet's lovesickness in my last entry which apparently discusses the issue on the true meaning of Youth. Y-O-U-T-H.  Aniway, it's unavoidable that ppl fake or hide their true feelings. In whatever case, all of you, please have more faith. F-A-I-T-H. Believe that no matter what our frends are shunning away from you, it's all for your own good. even if you may be decieved by them, calm down and trust that it's a white lie. 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Some people just cannot understand,  the unintentional hurt they cause,  the unintentional pain they bring.   Call me sensitive, call me naive,  But call others insensitive, call others ignorant.   I once asked someone,  their purpose, their meaning in life.  Christians themselves sometimes do not know,  At other times I question my own.   Refering to both SJ's and Amanda's posts,  life is indeed too short for one's liking,  to be squandered on books, wasted on grades.   It makes us empty inside,  putting on false smiles, false laughs.  People around us do not realise, do not understand,  but what hurts the most is that we ourselves don't either.   Break free of your bonds,  ask your heart what it wants in life.  tell your heart to be happy.   I hope one day that everyone will be able to answer that question.  Truthfully, honestly,  but&nbsp;most importantly&nbsp;happily and proud.   For the Christians: In the Lord we trust and hope until his glorious second coming. Amen.   Written by: Janet the Weary  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i write too much,  spanning for pages,  but I never write enough,  i always have more emotions,  never expressed,  only felt.   they are the secret emotions that no one talks about,  they have no name.  they are expressions,  lasting for a simple millisecond,  before being hidden away,  that a thousand words could not describe,  that a hundred pictures could not express.   sometimes I smile,  who knows if its fake or real.  then again,  who really cares?  everyone enjoys false niceties.  so they can tell themselves everyone is all right,  and justify their walking away,  not caring.   maybe its easier that way.  pretending you didnt know,  that inside she was,  no,  I was screaming,  shouting,  hoping to be heard,  recognized,   but wearing a mask,  with a smile.  and knowing that,  the milliseconds,  when the mask falls off,  are ignored.   haha well just felt like&nbsp;putting it up&nbsp;to make a statement that everyone is not what they seem. food for the thought people..&nbsp;  oh and tmrw is almost like a half day!&nbsp;let's see how many ppl pon!&nbsp;   
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       "There's nothing that can warm your heart more than making someone else feel better."    The above is a meaningful sentence i extracted from a page of the "Opposing viewpoint". Well, be it webpage or printed material form, it's hard to bring myself to read on political issues.  SADDENING    &nbsp;  Have anyone ever chucked your uncompleted tutorials aside to think of this: What it should be like to be a  youth ?   Does being youthful necessarily means that we must play, joking and laugh but not work at all? I'm not really sure but certainly it's an universal truth that one has the choice to slack or work. No one shd be deemed outcast or deprived from been a true youth if the slacks whilst others mug or mugs whilst others slack. The dictationary does not give other description besides "young" to the word "youth".  There's a plan for everyone. We hardly have the power to plan ahead but we could move ahead with the plan. Ignorance is the main cause for fear in Mankind.&nbsp; Just live the way you wont regret at the end of the day. Don't need to be affected by others' behaviour as their effects on you are psychological. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        *Guess the Title*     &nbsp;  Walking blind,  In the dark,  Searching for a sign,  Pressing my luck.  &nbsp;  Trying to catch a hint,  Trying to find some hope.  Even something as small as a pin,  Still helps me to cope  &nbsp;  Everyday unexpected,  One happy, one sad.  Time should be suspended,  It's almost driving me mad.  &nbsp;  Guessing at every turn,  Struggling along the road.  Lessons&nbsp;are still&nbsp;learnt,  But can I handle the load?  &nbsp;  So much hurt,  So much pain,  Yet a beautiful smile,  Washes all doubt away.  &nbsp;  Human nature to seek,  Human nature to shun,  Will I ever find you,  O&nbsp;mysterious one?  &nbsp;  Written by: Janet the cOnFuSeD  &nbsp;  Note: Sort of like a riddle. Give me a suggestion for the title :P  &nbsp;     &nbsp;   &nbsp;    
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Huh? Got CIP at expo??? How come i dunno? Can sum1 pls tell me the upcoming cip shit cos i need more cip hours u noe . .. .&nbsp; Note to sj, can pls tell me? Thx! 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wahh no one has updated ever since thursday! that is TOO long. so i am obviously updating to break the trend. heh whee sj, pohshin and i are going for CIP later at expo! and i just checked the mrt travelling times online, and it take s 36 mins to travel from Buona Vista to the Expo MRT station. MY GOODNESS so  LONGG  GG Gg gg  gg   means i have to leave at like 4 pm to travel to Buona Vista MRT to reach there at 445pm to meet sj. things i do just to get CIP hours. anyway mug hard people. let's learn from MINDY! and weijian get well soon! DONT scratch man hahha and when u come back like what nuria said, DO DO DO try to infect the chem teacher x)  
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      seriously aiya sj don't want to say then don't make her say la. no difference what.. just a dream only. however, being typical humans we obviously want to find out who sj was talking about. who doesn't? but just chill la. yes nuria i think we did see that it was just a dream..  anyway cool man keefe was online. let's hope more good things come our way. cause good things don't come singly yes? such as a major breakthrough in PW which would be very very good.  anyway i've finally finished the Da Vinci Code after trying to 'savour' it for the entire week. must say that it is quite an interesting read just that all the hype about it made me have such high expectations for it. such that in the end, the ending of the book sort of fell short from my expectations. nevertheless, still a good read. one thing we should learn is not too expect too much man.. 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i see the commotion shu jun caused with her dream.it makes me wonder....DID U ALL READ THE LAST PART ABOUT THE WHOLE THING BEING A   DREAM?!!       *ahem*  sorry about that...i just got disturbed by all your comments...like as if the whole thing was real.but shujun,your story telling damn good..when i was reading it i also forgot that it was a dream u were describing.     oh yeah..KEEFE was online just now.for like less than 5 minutes..hahaha.that's already counted as a great feat ok.  a second reminder: 1.Be at esplanade on sunday.remember our school motto: Service with HONOUR. no point being scholars and all that *SHIT* when you don't fulfill the first and most important line in the whole crap of lines about being leaders,scholars and whatever crappy ambitious stuff they want us to be. 2. WATCH SINGAPORE IDOL       -nus   
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Manda: I Cant tell and i should not tell. i din wanna spread the rubbish dream around. it's an embarrassment.... but i thought quite obvious lor... i gave some clues le. =)  back to the topic.  *ahem* Went to giant IMM with mum juz now. i cant help but to on the com on and tell u ppl about this: Bio-essence roX!  haha, as usual i went to the cosmetic section lah.... instead of picking every bottle of wad-the-hell-it-is, i straight away grab the self-explanatory booklet and read it on my way home ( or rather immediately after i left that section). IT'S AMAZING!!!! SO MANY BIO-ESSENCE PRODUCTS WAITING ON THE SHELVES FOR ME TO PURCHASE. i'm so impressive by companies which produce such explanatory booklet. 1st was nikon, and now it's B-E. the front page is nice lor, with a nice heading:  Discover the Miracle of Youth Bio-Essence - the essence of women  It has much impact on me sia...Miracle....wow....there's HOPE!!!! it's interesting lah, maybe i'll bring it on sun for u ppl to read..  New: Bio-essence face lifting cream  heyhey, i think janet need this. it was written " Also suitable for men's use". buy lah!! if u find that it has negligible effect on you den give it to me while it's fresh.  i really envy some celebrities.....they are able to use these product for free...... how i wish i'm sammi cheng.... able to use SK II products....( hm, onli the part of her being SK II spokeman worth envy about) 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this is a saturday morning. i've juz woke up from a *** dream ( i'm not sure wad adjective to use. some possible words for substitution are ridiculous, horrible, etc) which i dare say was very real!!! It goes like this:  I came across some njcsb (sb is not symphonic band but rather softball) softballer. i shall not reveal the name but basically it's a SHE. i wun describe the degree of good-lookingness but basically ppl who noe me shd that i have some taste. From which house i wun say, but surely it must be something so closely (or rather directly) related to mine. Okay, that's all. other information eg complexion shd not be told lest the softballers in our class would start guessing who the hell i'm refering to ( well, surely manda elsa and nana muz be guessing, if not, already got the idea who i might be toking about)   jus in case THAT softballer i'm toking about happens to read this. I HAVE NO OFFENCE. I WAS JUST A DREAM WHICH I ALSO FIND UNBELIEVABLE. 
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *see my title. who the hell is that shit?  Well, i certainly doubt nus would BE patriotic. Thought you are greatly inspired to migrate over to US rite? Haha, do reserve your patriotism for Sun's flag selling since you can't rely on your magical contact list anymore =p  And Emergency!!! Our salvation army flag day has not been propose to Daniel Wong yet!!! and the next time sch reopens would be wed( am i right ar?)...... merely 3 days before the event!!!!  OKAY. Whatever the case, please, everyone, i seek your cooperation to do the following stuff. though i'm the used-to-be CIP rep, i'm sure my darling (*puke) currently-in-office Nus would think likewise.  1) watch fireworks & sell collar pins whole-heartedly 2) Catch NDP on Mon and SING "home" with kit chan and JJ lim. i repeat, pls "SING", SINGapore.  lastly and the impt of all, so impt that u should ignore the above tasks,....    CATCH THE " SINGAPORE IDOL" ON MON 8.15 PM ON CHANNEL 5   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      juz for laugh....  Isaac Newton 's Answer:The duck suggested to the chicken that they playfollow the leader then the duck crossed the road causing the chicken to cross after it, but at the same time holding up traffic, thus proving that for every action there is an equal and opposite reaction .  Gandhi 's Answer:All chickens should peacefully resist by crossing the road.  George Bush's Answer:We don't really care why the chicken crossed the road. We just want to know if the chicken is on our side of the road or not. The chicken is either with us or it is against us. There is no middle ground here.  Al Gore's Answer: I fight for the chickens and I am fighting for the chickens right now. I will not give up on the chickens crossing the road! I will fight for the chickens and I will not disappoint them.  Saddam Hussein's Answer:This was an unprovoked act of rebellion and we were quite justified indropping 50 tons of nerve gas on it.  Buddha's Answer:If you ask this question, you deny your own chicken nature.   by: Wee^2 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        if u all haven't noticed by now,i have been DORMANT in the msn scene for the   past week... amazing  eh?my internet screwed up this past week,no idea what   happened.and for no apparant reason,like as if it KNEW it was the long national   day weekend and i'd just rot away without msn..it now works!!yahoo.yes,i miss   msn SOOOOO much.i finally realise that we definitely rely a lot on the   internet.did u know that just TEN years ago(not that long ago)people were still   not using email as frequently as we are using it now??post offices could still feel   needed.Ok folks,in recognition of our nation's 39th birthday coming up soon,i   have made this entry red and grey :) (i wanted white lah but it wouldn't show,so  we'll just have to settle with nj colours.)hey,i AM quite patriotic    k..sometimes.like tan kheng hua,i'm the sort who can be deeply touched while     singing national day songs..haha.we have to admit..singapore has definitely   come a long way.   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sigh . . . am sucking on a  blackcurrant-flavored lozenge  right now, typing in (finally!) the comfort of my house while you guys are pigging out on chicken cutlet, roti prata, cai fan and poultry rice in canteen right now ( with the exception of a certain hawker from s08 . . . ). Trust me, I'd rather be in your place and slog at school then rot here at home ( with a dripping sewer for a nose) and wonder wat sb mania would be like. . .  Just saw doctor b4 this, she said my throat inside   bloody swollen,    no wonder it hurt as hell to talk and i even thought at first that i got tonsillitis!Tried to take medicince and even swallowing the tablets also sooo uncomfortable. Will have to keep talking to a minimum and let throat heal or else cannot sell collar pin on sunday.   But nvm, on the  bright side  however . . . .:)  I got mc now!!! YAY! I can officially pon tml and go str8 to   SCGS   ! Although i cant play for sb mania ( cos its a physical activity and  will  be bad for me), i still can go to scgs (jus be a mute there and dun talk), and aint    NUHTHING'S    gonna stop me haha! ( except if the flu gets worse of cos). So nuria, manda and wai teng, see u guys tml!!!:) Have fun in gp;), this is the 2nd time in a row im missing a 2hr gp lesson. Sigh . . . life has its pros and cons heh?   P.S. Manda and Mindy, jiayou for sb mania k? I demand at least a silver from u guys here cos we cannot lose! N pls show mercy to the "lions" k? Taataa! Am gonna drool over cook books now to see all the delicious food i cannot eat, this is elsa's standard ways-to-occupy-your-time flu activity . . .   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       hello all!      just wanted to update and say nuria, elsa and waiteng! let's please PON SCHOOL (NJC) and go back to the other school (SCGS) on friday! please? aiya but i know nuria has to settle the 'economy' costume, waiteng probably busy and elsa likewise. AIYA i think i may not pon too now. heard that there will be   FIREWORKS  ! so quite a nice sight right? oh yeah can't wait for this weeks CIP then can see the fireworks. so  PRETTY ! okay yes i know cheap thrill. nvm =      anyway no one ever updates anymore man. as i have mentioned without fail in my previous entries. however, i just realised that quite alot of class people read this but they never ever write anything. one good example is HERMAWAN. oh and WEE SIANG. hahha i am not stupid. contary to popular belief. because i have  bionic ears  la. hahha i am like insulting myself.. i am so going crazy.      shall leave before i spout more crap. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       y  a  h  o  o .today we had a much needed half day.but then again,it kinda sucked cos  #1 .it's not a full day  #2 .we have to do chem spa some other time when other people are enjoying themselves.but all the same,it's a half day and i'm not gonna complain any further:)  p.s sc girls wear sleeveless blue uniform on friday!!now THAT'S something to look forward to  -nus 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey there's SUPPOSED to be music on the site now...think have to wait a while for it to download. so pls wait for like a few mins ok? tell me if it's working... thx 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WEEE!!! Yesterday, me and my scgs kakis, ying ying, francine and melissa, went to watch the scgs drama fest and boy that was one of the  funniest  shit i've seen since coming to njc. Scgs gals really   KICK ASS   man. Nowhere willl u see as much talent as i saw last night. To all not present, it was a peranakan-themed nigth with all the 4 classes performing, having a peranakan theme/storyline. 3 sec4 and my sister's (!) sec3 class was performing. Naturally, the sec3s lost but damn, the sec 4s were   gooood.   I nearly peed in my pants when i watched the first play, a comedy remake of shakespeares' The Merchant Of Venice. It was so funny cos they keep emphasising Antonio's gayness and the "loan" of Antonio from shylock was "nine-layered cake" or  jio chen gao.  All the characters were peranakan and Portia was a  bibik.  The last play by tessa rambles' class, was equally as funny and they won the dramafest (the story was about a pair of worried peranakan parents trying to marry off their son after he comes back from the states from uni education). Im definitely going back next year and to all the mean gals who  didn't  want to come along: HAH! U dun noe wat u missed man!  Sigh . . . being back in sc was sooo nostalgic, seeing all the teachers dressed up in peranakan clothes and being in a WHITE not  grey   school   for once. And there was NOT, i repeat, not a single J1 in da house! That means no sc gals in j1 now actually came back to watch except for me and my entourage. Wow, they missed some good shit cos it was even better than sc dance nite. But there were j2s though . . .    P.S. Somehow all the sc gals now look better (but also sluttier) 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    (   this image is copyrighted by Nuria)   ..."but LOVE is the most important of all" :)  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     (this image is copyrighted by Nuria)   let your star shine!  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I LOVE THIS BLOG! i love the fact that it's becoming a photoblog..new name:PHLOG. haha.if this website still exists in 30 yrs time,we'll be laughing at our 17 yr old selves:)  pple,post more pictures!!get "Hello".tell me your account usernames so that i can add u to my list of friends.   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WHICH SIAO LANG POSTED THE UGLY PICS??? that's very mean ok. if the person dun own up. i'll juz remove the pic myself. (i'm the administer, haha, i can remove it.HAHAHA)   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    clay-love-crazy nuria haha... yes she's actually hugging the ad.  sorry nus :P urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      a brief intro to certain members of our class.as u can see,we are not sane.not sane indeed.   urlLink    one of the many faces of qian jin  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    am i pretty?AM I?&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    shujun's normal face&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    caught red-TIED! (haha..ok lame)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    i took one, nice hor? 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      People! I've read thru all the entries and comments in this blog on our lovely national day afternoon. They are so entertaining that i think we must create a     B  LO  G    AWA   R D    to recognise some excellent crap-writer's effort. Of cos, i'm not the only in the jury. In fact all S08s are part of the judging process. As for a start, I'll nominate some nice entries and comments.  nominees for:      B E  S T   EN  TR  Y      1) Ian aka Janet Jackson  Friday, July 09, 2004    What the ****?  I really dun have much to say lor, except... CURSE YOU JUSTIN TIMBERLAKE, u're just made of wood, CURSE YOU JUSTIN TIMBERLAKE, u just had to be in the mood... CURSE YOU JUSTIN TIMBERLAKE, for passing down that "joke" CURSE YOU JUSTIN TIMBERLAKE, wish i could wash ur mouth with soap... CURSE YOU JUSTIN TIMBERLAKE, it spread like wildfire without control, CURSE YOU JUSTIN TIMBERLAKE, i hope the other party din get to know... CURSE YOU JUSTIN TIMBERLAKE, my reputation has flown the coop, CURSE YOU JUSTIN TIMBERLAKE, for revealing my b**bs!   2) Amanda Tuesday, July 27, 2004    giving janet a run for his money!  i write too much, spanning for pages, but I never write enough, i always have more emotions, never expressed,  only felt.  they are the secret emotions that no one talks about, they have no name. they are expressions, lasting for a simple millisecond, before being hidden away, that a thousand words could not describe, that a hundred pictures could not express. sometimes I smile, who knows if its fake or real. then again, who really cares? everyone enjoys false niceties. so they can tell themselves everyone is all right, and justify their walking away, not caring.  maybe its easier that way. pretending you didnt know, that inside she was, no, I was screaming, shouting, hoping to be heard, recognized,  but wearing a mask, with a smile. and knowing that, the milliseconds, when the mask falls off, are ignored.  haha well just felt like putting it up to make a statement that everyone is not what they seem. food for the thought people..  3) Nuria aka nus  -this is for weijian-  ..who by the way is SLACKING at home somewhere in MALAYSIA eating D24 durians and having an itch.wahhh get chicken pox and get sent to m'sia?!that's what i call good life man.when i had chicken pox by the way,I did not go m'sia for one, nor did i get sent to cdc.i was at home applying lots of calamine lotion and looking like a ghost all in white.hey,u noe what..u should share the joy with your lovely classmates in 04s08 who are mugging so hard and being trashed by all the teachers.and u noe HOW u can do that??by popping up in our class for just ONE chem tutorial :) this will not only benefit YOU,the individual,but ALSO has FAR REACHING benefits for US,the society at large.(that line was in my GP essay,couldn't help it.haha) #1. You might infect half the class..meaning we'll have a empty class,which means teachers might cut us some slack and we can give the excuse that "half the class is not here",which means our workload might be lessoned,which means we have more time to write in the blog,which means we'll have a life,which means...... (u get the picture)#2. (this is the best part) You might infect the chem teacher!! HOORAY!! she hasn't got immunity yet,she told us during chem prac.so u are actually doing her some good by GIVING her immunity by infecting her...good eh?2 in one. yup,u know what u have to do ;) -nus       B E S T     C  OM M E N  T S      1) ELS@ (u rock man, i'll support u)  HAHAHAHAHA!!! I remember the frumpy, indignant look on your face (like you've just been slapped)when manda sms u the "ian" msg. Is this wat ur cursing is about? Nuria GOH will be very upset if she reads such foul language leh . . . ELSA     2) Nus just a note to everyone, WrITiNG lIkE tHiS is SO NoT cUtE.pls stop it before this whole blog looks like it belongs to some    broken-english  ,  boliao ,brainless    ah lian .thank u.     B  L O  G    I  D OL    My personal choices:    Elsa- powerful writer; funny; sacrastic; daring; good sense of humour   Nus- incredible ideas and concepts. Stern and mean at times.   Ian - nothing much other than poems than neutralise the MEAN pH of this blog      * best graphic - amanda: pictorial presentation of our day. (i can nominate ian, i dun hear any music coming out)  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        fireworks!    urlLink      fireworks!    urlLink      at the singapore river!    urlLink      raffles city MRT station - the place where nuria met the clay lookalike    urlLink       scgs    urlLink    just felt like posting it up =] copy shujun ma!  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    yoyo, nus!!! i got it first!!!! hahaha. it's a testing pic. but this pic's cute. juz leave it here ba. 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Firstly, i gotta   congratulate Nus   for spotting her clay-look-alike at Raffles Place. I'm one of the witnesses so i thereby justified that she was telling the truth. That afro hair guy did look like clay but i onli managed to see the sideview. haha, but he very weird lor, dressed the way PAP would at todae's NDP.  Ydae's CIP was crazy. we got a nice spot to take picture of and watch the fireworks too. haha, thanks to elsa. after that was chaotic cos all the crowd tried to jay-walk across the road to marina shopping centre ( i think that's the name). of cos, we broke the rule too. some time later, we reached suntec city. that place sux! we spent 1 hour juz to search for affordable food with short Q. in the end, we settled with sandwiches from carrefour's delight corner. haha. den, going home from suntec is problematic too. since the collaspe of nicoll highway, many suntec's busstop are no longer in use. *damn it* once again, like last week, nus and i ( this time plus a couple more ppl) were trapped at suntec. we finally boarded a bus from esplanade (it's still crowded, think 5566 went to perform, i saw them when i'm on the bus) at 11+. needless to say, by the time i rched home, it's   THE NEXT DAY !!!      nevermind, juz to let S08s noe, i've never regretted to sign up for this CIP. Though it's not a nice way to spend a sunday, we got to spend it together in an interesting way. isn't it fun that we cracked our brains and try to find a way out together. that would certainly bind us together. heehee. haha,   love you guys and gals, we rock!!!    
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       hey guys...Check this out ...  urlLink  www.jcguide.org    then click on our  favourite nj logo  n see the ratings for our  great greyish  u , canteen food, toilets ,teachers , facilities , chiobus n yandaos   u can compare our   lovely     school wif other jcs... some parts quite true n some very hilarious...      sneak peak:          ...and camouflage them amongst our nation's concrete jungle...      ...it took bout  8 seconds  for  a drop of  H20   to seep out of nj shirt....      ...the food is of high quality....(err...)    ....jc with the most stupid name.....      ....jc with the most stupid anthem...       -naijiewmil aka     saturn   (definitely not g.wj)-   
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      as u can see...this encounter must have had a LOT of impact on me as i'm writing this entry immediately when i'm home from doing cip since 4pm.this cannot wait any longer..it's way too miraculous. i was doing cip,selling collar pins(more like begging pple to buy) ard raffles place mrt..nice quiet place where pple can sit ard and rest.ANYWAY..i was damn tired walking ard and being turned down by so many selfish singaporeans when SUDDENLY................    I S  AW   MY C LA Y CL  ONE     at first i was distracted by his hair..cos it was some afro hairstyle thing..but his FACE.it's an EXACT COPY i tell u.he had DREAMY EYES which sort of gently closes as he glances past(claymates would understand) and he had the SAME NOSE and LIPS.   crap    lah!never take photo!!!all i have now is the best memory i've ever had ever since this year started.  i dunno what's happening here in singapore...somehow clay sightings have gone up..check this page out  urlLink http://s2.invisionfree.com/Clay_Aiken_Singapore/index.php?showtopic=1515  its an article on this person who saw ANOTHER lookalike at ntu canteen.looks like i'll be heading there for many meals to come..HAHA. -nus 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>