<Blog>

<date>28,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Here again, I sit infront if my computer wasting all my time instead of studying. Here I lay, new to this blogspot, trying to find out more stuff on html. It may be late into the night but there, i lay infront of the computer exploring new html codes. because of this...Studies are neglected.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Muahahahahaha...we thrashed Compassvale 22-4...= we won.....so after all the score isnt 100-0. MY batting in the game really suka budden i still safe thanks to lousy fielding by compassvale.....Msh Softball team doesnt rely on me cause there are Aaron, Jia Yuan(WHO ALMOST MADE A GRANDSLAM), Timothy(who made a solo homerun), Nicholas the zai catcher...all batting pros....My pitching ar......2nd inning so suky pitched 7 balls in a row OMFG! budden marcus say must set the target for me hehe and strike all the way untill the inning ends hehe..Gary took over me and did a good job dut only to find out that he was only able to play for one inning due to time constrain. The B boys made a superb come back coming from below 3-5 to beat them 15-5 muahahahahah..MSH SOFTBALL TEAM ROX(but hey, that is obvious)
     
    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Muahahahahahaha....The compassvale game coming up is gonna be easy man...let me predict the score...100-0.....its gotta be true check it out on saturday......
     
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Muahahahaha....Today coach not back from overseas so marcus trained us. We had much fun without the other coach... can do anything we like so fun man....yea. And the following game is compassvale also without coach..song bo...no pressure liaoz........ Today the B team also won North Vista (OBvious).. :D
     
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today in school i pitched and managed to make my ball curve by alot. Then the maths test so easy one..... test = no need at all lah. So sian..nothing to type here liaoz
     
    
</post>

<date>21,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
           Woohoo!! We thrashed Woodland Ring 25:5. what a score!!We Played our 1st match and did this good job.I pitched for the 1st -3rd inning before being substitued by Gary finishing the game. My 1st inning was perfect man! I strike 2 out and tag one out. My 2nd inning wasnt as good but my 3rd was bad. I let in 5 runs by giving pitches that were low and runner from three could come in. It was because of this then i was taken over by gary who did a good job. I have to hao lian cause i don't keep my good thoughts in my heart.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
               The new day meant another day closer to the woodland ring match. It is gonna be exciting. In the afternoon, i helped an old man in his fifties. I met him at the bus stop. He wanted to go to the Paya Leba church and i lead him up the 100 bus. He was wearing blue shirt and talked alot but i didnt mind as long as he reaches his destination. He even wanted me to bring him the the church. I did and went back home with a smile hanging on my face. I felt good
     
    
</post>

<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today my Seniors Lost to Orchid park ....wah kao......poor game man softball........So we will take revenge and win woodland ring to let out our angryness......ZzZzZ
     
    
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      aiyo!!!!I missed my cross country again just like last year. I fell ill ar... then cannot run lor. Some say they dowan to run but then ar......I want to run leh... today damn suay.....
     
    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      LoLz™...losing to ACSi with a thrashing is really a blessing in disguise. That game was watched by some RI players and their coach. this is my conclusion on why we could win RI. 1.  RI saw our score kena thrashed by ACSi 14-4 and they lost to ACSi 10-11. So they thought that they are capable of winning us and became complacent in the game against us.  2. We are just too strong for RI.  3.  RI is just to lousy to win us.  4.  MIRACLE. 5  RI sux to the core. It really was a blessing in disguise. SoftBallerz, think about it. 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      yaY! we won the 3rd position in SRC yaY! i think aRr... MVP for Marist Team could be Jia Yuan, OR JIAO or Harng-Yi...LoLz™ shoik lor many years since our C boys got a spot in SRC. Maybe if i work harder on my pitching, i may stand a chance to get into combined schools. I want to.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      MSH vs GMS Full Time Report-- Padang Field A...The game started AGAIN with team Marist fielding first. This time, the Marist Pitcher felt more nervous than in any other game(i dunno why leh budden its the easiest team leh...).Marist Team let in 2 runs in the very first inning and thought this would be the end. BUT, we bounced back and scored the maximum 7 which again inspired the team. Timothy again made a solo homerun, Jia Yuan made another homerun which brought...(how many in aRr..?) This would mean that GeyLang's hope of getting a 3rd place would be gone. It would go to the rightfull owner, Marist. If not for the win against RI, the Marist would not be even here in this 3rd and 4th placing and it might be RI that come. RI were C boys champion in the Nationals. And the Marist won them. Well done C boys Marist. This is the last game of the SRC and GoodBye.~*~Full Time Report By Simhyi~*~
     
    
</post>

<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      MSH vs RI Full Time Report-- Padang Field D...The game started with Team Marist fielding first. Marist had not expected a win in this game. Neither do I. RI did expect a win against Marist. But what is the OutCome? aiya...tell you the result now laH its 9-1...who win? MARIS STELLA. Harng-Yi entered the field without a cap(he didn't bring his)and used Jason's cap. Harng-Yi started well by giving the first batter a strikeout, the 2nd batter hit a slow grounder to the pitcher and made easy play to 1st base. It was now that The pitcher started his nonsense again.(you tell me now which pitcher in this whole wide whole doesnt give any balls in the whole game)When it was the Marists' turn to bat, OR JIAO made some excellent+SUPERB+divine GrandSlam.(budden it wasnt really counted as there is only a max of 7 runs that can be brought in but he only brought all but himself)(OR JIAO now crying) This motivated the whole team which brought Victory to the Marist they deserved.(if there was betting...the bookies would make BIG BIG BIG$$) They have now booked their flight to field A to play the 3rd and 4th placing against GMS.~*~Full Time Report By Simhyi~*~
     
    
</post>

<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      MSH vs PCSS Full Time Report--Padang Field C...The game started off with the Marist, as usual, going for fielding, fielded first! It was excellent performance by the Marist Pitcher, Harng-Yi who strike out all 3 batters who came out to bat. All these made Harng-Yi complacent, who striked out only 1 in the following inning, received a slow easy ground ball and made a simple play to one who got out. Marist's catcher, known as OR JIAO, has made a couple of homeruns did not make any in this game. However, he was agressive and made several good stops. If you watch closely, Harng-Yi is weak is the sense that he may not have stamina to pitch throughout. And if you watch his pitching, his pitches makes use of gravitational pull as the ball sinks right at the spot the batter bats, which makes stikeouts. Does he plan to do this? Was that tyco? Or pure skill? i would say its 1/3 of all. The Marists have disappoint PCSS as they go home with a knockout. Marist have now proceeded to the 2nd round. Well Done Marist. ~*~Full Time Report By Simhyi~*~
     
    
</post>

<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Good News: We  WON  PeiCai  5-1  . Bad News: I told coach that Im abit tired and he decided to put Gary to pitch. We lost to ACSi 9999999-O.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      How nice a day could it be when both the C boys and the B boys won our games. The B boys won Temasek 15-0 while the C boys won Chinese High 7-5. WOOHOO! IM feeling great today! My pitching was as good as can be for today. I only wish i could do the same against PeiCai and that would surely secure a win. The game was too exciting for us. Nicholas made a homerun bringing 2 runs in (exculding himself) coming from below 4-5 to win the game 7-5(maybe we could had scored more) and that was the very last inning. They had no chances against us but i liked 1 thing about them. That is Good Sportsmentship. They even clapped for us when Nicholas made his homerun. They Fielded many sec 1s.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      MSH vs CHS  Full Time Report--Padang Field C The game started off with the Marist fielding. Hai Wei started pitching which was his 1st time with lacking experience. Hai Wei wasn't in good form and let in 5 runs which resulted in the change of pitcher, Harng-Yi. Harng-Yi was in a good form and let in no runs from the moment he made his 1st pitch to the moment he made his last pitch. You can easily tell that his pitching is made fit with the opponent's team name. Whenever a team is lousy, it boosts his morale confidence which makes his pitching superb. But whenever he pitches against a good team, he will not be as good. Nicholas Ong ended the game SUPERBLY WHICH HE MADE A 2/3 GRANDSLAM which brings the Marist Team to a 7-5 win. He brought in 3 runs(incuding himself) and was therefore the man of the match(In my personal opinion). The decision of whether This team would get into the 2nd round would depend on the game against PeiCai Full Time Report by Simhyi
     
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      MSH vs TMS Full Time Report--Padang Field D  The game started off with the Marist batting first. They Scored a Maximum of 7 runs which lifted confidence in the team spirit. Jeri hit a perfect grandslam (which i witnessed) and that ends the inning.there wasn't much in the 2nd inning but the Marist Team still scored the maximum which is 7 runs too. It was in the 3rd inning when Temasek felt something was wrong and bucked up but only to let in 1 run in the 3rd inning. In the last inning, they changed their pitcher who did a very good job. The game ended with a score line of 15-0. They have now reserved their seat in the 2nd round regardless of the outcome of the next game which is against ACS
     
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Haiz...Losing to another team is heart aching. To Maris Stella, SRC Softball Carnival is just some friendly game held. But to the others, its some kind of serious game to play. Catholic High fielded all their best players to beat our mixed team which consist of juniors and seniors.(Must let sec 1 experience mah) Although losing to Catholic High wasn't as bad as montfort, we still lost! 1-8. We can only pray hard that we win Chinese High in order to even have a slim hope of getting into the 2nd round.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Have you ever seen a Marist pitcher tossing in the softball team? Well...we just did in the game against North Vista. It was almost called off due to another rain...why does it always seem to rain when we play North Vista.?.?.? The umpire didnt want to be known as a (come here get money for free then go) so decided to make the game go on under the heavy rain. I was left with no choice...not to pitch but tossing(hahaha i strike out countless ppl with that...) Bertram felt funny for the team as he always thought Marist do not toss...well...can he pitch in this condition? It was coach's wish to toss...We also fielded many sec 1s except for pitcher, catcher, 3rd base 1st base and centre field....The game ended with a score 14-6
     
    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today, we sat at our chair witnessing the invigilator stepping into this classroom 5 minutes late. Needless to say, we started our exams late. Although i didn't revise for my geo at all, i still managed and found it easier than i thought. I don't think i will get a high mark, neither do i think that i will fail. Softball match against North Vista was boring as can ever be. I was made to pitch(at least more experience gained) for only 1 inning before god said "ok softballers its time to stop your game". I striked 2 out before having the 3rd to come out and it rained. What a day! the score shan't be postphoned like what the game did and start with a fresh sheet. As you know, it seems like a glory pitching strikes and hard to come by (if i'm not on form). In other words, all my efforts were wasted for nothing excpet on those vistarains(who tasted the power of msh pitcher). Following that i am going to have the game of the season which is held at kallang against MSS(Montfort Secondary School). They are known to be local rivals who are competing with us for the prestigious championship title.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
           Today, was the worst day i have ever experienced in secondary school life. 1st of all, we already had trouble in the 1st period of the day(CME). Ms Koh had to come down to give us a gentle reminder that the sec 3s are having their CA. But i failed to perform my duty as a class chairman and Mr. Koh had to come down personally to give us an unforgetable lesson to learn. The whole class was made to stand outside the class in 2s and then head for the porch. He mentioned about having the whole class to get caned. every will get 2 strokes. Councillors have  3 and the class commitee to suffer 4. He seemed damn bloody serious and thought this is the end of my flawless record and it would be broken in 8 years (i have not been caned the moment i stepped into the school). Mr Koh asked for a volunteer to be the 1st and without any hesitation Song Yuan was willing to take the 1st stroke of the day(he is a councillor). But Mr Koh requested for the biggest boy to take it. Even before taking the stroke, he weapt(NO INSULTS!!) and was sent back into the queue and Mr.Koh letting us off with a stern warning saying that if there is going to be a 2nd time, councillor will face the axe, class commitee member will be likewise, sacked. The whole class was let off walking back to class without any noise made. It was so unlike of 2I. Then, there were 2 new trainee teachers covering us for 3 weeks(Maths + English Lit). I just dont see why Mr. Koh have to resort to suspension. Gary was one of his victim. He was caught studying Geography in CME lesson and was therefore sent out of class. Mr. Qualye got to know about this and gave him a letter for a new CCA. I felt this is so unfair and mean to do such thing because he already have a bat, glove and more which i think will not be useful in the coming future. Then, Mrs.Sim demanded us to stand for the whole 3 periods and reflect on out behaviour in class. That's how bad the day can ever be. How much worse could it be?
     
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hmm..Today had my last lesson with Miss Leong, who is not just a trainee teacher but a caring 1 too .(and i got her email!)  She is leaving as she only takes over Mrs Champion untill the Mid-Year Exams. Today is RI VS DAMAI at turf city, which is no doubt the match of the season. The score has been 2-2 going through extra time. Exciting and vacum tight game. it was 3-3 in extra time. Both teams escaped from hell, facing heaven. So the poor umpire had to spend more time with them in extra time, rather then having the privillage of sleeping at home. in was the same for the next inning. Again 4-4. But the next was diferent. RI caught up with awakening spirit to score just 1 run to win the game. The end. The good and bad had now been obvious and clear. Separated with tears.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today is another boring day. Nothing special. Nothing significant enough to be written here. But just to tell you that Arsenal are now the English Premier League Champions. BOOO i am supporting Man Utd.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today at our B Boys Game. We were 1-6 down. Untill when all bases were loaded...The pitcher hit linden in the thigh and had a full base walk. 2-6. Jun long came up, with full confidence both mentally and phyiscally. It was also totally unexpected yet Trully remarkable. Jun Long had just made an impact in his life, which is to make a grandslam (obviously to bring himself and 3 others home). But his running was not fast enough to outrun the ball which was brought back into field and was nearly tagged  out! If i was the umpire i would have called OUT! And all the runs brought in would have been wasted because it was already 2 OUT!! What i risk he took.he score drew level to 6-6, with 2 more innings to go. All we have to do is to score a run and control them till they are pressed. But it proved the otherwise. They made some good hits and we made some good saves. But their good hits overpowered us and we started losing confidence and hope. They were demoralised deeply and badly and hence needed to play with a lost heart. They lost and the final score at Chinese High is Chinese High 12 Maris Stella 7
     
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ...Today so sian aRRR
     
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Wow! I have been offered a job to tutor Primary 6 students who are very weak in their Mathematics. I could be a teacher in a class teaching! Cool! For this, i get CIP hours as a reward. I also believe that it makes full use of my june holidays instead of playing Computer games at home. If i ever get a chance to see a computer, what's next? That peer tutoring will be a good excuse to 'get out of home' and also make full use of my time. It will give me a very good experience to be a teacher rather than to be a student. But i may not be free. I have my softball training that cannot be missed out.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today, a very usual thursday, was an exciting day. Our B Boys have just defeated YuYing to qualify for  AT LEAST a 4th place . They would have to play against Chinese High. If they win, they will play the 1st and 2nd placing. If they lose, they will play for the 3rd and 4th placing. It gurantees an extra trophy in their cabinet.  Congratulation to B Boys.  They won them 15-1
     
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Is our team falling apart? Is this the end to our United Marist Team? Are we still capable of getting better results in the Nationals like in the SRC? Will we? We cannot let our team ever fall apart. Team-Mates are throwing insults at each other. Maybe its the scrimage that causes the disputes, but we do really need training on real games. So what is the solution to our never ending quarellings, but at the same time train up our 'real game skills'? Perhaps the most significant dispute was the packing of equipments. The captain have to arrange and organise it. Its not gonna be me! Nor anybody else! Aaron claims that the sec2 gang (tim, gary, or_jiao, jia yuan) are responsible for it. It may be true that they come earlier than us to have breakfast at MacDonals and arrive at the field for early Game that they play on their own. To do that, they would have to take out the equiments. That's already half the job done.but in the afternoon we take turns to keep.  So, i would suggest that they would be the one to take out the equipments and the rest to keep the equipments in the afternoon during trainings on saturday. 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
          I just  found a word to replace my feelings on public transport. Lacking  self-esteam  . So i wasn't wrong. I just feel that some people do not welcome me on board. I also do not feel welcomed. It just gives me some funny feeling that is out of my vocabs. that there is something wrong with me. AS IF the whole world  is looking at me. So i am always eager to jump off the bus through the windows or emergency exit, looking at my watch. Why is this happening? Its not that im mad. Its lacking of self-esteam. I just read about it and i won't be wrong. I'm not writing it here to be proud of it. I won't keep my thoughts in my heart. Regardless STANDING in the MRT, LRT, bus, or whatever transport, my mind is forever twirling, beneath.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      woooo! Never felt so relieved from projects. Just few weeks ago my IPW group was tagged 'slacker group'. Now we are best group as we completed everything faster than the rest Ahha. Now i have no more worries about my IPW whereas the other still have to crack their brains aobut it. Anyway B boys so zai. Beat ACSi, PeiCai, Compassvale to finish off as 2nd in their group to qualify for top 6. Table tennis C boys have gotten a respectable national 4th. Congrats. Badminton also won Montfort 3-2 good score line hahaha. Its all i have to say and...ByE ByE
     
    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Sian aRr...Lost to TPJC A girls WTF im not a marist. Actually, i was 1% at fault(everybody is) in the game. Who told the Coach put 3rd choice pitcher to F*** Up the whole game, with all the sec 1s playing in the last inning, even worse right?? Somemore let in more than 12 runs in the very last inning, which you could blame no one but Hai Wei?? All the Ball no strikes caused it.(No Offence). HaHa the game lasted longer than Major League Baseball, especially in the last inning which lasted about 1/2 hour(1/2hr solely on the part where they batted )...I have no comments about that. Only that i have to hide my face.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Haha haven't been blogging since how many donkey years ago. By the way our B boys won PeiCai to book their place in the 2nd round which secures at least 6th in national. They won PeiCai 8-4. Although their perfomance still wasn't like of Marist, PeiCai still proved the weaklings of the match. They just couldn't hit the fast ptiches from Bertram.  Congratulation To Our B Boys 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yea! Our B boys won ACSi with a score of 7-6 woah. It's a damn exciting game nobody should ever miss out. Just to summarize why the whole game was so interesting. At the last inning, the score was 4-6 going 2 points down. All bases loaded. It wasn't a grandslam. It was a 2-runs-brought in by Linden Toh Xuan Li which made the gap close up to 6-6. our coach was like so damn happy. Then Sant came out to bat. With 2 strikes 0 ballz.we were all damn worried if he got striked out. But after many attempts on foul ballz, he made a slow yet tricky ball to 3rd base. Linden, from 2nd base ran all the way to home, at some neck breaking speed. Actually, the ball was thrown to 1st base but the 1st base man just somehow couldn't step on his baze properly and Sant just zoomed past him, forcing the umpire to call  SAFE . By then, Linden had already reached home and...GAME OVER WE  WIN ! Marist had just celebrated a tough fight against ACSi which the score was expected the otherwise.  WELL DONE B TEAM! 
     
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
          It has been very long since i last entered an entry, since i.....Well, I was at the Catholic VS RI game. Both Teamz were not as good as I expected. especially RI. Their Performance were poor. Fielding worse. Throwing is beyond vocabz. But pitching was Passable. In my opinion, thrashing RI is simply easier than last year, since their coach does not really concentrate.      As for Catholic High...i was there expecting some superb plays. But they were just like any strong TeAmZ. Their result against ACSi and FTP suggested something. But it seems that the suggestion was that FTP and ACSi were lousy, not divine Catholic High.      You may say im a spy. 俗语说得好：知已知彼，百战白盛。I was definately there for some reasonz. I also Dressed myself with a white shirt, so that i might blend into the crowd, as a spy. The final score was 14-2 but that does not mean the Catholic High were any stronger than we expected. Ri was a total disappointment.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
          It has been sometime since i last published something so, here i start. On saturday, 22-5-2004, i went to Ponggol Marina together with Eugene Gor Gor, his friend, Sophia, the sister, my brother and lastly another friend...? We rented a boat for Wakeboarding, which cost at least few hundred buckz, for about 3 hours. Well, to some pros, they may say that it is just some way to waste money buy hey, the 5 of us are new to this sport and i wouldn't dare to say im the best amoung them, and i can't say im the best!... aww its some shame to waste money right? Eugene's friend, being the best wakeboarder, demonstrated by being 1st.we all thought that it was some simple sport but it turned out the otherwise. So, sophia was the 1st beginner to try it out. She wasn't the worse but also wasn't the best, furthermore receiving 'bellay' lessons (better sense of balance)(how to spell bellay haR???)I went next, performing some funny falls that disappointed me and the boat load...
     
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      WooHoo!!! Maris Carved their way through the 3rd and 4th placing by winning ACSi in the 1st round and YuYing in the 2nd round. Although they had lost their crucial game in the semi-finals against RI, the spirit and passion was enough to beat off Chinese High 8-7 which was more than enough to give Bro.Anthony a good one, and to show denis koh what softballers have that he doesn't have. Now, the B Boys of Maris Stella High Softball Team have gotten and truly remarkable 3rd placing in the Inter-Schools Nationals Softball Competition. I was there to witness, the twist of fate. Gabriel and Bertram had no doubt contributed the lion's share of the team's success. I would like to thank Gabriel for his outstanding 2/3 grandslamwhich gave us 6-7, trailing them very closely. I also appreciated what Bertram had taught me to become what i am today in the softball team, and for pitching in his last game in Maris Stella High, in which he did superbly well. The pitching in the 1st inning was formidable. All strike outs in the 1st inning. What more could he ask for?? The weather was also perfect. Chinese High's batting form was lousier than you though so. Having gone through so much pain and scolding, sweat and bruises, our  B Boys proved that they were no weaklings by showing excellent skills in their last and final game in Maris Stella High! The sec.4 boys can now concentrate on their 'O' levels.  I will miss them for the Saturdays training.  Wishing them all the best for their exams. For those trying to make it to RJC, the Ri coach was there to pick his catch. Work harder and Good Luck! Like how we make it to the 3rd placing.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today, which is a sundaY, is another day gone. I just do not know why i just cannot sit down and study for my weaker subjects. Neither am i doing so for my other subjects! Ahhhh having said this i better go now. ByE All
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      School ReOpens. Or rather the holidays are the past. I spent 1 month of June Dreaming. I can't agree that school sux. I get the spirit together with the school. It's so nice to be back there, in my class room, those cheerful faces of those. I didn't exclude teachers. They are also the ones whom we once again, meet. It feels good to once again, learn those nice facts in the classroom. I never grumbled about leaving the holidays for the Term. In nicer facts, i was actually looking foward to it. But 1 thing, i might get sick of school once again, when the exams are looming. i hope the spirit of new school term would stay with me, forever till i leave school. 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
         What would be the Be$t Bet? Obviously,   is the Be$t show to catch. It makes use of Hokkien to captivate the attention of viewers. Jack Neo, making full use of his creativity, even made the hokkien rhyme together with humour added. For me, i seldom watch movies, which makes me very isolated from the movie gang. I shan't tell you details about the movie, just in case the J-Team sue me for letting interlectual propeties off...
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      My pitching nowadays have been lousy. Maybe it's the new boots that i have to get used to it. Untill yesterday, i faced difficulties, pitching strikes, which i usually do...somehow lost control. Only yesterday, i seemed to pick up some form. I managed to strike out many ppl, making my pitch fast. So, in other words, im confident that we will get a respectable position in the Nationals.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      YAY! at last, i get to participate in the Maths Olympiad. It is the most prestigious mathematics competition, and anybody would want to participate in it. No doubt, participants are the better ones in Mathematics. I don't expect Gold. But i certainly want my SilvER! It's  dream come true. I have been waiting for 1 year? I missed my softball training to attend this competition, some sacrifice.....Anyway, Our C Boys Nationalz are coming. I look foward to the day we play our very 1st game. I am also looking foward to the day we get Nationalz 1st. Since Ri and Chinese High, the 2 big Guns are down this year. We must make use of their downfall. On the other hand, Catholic High and PeiCai have improved alot. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      &nbsp;&nbsp; Maris Stella vs Catholic High. A highly anticipated game. I looked forward to it since the last day of SRC ended. Well, it started off rather well, 1st & 2nd inning 0-0. We lost the toss for fielding, we batted but to no good results.&nbsp;We managed to&nbsp;hold them down to a 0-0 tie for the 1st & 2nd inning.&nbsp;We had&nbsp;alot of confidence after all these good job, but soon became the opposite when some morale sinker came in the 3rd inning, where they hit my stamina-weaken pitch for a 2 run.&nbsp;All that nonsense came just after that very incident. 11 runs were brought in, we were feeling helpless about it, as more and more of us make mistakes. Nothing could help my stamina improve in the game itself, as my pitch became slower, nice for them to hit. This inning ended with a pop-fly to Jia Yuan. the game ended, with a scoreline of 12-0. Everybody performed very inadequately, i am not excluded, If only i had more stamina to pitch like what i did in the 1st and 2nd inning, the game would be some 0-0, since our fielding is not very good especially 2nd base, with nobody to fill that gap. I am looking forward to the game against PeiCai, hopefully we can beat them. Together with RI, i hope that they both get eliminated in this very stage, i really want a national position. &nbsp;&nbsp; Is my blog boring? Tell me what i should add in my blog, or maybe give me the link of the others which you think it's nice 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      &nbsp; I'm feeling so happy today, all thanks to my wonderful NAPFA 5-Item test day. Played soccer before NAPFA, then proceeded to the hall, took a piece of result recording slip, which could only contain 8 names, Aaron, Ding Hui and Xuan Ren had to find their own groups. Then we proceeded to the inclined pull-up station, which Hai Gay could not get an A, only B with 25 pulls. Hao Yuan is an exception(you know his weight). I did  30 pulls , then just gave up since&nbsp; already got A.&nbsp;Then we went for sit-ups with Poh Mah See. He was humourous. The only thing was that everybody was trying to sabo Gary...we pushed the back-board nearer to him, his result lousier =X. The only thing shocking was Hao Yuan, with his huge spare tire, he reached&nbsp;out to about 65cm, with everybody pushing his back actually. Poh Mah See also can be easily cheated, LoLz. I got  52cm(sit and reach)  with my personal record, some amazing A i got. (they also push me a little). We then headed for Mr. Ganesh, where we all were rude to him, esp jia yuan...1st attemp any how jump... So 2nd try i got  215cm(Jump) , just nice for an A. Then OrJiao so funny...225cm also cannot get A, short of 1 cm ONLY.(He is 14yrs). We proceeded to the Shaw Hall for our Shuttle run, after getting a drink from the canteen.&nbsp; We heard from Wei Jing that he got 8.86s. So we all went to that station. I actually fell in the 1st attempt XP. My second attempt was also my personal record, in which i made some stunning  9.42 s.  Jia Yuan also not bad la, he got 8.6s leh...Hao Yuan also got some good result by getting 10.68. We carried on to our final station, the Sit-Ups. Paul Leong penalised Gary for doing wrongly... I did  48 Sit-Ups , then stopped since it was an A, and my jerzy number =Þ. I went straight home after that and all these ended my happy Day 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; We won FTP, which put us as group champions of group B, my pitching also back to how i used to be, for the rest of the tournament i hope. More confidence have been pumped into me, every batter comes, every batter goes. I started 1st, doing fairly well. The team became motivated like how we used to be in the SRC. Nevertheless, we're still united as a team, undivided. The score was  36-2 , i pitched for 4 innings, only 3 strike-outs. Gary replaced me for batting and pitching, must give everybody chance lar. Gary also didn't perform to coach's expectation and couldn't get to pitch in the last inning, so hai wei took over to do a stunning good job. 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Did fairly against Chai Chee, lousy against Damai. The training session which i looked forward to was a sucess, to improve on my mistake, do better in games. I am getting back my form, or at least i hope. DAMAI WENT TO JAPAN AND THEREFORE WITHDREW FROM SOFTBALL NATIONALS SINGAPORE. WIN / LOSE WE WILL QUALIFY FOR 2nd ROUND!!!!!!!!! But undoubtly, a win against FTP will mean we avoid the likes of Catholic High and ACS. Win would put us in a better position. Lose will make life difficult. Anyway there is an irritatingg kia in my tag board, annon.&nbsp; Let's hope that the Best Softballers in Singapore be the Champs, with fair umpiring although... 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
             Got Sub. out in the 1st inning, for some stupit pitching. Well, gary did a fair job, but in only thing is..we didn't bat well enough. And maybe some fault from me. Lost the game, looking forward to the FTP game. And i vow to pitch better, properly, and concentrate better i hope. A win against FTP would mean a 2nd round place. But tougher, facing ACSi, Catholic High, and maybe YuYing. After that, still went back to kallang for more more training. Went home by bus 16. Halfway through air-conditioner disfunction. All the passengers got a complimentary ticket, continued the journey with bus 14.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
          8-2 was the final score. We didn't do well. Why? Got some reasons later. Well, Chai Chee was tossing. Our dear coach didn't really train us for that. Side toss batting does not lob. How can he compare these 2. We really had trouble hitting those lobbing ball. We were not trained to hit those. I repeat,  WE HAD NO TRAINING ON THOSE TOSS BALLS . And another thing, coach substituted me for no good reasons. When Gary came in for me, it was 3-0, no runs conceded yet. So the score became 3-2 just after Chai Chee was able to hit his pitch, deep to left field, why? Gary had good accuracy, i admit. But, he should gather more speed, so that enemies cant hit any. That's why i chose to be the fatest. Even balls can be strike, they swing as their eyes cant take fast pitches. I striked out 5 people in this game, 4 walks. What's wrong with walks? So, its only strike-out or walk, no hits. Coach doesn't praise for strike-outs. he only remembers those mistakes. I really think that gary need to improve his speed, other schools can hit better than Chai Chee, and with accuracy, many can hit far. Speed is really important. I am the fastest, with some accuracy. Gary is the most accurate, with some speed. Hai Wei has some accuracy and some speed. Well, Gary is really Good against schools which cant bat, accuracy takes an important part of the game. AGainst good schools, speed is more important. It's either strike-out (maybe they cant eye), or walk (since i dont have alot of accuracy as Gary.). I really doubt whether some can hit fast pitches. So, i decided to choose speed over accuracy. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
         Today, saturday, normal day, fun day. NOthing much to say about training, only that coach said that he was dyin?!?!?! He had some urea acid or whatever...he came late and went off early. After training, and after eating, went to play P00l with Tim, JIa Yuan and Orjiao. Was Fun and realised that tim was not bad after all. So Tim's mother came and fetch us. Sent Jia Yuan home. Then Proceeded to drop me at OrJiao's house, where i could take 82 home. 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
           Today, thursday, tricky 2.4km run coming in the afternoon. I set off as usual for our PE lessons, changing to our PE shorts, always stripping in class. Well, Mr. Leong mentioned many things about our discipline, our behaviour as a Marist. It actually took up half of our entire Precious PE lesson time, which we were all looking forward to, playing soccer of course. The bad thing was, we only had around 15 minutes left to complete our soccer match. We drew with the better team formed in this 2 classes, and both teams, were treated like losers when we stepped out of the Multi-Purpose-Court Gates. So, the game ended, we were preparing to return when something horribly disgusting happened. I walked up the stairs of the GrandStand. Only half my foot was anchored to the next step, and fell. I put my right foot forward, and as a fast walker, my next foot was already up. My left shin had just hit the wooden seats of the GrandStand. Initially, I thought to be some minor injury, perhaps carrying bruises or minor cuts around the school. But who would have thought that about 0.5cm³ of flesh was peeled off, with the shocking shock i got, it didn't seem as serious as anybody would have thought to be. With a white thing protruding out of the flat surface, it was thought to be a broken bone. But the truth behind that was, the fat came out. Being an athelete, its natural that our legs are stronger, if not my shin would have been gone. I was being carried up by Ka Wai and Mr. Leong, 2 stories, it wasn't easy as you think, I'm 50kg for goodness sake. I almost felt like sleeping when so much blood, the sudden gush of red liquid flowing out slowly. It dampened my white socks, which is as good as being thrown away. As i sat at the bench outside the general office, i thought about 1 thing in life : All you need is 1 step, you miss it, you fall, probably to your death. And Mr.Leong must have been joking about the need of being hospitalised. Shortly after being laid on the bench, Mr.Suresh, came running to my aid, with his medicine box, like how he always used to treat the other students. Well, there were indeed signs of concern. But when he said Oh shit, what is this man...I really thought over the seriousness of this fall. He got some water, probably clean water, together with a piece of cotton wool, to clean up the blood stains on my then handicapped leg. Nothing in my life could be worse than the situation I was in, the unknown situation of the injury. And Mr. Dennis Koh came shortly after receiving the news, bringing some hot water to treat the initial shock. After all that, he questioned me :" Guess what will happen in the year 2006." I replied saying I will be secondary 4 then. EH TO BE CONTINUED I GOT NO TIME NOW 2MORW THAN WRITE BB 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      On a saturday, where we all were looking forward to an exciting game against Raffles Institution, did not really turn out well. They were the defending champions, 1 year ago, they made an unbeatable run to win the Trophy. This year, they fell. They took the lead in the 1st inning, with 2 homeruns, they lead 2-1. That was not the end. We batted well, especially when Jia Yuan hit a homerun, bringing 1 in. All these were followed by a homerun, hit by an unbelievable samuel. He hit the ball into left field, where they all underestimated his size, came forward.  But perhaps, the most exciting part was the last inning. You may have thought that majority of the runs came in here. But you are WrOnG. We batted 1st, no advantage, more disadvantage. We batted our last inning, but to no avail, no runs. When it was their turn to bat, things were getting more tense. Their star batter came out, with a runner on 1st. I knew i had to give him a walk, or a homerun means GaMe oVeR. Nevertheless, i gave him an intentional walk. The Next batter was also powerful, but also got a walk. Then, it was all bases loaded. A short batter came out, perhaps a walker? It was 2 out. Strike-Out means we win. But it would seem ridiculous. Give him a free walk? NO WAY. So, all i did was to control my ball for him. I had 2 strikes on him. So when i pitched my final ball, I admired it moving towards the target, thinking of him getting strike-out, but he swang. The Ball went high. Every runner left their bases heading for the next. The most important was the runner from 3. Just at the corner of my eye, seeing him struggling to home, which means they were about to score another tie-breaking point. Fortunately, the ball went high to me, and i caught it. 3rd base was rushing for me. 1st base also wanted the ball. But i kept my cool, to insert it into the deep pocket, back in my glove, saved, we had just won Raffles institution 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      We did very very badly against PeiCai. That game should not be as expected. The score did not prove the stronger team nor the weaker team. Something was very wrong with the whole team, including ME. We did very badly overall and well...we lost 2-7.  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>