<Blog>

<date>21,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Dedicated to: JC, CL, AIAR, AMV, CA, DL, PD, AS, TM, RS and MY   The tender words are spoken each body and soul bared told secrets over endless days often doing more than dared.  New world beyond my door with intrigued and intensity since the sharing of our hearts bonds now make permanently.  Facing our days made easier despite any type of weather each others heart felt deeply all happy we stuck together.  Took us time and effort the bonding as strong as glue I now promise never to untie the bonds I've tied with you.  Understanding of each other knowing loving hearts care as a relationship interchanges these bonds will always be there.  To never leave on the outisde love entering each domain laughing, caring, and sharing forever friends we became.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I want to lay my head to rest Forget about this day Forget about the emotional ride That marked this shitty day.  I want to curl up beneath the covers Cleanse my mind of thoughts Cleanse the tainted train That I nearly caught today.  I just want to close my eyes Sleep a dreamless night Sleep until the end is near To end this eventful day.  Just want to have an early night Wake up and feel refreshed Wake up without the ringing In my fucking head
     

    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Dedicated to: CL, JC, AIAR, AMV, MB, PD, AS, TM, RS, DL and CA   This world is not for me as I am not for it I do not play the conformist games nor do I give a shit. What I am is me a pain for others to see mutilated...desecrated...humiliated, and a pain to be free! But I must go on I cannot die I must show others the way and that they must try. We must be one through individuality so to live this life and be who you have to be.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Dedicated to: SMR   This cold, grey place I call our home but the way things appear, it's where the demons roam I want nothing more than a warm beam of sun but then evil strikes and I'm on the run.  This cold, grey place where I dwell where I am, I look around, I am in hell the illusion of life straightening out lasts only a moment  the the straight life I want becomes suddenly bent.  This cold, grey place eats at me deep within I'm going straight downhill all over again am I this weak, or is it that strong no matter what I do it always seems wrong.  This cold, grey place takes it all away it hurts so bad, so why do I stay it's slowly devouring all of my sanity all I want is to be free.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Dedicated to: SMR, PD, AS and AJF   Sometimes it's hard to find a friendly face Among the bustling crowd or to understand a new look given by a passerby. The hurt of uncertainty of the wave from afar transforms itself into  a hope that comes too late.  I try to listen to the footsteps walking on the wet pavement but the light from sundown blocks my understanding of the lightening that struck you and the colours of sunrise hinder my perception of the coolness of your skin.  Little by little I reach the end of another day that went by; It was a face I didn't see A warmth I never felt It was the hurt of the uncertainty of a day that was never lived. 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dedicated to: ADMV, CA and SMR  As I quietly smoke this cigarette I distractedly look to the skies And there you are, the brightest star shining down from the sky And I wonder, Are you glowing so brightly where you are? Can they see you so clearly as I can?  As I quietly smoke this cigarette I abstractedly hear a passing car And there he goes, a complete stranger to you and I And i wonder Does his heart ache with such treacherous pain? Can he unburden his pain to his loves?  As I quietly smoke this cigarette I distantly focus on the street light And it cries out Lead me to their path to light up the way Lead me to their hearts to guide them nearby  As I quietly smoke end my cigarette I resolutely remember your words And I wonder If one day the sadness that invades you will ever disperse and leave you to smile?
     

    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dedicated to: ADMV  Your little ways intrigue me: the way your eyes wrinkle when you smile, your hands a cascade of butterflies as you talk to me,  your hair falling carelessly on your forehead as we talk well into the early hours of the morning, your mind a well of thoughts I dive into eagerly. I love the way I can pick you from a crowd by the way that you walk; self assured and carefree,  the way your laughter can fill a room, and echo, long after your not there anymore. I love the way you care, how you can go on loving  even if is unwanted,  how your heart can renew itself -like a spring, eternally - and that you are never short of emotions. I am lost in the tender lines of your body, how you can seem so fragile when you sleep you seem so childlike, so innocent yet the power that emanates from you  keep me strong, and keep me safe. I adore the way you look at me, each time as if you are seeing me for the first time,  the way our eyes meet over a crowded room and locked in silence,  I know you can read my thoughts, that I cannot hide from your penetrating glance. I love the way you fold your arms around me, hugging me so tight, keeping me close to your heart like I am part of your chest, like you will never let me get away. To me there is so much magic  hidden away in the depths of your eyes,  so much warmth in you embrace, so much beauty in your smile, that I cannot help but watch silently and in smiling silence  as you sleep, when you talk, when you dream, and wait to be swept along  and enchanted by all that is you, You mesmerize me… 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dedicated to: ADMV  For I have come across a glow, A brightness that I know not of, It radiates a warmth that I cannot explain, A light like no others before.  Why it has touched me is a mystery, For as my mind replays it’s touch, A smile races across my face, A tingle bounces in my heart.  It is an energy that I have dreamed, One not of this plane but instead, A gift from He who rules all. A reminder of the power of Love.  Though these words may be defined in ways Other than what their true meaning is, I shall endure in how they make me feel. For to really feel is the freedom of Life.  As I write the words in front of me, I continually travel to that moment When I stared into the eyes of this Light And truly felt removed from being physical.  I ramble now as I continue this mesmerizing Journey into a beauty, Warmth and Feel That I have dreamed about all  Of what is my recorded history.  My enormous thanks to the universe, For allowing me this moment of Glow, This opportunity to touch an Energy, I did not think could ever be real.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      To feel your touch my heart would no longer ache  To feel your tender kiss my heart would no longer wish  To see your hands reach for mine my heart would celebrate  To see your smile my heart would brightly glow  To feel your love my heart would simply rejoice  To feel your embrace my tears would cease...
     

    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Take me there where The sky is shimmering of a flourishing shuffling Dance through the night Magnetic sparkling of heavenly colours So spectacular so striking so bright Take me there where white drifts glittering like crystal and ice is the colour of the moon Where the Artic wind drifitng in the night is like the stars of diamonds shivering of cold Take me there where I can listen to silence to the place where my spirit grows far up north Take me there where in the bitter winter night I can call someplace  our home.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sitting here alone in my corner of the world Watching each day, this life I lead be told My mind wanders all these different paths Childhood memories, trauma, happiness, and death  As an adoloscent, you were my hero  Always there to rescue me from all my sorrows The years past by and I matured As always, there you were, leaving me feeling secure I ventured out on my own thinking I was mature, Knowing you would still be there to reassure Now here I am, all alone, Wishing that I could have you home I replay every minute of that day in my mind Hoping and wishing for answers I may find My corner gets smaller every day The walls keep closing in, making me afraid Those I ran to have all gone to hide, You are gone, my hero has died Leaving me here with all this pain and sorrow inside 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Words written down for all to see, Emotion love and fantasy, Intense deep open to all, A life lines to some for others a fall.  All aspects of life good and the bad, We write down our words happy or sad, Unspoken truths easy to write, To share with others who live far from sight.  Pen to paper or tips to the keys, Words keep on flowing some times with ease, Expression to rhythm the heart over flows, As feelings for writing just grows and grows.  Then comes the moment the words they dry up, Frustrating debating the brains empty cup, Advice for the writer to give it a rest, It will all come back I promise its best. 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don’t want to be the air you breathe I want to be the breath you take I don’t want to make you smile I want to be the lips as they curve I don’t want to make your heart beat I want to be the blood that flows I don’t want to be your world I want to be the sun that gives you life I don’t want to be the love of your life I want to be the girl you marry 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Based on another dream   Realigning my thoughts again Demons tangoing in my mind Angels screaming in my mind Thoughts jumbled, leaving me behind Heart falls to the floor Still beating as it descends Broken and battered I am Here in my shadows it begins Shards of broken glass Flowing through my veins Crystallizing it Then inhale the pain Monsters in my closet  Creatures under the bed Snow white is dissected The seven dwarves are dead No fairy tale happy ending Blood sprayed across the wall In non-geometric designs From a tripping mad mans mind Ligaments crash with sinew Muscles fall from bones Tongue swollen inside Despite the devils I’m alone Copper taste feels my mouth Smell of burnt hair in the air Screams building in my throat What the hell is going on here Let me go now to oblivion  Let me embrace the end It’s quieter and safer there I can’t do this again… again 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Based on a dream    Hear Me   Prayers uttered Alone I tremble Here in firelight Within your temple  Going crazy here Going insane A wicked twist Lost within pain  Labyrinth controlling  Lost in my maze A jaded worshiper Stuck in a pious daze  I hope for answers Prayers screamed aloud Incense burning I’m falling down  Hold me now Don’t leave me alone I lay upon the floor I’m growing cold  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Never ask me To hide my tears Away from you I owe you nothing So there is nothing To hide All will be revealed What I do What I say It will all be revealed I don't care If you hate it For you mean nothing I don't need it In fact I never did And you'll never know Why I owe you nothing And why I never will     
     

    
</post>


<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to: Lord of the boards - Guano Apes Mood: Content   
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ignorance is bliss   
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Listening to: Betrayed me - Adema Mood: Down    Been sitting on the balcony for the past 30 minutes just watching the world go by.  It's interesting to watch people go about their lives with no care or regard for anyone else, complete strangers crossing paths and never glancing at the person passing by them or giving a thought to what sorrow their lives may hold for them.  We all do this everyday of our lives and who can blame us when the people that  are  in our lives do not give a shit about our sorrow or joy, so why would we care about a stranger's? The world is a cruel, cold and lonely place for us mere humans to inhabit. That is the conclusion I reached with my 30 minutes of observation from my balcony...  Additionally, in my 30 minutes of quiet on looking, I also reached the conclusion that I am a complicated person with intricate beliefs. I can forgive those close to me who sometimes hurt me the most but I cannot forgive people that are mere acquaintances for sheer words.  I tried to find an explanation for this and came to the conclusion that I do make sense occasionally: those who are close to me are so for a reason, thus when hurt is spread my way, it is easier to forgive because of the good times that have been spent; however when an acquaintance says something of the nature I am referring to, it is impossible to forgive for various reasons: 1) I have nothing to fall back on regarding friendship; 2) the specific words I am referring to hurt me more than I could ever express (hell, I cried in front of my mother because of them); 3) the only person who defended me so far was someone who also criticized me, therefore I am still to be safeguarded.    And in this sense I fell very alone in my thoughts and feelings, because all of you say the same thing: ignore it; leave it, ‘caga nisso’… And some even go to the extreme of finding excuses or reasons to justify what was said.  Well, I can’t ignore it, or leave it or cagar nisso.  I wish I could but I can’t.  The thought of having to see these people and see them with a smile on my face, makes me feel physically sick.  Instead of telling me to ignore it and finding reasons for it, try to understand that I was the one who was insulted and I am the one who has to stand there with a cynical smile on my face. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Listening to: the radio at work  Mood: Happy but thoughtful    Woke up in a conflict of emotions and thoughts, but in 45mins someobody was able to calm my thoughts, make me laugh and get me thinking positively...     I'm not a perfect person There's many things I wish I didn't do But I continue learning I never meant to do those things to you And so I have to say before I go That I just want you to know  I've found a reason for me To change who I used to be A reason to start over new and the reason is you  I'm sorry that I hurt you It's something I must live with everyday And all the pain I put you through I wish that I could take it all away And be the one who catches all your tears Thats why i need you to hear  I've found a reason for me To change who I used to be A reason to start over new and the reason is You   I'm not a perfect person I never meant to do those things to you And so I have to say before I go That I just want you to know  I've found a reason for me To change who I used to be A reason to start over new and the reason is you  I've found a reason to show A side of me you didn't know A reason for all that I do And the reason is you    Hoobastank - The Reason    HASTA ;)     
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Listening to: the traffic outside Mood: tired, hurt and thoughtful    It's in the weirdest of places that I get inspired; was in the café with my colleague today and was just hit by the most powerful words.  Words that convey what I think of the world, what I believe to be true about certain people and the way I see others! And then the most overwhelming image came to my mind... so I wrote this:    I stare in awe as lightning strikes and  I see the beginnings of rain in a single crystalline droplet,  quick silver in the shadowy moonlight.  Such beauty!  Such sweet despair! What ecstasy it is to see those silver drops glimmering in the night.  Every drop a shimmering hope lost,  a dream lost to the wind. And yet rain continues to fall  every drop sparkling in the waning light.  Many hopes dashed lost to the world.  Yet on it comes, ceaselessly.  All those tears, dreams that have ceased to live,  shall my dreams be next to fall from the sky,  will my hopes be dashed, I cry. As the droplets of liquid crystal fall from the heavens all I can do is cry.  For these glimmering droplets are reflections of my sorrow.  These single droplets are all that I have.  They are beauty, life, spirit and they are all within me.  Yet those droplets are yet single, alone, as I am.  Alone in this pain filled world.  Those droplets are my only relief, my only escape from this hapless world.  I am tired of this consuming pain, this sickening sorrow.  Yet what can be done?  Just as the rain continues to fall down upon me I shall go on.  Just as the sun continues to rise, I will endure the lies.  Life has never been easy. Yet when shall this pain end?  When shall this abysmal darkness cease?      And I must be feeling inspired tonight because as I was driving home, frases and words were being played in my mind for this next piece:    When my silence is loud Lost in the roar of ocean waves It is only that I am listening  Following the tracks of echoes  That have led me to this shore  Swirling within the mist of me Are mysteries that fail to submit To the limitations of mere language Though their defiance is perplexing It is not without resolution As I redirect my focus within  With eyes closed and lips sealed My unfathomable depths  Are projected above the waves So you may see what I feel What my voice fails to convey The true colors of my dreams Splashed upon the dawn of night     But that's it for tonight folks. To be honest, I don't want to even touch upon what I'm feeling right now. I need to ignore my emotions for a while because otherwise they'll boil over and all hell will break loose.   To all of you who have shown support (you know who you are), I thank you with all my heart.       
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Listening to: Light my way - Audioslave Mood: Tired and melancholic    After a restless night and a brief but interesting morning, I find myself on here…  Yet another night spent tossing and turning, waking from dreams that made no sense, and walking around the house trying to dispel bad thoughts.  I dreamt so much and about things that were so strange: one particular dream that has remained with me was with  P  and  TP .  I guess it was because myself and  ADMV  were talking about them before going to bed, but strange nonetheless that my subconscious picked them to be included in my dreams.    I still don’t feel that I’m a-ok as  PD  would say with all that’s happened. I still feel a lot of resentment and anger towards certain people who are not worthy of being mentioned here.  The cynicism with which they are acting is beyond comprehension and is rather shocking.  Additionally, my mind’s still reeling with the news from work and the implications that it might cause.  Due to this, my sensitivity button is sky high as I realized this morning.    Anyway, I have a busy morning ahead of me.  The house needs tidying, books need organizing, lessons need preparing and I need to do my most favourite of all tasks: ironing… any offers??   
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Listening to: The reason - Hoobastank Mood: Down    I took the rest of the day off work.  I felt the need to be by myself for a while, take all the things in that have happened, and all the things that I’ve been told over the past few days.  My head feels like a concrete block filled with thoughts, anger, confusion, fear, and melancholy.  I feel  angry  because I didn’t speak about what I wanted to, I feel  frustrated  because I allowed somebody insignificant talk to me in a disrespectful manner, I feel  confused  about people’s actions, I feel  scared  because I fear that people will achieve what they seem to want…  I feel  betrayed  because I have been.  Earlier, I sat in my car and cried, not necessarily because of what people are doing but the preventable pressure they’re putting on others that do not deserve it.  Obviously, what they are doing/have done was also a factor in my sadness, but it was not the main one.  I think the main one is, quite honestly, because I’ve reached my breaking point, the point of no return as  Ice  used to say.    Every word and every action that everyone has done over these past few weeks, whether good or bad was replayed in my mind.  All that was replayed hurt; if it was good then it hurt because it wasn’t happening at that moment and if it was bad, then it was because it did happen at one point in time.  I don’t want to hurt anymore; I’ve done enough of that in my past.  Where’s the 'off' button??  HASTA 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Listening to: the radio at work Mood: Down   Sometimes things just get to me all at once, days pass where things just bounce off my shoulders, but then days like today come along, where  everything  affects me: every word, every action.   I've had enough of people getting involved in my life. I've had enough of trusting who I shouldn't. And I've had enough of being strong. Today I am not strong, today I cannot find the energy to ward off all the bad vibes or the tears. I want to go home. I want to lay down and just let everything go.  The pressure has finally got to me.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Listening to: The reason - Hoobastank Mood: Thoughtful    So, it's a fresh new blog, blank pages waiting to be filled with meaningful words or idle chatter...  Just like the old one, I guess.  However, there is one big difference with this one; as the title indicates; this is going to be in the hands of a very select few only.  After realizing that people I trust were commenting on the one thing I use as a drawing board of thoughts and feelings, I decided that I had to create something new and confidential.  It is irrelevant whether these comments were positive or negative, what is of importance is that they were made to people who do not know me and have no business knowing what I think or feel, and that  lies  were also expressed.   I believe that trust is something we all take for granted when we have it, but when it’s lost, we realize just how fragile it really is.   With the passing of each day, somebody disillusions me, whether it is in a noteworthy or slight way.  Is it that I give people too much credit or that people are so fickle that they change their attitudes according to their moods?  I know that it cannot be the first, because trust and confidence has never been easy for me to give, which leaves me wondering whether I can truly see people for what they are.    Anyway…  The same principles will apply to this blog: no names will be mentioned (new codes will be thought of as and when is necessary), feelings will be spilt upon these pages with no qualms or insecurities and trust will be placed in the four that will have the address.  Please do not let me down.    
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to: Silence Mood: Tired and insecure  Trust is a valuable thing in every relationship we have, it is also a  vunerable  thing. It sometimes takes time to build and others it can be almost instantaneous, but one thing is for sure: it only takes a minute to shatter. After all that I went through with SMR, trust is something I hold sacred and maybe that's why I'm strict on what I find acceptable and what isn't.   However, it is also something that with strength and perserverance can be "glued back together", but only if both parties are willing to fight for it. Something that was not the case with SMR.  However, this is  not  SMR or anything like that, therefore the willingness to fight to move forward is present and so is forgiveness.  I still want the same things and I still want them  yesterday , but now I wish it was last week instead of now... or maybe next month or next year... anything but now. Why? Because although it's strange to admit, all that happened just made me want those things even more, maybe because to me they represent stability and serenity or maybe because when you come close to losing something you hold onto it ever so dearly when the second time comes around. Right now what I want most in life isn't financial stability or a career or any of those materialistic statistics, I want ADMV living with me, I want to share a life with him and I want to be able to look at the   near   future and see marriage and children.  But right now, at this very moment, I would give anything to be with ADMV, anything at all.   HASTA
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to: Suffocate - Cold Mood:     When you most want life to be certain and steady, when you most feel the need to be secure, is when it's the least stable.  I want to get married and have kids, but I can’t see that happening in the near future.  I have no job security whatsoever and as for being able to save money… well, that’s a joke in itself.  ADMV’s life is also unsound at the moment, so that leaves both of us wanting what seems like an uphill struggle.  Call me pessimistic or whatever you want, but I am used to wanting something, fighting for it, getting it… patience and waiting have never, ever been my forte.  I want to share my life with ADMV, and with each passing day that want increases with a strength and a need that I cannot put into words.  It saddens me and anguishes me to not be able to have what I most want…    
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Listening to: Dream on - Aerosmith Mood: Perplexed    It sometimes confuses me how people can be so shallow! They're ability to cause confusion and hurt astounds me, but then they're ability to cover up is beyond words!  Anyway, this week has so far been a little on the stressful side what with the kids' shows and the money/work situation so this weekend I intend to grab hold of my ADMV and not let go as he's the only one who manages to keep me sane in all of this mess!   And now it's time to fly.  HASTA
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Listening to: students' complaining Mood:      So I've finally got a few minutes to spare... but as usual it's only a few.  Spoke to D today. I can't even imagine what he's going through. His child's life is on the line because of a very sick woman, namely the child's mother.  He's blaming himself, which I guess is understandable, but fruitless and unfounded. I didn't know quite what to say to him because I don't particularly believe there's any words that could be said to ease any of his suffering, so I just remained quiet and said pretty much nothing.  Additionally, I was offered a wonderful job today E1500 per month, accomodation paid for, during the summer months... in Spain. I've already turned it down, for obvious reasons. I think G was a bit upset/surprised at that, but life goes on... It's just not something I can do and that's the end of that.  Lately I've been contemplating my future and how I would like it to turn out and I've come to the conclusion that life isn't as stable as I thought it was because I can't for the life of me see what I want to happen, happening.    This is a turn for the books, someone who had life planned out to the max now without a plan... Unfortunately, I'm not OK with not having a plan. I don't like it one bit, in fact I feel very much lost and disorientated without one, however 'loose' it may be...  And now the few minutes to spare that I had are over...  HASTA  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Listening to: Alive - POD Mood: >..    Haven't got much time to write and unfortunately am in one of those moods that it would probably be best if I did write everything that went through my head.  Shit happens , I guess.  HASTA
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to: Silence Mood: Tired  I need/want holidays. Two weeks. Now.  Resting on a lovely beach (in the shade), with a Malibu and Pineapple juice, in the company of ADMV (naturally), with some decent music playing in the background.       
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Listening to: Send the pain below - Chevelle Mood: Happy, relaxed and calm    After a remarkable weekend away in the best of company, I find myself relaxed and serene.  However, money has an aptitude of being able to complicate (slightly) this mood of mine.  To say that this month is going to be short is an understatement; however, I am more than satisfied in saying that I actually have something to show for this shortage! For once, it has not been a month where it has gone to everyone else, this month I decided to treat myself: clothes, jewellery and a weekend away… Nevertheless, this was a once off as the following months I am not guaranteed work, even if I was, I really need to get my savings account back to what it once was and even better.  If I want the future to be filled with children of my own, then some sort of fund is going to have to be started because the last thing I want is to have the day-to-day stress of having a child to have the added grief of money troubles. But as somebody said to me only a few hours ago, there’s no point in thinking of what we don’t have, what’s now important is to try saving in the following months.  Regarding the weekend away, we went to Peniche and Foz do Arelho (see below), which are both fairly close by.  It was a restful and calm weekend, with laughter, conversation and love… and a really shitty football game in the middle (Portugal 1 – Greece 2)!!  It was one of those weekends that will be remembered, at least in my mind for the serenity it bought us… oh and the 2litres of sangria!!    Foz do Arelho    Baleal beach  HASTA 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to: cars passing in  the street below Mood: Content  I haven't written in a few days because I haven't felt the need to, to be honest. I don't feel the need to now, but before my inbox gets full of preocuped friends, I'll fill you in very briefly. I had another accident on Monday. No casualties, but a bit of a nightmare to say the least. Shit still is happening with ' friends '.  X  and I are fine... well actually beyond fine.  And now I'm waiting for the  LOML  to arrive so that we can go and spend an enjoyable weekend away.  HASTA  PS: D keep me informed.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Vive cada dia da tua vida como se fosse o último, pois um dia desses vai ser mesmo.    
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Listening to: silence Mood: not sure    Sorry, but yesterday was a one-off! My Portuguese is not up to being tested to the limits when expressing my feelings! (You don’t want to know how long it took me to write something so short!!) Maybe a course in written Portuguese is in order…   Anyway, a new day has started (albeit quite some time ago!) and it’s time to shrug off all the negative feelings and thoughts from the past few weeks, it’s time to look to the future with a positive outlook and embrace whatever life gives us with a smile.  Enough of paying attention to the insignificant! Enough of wasting time with the ignorant! Enough of worrying over possibilities!   Now is the time to grip what we know we have; To focus on the imperative; To take pleasure in moments taking place now; And to surrender to our emotions.   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to: some annoying guy outside Mood: feeling strong  Ok, todos nós temos os nossos dias: uns bons e outros maus, ontem foi o meu dia  mau . Shit happens... não é? Só espero é que os dias bons começam a ser mais do que os maus... mas também se não for, pelo menos tenho essas pessoas à minha volta que significam mais do que quaisquer palavras que poderia escrever aqui. Nomeadamente uma pessoa, a pessoa que me dá força para lutar, continuar, viver, sorrir, rir... Sem esta pessoa o mundo seria um lugar muito frio, vazio... negro.  Afinal isto é que é amar: sentir um dia cinzento tornar-se no dia mais brilhante apenas por ver um sorriso na cara da pessoa ou por ouvir 3 palavras (em Inglês) da boca dessa pessoa... sentir uma paz elucidante só por observar a pessoa a dormir ou por olhar nos olhos dessa pessoa e ver amor... Sentir uma força indescritível só por saber que estou com esta pessoa!  HASTA   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to: Complicated - Avril Lavigne Mood: Exhausted, sick and thoughtful  Sometimes there's a day or a night where the nightmares get too much, where tears start to flow and you can't seem to stop them.  No matter how hard you try to get in control of your emotions, you draw a blank each time.  It's only when you see that you're affecting someone you love dearly that you wipe away your tears and bottle them up to be released when you're alone so that you won't hurt or stress anyone out. And then just a few hours pass, and the nightmares get worse, they're no longer like the ones before; they're more gruesome, more chilling, more disturbing, they no longer contain the same old faces or the same scenes.   Sometimes there’s a day or a night where life gets too much, where thoughts start to gush and you can’t seem to stop them.  No matter how hard you try to stop them you think more each time.  It’s only when you’re exhausted mind switches off because it can no longer take any more, do you fall into a fitful sleep and the nightmares come to haunt you…  It’s all a vicious circle.     
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Listening to:&nbsp; Big in Japan - Guano Apes Mood: tired      "The best and most beautiful things in the world cannot be seen, nor touched... but are felt in the heart."(Helen Keller) 
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
              Listening to: Behind blue eyes - Limp Bizkit      Mood: Happy              &nbsp;   And so another weekend has passed... but like this there are few. Wonderful.&nbsp;  Palavras para quê?        
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        So it be said, So it be written. Words of wisdom through the eyes of love. From broken hearts that roam in the night. To lovers that embrace to their hearts content. Holdng on to sweet life of dreams of forever to be mine. Like roses that bloom under moon lit skies. He looks for my love,  Yet I am nowhere to be found. For my love awaits him calling like a puppy wanting attention. To feel his warmth in his cuddling arms. To know that his gentle caressive touch will comfort me. I'd be always faithful to his love. My heart starts to glow inside. For you have to give and take a little in love. To have each others arms. For where you are is where I want to be. For you are the love of my life.  
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        My eyes; like the night sky; darken as each day fades. My pain; once controlling; is replaced by the warmth of your heart. My mind was haunted by memories of what once was. Now it is consumed by the pleasure I can only find in you. Yesterday you were a distant, though sweet memory. Today you own me, body, soul and mind. We can't go back to yesterday and tomorrow may never come.  I choose to live in the moment; blanketed by our love. I cherish every moment, that together complete the puzzle of my life. I love you beyond time and space. You are my Immortal.  I'll love you today and forever more  
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Last night as your were sleeping,  And the night light gleam upon your face. I stared at you for a moment, As thoughts just filled my head. I thought to myself how my life would be. To live without you. Unbearable thoughts ran through my mind. How miserable my life would be. Not to hear your voice or feel your caress. I’d go mad within no time. For all colors would turn grey to my eyes. As the teardrops blind my view. For you’re the air that I inhale. For you’re the blood that flows within my heart. Just the thought to live without you. Makes me realize how complete life is with you. And as I kiss you goodnight and embrace you tight. For darling every day in my life. In my dreams, I see only you  
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Listening to: Suffocate - Cold  Mood: Down     Sometimes I think that the more you reflect on life, the more complicated it gets and the more sensitive you become. Or maybe it's at these times where the reality of life scares you so much that the insecurity affects your sensitivity.   I have always done what I thought was best to be happy and yet unhappiness has been my friend. I look back on the past and wonder what I have to show for my battles and my wars. Rarely do things go my way and I'm tired of living in a dreamland, believing that if I try harder or fight for longer that things will change. I'm tired of dreaming impossible dreams. But most of all I'm tired of being haunted by the memories of my past.   I've also started to hate looking around me these days and analysing who I can rely on on days such as these. The people I can turn to are becoming fewer and fewer with eahc passing day. And where is my reverie, Ice? The one person through 5 years of friendship who never let me down, disappointed me or disillusioned me? Dead and gone that's fucking where. Nearly two years has passed and the idea that I will never see him again is still new to me. I still find myself believing that he's out there in the States and that one summer (soon) he'll come back for a holiday. And on that holiday, I'll be able to tell him of all the good and bad moments that I've been through in these past two years... and he'll  listen , wipe away the tears and give a long sermon on how important it is to continue with life with the same strength and force as always. I miss him.   And today is the official start to my summer, where my work hours are a lot less and so is my salary. I feel useless. I'm not even going to be able to pay all the bills here. I'm going to have to revert back to being a teenager and ask my parents to help out. So much for working so fucking hard at university for my independence and freedom. 1 year and 9 months of independence only to go back to having to ask dad for money, and to make it all worse, ask money for a house that he shouldn't have to support. I hate that. I hate having to degrade myself in asking for help in that way. Yes, I'm proud... or I was. I was proud of what I had achieved but now I see that I achieved a big bag of  nothing .   All this makes me question as to what else I think I have achieved or that I think I have that I actually don't have. What else am I going to lose? What else is just a fantasy?   
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ... is a beautiful thing.......
    
</post>


</Blog>