<Blog>

<date>29,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Woke up with a bad headache..looks like my flu has not totally recovered. Decided to be lazy today skip tuition!!...My elder bro came back for lunch today..don't know why but just don't feel like talking to him at all..probably because I know all the things he did to my sister-in-law. Sigh unhappy stuff aside. The weather today seems good for suntanning and swimming but I guess I can just dream about it at home. With my current physical state, I think I'm having problems going shopping man..Oh boy..I missed French Fries..hahaha..funny that's how one feels when he's sick..start to crave for food which he seldoms eat when he was well :) Well, that's me..  Tomorrow's Monday again.awww.....
     

    
</post>

<date>29,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My first post...over here..was using something else previously..but oh well..never mind. Spend Saturday working and meeting my buddy for pool. He just broke off with his gf recently. Why?..I dont' know the real story and I don't really want to comment much abt it. I guess that's life. People move in and out of your life...you just got to take it.   Sigh..gotta wake up early and teach tomorrow...I'm pretty tired man..having a flu..yet got to teach.. I don't even feel like opening my mouth to eat.....let say teach.  
     

    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Got home slightly earlier today. And when I looked into a mirror...I suddenly realised that my skin is getting from bad to worst.eeeks..so oily..and open pores..it used to be better..sigh..too stressed up and never take good care of my skin. :(. Hey I was very onz in taking care of my skin last time man..every week, I will spread my favourite Glacial Marine Mud from Nu skin on my face and leave it on for half an hour..hmm..the feeling after washing off the mask..is SHIOK man..haha..sorry..been a Nu Skin freak for the pat three years. I'm not trying to sell..but I guess their products work best for me.  So what happen..well dashed to the bathroom started to shower and here i am..sitting right in front of the computer updating my blog at the same time waiting for the mask to dry. I think its quite therapatic..hopefully my skin will be better off in a few weeks time if I do it consistently like last time :X.  Seems to be falling sick soon..my throat kind of hurts hhaha..but never mind sick sick lah..been so busy that I can't even sleep well man.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow..so fast..Saturday's almost gone before I know it...had classes today..but don't know why I kept dozing off maybe it was due to the fact that I slept late last night and woke up really early to teach..at 7am..yawnz..tomorrow I've got classes again!!..Argh..9am man!!!! Grrrr....  Today I received an sms from a very very long time irc friend..or should I say friend..haha..I got to know him from IRC long long long time ago..that was during the dial up days..haha..but we hit it off..and become good friends..that's why i don't really brand him as a IRC friend..haha..anyway..it was a pleasant surprise to receive his sms..because we have lost contact for a long time....and coincidentally he came into my mind a few days back when I took the train home and pass by Redhill which is somewhere near where he stay. Haha..its really nice to talk to him. He said he miss me?? Make me almost fell down from the chair man..ahha..  Anyway today's really fast, to me weekend is really tooo short. I'm sure it applies to alot of my friends as well..arghh..I betta sleep early man :p
     

    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WA...I watched American Idol on the bus through TV Mobile today...and heard the contestant sang "Amazed"..hmm..very nice..hahahahahha...  But sigh..everytime after taking the bus home on Tuesday and Thursday after classes...I always get motion sickeness..hahahaha  Anyway..I'm goin to watch "The Eye" VCD..hope its not too scary for me to go to work tomorrow night..everybody been telling me its nice..should watch it if I'm goin to watch Eye 2..haha..  Tomorrow's Friday..yea..I know in my previous post I said I will be determined enough to go for Yoga classes every week..but..sigh..can't man..my work is really piling up..so high man....  hahaha...
     

    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      haha..so fast tomorrow's Thursday already..been a great day. My elder brother just smsed me that he has paid for my contact lenses already..hmm..feel kind of bad and touched at the same time..hmm probably get him something else soon.  Been really busy at work..so busy that I don't even have the time to feel sleepy lolxx...Files piling up etc..I've set my mind in starting my revision this weekend yea..must be focused..must be focused. I want to pass my exams..not only pass..but I must try to work hard enough to score!!!..FOCUS FOCUS....  haha..due to the heavy schedule..I've decided not to go to the gym twice a week till end April...but will definitely go for at least once a week..haha..for yoga..yea..I'm hooked on it..cos its really fun :P  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lousy morning..wonderful evening...  I started Monday feeling sleepy, angry and upset..horrible Monday...so sleepy.couldn't concentrate on my work at all..  My elder brother lost his glasses at the swimming pool yesterday. He called me to see if I have lobang to make cheap glasses. I was glad that he called me. I arranged to meet him after work and bring him to this optical shop which alot of my friends swear that its CHEAP AND GOOD..haha  To my surprise, my brother reached my office at 530 sharp..wow..something different. Before 530, I was actually panicking in the office, because things has not been good between us. I got so nervous that my hands actually went cold..I even told my SD that I don't know that to say or how to behave if I see my brother because its been sooo long since we last seen each other and talk to each other. Phew..luckily..things went well..at the optical shop he volunteer to pay for my contact lenses which I of course rejected. I know he has his own financial problems so I have to pay for my own. In fact, I'm thinking of paying for his glasses too :)  Sigh..suddenly at that point of time, I do miss the days where my elder brother and I are really close....well but at least things are good for now and I know how to appreciate it already :P
     

    
</post>

<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Blogging from the office at this time of the day this time of the week. ARghh..been extremely busy man..haven't got the time to revise..at all..NOt really stressed up but can feel it coming..haha..anyway...I think someone just farted..but DEFINITELY not me..cos i'm not alone in the office..haha..i'm not going to mention names either..but stink..haha..human nature..:p  A few friends around me have been bugged by relationship problems recently..which makes me think over and over again. Is there a thing call everlasting love? Wat is meant by everlasting love? A relationship which eventually leads to marriage? or A short relationship which last for less than a year..but that year was the happiest times that you ever have. But come again, if that year was the happiest period of time? How come the relationship didn't last? Seriously speaking, I have never dared to tell people around me abt everlasting relationships because there's no such thing as finding THE ONE. I think I will only know it when I'm old and feeble yet this guy can still hold my hand and walk around the streets. That's probably when I know that I've found the right one.   So what can I conclude? Marriage's a gamble? Something which you won't know whether you lost or win until old? We never know what a new relationship or a ending of a relationship might bring us...good or bad we never know. But the most important thing is to move on wif life. Gals wont' die without man..and man won't die without gals either..at this time in this day, everyone is independent. There's no longer such thing as guys must work hard so that next time can support the family, and there's no such things like as a woman you must follow what the man says. Times has changed..probably it has also changed our persepective on relationship...such changes have shaped the society and improve the economy but it has also changed the way people regard relationships..  Sigh...
     

    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yawnz..just got home from work...Tiring man..will be really busy for the next one or two mths before my exams starts..haha..  Whole body been aching since Monday's gym session..but I'm kind of looking forward to the Friday session where i may be goin for yoga classes.  Tomorrow's Thursday.....nothing much but got class..haha.means no OT for me..phew..    
     

    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yoz..back from gym...awwww..tired man..body combat..can kill me. Hahaha..probably lack of really good exercise these few mths. But it certainly freshen me up abit. Can't wait to start other classes.hahaha..  Decided to go to the gym at Republic Plaza today. Simply no way for me to go to the one at Orchard cos Joel is working there. Kind of awkward when I see him. Don't know to say hi or not. He probably can't recognize me and seriously speaking I don't want to have anything to do with him at all.  Yawnz..tired leh..I think I want to sleep liao..
     

    
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lazy Sunday...  Yawnz...got back at 4am this morning from Shaun's place. Both Jeff and Shaun walked me back. So nice of them ya.Thanks..  Slept till 1pm this afternoon..woke up in a daze..tryin to decide which day of the week today is. After washing up and lunch, I thought i will be awake enough to watch super sunday!!...but....I doze off again...when I woke up..I saw Li Nanxing on TV...then I ask my younger bro.."wow..Li Nanxing now so popular lah..go all the way to Taiwan liao"..hahahahahahahhaaha   Well, really nothing much to write already. This weekend's really fast. I have not done any revision at all!!  Argh..  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yawnz..bloggin now from Shaun's computer. Both Shaun and Jeff are crazy over the xbox...I played some but only end up having them laughing at me...hahaha  We had KFC for dinner..hmmm..yummy. I made a chicken burger myself:  one sweet bun one piece of nugget one spoonful of coleslaw one teaspoon of whipped potato  Stuff the nugget sloeslaw and whipped potato into the sweet bun..wala...chicken burger..hahahahahahha  Very sleepy..now..practically closing my eyes while typing...but then..its only once in a while that the three of us get to gather together like that..so hahaha...
     

    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today's SATURDAY..guess what..I'm in the office!!..Haha..nope..you are wrong..I'm not even stressed up about it~~..I'm right now sitting in the office without managers staring at me that's why I'm updated my blog NOW!  Wow..busy morning for me...woke up at 9am because got to rush to Tiong Bahru to meet my SD for breakfast before going to Tanjong Pagar for some survey participation. Good money earned today because they paid me 15 bucks to drink some beverages and tell them whether its yummy or not. The whole process took me less than half an hour@!!..Good money heh...$$  After the survey, I went to AMK..because my naive brother bought a mobile phone from this mobile shop there and he kind of got cheated. The guy withheld the original nokia battery and gave him some compatible ones claiming that the compatible ones were better. Bullshit man, they probably take the original one and sell it to other ppl and make some money out of it. The phone came without a warrranty card somemore~ When I went down, the shop was a big one but then alot of young man with long bleached hair and tattooed arms..kind of scary though but hey..I'm not goody two shoes all the time. Luckily, they replaced the batteries with the original ones and gave me the warranty card if not..I'm gonna complain to CASE..after AMK yea..I"m back in the office at Bugis. It seems like I've done alot of travelling today~~  Later, I will be goin to Shaun's place for some potluck party. Not really a big party, but only Shaun, Jeff and their secondary school friends and myself. Kind of weird going because I don't even know their friends. My main worry is being feel left out. After all, I'm not someone who can really "click" on with people that fast. But hell ya, I've promised them to go. So I better go~  Okie..that's all for now. Will try to update soon  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Horrible day..I couldn't sleep the whole of last nite...only got to sleep around 4 am and woke up at 645am to get to work. When I reach the office, I was so sleepy. Couldn't even hold a mug properly. And now, I'm having a very bad tummyache because I guess I drank too much tea in the afternoon in order to keep myself awake.  Was hyper during class today. This gal sitting infront of me was so selfish. She didn't want to switch her phone to silent mode and then it keep on rang during the lessons. Almost kick her arse man.  Tomorrow's Friday..wow..every week seems to pass so fast. I just got my membership card from California today. Wahaahhaa..will definitely check that place out tomorrow after work!!  Watched American Idol on the bus just now. The bus journey took me 1 hour man..Don't know why but I feel sick after taking the bus. Almost all the time. With alot of air in my tummy..keep on burp and burp and burp..sigh..motion sickness I suppose..haaha..puke when I got home Arghh... :(  Okie...I must really try to get some sleep..if not..I think its pretty terrible liao :P
     

    
</post>

<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Much better today..I'm alright after one or two days. Don't know whether is it because I'm strong or I just choose to ignore it.  Started tuition again. Ya I know I'm tired of tutoring, but then it really pays well and just nice at this point of time I think money's the most impt thing right now. Not too bad, my student has become more sensible..been teaching him and his sister for 3 years already. So, not too bad lah. I think i must be quite a good tutor that's why can continue for so long..hahahahaa  Tomorrow's a brand new day, Thursday..got classes..don't know to feel happy or bored. IS is a very dry subject but sometimes drawing all the data flow diagram seems to be quite interesting.....  Okie..should be all lah..got to go..American Idols time!!
     

    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Geez..today's Monday. Feeling very freshed at work this morning. :) Just got home from work and look at the time..its almost 12am!!!! I think its high time that I make an effort to do abit of revision at least 1 hour a day. Though exams are in June, I've got friends asking me out to do revision from this coming Saturday onwards!! KS hor..haha..  Recently, I'm hooked on eating food like sunflower seeds and Granola (its not hamster food okie!!)..just hooked on it and I believed its too dry which explains why my flu is still bad..coughing, blocked nose etc. I'm so desperate to get well, that I drink lots and lots of water as much at 4 litres a day which excludes, the Vitamin C drink that I have. Yaya..laugh at me for being a water tank or whatever, but I guess its still good for me right.   My best friend W,called me just now about the California gym issue. She told me that she will passed me her membership for the time being so that I can go because she's starting her yoga classes at some community centres soon so her membership will go waste. So I will be going to California gym very soon..excited yeah :p. And three mths later, she will use my name to register for another membership and from there we will exchange..geez..quite smart of her yea. But I'm pretty alright with it as long as I pay the same amt for joining.  Okie got to go..really got to sleep already. I feel better when I get enough sleep..haha..who doesn't right??
     

    
</post>

<date>07,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wOWOWW........new colours finally!!...haha..special thanks to one friend who introduced me wat colours to use..hahaha..bus is the background too striking..I find it abit too striking..initially..haha..if its painful for the eyes let me know ya.  Busy Saturday...went to my daddy's stall to help...business was abit poor..though it was a Saturday. I think times are really bad and alot of people are trying to cut back on expenses, including myself. I've been really cutting back because there are soo many things to pay for like exam fees, course fees. These two are burning a big hole in my pocket manz.   tomorrow's sunday, got to teach again. Wow it was like only last week that I've caught a flu..but sigh..I have not fully recovered yet. Can't help but feeling tired the whole day with runny nose and bad throat. Sigh, its been a long time that I've been sick for so long :(.   Sigh my J is having fun at S's place again. How I wish I can join them but I can't because I've made up my mind to do some revision tonight. Exams are in June. Ya..laugh at me for being KS..but then, I'm so busy with work the only thing that I can do to ensure myself is to do regular revision. No more last min like I use to do when I was in polytechnic. Last min works for me then because i didn't had to work but now..sigh..if one day I have all the money in the world, I will do nothing except studying and studying and studying. I love EXAMS!!..lolxx  
     

    
</post>

<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      HAHA..another look ya...blue and red first..will slowly change abit here and there..hopefully its nt too painful for the eyes :)  Went out wif my colleagues after work today. Went KTV..wowo.s.ang to my hearts content. But because I went out tonight..that means tomorrow chances of me going back to the office to work is EXTREMELY HIGH...its peak period now..extremely busy also..half the time my tables are covered with file.  Soon soon..i will be puting up pictures lah..slowly okie..till then..  Wonderful weekend ahead!!
     

    
</post>

<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh man..i'm so freaking sleepy...finally managed to change the colour of my headings..i'm trying to create a retro theme..but seems to have lost all my colour senses after losing touch for almost 5 years. :(..but never mind, will soon learn how to do it.  I missed American Idols today..yea I'm crazy over this show. I took the bus without any TV mobile..and it was packed!! Very packed..felt breathless..and started to feel irritated..haha..  Didn't get to go California gym today because there were some delay in paper work..awww..can't wait to start!! Haha..Anyway..any suggestions for colours? Lolxx..  Tomorrow's Friday!!!!!..End of the week..nothing much except that my mother will be going to Malaysia to attend a wedding dinner. I'm not going because not much common topic to chat with my cousins from Malaysia. Frequency different lah okie..not because I'm proud or something.  Can't wait for weekend to come..I'm suddenly very enthusiatic about revising for my exams!!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Feeling much better today...  Got home from work much much earlier than usual. Its been almost a week..but my flu's no where better..so decided to come home earlier to rest and take medicine..so that I can get knocked out earlier. :)  Went to the supermarket do shop for a while. Been a long time since I went to Jurong Point even though its only like 15 mins walk from my place. Its always closed by the time i go home..heehee. Went to Liberty..bought my favourite fruits..make a guess what issit?..haha APPLES and DRAGONFRUIT..bought some muselis and a packet of milk too. Don't know how come just suddenly feel very motivated to take good care of my health by eating correctly..haha..hopefully it last.  Tomorrow's da day!!..I'm meeting my friend to go down to California Gym...to sign up. Yeah..can get to exercise regularly...can't wait to start classes like yoga..aerobics etc..:)  Okie..got to go..its American Idol time~~~~~ 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wonderful Monday....the day passed smoothly without much hiccups at work. I'm feeling much better after a long weekend except for the blocked ears and runny,blocked nose...haha..  had a brief chat wif "Y".....(yea "j" if you are reading this you probably hate me man..but i'm just being neutral..I think me being friends with "y" should not have a effect on our friendship since you and her are no longer together.) Anyway, I was pretty pissed off initially with Y for cheating on my friend. But after a while, I think which human doesn't make a mistake in life. Ya..its easy for me to try to get one to forgive the mistakes made by another one. Probably if it happens to me, I may not be that forgiving already. So for this, I'm not going to get J to forgive Y. All I can do is ask J to be fair to Y by reading her emails and reply if possible. If can't reply, then never mind. Y please understand afterall I'm closer to J and I can understand how hurt and angry J is.  What moved me was the way Y told me how sorry she was and how determined she is to changed. I told her the most impt thing is to change for herself and her family but not for anyone. Because in years to come if she realise that the one that she is changing for does not appreciate her effort..she will definitely have hatred..for him. Just like me. You know something, Y you do remind me of myself during my younger days..okie not that I'm very old..but years ago I was like you..fickle minded..not sure what I wanted.. and in turn I've hurt someone....and tell you the truth..I changed becausse of him..but after a few years..I realised that he didnt quite appreciate it at all..so now what..I hate that guy..but I think now..I'm already neutral abt it. Not much hatred..but just kind of sad to lose someone this way. So Y please..change for yourself..not others. If you determined..you will be able to do it.   As for J, you have been one of the few good friends who have stayed by my side for the past few years braving through winds and storms (wa..drama..) and of course not forgetting S..you were there for me too. I would say you two are one of the few friends which I want to keep for life. The trip from City Hall to Jurong East Mrt and from there back to the bustop to wait for bus 198 was hilarious. Hahaha..yea..I think you are right J accountants are crazy. Hahahaa....I hope you won't really mind me being friends with Y..:) and I do look forward to a few more good years of craziness..hahahahahahhaa  Seeing what happen between this two friends, somehow it really affected me very much. It suddenly brings me back to think..how easy it is for two to get together..not only as bfs or gfs..but also as friends..and how easy it is for one to spoil the relationship/friendship. It did dwell on me..that sometimes you must not take friends or ppl around you for granted...cos you never know..every little action that you do may just hurt them deeply.....it may be easy for them to forgive you for your action..but the truth is its difficult to forget.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Aiyoh..finally..I got to linked Audrey's blog to mine..and put up a chatterbox and some puzzle for the day for ppl who will be visiting my blog. HOpefully, I get to learn more stuff as the days go..I'm trying to use this opportunity to learn more abt html..but manz..its so confuzingggg ^_^...haha..But I've made Shaun (my best IT geek friend) promise to teach me more and more the next time I pop by his place.   Meanwhile do bear wif me ya..if this page seems abit dull..hahah 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Grrr..nobody wants to go to the big walk with me!!!!!!!...I was so glad that the Big Walk was not cancelled because of the terrible accident that happened at Nicoll Highway..but right now..seems like my friends in my miserable social circle are all not keen..grrrrr...anyone of you reading this keen? Do please let me know..we can go together!!!!!  Like my previous post, I mention that I was meeting for Candice for revision..yea did some..but not much..met Tommy at 7....that idoit..made me travel from Bugis train station to Paya Lebar..beause he doesn't know how to drive from his place to Bugis..haha..*pengz* but oh well he's been kind enough lah..drive me to the Macdonalds at King Albert Park where we did our revision there till almost 1am..by 1230, my eyelids were already heavy..droping....like right now..hahaha..but then just got the bear wif it ..but that Tommy still remains hyper as ever..argghh..wonder where he gets his energy from...finally 1am came..I was quite worried that I have to take a cab home..heng ar...he offer to drive me home before going back to Tampines...phew..we even arranged to meet up next week to study again..I told him I don't mind ttravelling if its in the day time..and that guy..actually mention CHANGI AIRPORT.....and ask if its alright if we study till late...i really went.................*lost for words*  Reaney send me a funny sms today..sound kind of crude..but I Dont care...I'm going to post it here:   Worker: Boss today me sick cannot work... Boss:    Everytime when I'm sick I will have sex with my wife..you should try it to..it works  2 hours later.......  Worker: Boss you were right..I'm alright already can start work anytime..You have a nice house leh...  How dumb can ppl get I wonder. Lame jokes..but then it did managed to wake me up while I was tutoring..hahah 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow..busy week..yea I have not been blogging for almost a week. I started the week feeling happy because it seems like I've lost 1/2 kg.hahahhaah..but then..sigh..it was my boss birthday on thursday..and all the good food seems to came in at one go!!! All the sinful stuff..hahaha  Anyway..though peak period is officially over..I'm still busy with alot of other work. Office been really messy these few days with alot of moving around. Yea some major restructuring going on recently. What can I say? Hmm..I'm sure that this restructure would be of great benefits to me and my future. So I don't mind getting my hands dirty for the moment and move stuff around.  Yea..suddenly one of the major accidents in Singapore suddenly came to my mind. The collapse of Nicoll Highway..oh no.."my" highwway..haha..okie serious I know I should not be laughing over such accidents. The area is pretty near my office. On Tuesday afternoon just before 4pm, sirens from the ambulance and SCDF vehicles could be heard from my office. The thought of it now really send shivers to my body. Its really scary. Initially we thought that some accident had happen..but never did we realised that it was a collapsed. It really scary. Even right now I really dont' know what to say except the word SCARY. I have been too busy to keep myself updated with the news...but I hope things will be alright soon.   Those who know me well will know that I'm a BIG WALK fanatic..but with such tragic event, I suppose the Big Walk may be postponed..sigh..  okie got to go...will meet my friend to study tomorrow. Take care everyone!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The weather have been terrible for the past few days..even with my short hair now..its still warm. Can you imagine this..me waking up at 5am because its too warm for me to sleep..ARRRGgghHHH...  well well..horrible saturday..no dates no activities etc..it was really terrible!! I was bored to tears at home. Was supposed to meet Candice to go back to school and do some revision...but she knocked off from work too late while I finished tutoring too late. So we decided to call it off instead. So in the end I ended up slacking at home the occasionaly scribbling of notes and the frequent visits to my comfy bed. Argh..very very unproductive.   Been dying to go to Jurong Point, but couldn't find someone to go with me..until I saw Audrey online..but by then it was almost 9..go jurong point..hahaha..watch the sercurity guards close shop huh..hahaha  Today I've got classes..yea Sunday classes from 10 am *yawnzzz* to 1pm..then I will REALLY REALLY stay in school to study today.  Yoga is really fun fun fun...went for yoga with my colleague on friday. After that I met Dylan and Shuan to talk. Dylan's a good financial planner, I was glad that he was not too aggressive to force me to buy any stuff. Seriously speaking, right now..I'm more keen in letting my CPF grow. After the discussion, we went to play pool though actually I was feeling more like singing..but three persons how to sing??? So I decided to go along with playing pool rather than bowling which the two man wants anyway. We played till 2am and then went home..so tired..now body is still aching from all the stretching and twisting..hahaha..I think i'm not very flexible can't really twist and turn and balance well..got to work on that..  okie..got to go...for classes..hahahahahah    
     

    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      YES.....finally I've plucked up enough courage to snip away my long hair..now my hair is SHORT...not as short as a boy boy lah...but shorter than long..oh no...what am I talking about. Well though I kind of regretted cutting away the hair..but then..i feel good..haha  Been very very stressed and busy recently. That's why didn't update...haha.got to go..!!!!   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh man..after a fun evening out..I'm still depressed...On my way back on the bus..I started to think and think about life..and got depressed again. I don't know why. I looked at my mobile and for a moment I wonder..how come it's not ringing.I've been waiting for it to ring for the longest time...but everytime I check..its always not ringing...arghh..dont know why I'm feeling this way..suddenly feel that I actually don't have much close friends. Alot of them are those Hi Bye friends..how many of them will actually realised that a friend is gone before they know it..  Couldnt' slept last night..and talk to Alex on the phone..for a while..funny chap..but then it didn't make me feel better either..I kept on waking up every three hours after that...  went to teach...i'm stressed..want to exercise..but I"m not free to do it..haha..got to revise and revise...argh..  WHAT TO DO..THAT'S LIFE!
     

    
</post>

<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Saturday...  Woke up feeling depressed. Yesterday was a public holiday yet I was slogging away in office..wat to do..deadlines to meet..haha  Was alone in the office from 2 to 10++1...but then went out for dim sum in between..hahahah..from 9-11 I was alone..sounds kind of scary especially when my colleagues told me that there are always noises..even when the office is very empty. Eeeee..so scary..I really heard voices man..Anyway..when I got home it was already 12...bathe..and sleep..but dont know why I feel depressed this morning..hahahah  just had lunch..sinful lunch of fried bee hoon..yummy. I loved Bee Hoon..after this I'm goin to change ang prepare to go FTC to do revision. Its far..veyr far from my place to Orchard. But then I don't care anymore as long as I get revision done. I'm gettting DESPERATE for time..after that will meet my poly mates for dinner at 5pm. I miss them tonnes~!!..okie got to go..will update again soon!!!!   
     

    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wah piangz..breakout recently..like its really FOC..so many pimples on my face..oh no..wat happen@?@?@??@@?@
     

    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Superb SuNdAy!!!...After tutoring today, I went home for lunch and don't know what happen my engine just started and I managed to get some revision done!! Yeah..though not much..but definitely better than nothing..Went to my dad's stall to help..well business was alright..then luckily my brother went down that's why I quickly cycled back home..  Went to work yesterday...spent almost the whole day working..sigh..that's life right..but I took a break to go Carrefour to visit my cousin who was working there. Hmmm..he spoilt me when I was a child man...constant shopping trips and macdonalds trips..ahaha....I would say I was his favourite?..haha..opps my cousin is very old already..almost 20 years older than me :P..suddenly when i went to look for him I felt so grown up..haha..can go shopping with him...the feeling hmm..just weird lah..ha  I'm so looking forward to the coming week..because long weekend!!!....I'm applying leave of Thursday to visit my granny's grave..sigh. Tears never fail to flow when I visit the grave every year. Times seems to pass so fast.. its been 6 years already..since she passed away..but I still missed her. Sometimes I wonder..how would it be like if she's still around. I mean she passed away before my brothers and I started working. We couldn't provide her anything good except for the occasional treats..hmm..think my family will be very complete with her around now...
     

    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wowow..been so many days since I last updated my journal. Well well..I'm extremely busy..can feel the stress already..haha...but its still manageable.   Wanted to update last night but was soo tired that I jump right into bed instead :) Decided to blog now before I rush to work because I know..tonight I will be very tired again.  Awww..feel fat these few days....very fat..I must really really cut back on my fats man..haha.but its tough when my father cook food for me to bring to the office everyday to eat.all the char kway teow..fried rice..etc..yummy yummy..haha..in an attempt to save money by bringing food to work...i piled up on my fats again..haha..really got to hit the gym after 15 April!!!!! If not..sigh......  Today's Thursday already..got classes..aww..my contact lenses are still not ready yet. I hope it will be ready by this weekend..Willaim says he will go and collect it for me if its ready.phew..luckily man..if not I may have to makde a tripe down just to collect the contact lenses.  Okie...748am..oh gosh..i betta rush..byeeeeee
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hah...another week gone...finally I'M ON LEAVE OFFICIALLY...finally got time to revise for my exams..so stressed up.a.rghh......haha..right now I'm in the office..studying..haha some of you might be thinking..kaoz..nik must be crazee..always go back office..even on leave also want to go back..but hey..you should check out my office if there is a chance..its a very cosy place..especially the place where I sit...so I don't mind coming back to study..since there's air con here..the weather is sooo freaking warm..its really difficult to study anywhere else...  just had a chicken feet feast with PP...my colleague..haha..we both share the same passion for potato, bright colours and CHICKEN FEET..hahahaha..went to crystal jade for the feast..it was...ABSOULTELY YUMMYYYYYYY...so then its studying time now..but getting restless so update my blog.  I'm goin to meet a few friends later, going to meet them to attend this open house at BPP another school offering ACCA courses..its giving away $100 voucher to those who attend today's open session..hey its attractive ACCA courses are really expensive..especially the exam fees..all in pounds man..can make me go broke for a few mths at least. Haha  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    mini coopers&nbsp; urlLink      haha..blogger got a new look and some new features..i like it..cos its now very much easier for me to post pictures...i'm still learning..but I kind of given up hope on HTML so decided to change the background to pink..don't know why probably been influenced by alot of my friends around me..now I kind of appreciate pink colours too..hahah.. 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Phew..another week gone..today..I didn't met up with Tommy to study..that lazy bum..don't want to study in the day time only want to study at night..so I met Candice instead..at Bras Brasah to study before meeting SK to go to Xiaohui's 21st birthday. Met a few old classmates there and glad to say that everyone is doing pretty well. Geezz.good thing right..  After the birthday party, SK and I drove down to Circuit Road to meet another friend Celes..well Celes been feeling down recently so we went to meet her up to talk. After driving around and around, we ended up at Changi Village for drinks..ha..and finally..i'm home now.. 3am bloggin in front of the computer..  been very busy, this week..and probably for the next few weeks until my exams are over. Sigh..its exam fever....high fever I would say..haha..nothing in my brain..except examss...examsss..and EXAMS..in fact SK just mentioned that he has never seen me so hardworking before..haha..probably last time things were different in poly. I find the school work in poly very much easier..but not now...haha..okie i'm sleepy already..still got to teach tuition in the morning tomorrow morning..betta go sleep..good nites...  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow..busy week..yea right now  I've changed my seats in office already. I no longer faced cartons of documents..finally someone's sitting opposite me..though now I'm seated far far far away from my SD..I'm pretty happy sitting opposite HS..  nothing much happen this week except the shifting of seats..in office which left me really tired very tired..oh ya..went to David's saloon to get my hair colour done..was no a fantastic job..but then oh well its FOC so no complains abt it ya :P  Yea went to KAP to study with Tommy again on Saturday. But then the weather was freaking hot and that Tommy insist on sitting outside..I almost melted there man!!! ARgh..I don't care anymore man next week must study indoors..hhaha
     

    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Been listening to this song a few times today..like the tune..very much..rock rock one..hahahah   "This Love"  I was so high I did not recognize The fire burning in her eyes The chaos that controlled my mind Whispered goodbye and she got on a plane Never to return again But always in my heart  This love has taken its toll on me She said Goodbye too many times before And her heart is breaking in front of me I have no choice cause I won't say goodbye anymore  I tried my best to feed her appetite Keep her coming every night So hard to keep her satisfied Kept playing love like it was just a game Pretending to feel the same Then turn around and leave again  This love has taken its toll on me She said Goodbye too many times before And her heart is breaking in front of me I have no choice cause I won't say goodbye anymore  I'll fix these broken things Repair your broken wings And make sure everything's alright My pressure on your hips Sinking my fingertips Into every inch of you Cause I know that's what you want me to do  This love has taken its toll on me She said Goodbye too many times before And her heart is breaking in front of me I have no choice cause I won't say goodbye anymore  This love has taken its toll on me She said Goodbye too many times before And her heart is breaking in front of me She said Goodbye too many times before  This love has taken its toll on me She said Goodbye too many times before And her heart is breaking in front of me I have no choice cause I won't say goodbye anymore
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow..for those who saw me on MSN today might wonder why..how come 1/2 De@d and 1/2 alive..don't worry I'm not depressed or something. I feel perfectly alright infact happy.  After 7 long years, I've met up wif all my old time IRC friends:  Cat Cat Luna Val Hansel Manx and Roy  The outing was wonderful, we went for dinner, coffee and ended the night with a drinking session at this very cool place which Val recommended. Ya had a drop too much seriously high when I got home. But after the shower, I just couldn't sleep anymore till this morning. So to be exact, I've not been sleeping since I woke up yesterday morning at 7am. Hahahaha..I'm still hyper...grrrr..  Everybody seems to be doing very well, Cat got married, Luna is doing nothing lookin for a job, Val is working for some magazine, Hansel is studying at SMU, Manx is doing well in his business too...and Roy, going to Australia this weekend.  Basically these two weeks so many friends coming in and out of Singapore..so busy man....alot of gatherings alot of dinners..alot of meeting up..etc etc..so fun..  Well soon soon, August is coming and Bee Leng is coming back!!! I always feel very happy when she's back..dont know why also..hahaha..but I'm beginning to count down the days already.....
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow....lazy Saturday. Didn't blogged for a day. Got home late on Friday and by the time I got home was too tired to blog.   Went for HOT POT at Suntec City wif my colleagues. The hot pot was really spicy. I was abit disappointed though because there wasn't any crab sticks :( I love crab sticks. But all my colleagues felt that I was quite dumb to eat crab sticks at a buffet. Hahaa..yea lah they are qutie right but I love it just couldn't help it.   Besides spicy, the hot pot was very hot and I can't seem to decide what to cook and what to eat. But alot of good food. The prawns were fresh very fresh. AFter the hot pot, I went to carrefour wif a collague to get some stuff before getting a lift from her back.  This morning I woke up and went to work. Nothing much special happened since its just like any normal working day. After work, I went to my daddy's stall to help. Good girl right..hahahaha  Found alot of old friends back recently especially those who I irc wif long long time ago. Those were the days where comic chat was still popular. Yea 7 years ago. That time I was the baby of the chatroom with friends who were way older than me. So happy to have found them back. We are going to meet soon but I just can't remember the date!!! Because I've got alot of outings recently so many ppl to meet!!!!!  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh sucks...I woke up late today!!! When I open my eyes it was 8am!!!...I don't know where I found the courage to take my time and took a train instead of taking a cab hahahaha..getting from bad to worst..haha  well well..nothing much happened on Monday except work work and more work. OT..as usual and took the train back home. Boring right but hey I guess its working life which everybody goes through but I'm looking forward to the later part of the week where there will be more activities.  Went to the gym today..finally managed to do some work out. The feeling was SHIOK!! I like to exercise but sigh..spirit is weak. But never mind I'm trying to work on that right now.   Nothing much to blog abt actually, I just want to make a habit to try blogging everyday before I sleep that's all. If not also nothing to do right.  Oh man..I dont know what I'm talking abt at all..betta stop here...
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lazy sunday...found my former student grace on friendster..haha..so happy :p wa..her blog looks good you guys can check out her blog :)  Did nothing much except some reading..finished a book called Kezzie by Theresa Breslin today..nothing special abt the book its abt a sister's love that's all. A good book for me to start reading especially since its been soooo long I've read other books besides my textbooks. Now starting on another book called Ex-appeal.  I looked into the mirror today..and gosh! It suddenly dawned on me that I do look better with long hair oh man, I should have heed my mummy's advice nt to snip my long hair away. I look ABSOLUTELY auntie leh with short hair..haha..well, the main reason I snipped off my hair was I was tired of having rebonded hair every year got to go and do rebonding, I just want natural long hair, so I just hope my short hair will grow faster.   Very warm, feel very fat today, I will wake up early tomorrow to go to the gym I guess.  I'm planning to meet Margaret and Willynn soon, we haven' met up wif each other for the longest time especially Margaret, I havent seen her since she went to the States as for Willynn haha..she's in Singapore, I see her often. But I guess she has not seen Margaret for a long time too.   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          How to make a Nikko        Ingredients:   5 parts intelligence  1 part ambition  5 parts joy        Method:  Combine in a tall glass half filled with crushed ice. Add a little sadness if desired!        Username:       urlLink Personality cocktail  From  urlLink Go-Quiz.com     wahahahahahah.....5 parts of intelligence!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!.......got this from Yolanda's webby..its fun..thanks gal..
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      These few days had been terrible, especially today. I woke up alot of time last night because my eyes itch. This morning when I woke up my eye was really really swollen, red and painful. IT was really bad that I had to scream for my mother. I then started crying. For that moment I was really afraid that the worst feared situation is here..retinal detachment. But I guess not becuase I could still see clearly but still I was really scared so decided to take a day off and went to see my doctor. Doctor say its just some irritation Phew...yea laugh at me for being paranoid but you can't blame me for thinking this way.  After what my eye doctors told me recently I've been trying to surf the web to see what's retinal detachment. And its as follows..I've decided to put it here for ppl to see so as to spread the word around because I think it happens to anyone who has high myphoia and not only me.   Retinal Detachment      Normal Vision   The retina is the nerve cell layer of the eye and acts much like film in a camera. When light enters the eye, it passes through the cornea and lens and is focused onto the retina. The retina transforms the light energy into vision and sends the information back to the brain through the optic nerve. The macula is the sensitive, central part of the retina and provides for sharp, detailed vision.      Retinal Detachment   In retinal detachment, the retina separates from the outer layers of the eye thus losing its function. If not treated early, retinal detachment may lead to impairment or complete loss of vision.    Cause   Most retinal detachments are preceded by one or more tears or holes in the retina. Fluid passes through these openings and separates the retina from the adjacent layers of the eye.   Near-sighted individuals are more commonly affected due to thinning of the retina. Holes or tears can then develop in the thinned retina.   The vitreous (gel fluid in the eye) also plays a significant role by causing tugging on the retina especially when shrinkage occurs. Cataract surgery can also be a precipitating cause. A positive family history of retinal detachment is another risk factor.   A combination of factors is usually responsible for retinal detachment. Retinal detachments can also be caused by other diseases in the eye such as tumours, severe inflammations, or complications of diabetes.    Symptoms   Middle-aged and older persons may see floating black spots called floaters and flashes of light. In most cases, these symptoms do not indicate serious problems. In some eyes, the sudden appearance of spots or flashes of light may herald the onset of retinal detachment. A thorough examination of the retina by an ophthalmologist after dilatation of the pupil is necessary to determine the cause of the symptoms.   Some retinal detachments can proceed unnoticed until a large section of the retina is detached. In these instances, patients may notice the appearance of a dark shadow in some parts of their vision. Further development of the retinal detachment will blur central vision and create significant sight loss in the affected eye.   A few detachments may occur suddenly and the patient will experience a total loss of vision in one eye. Similar rapid loss of vision may also be caused by bleeding into the vitreous which may happen when the retina is torn.    Treatment   If the retina is torn but detachment has not yet occurred, prompt treatment may prevent the occurrence of a complete detachment. Once the retina becomes detached, it must be repaired surgically.    Laser Photocoagulation  When new small retinal tears are found with little or no nearby retinal detachment, the tears are sometimes sealed with a laser light. The laser places small burns around the edge of the tear. These produce scars that seal the edges of the tear and prevent fluid from passing through and collecting under the retina.    Freezing or Cryopexy   Freezing through the sclera (white of the eye) behind a retinal tear will also stimulate scar formation and seal down the edges.    Surgical Repair   Successful reattachment of the retina consists of sealing the retinal tear with a silicone material which is sutured to the sclera (white of the eye) to indent the eye ball inwards. Freezing applications are then used to bind the retina to the underlying layers.   Newer procedures have been developed to achieve the same result using the injection of a gas into the eye in suitable cases. The surgery may be performed under local or general anaesthesia depending on the procedure, age and general health of the patient.   In more complex retinal detachments, it may be necessary to use a technique called vitrectomy. This operation removes the vitreous body from the eye. In some cases, when the detached retina itself is severely shrunken or scarred, air or gas may have to be used to fill the vitreous cavity temporarily.    Prognosis   Over 90% of all retinal detachments can be reattached by modern surgical techniques. Occasionally, more than one operation may be required. The degree of vision which finally returns about six months after successful surgery depends upon a number of factors.   * This is a general guide. If in doubt, please consult your doctor.      
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    &nbsp; urlLink     hah..i've got this bottle of perfume last year as a birthday pressie and since then..I've been sticking to this fragance for almost a year except that its abit expensive for me 60 odd dollars for a bottle of 30ml. Today, I realised that I've used it up again. Sigh, but I've decided that this shall be my birthday present for myself this year. Will get this perfume in August!!!..haha..  Meanwhile, if you are reading this blog and are going overseas and you don't mind being a kind soul by getting the perfume for me please please let me know~!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Been feeling moody ever since I came back from my doctor's appointment on Wednesday. My eyes are getting from bad to worst. Most shocking news that the doctors told me..my retinals are weak, there is a very high chance of getting retinal detachment. So I asked the doctor what could be done to prevent this from happening. The doctor then told me to go back on 7 July 2004 to see another doctor who specialised in retinal detachments to decide if it is advisable to go for an op to prevent it from happening. Upon hearing that, I lost all my mood by hey I know retinal detachment is not really rare. I know it happens to people like me who has high mypoia but you can't help feeling worried abt it because its my EYES that I'm talking about here. And if you have been to see an eye doctor before you will know how terrible it feels to have those strong bright lights shining right into your eyes. Its just so..so..glaring and you have to follow the instructions and its so tedious.."look at my right ear..look upper right, extreme right,..bottom right.." all these instructions I can even memorise them. And its not just doing one time on each eye. I have to do two times for each eye..and worst still sometimes more than that. Yea I know I got to be patient, but its really glaring and painful. Sigh,.......  
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ahhhhhh...two whole weeks didn't update my blog. Ppl around me will know I was having EXAMS FEVER...and now, finally its over!! So tired..restless..ha..luckily I'm on leave tomorrow to rest for one more day and make a trip down to NUH for my eye appointment.   The exams were alright except for 2.1..It was horrible man I couldn't understand what I was writing either it was like writing my own textbook..haha..alot of my peers couldn't do it too...  Law was alright, confident of passing but don't know whether will score or not oh well, I don't care anymore because I just hope to pass.  Free for the next half a year till the next exams hahaha..yea because my next paper will be 2.3 which is related to my job. So there's no point in going for classes when I can do revision on my own. Actually I planned to go for classes for 2.4 too but after Monday's exam I was not so confident abt passing it so decided not to take the paper first unless a miracle happens haha..then I will enrol for the August intake. So I will be free..hmm plans plans plans alot of plans I've got plans to do alot of things but don't know what things to do yet cos the list just goes on and on and on..haha..  okie will update again soon.....
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         &nbsp;   LOOK OUT!         nicolelaw is a radioactive squirrel!!       
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Its been a lousy week. Came down with a bad throat on Friday night on my way back home. I quickily went to see a doctor on Saturday morning because I could sense something bad coming and I don't wanna disrupt my work in case I can't go to work on Monday. The doctor gave me some  antibiotics  and  lozenges  with some  cough syrup . But sigh..who would know that I'm that sick that I came down with a runny nose on Sat night. So since then, I've been going around with my red nose and a piece of yucky tissue in my hand. And now, I'm still having it!  My conclusion PANADOL COLD (the blue colour box) does not work for me!! I've almost done with 10 tablets since monday but yet it still does not get betta!!!!...grrrr  okie time to blow my nose till then.... 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So long never been blogging....I'm really busy with work man..so busy that now I'm sick with a bad bad bad throat..can't talk so BLOG..ha &nbsp; Yea new features from Blogspot again..cool...now i can  BOLD   italic  my text with  COLOURS!!   hahahaha....    &nbsp;  oh manz...dont know what to do this weekend..I'm supposed to go Sentosa with Audrey and Jas tomorrow..and rush off to MF's place for curry. But I'm just too sick and weak to go anywhere...except home and sleep..grrrr..so much so for working so hard for the past week.    &nbsp;   &nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hasn't been bloggin for almost a week. This week passed quickly with tons and tons and tons of work~~No time for gym, shopping, sleeping and BLOGGING..hahahah  Wednesday was a TERRIBLE day manz..I went for my medical appointment with the hope that I could see a retinal doctor on that day..but it turned out that my stupid doctor made a mistake. !@!$#!@$%$#^%$&^%$^%$%@$#@....here's wat happened  7 June 2004  Doctor : I would suggest that you come back a month later to see a retinal consultant who will decide whether you need to undergo an operation or not...if you don't have to go for an operation, we will see you once every six months...  Me: Okie then..  Doctor: then you come back on the 7 July 2004  7 July 2004  I went to the eye clinic....I waited for 3 whole hours for my turn to see the doctor..the nurses just keep on dilute my pupils again and again and again till I can't really see well. Finally its my turn..i walked into the clinic..the doctor was the same doctor previously!! I was expecting someone else...  Doctor : Let me check your eyes....  Me : ...........(wondering if i should ask him where is the retinal doctor....)  After the check up....  Doctor : I suggest you come back one mth later to see the retinal consultant...  me: (Volcano erupt)....but i thought you told me its today..  Doctor: well i made a mistake...  me:........................   yea..i quarrelled with the doctor..exact words I shall not used here..cos its not nice right..  anyway...  FCUKING DOCTOR~!!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Saturday is here, this week passed smoothly with two outings, one of which I mentioned earlier on. Another one was at West Mall on Thursday evening. I met up with three friends from secondary school. Had sushi..yummy..been eating alot of sushi these two weeks. Jing is going to Australia to further her studies soon. So cool heh. How I wish I can go too..awwww...  My SD left for her Europe tour on Wednesday..sigh without her in the office..its so BORING!!! nobody to create nonsense with me. its not fun..hahaa nvm hope she comes back soon.  Went for Yoga yesterday, I feel good energized but fat!!...hahahaha after Yoga classes, I received a message from a friend Kelvin. He asked me to listen to the song "The Reason" by Hoobastank. I downloaded it and hmmmmzzzzz really meaningful and nice lyrics here it goes...   I'm not a perfect person There's many things I wish I didn't do But I continue learning I never meant to do those things to you  And so I have to say before I go That I just want you to know  I've found a reason for me To change who I used to be A reason to start over new and the reason is you  I'm sorry that I hurt you It's something I must live with everyday And all the pain I put you through I wish that I could take it all away  And be the one who catches all your tears Thats why i need you to hear  I've found a reason for me To change who I used to be A reason to start over new and the reason is You [x4]  I'm not a perfect person I never meant to do those things to you And so I have to say before I go That I just want you to know  I've found a reason for me To change who I used to be A reason to start over new and the reason is you I've found a reason to show A side of me you didn't know A reason for all that I do And the reason is you   The Reason is me?!!? Don't be silly..hahaha  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO ME!!!         Haha..I'm 24 today. So happy..don't know why also. Probably because I know I've got a good present from dearest Ah Qiong and Soon Kuan. They have been the sweetest. This year kind of different, I got to choose my own present so the feeling is good you know. You walked into a shop pick something you like and someone is there to pay for you geezz. I picked a black watch from iwatch. It looks oh well ruggard?. Big watches always attracts me. But naughty me insist that they bring the present back and wrap it up before giving it to me on Saturday. Hahaha we are going for ktv and steamboat this saturday. I'm looking very much forward to it. :P      Well, in case you are one of the generous people in the world or one of my friends and don't mind getting me a present, these are my birthday wishes..hahahaha..(in my dreams...)      1. Mini cooper   2. A mobile phone   3. A brand new wardrobe   4. mp3 player      hahaha..i find it quite scary also lah..crazy me. So friends please ignore the above list. The above are rather the stuff which I want to save up MY OWN MONEY for. But the list below are my birthday resolution...       1.  I will keep myself healthy    2. I will sleep early to get rid of my   horr  ible   eye rings and bags..   3.  I will wake up very early too so that I will be in time to get to the gym and work.       4.  I will save more money.      5.  I will be more focused and careful in my work!      6.  I will KEEP THE ABOVE RESOLUTIONS IN MIND AND TAKE ACTION..HAHA         okie will update soon!!         5.    
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Finally after missing out my gym sessions for almost a month, I went back to the gym on Saturday after work. It was very quiet..probably it was a Saturday evening and ppl don't go there. :) But I like it when the gym is not crowded. Did some simple stretching and as ususal lah the normal stuff. But sucks..the steam bath is still out of order after so long. It been more than a month already. Sigh thought I could relax in the steam bath after the work out. Right now, I'm planning to go to the gym again on Tuesday morning before work. Very onz right..sigh what to do, I PUT ON WEIGHT again!!!...grrr Alot of functions coming up leh..and the most headache one would be the company's DND in October at SENTOSA.....wa kaoz....so now I chant every day..."must lose weight...must lose weight...must lose weight...." while I'm on the treadmill. Lolxx.  Sigh but today guess what, my colleagues and I had a gathering at MF's place. Yea so what happened all the good food!! Argghhh so sinful..hahaha..must be more disciplined manz..  Tomorrow's National Day.....as a child I've always loved National Day because..its near my birthday..12 August!! Oh boy, my birthday's coming and I"m 24!! Sigh..really old liao..haha  This year, nothing much for my birthday because I'm so held up by work. But I've made plans with SK and Ah Qiong (my 2 buddies from school) to meet up on Saturday to go for KTV...oh yeah! can't wait to go KTV...hahaha..I loved singing!!  Okie that should be all guess will try to update soon :) 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm back....after a week or so..haha..nothing special as usual busy with work..  Went to the Moscow Circus last night. The circus was terrific!! Haven't been one before so I was really amazed by the performance. All the clowns, dogs playing soccer and the cowboys with the whip etc made me went wowowowowowo...ahahha  My student cancelled her tuition today so I had a chance to sleep in on a Sunday morning..its been ages since I last did that. slept till 12 and woke up with a bad headache..haha..after my late breakfast I started to read..I've got to finish my books from the library first before I can start on my newly acquired book from the bookshop on Saturday. I've got the book "The Present" by Spencer Johnson..the same guy who wrote "Who Moved My Cheese" I like that book very much. Not really because I learnt from it but rather I'm impressed with how the author made one understand the meaning of life with simple things like Cheese and Mice. It was for the first time I could really relate things in books to life :) I seldom read non-fiction books. I'm a sucker for novels...yea..give me all the novels and love stories..I can finish them all in a weekend like today. Everytime when I read, I always dream that I don't have to work and just stay at home and read non-stop how good will tat be!!  Anyway, I haven't been going to the gym recently because of the bad cold and all the work that's piling up. Feel damn guilty manz..I betta start going again. Meanwhile, I will just continue reading and reading and reading and reading.  oh yea if you are reading this, do you have any good books to recommend? I've got some borders gift card and I WANT TO GET A NEW BOOK AGAIN!!!!   hahahahaha       
     

    
</post>


</Blog>