<Blog>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I have always thought that hospitals are kind of like airports for souls - where children are born, the elderly depart, and the rest of us make unexpected but hopefully temporary trips.      I thought of this analogy when my nephew Bahram was born. As I was sitting in the waiting room with my parents, it suddenly hit me how odd it was that "five" of us had arrived at the hospital hours earlier but that "six" of us would leave. One extra physical being coming out of no where into the hospital and our lives. As I wondered about this thought, I realized that only one or two floors away in the emergency rooms and operating rooms people were passing away. A place full of arrivals and departures. A 'soul port' full of tears; tears of joy and devastation.      I remembered this analogy as I stood in the lobby of the John Hopkins Medical Centre this morning; this time I realized that this was a very special soul port, that this was a place where people are fighting to stay in this world a little bit longer. It is also a special place because it has state of the art technologies that help people survive some of nature's vicious attempts against us. This gave me peace of mind that my sister's bone marrow transplant will be a success, and that this is only a temporary stop at this soul port.  
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Today was the day I departed for Washington D.C. for the “pre” evaluation tests associated with my being a donor for my sister’s bone marrow transplant scheduled for mid-august sometime. I have to have various tests undertaken at John Hopkins Medical Centre in Baltimore on Thursday and Friday. I return to Vancouver on Sunday. Subject to any schedule changes, I return back to Washington D.C. during the week of August 2nd for pre-operative checks on August 5th and the actual transplant on August 6th.   En-route, I was once again subject to the “disheartening” practices of US immigration. Right clicking on the word “disheartening” in MS-WORD and using its thesaurus, one gets “intimidating”, “off-putting”, “discouraging”, “scary”, “frightening”, “overwhelming”, and “demoralizing”; all of these words apply. Their Special Registration processes essentially starts with a blatant accusation that the Canadian government has issued me a false passport – meaning that my nationality as a Canadian citizen is not recognized by the US government, even though I carry a valid Canadian passport. Once my nationality is discounted, I am screen based on my place of birth: Tehran, Iran. Although I left Iran in 1979 when I was 12 years old and never to return, my place of birth signifies that I pose a threat to the American public and that I should be finger printed and photographed each time I enter and exit the US. It is difficult for me to pinpoint what bothers me most about this:   => the fact that I became a Canadian to escape the racism that Iranians face?  => the fact that it is humiliating to be designated as a second class Canadian citizen?  => the fact that the US immigration staff that execute their government’s distorted policies come from the most&nbsp;vile bowels of society?  => the fact that I am not a threat to anyone?  => the fact that the largest state sponsor of terror in the world is the United States of America?  => the fact that I must endure what I am exposed to because a life is at stake?   urlLink    Although I may not know what bothers me most about this, I know what helps me endure it, and that is threefold: firstly and most importantly I will be able to battle something that is a threat to all of us (cancer), secondly – I will be able to raise this issue (once again) with the media and Canada’s federal government and hopefully rectify it through the appropriate channels, and thirdly, I can choose to not travel to the US for any other purposes. These reasons empower me to fool the immigration officials to think that I am complying with respect, even though deep down inside I am revolted by everything that they stand for.  &nbsp;And alas, this is exactly what I did today; I complied with respect ;) and after the 2 hour ordeal was able to catch my flight arrive in DC on the eve of my appointments at the hospital and on time.      
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         &nbsp;    A thousand years, a thousand more, a thousand times a million doors to eternity; I may have lived a thousand lives, a thousand times an endless turning stairway climbs to a tower of souls; if it takes another thousand years, a thousand wars, the towers rise to numberless floors in space; I could shed another million tears, a million breaths, a million names but only one truth to face.   
    
</post>


</Blog>