<Blog>

<date>31,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       What a day I had yesterday .  So I woke up at the wee hour that is know as 7:00am.  Ok, actually I woke up at 5:00 with an attempt to roll over and fall back asleep.  But one of the weird quirks about Abigail my cat is if you make any noise that resembles waking up she comes running up for attention.  I have developed the barring my head in the pillow technique and she leaves me alone.  So anyways back to my day.  I was off to work and then had an hour lunch.    Then after work I made a mad dash home to change into some comfy Excelsior type attire and I was off to work again.  It was quite the crazy night with a lot of kids going off.  All I can say is that I am glad that I am not PART trained and that means that I do not have to go on any response teams.  I am free of getting bit or punched or many other much unwanted behavior.    Today I have been in and out of the office for meetings and other wonderful business reasons.  I just got a call from Excelsior and it looks like I will be partaking in round two of the long work days.  Tonight Jen is working and this is her last day at Excelsior.  So I hope that it is a good night and we can work side by side with out any response teams being called.  She is one of my favorite people to work with there and it will be sad and happy to see her go.  Good job Jen on finding a better job!  Here is to hoping that everything works out well for you.  Talk to you later! Tiff :-)
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Good Afternoon!    Well, last night was not that eventful unless you consider the cross country hike and backpacking experience extreme.  WHICH I DO!  I was breaking out in a sweat all over.  And then we came home and had a delicious hamburger and fries.  After my consumption I felt that the walk had little effect to a healthier lifestyle.  And then we headed out to meet the boys at the BB.  And thankfully I did not have a beer, I do not need the extra calories.  My intertube of love keeps growing.  Pretty soon I will be able to support a party's worth of amount of fun on the intertube.  I hope that makes sense, because it does to me.  Today work was hectic.  Brooke got a little annoyed with me, but we patched things up with our handy dandy step counters.  We are in a competition with other Faculty and Staff to earn a one night stay at a nice hotel.  You know Brooke and I we are always shagging it up with naughty men at hotels.  Perhaps good old Josh Hartnett will want to meet me there.  A girl can hope can't she?  Anyways I am off to Excelsior for a night shift.  Dan called in sick and they were desperate for someone to cover, so I said yes.  We all know I can use the money to cover my spending problems.  So until tomorrow sweet dreams!  Tiff ;-)
    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, what a weekend!  Thursday and Friday I did my usual overnight shifts.  This week I tried to sleep my eight hours during the day and hang out with people right before work.  This proved to not be the best way to get through overnights.  Also, it probably didn't help that I had a drink or two right before I went to work.  My bad!  By the time it was Saturday I was sick of doing overnights and decided to call in sick.  Which I really was sick, wink wink!  I kind of feel bad about not going into work when I really did not have a good excuse, but Debi needed the hours.    I then spent my evening at Josh's house, which I thought more people would be at.  Since there were not that many people Brooke ended up going home.  A few more people showed up but I really couldn't get many people to dance.  Of coarse I did have a little bit of fun dancing, but I won't go into the details.  What can I say, I'm a horny girl and when a little fun comes my way I take it.  I hope you don't think bad things about me, but that is just who I am.  Thanks Sean for giving me a ride home!  Well work is kind of busy right now, people are looking at me funny that I am not doing anything professional.  Well John I wish you lots of fun on your mini vaca.  Think of us often sitting in your roof top swimming pool.  I will think of you often at my sweaty desk.  Peace! Tiff-a-Roo!:-)
    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hey y'all!   So I think that Brooke and I should never be able to go to the mall alone.  We start buying things we have no reason to buy, and then come home and take hundreds of pictures of ourselves.  So pretty much I will just let your mind think of what we could have bought.   Anyways, we spent way to much time at the mall, spent way to much money, and really didn't come home with a whole heck of a lot.  Then we watched T.V. and I fell asleep on the couch.    Not much more to report besides the fact that no one called Brooke or I yesterday.  So as Brooke was complaining all night I decided to give her phone a call.  We were in the car and the music was up so loud you could not hear the ringer.  But I still said, "is that your phone".  Brooke was none the wiser as she almost rammed her car into the sidewalk desperately reaching for her phone.  It was so hilarious I almost peed my pants.  Once she found out it was me she was so mad, and pretty much laughing her head off.  Screeching in my ear that I almost got us in a car wreck.  Yeah right!  Well I'm off to work, I hope you have a good day!!!    
    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Wow!   It was fun having the boyz over for dinner last night.  Oh how we were oh so talkative all night.  I have come to the conclusion that we hang out so much that we just have nothing to talk about.  I mean you can only joke about Scotty not having a job so many times.  Ok, I can never get enough of making fun of PaPa, it is all love though.  Work has been crazy busy today!  So I really have no time to think of more things to write, but I really do not have much to say anyways.  I hope everyone has a wonderful rainy day.  I love days like this, but what I really want to be doing is sitting curled up in a blanket reading a book in front of a window.  Ahh that sounds wonderful.  But instead I am sitting at my desk in a room with no windows.  I think it could be worse.  Bye! TIFF!
    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Good Morning!  Well last night Brooke, John, and myself went to the ever popular Baby Bar!  BOB was working, what a crazy kid.  Sugar momma Tiff was in the house, and I was happy to buy the drinks.  Now all you who weren't there are wishing you were there for some free drinks.  But you know that will probably not happen for a few more months.   I'm so excited that summer is almost upon us.  I can't wait for the sun and all the outdoor fun!  Good rhyme huh?  Ok, whatever, keep your comments to yourself.  We were talking about camping, and hiking and I am getting all excited.  But then I think of my car without air conditioning and can not wait until I get a new car.  Hopefully my beautiful Dodge Dakota will be at my finger tips by the first of July.  Here is to hoping for continual employment at Whitworth.  Well, that is if they do not find out how much I goof off at work.  Like taking test at Spark.com.  I just took the sex test and it says that I will have sex with three people in my lifetime, and I will love all three of them.  Of coarse they predicted that I would have to wait three more years, ahhhhhhh!  Ok, enough about that.  I'm off to work, or another website to play around on instead of working.  Hee hee!  Talk to ya later, Tiff!
    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just took the OK Cupid love test.  Here are my results!  Man can they get a person right on.  Both Brooke's and my results seem to be dead on.  This is me:  The Sonnet Deliberate Gentle Love Dreamer (DGLDf)      Romantic, hopeful, and composed. You are the Sonnet. Get it? Composed?       Sonnets want Love and have high ideals about it. They're conscientious people, caring & careful. You yourself have deep convictions, and you devote a lot of thought to romance and what it should be. This will frighten away most potential mates, but that's okay, because you're very choosy with your affections anyway. You'd absolutely refuse to date someone dumber than you, for instance.    Your exact opposite: Genghis Khunt  Random Brutal Sex Master      Lovers who share your idealized perspective, or who are at least willing to totally throw themselves into a relationship, will be very, very happy with you. And you with them. You're already selfless and compassionate, and with the right partner, there's no doubt you can be sensual, even adventurously so.       You probably have lots of female friends, and they have a special soft spot for you. Babies do, too, at the tippy-top of their baby skulls.     ALWAYS AVOID: The 5-Night Stand, The False Messiah, The Hornivore, The Last Man on Earth   CONSIDER: The Loverboy 
    
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey All-  I have had a really busy weekend.  I'm sure you are jealous that I had so much fun.  Ok, so all I did was work at Excelsior and sleep.  Fun times!  Friday I picked up Abigail from the vet since I had her declawed.  Ouch, she is in so much pain.  All she does is sleep and hobble around.  So actually I did not feel bad that all I do during the day is sleep since that is all she is doing with me right now.  She is not her usual psycho self running around, getting on the counters and playing with every bread product we have.  And at our house there are always 15 different kinds of bread.  Anyways, she is starting to move around more and is jumping on the counters.  Ah, she isn't supposed to be doing that for a week.  I have already spend $500 on this cat and she better not cost me anymore for a while.  On Saturday I was going to get a lot of sleep and then go out with Brooke, Sean, and John or who ever all wanted to go out.  But I ended up sleeping down in our dungeon of a room with out windows.  AKA Abigail's room.  She came home and I was so out of it.  We didn't end up going anywhere and it was off to work for my double shift.   On Sunday I was scheduled to also work the 8-1 shift in Disco.  I ended up staying until 4, and it was so much fun.  I think I was a little intoxicated, but because of the lack of sleep.  I'm sure that all the staff and kids think I'm a little psycho now.  But I think the reason that I ended up staying so long is because I really miss working during the day.  I love talking and hanging out with the staff and kids.  I can't wait for next month and being there during the day.  Overnights SUCK!  I'm so glad that I didn't take that position.    Well, I need to get back to the piles of work that have accumulated over Friday and this morning.  Until later! Peace - Tiff! :-)
    
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Mystery Solved!  Karen and Jill are my two secret admirers that keep giving me flowers.  The final plant came in along with Jill.  Those girls are great.  Also, when Jill was here my mother and brother came in and gave me a huge plant.  If I get anything else I will have to start taking over other parts of the office.  Hopefully I will be able to keep these plants alive.  I love flowers!!!
    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What a GREAT birthday.  I never knew that working on your birthday could be fun.  I had three wonderful visitors today.  They go by the names of Jen, John, and Sean.  And now my work environment will forever be more pleasant because of the three of you.  My pits thank you for the fan.  And also for the lovely pink flowers that brighten up my day to see.  Also, I got a message while I was at lunch that I had flowers waiting for me at the post office.  They are beautiful and I want to thank my secret admirers.  I have a hunch that they are no other than my two roommates.  They are beautiful and all my flowers make my little work environment so so happy.  Did I ever tell everyone how much I love flowers, because if I haven't good job at getting me what I love.  Now it is back to work for a few hours and then dinner at the Elk, free beer thanks to Dale, a nap and then off to work.  It shouldn't be too bad because it is latte night and the wonderful Bill is working tonight.  I love that guy!  Thanks again to all of the people that have given me a present or phone call.  I really feel the love!!!!! Love, Tiff!:-)
    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well last night was fun.  We did a double whammy in one.  John, Jen, Sean, Scotty, Brooke, and myself went out and celebrate St. Patty's day and my birthday.  Sean and Scotty got me a wonderful gift certificate to the Elk to buy a T-Shirt.  They didn't have the one I wanted so I can go back and pick one out.    To Start off the night we had cosmos and sparkling wine from bartender Sean.  All of the drinks I had were quite lovely, but Jen had a bad batch.  And also, we found out that you can't mix cosmos and fudge covered chocolate oreos.  Go figure!  After a little bump and grind to the ever lovely Brittney Spears we headed downtown for a little bar hopping.  Walking since all of us were a little intoxicated and plus we were right down there anyways.  We headed to O'Doherty.  Well that was our first mistake there was a line half way down the block.  We pretty much knew that this would be the case but I really wanted to go to an Irish pub.  And despite the unwilling John to go he let me pick that place.  But we didn't stay.  So now we were on our way South with a few options at our fingertips.  Oh yeah, at this time Scotty was hopping, wiggling, and doing just about every potty dance in the book.  Scotty then started to wonder towards a restaurant and we figured that he was heading to a bathroom.  Five minutes late here comes Scotty hiding behind Sean saying he pittled himself.  We all just about died with laughter.  Funny drunk boy.    So then we finally arrived at Mootsies after being turned down from Gabby's.  We were not about to start a line.  When we got in there Sean and John headed for the bar to get some shots.  Little did John know that you shouldn't say you are drunk right in front of the bartender.  He was cut off before he even started there.  So two shots later we were headed to the Blue Spark.  We stuck around this place for a little while.  A few drinks were ordered we talked, we went pee, we drank and then we moved on to the next bar.  The Baby Bar, where we stood outside and waited for John and Jen to get back from the Blue Spark, seeing that John forgot his pullover there.  We said leave it.  And he preceded to tell us how he has had this extra long sleeved pullover since he was in the womb.    After the two got back we went to a little bar that I can not remember the name of.  But let me tell you it was amazing.  The crabcakes were unreal.  Mouth watering delicious treats that you need to savior every bite.  I had the cheesecake turtle and it was wonderful.  John was so kind to treat me to my desert and portions of all the food he had.  We will have to go back and drop a pretty penny on that lovely food.    By now it is 11:00 and time to head home.  We are all tired and I hear Brooke whining that she is tired and doesn't want to walk home.  We have drunk Scotty puking in the bathroom and the rest of us are stuffed.  We pay the bill and start the walk.  John, Sean, Jen and myself nearly got wiped out by a bus as we crossed the street.  I yelled that a bus was coming to Jen and had to retract my words when I told her that I said her name because she is an airhead.  Ok she is not an airhead, not the words I meant.  I meant Spacey or something like that.  Anyways when I was explaining this to her she ran into the wall and it seemed to me like the funniest thing I have ever seen.  I nearly pittled myself and my back now hurt from all of the laughter.  John was on the ground and Sean was supporting himself by the wall because we were all laughing so hard.  It was great.  We all made it home safely after this and all lived to get drunk another day.  I really wasn't drunk, but feeling good all night.  I ended up only having a few drinks but that was great.  I had a wonderful birthday and want to thank all my friends that shared the night with me.  You are all the best and I wouldn't want to have spent it with anyone else.  Way to go WINGMEN!  Ok, I must get to work, sorry about the long entry.  It was a great night.  Bye!  Love Tiff-A-Roo!
    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      HAPPY ST. PATRICK'S DAY!!!! I like to dress for this day more than Halloween.  And that is saying a lot.  If I had a pair of green pants I would probably be wearing them.  I like to give a shout out to all of the Irish relatives that have come before me.  Now that I am 1/5th or 1/8th or some percentage of Irish this is the holiday of my ancestors. Yesterday Brooklyn and I had a fun night.  Ok, well we were drinking and that was fun.  And we did not even crack one PBR.  We went all out and it pays off.  I feel great today, a little tired but that comes with the territory of a drunken sleep.  I had a fun time dancing in the Baby Bar.  Good old John was bartending and he is great.  Sitting at the bar having a flying nun.  And I asked for a flying pastor but John said he doesn't make those.  Anyways a flying nun is what ever John feels like putting in a shot.  But being the great person that he is we did not pay for it.  The night was fun, Brooke kept getting groped by a guy but other than that it was kind of empty.  Ass hole Aaron came in and was actually ok until people he knew came in.  He must struggle with keeping up on how he should act when different people are around.  I just like to make him feel like a dork by talking to me and then I say something dorky or dance around the bar.  As if he would associate himself with someone who acted like me.  You got to love making fun of people.   Well, I should get back to work.  I will write you more tomorrow after we go out to night for the holidays.  And to also celebrate my birthday.  I will finally be 23 tomorrow.  I have a very exciting day planned.  Work at Whitworth 8-5 and then do a overnight.  Boy don't you wish you could do that on your birthday.  I know, you can let it out.  I won't feel bad about your jealousy.  I'm a little envious of myself that this wonderful thing is going to happen.  Well, until tomorrow. PEACE! TIFF
    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've got time for a quick posting.  Last night Brooklyn, Scotty, John and I all went to the Elk.  I was in heaven each bite of my lamb sandwich.  The whole ride home I enjoyed the after taste.  Anyways, I will leave it at that until another wonderful day at the Elk.     I would like to let everyone know that I realize I have a shopping problem.  But it is only a problem and I am searching the internet for support groups.  If they have AA and NA groups there must be some SA groups out there.  That would be shoppers anonymous if you couldn't figure it out.  Anyways, I'm going to buy a pair of pink pants now on the web.  I said I knew that I have a problem, not that I am cured.  I hope you have a good day and I will talk to you later! Tiff ;-) 
    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, as you can see it has been a little while since I last updated you on my life.  That is because this is the month from hell.  Ok, not really, because things have been working out great for me.  But I do have to work every day this month and that leaves little time for hanging out with my friends.  So I would like to give a little shout out to my fans that are daily bloggers and count on my entries to feel apart of my life.  So what what John!    Ok, back to my life.  I have been working, and working, and yet working some more.  Also, Brooklyn and I have started walking in hopes of a healthier lifestyle.  Or it is just a kick and will be gone in a week.  But here is to preparing for living downtown and walking everywhere.  Well, I should get back to work, I do not work at Whitworth on Fridays and the work has piled up.  So, off to work, I will try to update you more than on a weekly basis.
    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This week I have been training for my new position at Whitworth College.  I guess you can call it training, but I had enough time to set up this website.  It is not exactly how I want it but I have yet to mess around with the colors and fonts.  Anyways, the person I am replacing is finally on her way to a much better place.  Sunny Hawaii.  And I am here in snowy Spokane.  Ok, so the sun did come out today, but there are still patches of snow.  But I should not complain, I now have a full time job, with benefits and a good pay.  There are worst things that could be going on.  Well, as for the fun in my life there is my new Kitty, Abigail.  But she has a cold, and the runs.  So it is not much fun to pet a smelly cat that sneezes or coughs on you.  But she sure is cute.  The story of the night is how I woke up to find crap on my sheets.  I guess I scared the shit out of her.  Maybe I was rolling over in the night and got her.  Anyhow, in the end I had to wash my sheets when I woke up.  Perhaps Abigail will just have to sleep in her own room until she gets better.  Well I should head home, Brooke and I are headed downtown for a little shopping.  Well, she will shop and I will walk and wait patiently until I get paid on Monday.  Talk to ya later! BYE! Tiff
    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is the first of my many postings to come.  Give me awhile as I learn how to do it more.  Welcome to my website
    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Just a quick little post for you.   Last night Brooke and I drove around town looking at areas that we would like to live.  I think we have narrowed it down to the area around Audubon park.  Or however you spell it.  It is nice to be closer to downtown but still be close to the north side.  Since both of us will probably be working at Whitworth.  After that we did a little BBQ and it was off to the bachelorette party.  Which meant a house I have never been too before, and a bunch of people I have never seen before.  I swear that I felt like I was back in high school.  And since I never went to parties when I was in high school it was really weird.  I did do my first beer bong, and that was quite fun.  I must say that I liked it better than shot-gunning a beer.  Less messy!  Tonight is the rehearsal and dinner.  Hopefully it won't go to long so that I can celebrate the lovely Jen's b-day.  There is just way too much going on this weekend.  Well, I will fill you in on how it all goes when I get in on Monday!!!  Have a great weekend!  Tiff-a-roo :-)
    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       HAPPY BIRTHDAY  Jenny from the Block!!!!!!
    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You so have to check out this website!  It is   hilarious  !!!!  http://worldzonepro.com/webdude/kozo.html 
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Scotty's birthday was quite fun.  It all started at the famous Pete's table at the Steamplant Grill.  Who knew that Scotty's dad was so famous to have his own table.  While there I had a wonderful pint of Huckleberry beer.  It was quite tasty, I just wish I was outside in the sun sipping it.  Ahh, I can't wait for the summer.  Then it was upstairs for some dinner.  I had a delicious salmon wrap, and shared Sean's Thai wrap.  Both were good, but not as mouth watering as the amazing food from the Elk.  But really is there any place better than the Elk, and at their prices?  Then we all headed to play some darts and have a few more drinks.  I held back since tonight is a batchelorette party and I just can't drink that much.  I will probably be the DD tonight, but we will see.  Anyways then it was off to Fast Eddies to spin the wheel.  Since Brooklyn went out with the Finn I hoped a ride with Scotty home.  After we were more than half way home I realized that I did not have my key to the house.  I called Brooke after we swept through the Swinging Doors to see if Loretta just happened to be there.  She wasn't, not yet!  Anyways, Brooke said she would come by as soon as she finished her drink.    So Papa dropped me off and I headed for the back porch to sit and wait.  Well let me tell you it was a bit cold out there and I did not have a jacket.  I then called Loretta to see if she would come let me in.  I really didn't expect her to pick up, but she did.  And she agreed to come let me in.  It was good to talk to her for a few minutes before she headed to the Doors.  Nothing was really settled but, it was good for her to get some things off her chest and hear what I had to say.  Drama continues but big things should be happening soon.  More details to come!  Well, I have done very little this afternoon.  I should use the last 15 minutes and be productive.  I'll let you know what comes of the night.  Talk to you later!!!!!!!
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Not much to update you on.  Last night I finally saw Kill Bill, and I really liked it.  Sometimes I had to cringe at the brutality.  Such as the slamming the head in the door and the slicing of the achilles heel.  But I made it through and can not wait to see the next one.    The only other thing I did was watch T.V. and hit the hay.  Sad really but it was a Tuesday night.  Today has been  draaaaaaaaaaaaaaging  on.  I swear, people are getting on my nerves and I just want to get out of here.  Yet the clock seems to be ticking ever so slowly by.  What is a girl to do?  Anyways tonight should be fun, we are going out for Scotty's birthday and I am stoked.  I wonder if his girl will be there, my first thought is that she will not.  What is up with that papa?  Anyways until tomorrow! Tiff :-)
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last test I swear!  This is my Passion Personality   Belle of the Ball   One of great things about being you is that you have a healthy dose of self-respect. It's not every Tom, Dick, or Harry who gets to land a date with you. Your natural tendency to really check someone out before letting 'em in the door serves you well. You don't get stuck with the bottom-feeders.   So what if some people think you're a challenge? That isn't always a bad thing. Being picky just means you don't settle for anything but the best. You want someone who will dote on you and take good care of you, while still keeping you on your toes. Thank goodness you're not one of the many women who underestimate their self-worth (men tend to overestimate). That's why you see so many gorgeous gals going out with meatheads.  Is it possible that your romantic standards are just protecting the heart of gold inside? Once you let your guard down, successful suitors find a loving, generous gal who will throw herself into a relationship. Our only advice is that in your quest for love, carry with you the immortal words of Mother Teresa: "If you judge people, you have no time to love them."     
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just took What is your best quality quiz, here are my results:  Tiff, your best quality shines through in how  Intelligent  you are.  The fact that you're a smart person who is more able to understand complex concepts than many other people are really draws people to you! But that's not the only thing. Your answers on the test indicate you're a romantic and affectionate person who can radiate passion — whether for certain ideas or for matters of love. You are a caring and considerate person who is typically very loving, as well, too.  In all, there are 15 qualities that help define you when you're at your best. Those are the traits potential employers, friends, and partners look for in you. What makes you unique is your particular distribution of those 15 qualities.  We've found that your particular combination of qualities is rare — only 3 in 10,000 people share the same general mix of traits. Those are great odds if you're trying to show a potential employer, colleague, friend, or date why you're exactly the right person for them. 
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        HAPPY BIRTHDAY SCOTTY!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Not much to update from yesterday.  Softball practice was fun, and I loved the lovely sun.  Today is quite the opposite in the weather department.  After practice I finally went grocery shopping and then headed over to Jen's house.  I  LOVE  the fire pit!  Plus my girl John was there and that makes all the difference if a person has had a good day or not. :-)  All were present from the gang with exception of Papa Sco, who was most likely at a intramural sport of some sort.  Hopefully tonight I will finally watch Kill Bill, and I can get on the same page as everyone else.  But other than that not much has gone on.  Maybe something exciting will happen tonight, but don't count on it.  Talk to ya later!!  TIFF-A-ROO !
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Brooklyn look my signature city is  Seattle  also.  Interesting!
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        So long since an update!    My weekend was busy, busy, busy, as always.  And work has been crazy all day, so I really do not have much time for an update.  I will give you the quick version.   Friday  night Brooke and I took in a little Greek food and experience.  We had the opportunity to see a belly dancer during our meal.  After dinner it was home and then to papa Sco's house.  It was pretty fun hanging out with the trainers, though I really didn't talk to too many of them and I only participated in one drinking game.  I had to relieve the ever drunk Sean, he was at least five sheets to the wind.   Saturday  I got my hair done in the morning and then ran errands to get the last of the things needed for the bridal shower.  Ok, everything for all the games that I was doing and the present.  I'm a procrastinator this is nothing new.  Then it was off to work at Excelsior.  Two girls ran on me and then decided to overdose by taking 24 cold and flu tablets.  They did this to get high, but they got the wrong kind of medicine.  All it does is destroy their liver.  Good job girls!  I got home around 1:00am.   Sunday  I had to be back to work at 8:00, but the senior let me come in at 8:30.  Work was a bit calmer, but I had to finish up a stack of papers and pretty much make sure things got done.  I was working with a staff member that sits on her ass the whole time and wouldn't even cook the eggs.  Redick!!!  After work I was off to the bridal shower.  Everything went well, but since I was in charge of games it was not a relaxing night.  I got home around 9:00 and hit the hay at 10:00.  Well there you go, my weekend in a nut shell.  Today I have been working on spreadsheets and in different programs.  I'm sure you are jealous.  Don't be, I am about to poke my eyes out.  I need a neck massage because my head has been bent over looking at papers all day.  If I keep this pace up then I will end up with a hump on my neck, I can just picture it.  Well, I'm going home now, have a great night!!!! Tiff:-)
    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just took the  How are you turned on test , here are my results!  Tiff, you're most turned on by  Physical-Personality-Environment   People who are equally turned on by a person's physical appearance, their personality, and environmental factors can be turned on by any of these factors on any given day.  Look John I'm not a nymph!  I am just a well balanced turned on person, any given day, at any given time!  So pretty much I am just like a guy.
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Hello!!!    Well here is a little review for you.  Monday softball practice was quite interesting.  It all started with Loretta making yet another excuse as to why she didn't return my calls and then continued to get weird when Sara came over and gave me a hug.  I just stood there and did not reciprocate the notion.  Please, your sisters get all up in my face a few days ago and Sara was obviously pissed at me too, and then a few days later she hugs me.  Please, one of my biggest pet peeves is the fact that I hate when people are fake.  Plus I had no clue that both Sara and Loretta still had issues with me.    I swear those girls equal drama and it is a part of my life I can live without.  Really I can not wait until Brooke and I have a place of our own.  We live well together, and seems to be pretty drama free.  Perhaps it is due to the fact that we are the two most wonderful girls in the   WORLD  ! Jk!  Yesterday Brooke and I rented Kill Bob and we did the Grind workout.  The lovely passer byers got a good look at us shaking our things.  And then we preceded to watch TV for the night and did not get to the movie.  But we have it for a few days and we will finally see this movie the boys keep ranting about.  Lo dog was supposed to call me so that we could work out a few bugs in our relationship.  Did she call,  hell no,  and that was no surprise.  I swear I am not going to call her because I left the last two messages and have yet to get a call back.  Any ways, I am sick of trying to deal with her and if she wants some resolution then she has to put some effort into making our friendship better.  She can't just sit back and let people fight her battles and continue to complain about it.  Well, tonight is ladies night in our office.  That means drinks and food.  The place of choice is the Doors, we will see how it goes tonight.  Hopefully I will not get in any arguments.  Well, talk to ya later!  Tiff
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Update : I totally forgot about dinner with Brooke's dad.  It was quite fun to listen to his stories.  He makes me laugh every time we get together.  And the lady yelling at me when we were parking.  That was funny!  So I was driving down the road and spotted a spot on the other side, so I pull a U-turn.  I saw the car in front of me pulling into the ally but didn't think anything of it.  So I prepared my car to parallel park and the lady gets on my ass.  I decide I don't care about this lady so I precede to park and she reverses so that I won't hit her.  I expected her to flip me off or something, but she rolls her window down and accuses me of knowing she was going for that spot and that it was a low blow to park there.  How the hell was I supposed to know she was turning around.  Redic if you ask me.  So funny, I guess that set the pace for the night to come.  I had people attacking me from the get go.
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Weekend summary:   WANNA FIGHT    So for some reason I can see Brooke's and my blogs, but not Scottys.  Who knows I do not understand it.  So here is the weekend update.  Friday, Yeah I have the night off.  So good old Jonny came over and we had a few drinks, danced around the room, talked about being  HORNY,  and then it was off to the Doors.  The way there was quite funny, and quite illegal.  I was in the back, aware of my speed, and my drunken state of affairs.  But I was also laughing so hard because John and Brooke were doing a little competition and for some reason John thought that it would be fun to swerve into Brookes lane.  Of coarse Brooke had a delayed reaction and almost a whole minute later she swerved out of the way.   HILARIOUS !  And so the night continues.  I thought it was going to be fun to see a lot of people.  Well that just wasn't the case.  Loretta started to cry and I thought that it was a little odd but I was talking to Wes and did not want to interrupt him.  So here comes Sara demanding to talk to me and Sara's sisters attacking Brooke.  I thought that they were just joking and left it at that.    So of coarse Sara was going off and talking with me, and in the mean time Sean, John, and Brooke all high tail it out of there because one of Sara's sisters is really going in on Brooke.  I swear it was like they were in Jr. High.  Anyways I came back to the group and talked with Loretta, evidently she still has issues with me and Brooke.  Perhaps that is why she is never home, even though she said earlier that day that she has been coming home we are just never there.   Interesting !  Now as the night continues I become the victim of the 30 year old Jr high acting sisters, as they are arguing that I am the worst kind of person.  But of coarse they are not judging me.  Do not worry I did not get in a fight, as much as I would love to punch someone and rub their face into the concrete.  But I will not go to their level.  But I will tell you that I have been having visions.  Well, I didn't stay much longer because they left and I was drained.    The next night we were off to Jen's house and it was wonderful. The food was great, the people were awesome, and CJ (Crazy Jim) was hilarious.  I swear I could have listened to him for hours.  Sunday I spent much of the day working and went home.  There you go, my weekend in a wam bam thank ya mam kind of way.  Lo dog has still not returned my calls and it should be interesting to see if she goes to softball practice tonight.  Lets just hope that I do not lay into her tonight.  Talk to ya later! Tiff
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am seriously   pissed   at Whitworth for blocking this site!  And this morning I could look at Scotty's webpage, but not now.  I guess I do write a blog and post it everyday, but look I can still do it.  It just means that I can't look at my website.  And I LOVE my website.  Well pretty much just the pinkness of it.  Anyways, yesterday was not all that exciting.  I got new glasses and Brooke and I went on a walk to the grocery store.  Even though it was raining and cold, we fought through the pain.  Ok, it wasn't a winter storm or anything but it wasn't pleasant.  I thought that I would have to work tonight but I ended up not being scheduled, that was a pleasant surprise.  Brooke and I are going to dinner with her dad at the Olive Garden, so that should be good.  Then we will have to wait and see where the night takes us.  I mean I haven't had a real Friday night off in a while, so watch out boys here comes the tiffster.  Well, I better get back to work, I hope you have a great weekend and I will talk to ya soon.  Peace! Tiff :-)
    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I Give UP!!!!!     I have been working on the same report at work for the last two hours, and it is not working for me.  I think that I have to stop for the afternoon and try again in the morning.  I feel bad for Rick because he needs it, but he will just have to wait.    Last night Brooke and I went to REI to meet her dad to look at kayaks and the car rack.  It was quite informative and has me excited to go kayaking.  Brooke is buying a kayak tonight and I will just borrow her parents, because I have way to much debt as it is.  After REI we met the boys at The Elk and had a delicious meal.  I LOVE that place!  Then Brooke and I continued to price kayaks and make a few other pit stops.  I bought a new swimsuit but have decided to take it back.  I found out that I am actually getting a return this year from my taxes.  So I am going to celebrate by getting the perfect swimsuit, instead of something I can afford.  I might even get a rashguard, you know the things the surfers put over the swimsuit.  Pretty much it is not necessary, but I have wanted one ever since we watched the surfing show last year.  And BLUE CRUSH, the best movie   EVER  .  JK!  Anyways, I should try the stupid report a few more times.  Or, perhaps more shopping online.  Much better!!! Till later, Tiff!
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Holler!!!!!!    Not much to report.  I spent most of the evening yesterday doing pretty much nothing.  I whitened my teeth, listened to music, crochet, watched a little Miss USA and went over to Scotty's house to kick some ASS in Mario Cart.  Wait strike that, reverse it, I got my ASS KICK!!! Whatever, it was fun and kept me up later than I should have.  Today I have been a bit tired, and work has sucked.  I have been bored out of my mind.  I need more responsibilities!!!!!  Tonight should be fun I think we are going bowling, perhaps my game will be on tonight, only time will tell.  Well, got to go home now and wax my ball. JK!  Talk to ya later. Tiff-a-Roo! :-)
    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        HELLO!!!!!!!    What a weekend, or not.     Friday : I had to get up pretty early and head to the eye doctor.  I am in need of some new glasses and they fixed my old ones.  No more staple holding my glasses together, darn I really liked that look.  So then I was downtown, with dilated eyes driving myself to the North side.  Let me tell you there were a few moments when I had to close my eyes.  Don't worry, only during one of those times was I driving.  JK!  Then I took a nap before I headed to the good old Excelsior for a swing shift.  I wanted to meet the gang at the BB but they had dispersed before I was off.  John said to come down and give him a lap dance, but I choose to go to a birthday party.  It was lame so I am sorry Jonny boy it would have been more fun to come down and give you a show.   Saturday : I spent the morning doing yardwork and laundry.  Then yet again it was off to Excelsior I go.  I got to take the girls on the weekend outing, free movie oh oh oh!  We saw the Johnson's Family Reunion, and it wasn't that bad and it wasn't that good.  I would not recommend it, but you can make up your own decision.     Sunday : Not only was it Easter but it was an all day workday for the Tiffster.  I got to take three girls to the service at the Arena.  I really wanted to go to the Met where New Community had their service but I couldn't take the girls downtown.  Boy I sure think the arena is very close to downtown, like two blocks but I wasn't going to argue.  I thought that the service was a little too showy, but that is just me.  Anyways, when I got back I got to hide the eggs for the egg hunt and that was quite fun.  Work seemed to drag on but it wasn't that bad.  I had a laughing attack and thought Sara was the funniest person last night.  It felt good to get a good laugh out.  Thanks to Sean and Sara I got stuck writing a Special Incident Report, because a girl swallowed her ring, even though I was supposed to be off at 11:00.  I didn't get out of there until well after 11:30, but I won't hold that against them.  Well not for more than a month :-).     Monday : I have been working hard all day and have just now had a moment to write this blog.  I like having lots of work to do.  It is better than looking for things to do.  I am still trying to decide if I am going to softball tonight or if I should play the dumb card that I forgot we had practice.  That sounds like a plan!  Well I'll write more tomorrow.  PEACE! Tiff 
    
</post>

<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Good afternoon to you!!!    Last night I finally got to hang out with my good friend Sean.  It was good to have dinner at the Elk and see him again.  It is really sad when you live in the same city as someone and you never see them.  But I guess that is how it goes after you graduate from college.  Then it was off to Sean and John's house.  We sat and chatted until Papa showed up and we went to the food court of Riverpart Square and sat at the Subway for two hours.  It was fun talking to the boys.  Hey now I know more personal details than I probably wanted to know.  All I have to say is "6 in a day all the way!"  Keep UP the good work Papa!    After Brooke got off at the PB we headed to the Bulldog for some fun games and the boys had some drinks.  Brooke and I have decided that there are just way too many calories in beer and we are just going for hard A.  Pricey but the effects and lower calories will pay off.  Hey at least it makes sense in our heads.  Plus this way when we do decided to have the wonderful cup of brew it will be that much better.  Thinking about that statement and what my feelings of beer were 9 months ago is quite funny.  I could hardly stand to have a few sips let alone four or five beers.    Well, work has gone by quite quickly and seeing that I am the only personnel from HR I have been on the lower end of productivity.  I mean it was my responsibility to go to Didiers and get some yogurt and take Jason to pick up his truck.  All very important aspects of my job responsibilities.    No work tomorrow, YES!! So I will write to you all on Monday.  HAPPY EASTER!  And don't forget to take the poll located to the right.  See ya! Tiff-a-Roo :-) 
    
</post>

<date>07,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Everyone except me is out of the office. YIPEE!!!!!!!!  What the heck are they thinking?  Like I am not going to spend much of my time goofing off!  I just have to make sure to keep the students busy.  That is a task in itself.    FREEDOM!!!!!!!!  
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Hey Y'all!!!!    Last night was pretty uneventful.  I attempted to go running with Brooklyn but had to bail out 1/3 of the way.  I cut back through the neighborhood and ran a little and walked a lot.  Hey it was my first attempt and I will make if a little further each time.  It is definitely weird to still live and walk around the neighborhood I grew up in.    After I got back with my heart pounding I was greeted by the ever so Lovely Sean and John, DQ in hand and none to share rrrrrrrrr!  JK, I made a home made coconut cream pie and that fulfilled my sweet tooth.  Then we watched some TV and I headed to bed early.  It was great to get a full nights sleep.  Work has been busy, and now it is off to lunch.  Brooke and I went to the grocery store yesterday so now I have some good fresh food to eat, not just out of a can.  Praise Jesus!  Till later, Tiff! :-)
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        WOW!!!!!!!!    So not much to report.  I had my first softball practice.  And in terms of first I mean the first practice since I was in the sixth grade.  So pretty much you can imagine how it went.  I got hit in the leg with a ball, I completely missed the ball when I swung at it a few times, and the hilarious moments continue from there.  Thank goodness there are four or five practices before our first game.  I probably would quit if they weren't so desperate for girls.  So pretty much they should be thankful that I am around.  I just wish I wasn't so dang competitive.  I hate sucking out there.  But from the way I look at it I have no where to go but up in my ability to play the "game".  When I got home I was pretty much on an energy kick.  The first one of the day, which is pretty sad since I had a cup of coffee and  energy boosted smoothie.  I guess sleep is the only way I will gain any energy.  Today at work has been same old same old.  I have yet to virtually make a car, but now that I am thinking of it I will head there right after my blog.  I am on a build your own car kick.  I have pretty much been to every car website and built all the little black cars that you can.  And to think I have to wait until July to buy a car.  I think I am setting myself up for a long few months.  But I will not go test drive cars until June.  That way I will only have a month to wait until I have my new wheels.    I'm not sure if I mentioned that I am probably not going to get a Dodge Dakota.  I am afraid at the current time that it would not be a good idea for me to put my money in a truck.         1)  They are gas hogs       2)  It is more expensive than a car      3)  I have no clue where I am going to be in a few years.  Perhaps in Cali, or Portland, or Seattle, where a truck is just not as handy as a car.        4)  Plus I will just find a guy who has a truck/SUV, therefore desire fulfilled.  So there you go!  Well I will talk to ya later! Tiff :-)  
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        What a beautiful weekend!    It was so great to have a Friday night without having to work.  It has been quiet some time since that has happened for me.  Brooklyn and myself headed down town, and after hopping in and out of three places we had a drink at Catacomes.  While we were there a wedding or birthday party came in.  The crew took over the joint and began ordering drinks like crazy people.  Actually there was one guy who must have ordered 15 drinks while we were there.  We decided that it would be great one day if we would be able to order drinks without thinking how it would put a damper in our budget.  Anywho I had so much fun watching the bartender make drinks.  I'm sure he was getting annoyed that I would constantly ask him what he was making.  And he probably didn't appreciate my comments on his ability to poor the ever so lovely cup of beer.  I think he got more head in the glass than beer.  He needed to slow down and pay attention to what he was doing.  At one point the beer from one glass was all over the floor because it was spilling over so much.  After Catacombs we headed for the BB and it was lame so we decided to head home.  It was quite the night with popping in and out of bars without ordering drinks.  There were a lot of people out and about.  I love this warm weather.    Saturday I spent the morning in the ever so lovely Pineridge.  It was all going well until the boys had to go back to their rooms for high clean.  There was only relief staff working and the other person I was working with did jack shit.  It sucks that I had to handle all the boys by myself especially when I have only been in the apartment three or four times since I have worked there.  Now if it happened in Discovery I would be fine.  Anyways, when I was off I bolted out of there.    On Saturday night we headed down to Far West and listened to the rhythms of Jamaica.  Man it was fun to hear a different style of music.  Not everyone was feeling the island vibe so we headed to the BB.  Where else would we go?  It ended up being a lot of fun.  Singing, dancing and driking.  Good old John got back to town and had some wonderful beads to give all of us.  And get this we didn't even have to flash him for them, holy Moses!  My Sunday was quite laid back and fun.  I went to work at 8:30, which it was really 7:30 due to that stupid Spring ahead.  But it was so nice to have daylight at 7:30 in the afternoon.  Anyways for work I got to take one of the girls to the airport and then a couple of girls to Loretta's football game.  And I got to take the Ford Explorer.  I love that car.  It was the original SUV that I wanted, which transitioned to the Dodge Dakota.  I know the Dakota is a truck not an SUV, but I mean in the ability to move things and eat up gas.  Anyways, then I sun bathed for a few hours, went to some stores, and then headed to the movies with Sean and Brooke.  We watched Taking Lives and it was wonderful.  Sean kept jumping like a scared little school girl, JK, but all in all it was a good movie.  I still have a hard time getting over one part, but I do not want to ruin it for any that haven't seen it.    Now I am sitting at work actually staying busy.  There are a lot of people gone this whole week so the office is quite empty.  I have taken on the responsibility of going through all of the mail, so that eats up a lot of my time.  But I love to open mail and see what is going on.  A lot of money has passed through my fingertips today and yet I am still broke.  Interesting!  Well I hope you have a great day and I will talk to you later.  Tiff-a-Roo!
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       WOWWWWW!!!!!!!!   What a good concert.  I would have easily paid double to see both Damien Rice and the Frames.  Of coarse if I did pay double I would have yelled at the rude people talking throughout the concert and would have had some choice words for the girl who stood in front of me for over one of the songs.  Please I did not come to watch her ass move back and forth.  Seriously my neck started to tense up from my frustration from the girl.  But other than those two misfortunes I was amazed by the music.  So amazed that I bought two CD's this morning.  I purchased Damien's "Woman Like a Man" single and the Frames "Set List" CD.   I know Sean said he was going to buy the Frames but hopefully he will get a different one.  If not it is always fun to have the original.    Man I can't wait for those CD's to come in.  I think my online spending has come to a halt for awhile.  Well at least until my next paycheck.  The bills need to start to become a priority, or else I will not be able to afford my Dodge Dakota.  And it would not be cool if I couldn't get that in July.  Well, I am off to do some more work.  I just had to fill you in on my latest purchases. Tiff ;-)
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, yes I just took another online test.  That is better than spending more money! :-)   Damn, J-Lo! You are...  72% dateable! Attractive and confident, witty and charming, a healthy ambrosia-based diet... you're wanted in the 48 contiguous states, you slayer. Call me. Seduce me. Make me a man. Not only do you know how to turn a guy's engines on, but you also know how to oil, lube and rotate it. You put the "elation" back into "relationship," and the "night" back into "one-night stand."  
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      By the way, it is  April fools day  and I have yet to pull a prank.  Jason is gone for the weekend, maybe I could find something to do to his open room.  Ahh, the wheels are starting to turn in my little head!
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Work is SLOWWWWWW!!!!!!!   Man, being the first of the month I should have a lot to do.  But unfortunately I have gotten all that I can done.  A few people are out of the office so I can not ask them the questions I need answers to.  Plus, everyone other than the annoying secretary and me are out of the office.  So let me give you the run down of my day.  This morning I had two meetings, I processed paperwork, and went to lunch.  Brooke and I had lunch with her mom, and let me tell you she is a crack up.  I swear she is so spastic it is hilarious.  She was telling us about her prison lover, ok she denies that it is her lover.  But when she was in Seattle she had a few dates with him.  They went to the movies, dinner and the park.  All very datish places if you ask me.  No seriously she is hilarious.  Plus she wants to hook Brooke up with a few ex-cons.  So that is always good for a good laugh.  Anyways after lunch, yes I have been back for an hour and a half now, and I have yet to do anything.  I have written this blog, bought some CD's, and contemplated to buy some stuff from the Victoria Secret website.  But my self control finally kicked in and I am done purchasing things for the day.  Praise Jesus I put a stop to that.  Tonight there is a group of us heading to the Damien Rice concert at the Big Easy.  It is a spur of the moment decision to go, but we have been talking about going for some time now.  We might as well go though since it is only around $15 after taxes.  Who can say no to that price.  It should be a pretty low key concert from what I have heard of Damien's.  I like his style though!  I finally said no to a night at Excelsior.  I swear they are calling me every night now to come in.  I do not know what is going on but they have really needed relief lately.  I was in Pineridge last night.  That is the apartment that has been crazy lately and it was actually not that bad.  None of the kids were really going off so that was nice.  There were a lot of kids off structure, but I would rather that then a kid throwing things or getting out of control.    Well I should moves some papers around to make it look like I am working.  Talk to you later! Tiff-a-Roo :-)
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night I went to help my dad move some things around at Aardvarks and then it was off to Sean's house.  I must say I love that pizza.  It was fun to hang out with the gang again.  And Dan was also there, a very nice guy!  Thanks Sean for the dinner!!!  Tonight I am going to go shopping with Mindy and hopefully I will find some nice deals.  I really need to find some more short sleeved work shirts or a pair of Jeans.  To buy means to give.  I have decided that if I am going to buy any more clothes then I have to go through my old clothes and get rid of anything that I really do not wear.  Let me tell you, there is way too much that just sits and gathers dust.  I'm sure that the girls at Excelsior would find a better use of it.  Even if it would mean cutting it up and recreating it.  I have to learn to let go of things.  This weekend it will just be Abigail and myself hanging out at the house.  I picked up a few extra shifts at Excelsior, so it is probably a good thing that Brooke is out of town.  Not that she doesn't end up spending most of her extra time with the Finn, but I like to think she would be lonely without me.    Well, I hope you have a fun weekend!  Tiff :-)
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, not much has been going on with me.  I have all of my laundry done!  And for most that would not be a big accomplishment, but let me tell you it was.  I had four or five loads to do and now my closet and dresser are full.  For awhile there I was wondering why I ever thought I had way to many clothes, I never had anything to wear.  Note to self, all you clothes were dirty.  Go figure!  Other than that all I have done is watch T.V. and help out at my parent's shop.  We are migrating the stuff from the middle section all over to the other side.  And then in a few months we will be moving it all to my parent's garage.  This will be a good thing since my dad's health keeps getting worst.  Plus, it is good to hang out with the family again, I really miss hanging out with my brothers.  Tonight big plans, no strike that no plans.  Ahhhh!!!!!!!!  Talk to you later, Tiff-a-roo :-)
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So here is the run down!   Friday : A lovely shin dig in honor of the ever so lovely Brooklyn.  Spaghetti + alcohol + music + a lot of people = a whole bunch of fun, especially when beeze is in the mix.  After the dinner party ended we headed downtown for the pub club to get our groove on.  Pretty fun, but a little ghetto.   Saturday : Work in the morning with too little sleep, then a quick shower and off to Sarah and Michael's wedding.  It was a very pretty wedding and the reception was fun.  It seemed especially fun after four beers.  Needless to say I got a little out of control and things happened that I wasn't expecting.  All I have to say is that check one has been submitted for the little Brooklyn vs Tiffany summer fun bet.  Bring it on!   Sunday : Work in the morning with way way too little sleep.  Once I finally got home from work I popped on a movie and fell asleep.  Brooke got home and we watch another movie and then I fell asleep.  Humm I am seeing a pattern, my body is telling me I need more sleep.   Monday :  Work at Whitworth, and I am still a tired girl!  Man am I getting old, because if I do not get 8 hours of sleep I am not on the top of my game.  Well that is the weekend review, I hope you had a fun time this last weekend!  Tiff
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Happy Birthday Brooklyn!!!!!  23 and oh so close to 80!!!!!!! :-)&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I have yet to fill you in on my weekend.  It was a quite interesting one at the good old Excelsior.  Friday: Dinner with Brooke, David, Caitlan and her brother.  It was delicious.  Then it was off to Far West and Brooke and I kicked some butt in darts.  I say watch out my gun is going good.  Saturday: Work, which went a few hours long due to some kids going off.  McCayla and Steph were staying at our house, so I went to dinner with them.  Then I watched Gothica, what a movie.  It reminded me of the kids at work, creepy!  Sunday: Work, which again went a few hours long.  A boy decided to lock himself in the cafeteria bathroom and soap up his body.  I wish I could have seen it but since I am not PART trained I am no good in the restraint world.  Monday: Played softball, and it was fun.  A little awkward since Loretta was there.  I swear it isn't even weird when I just see Sara, but at the game with all the people Lo didn't know what to do.  Her fam was there to so that made it a little weird since they still like me.  Oh well!  Work has been busy here at Whitworth but I played around a little on my blog today.  I am starting to really like the way it looks.  Well, I am off work since I came in early today.  Write to ya later.  Bye!  Tiff-a-roo :-)
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Aviators are back BABY!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       TOP TEN THINGS THAT SOUND DIRTY, BUT AT THE OFFICE  AREN'T:    10. I need to whip it out by 5.  9. Mind if I use your laptop.  8. Just stick it in my box.  7. If I have to lick one more, I'll gag!  6. I want it on my desk, NOW!!!!!  5. HMMMMMMMMM, I think it's out of fluid!  4. My equipment is so old, it takes forever to finish.  3. It's an entry level position.  2. When do you think you'll be getting off today?   And the number 1 thing that sounds dirty at the office but isn't:   1. It's not fair. I do all the work while he just sits  there!!!     TOP TEN THINGS THAT SOUND DIRTY, BUT IN LAW AREN'T:    10. Have you looked through her briefs?  9. He is one hard judge!  8. Counselor, let's do it in chambers.  7. Her attorney withdrew at the last minute.  6. Is it a penal offense?  5. Better leave the handcuffs on.  4. For $200 an hour, she better be good!  3. Can you get him to drop his suit?  2. The judge gave her the stiffest one he could.   And the number 1 thing that sounds dirty but in law isn't   1. Think you can get me off?     TOP TEN THINGS THAT SOUND DIRTY BUT IN GOLF AREN'T:    (Scotty you should like these!)  10. Damn, my shaft is bent.  9. After 18 holes, I can barely walk.  8. You really whacked the hell out of that sucker.  7. Look at the size of his putter.  6. Keep your head down and spread your legs a bit more.  5. Mind if I join your threesome?  4. Stand with your back turned and drop it.  3. My hands are so sweaty I can't get a good grip.  2. Nice stroke, but your follow-through leaves a lot to be desired.   And the number 1 thing that sounds dirty but in golf isn't:   1. Hold up! I need to wash my balls first. 
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This website isn't better, just new and fun.  With the blog world taking off I figured I should stay on top of my website.  I will have to mess around with the template when I get some time.  But this will do for now.  I lost all of my links, but I will add them back in the near future.    Let me know how you like my website, now that I have the lovely comment feature on my website.  It only took forever to get it on.  But I figured they would make it easy for me to add that feature.
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Hello    It has been a long two days at work.  But enough about that, lets move on to the weekend update.  Friday: Hmm, not much Brooke bought couches, and then we ate dinner at the ever so posh River Park Square food court.  Ahh, mouth watering.  Then we headed over and hung out with Scotty, Sean and then headed to the BB.  Quite the crazy night at our little bar.  I really do not like it as much when it is so packed out.  Saturday: Worked at Excelsior in the morning, dealing with the girls that came back from the run.  Let me tell you I was glad when I was able to go home.  Then it was off to Sarah Serbell's bridal shower.  Hello pleasure party.  I leaned more about sex toys and lotions than I knew were on the market.   VERY INFORMATIVE !!!  Sunday: Yet again I was at Excelsior.  I had fun though, I like to work upstairs to be with some girls that are a little easier.  Plus I got to work with some fun people, a.k.a. Sean and Josh.  Then I came home, did some errands, watched TV and went to spend some time with my mom.    Not really an eventful weekend, but who says every weekend needs to be action packed.  I will leave most of those fun events for the summer.  Oh yeah, Aaron totally broke his ankle on Sunday night when he was drunk skateboarding.  I feel bad for the boy, but please that was doomed for disaster.  Oh to be young and stupid.  Wait isn't he older than me?   Interesting !
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, the next time I start to complain about not having enough to do at work  SLAP  me!  I have knots galore on my neck from all of the work I have right now.  I swear I could have used some work last week and this week I need more hours to get all the stuff I need to do done.   AHHHHHHHHHH !!!!!  At least it is the weekend and that means I have more time to get things done.  I really do not have any plans this weekend so we will have to see what comes up.  I will fill you in sometime next week.  I still have major deadlines at the beginning but I will try to fill you in.  I hope you have a great weekend! Tiff-a-Roo :-)  Oh, congrats to John for getting the house.  I look forward to spending many a nights helping you clean it up.
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        UPDATE!!!!!!!!    Ahhh, sorry that it has been so long since an update.  Work has been crazy and I have bolted out the door each day.  Anyways on to the update!   Friday : Rehearsal for the wedding and off to Jen's B-day!  All I can say is that I had my doubts that anyone really knew what was going on at the rehearsal.  Everyone showed up late and then it was off to the rents house for dinner.  Man my mom made a mad spread, and I think it helped me gain so much unwanted weight.  Jen's house was fun, but I was drained and called it a night early.   Saturday : I was told by the bride to call her as early as I could, and then come over to her house.  So I got up early and did not sleep in, ahh.  I called her at 9:30 and she said to call her back at 11:30.  Ok, just a few hours, but that wasn't a big deal.  So at 11:30 I call and she tells me to meet her at her parent's house at 1:00.  For the love I could have slept in.  Oh, and I get a call from my brother asking me to bring music to dance to.  Because he is also a procrastinator and left the music gathering to the morning of the wedding.  So after I gather my music I head out of the door at 12:50, then a few minutes later I get a phone call.  Kim told me that she would not be up at her parent's house until 2:30.  What was going on, in my head I didn't think she would make it to the wedding.  I decided to go up there and finally get my makeup on and do my hair.  Screw doing it together.  She finally did show up a little after 2:30.  And it was a mad dash to get her ready and the other bridesmaid with her ready.  Then it was off to the Gathering Place for photos.  Let me tell you why did the pick the hottest day yet to get married.  I was sweating everywhere possible, and my face was shiny in every photo.  Then it was finally time for the wedding.  It went really well, except my brother messing up on his vows.  But it made it really funny!  Supriseingly everything seemed to work its way out.  The reception was great, and I danced for hours.  Surprise, Surprise!!!  We were out of there by 11 and then off to my brothers house.  I called it a night around 1:00 and headed home.   Sunday :  Bloomsday !!!!  So much fun!  John and Brooke ran for a lot of it and that left Jen and I in the back.  We liked to run down the hills and walk the rest.  We did fairly well for walking most of the race.  Finishing with a top qualifying time of 1hour and 49 minutes.  Yeah to us!!!  Then we walked back to Jen's house since we didn't want to park downtown anywhere.  Little did we realize that Bloomsday ran the full length of Broadway and our car was trapped.  We were hungry tired people and still had to walk to get to the ever lovely food at the Elk.  So hi ho we go to browns addition.  John's knee was killing him, and I did something to my arches.  Once we got to the food it was well worth it.  I had the french dip sandwich and it was heavenly.  Well that is the weekend update.  Not much has happened since then.  I have watched T.V., did some shopping, work, and got some chores around the house done.  Oh yeah, Loretta is moving out, surprise that it was Brooke and I two months ago wanting to move out.  Oh how the tables have turned.  Well, I am going home now.  More chores to do and some bill paying.  Write to ya later!  Tiff-a-roo!  
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So this weekend was pretty busy between work and Hoopfest.  But man was it worth it.  Thanks to Sean and all the blisters he gained from going to all the games I wanted to go to, I got to see all the teams that I wanted to.  Saturday was cloudy for most of the day so I didn't burn at all, but Sunday was a different story.  I am as read as a lobster on my shoulders and neck.  Thank goodness that I remembered to use the moisturizer with SPF 30 in it.  All of the boys at Excelsior thought it was the funniest thing that I burnt myself.  And let me tell you they all showed great restraint and did not slap or hurt my burn.  You would think after years of burning myself I would figure out to wear sunscreen all the time.  Not so!  Today work has been the same old same old.  Busy, and having to deal with not know if I will have a job come this Thursday.  Plus, I have to sit here and listen to the secretary set up all the other interviews.  Please, no one else has to deal with this.  I actually talked to JoAnn in our office about it and she said that I should use this as an example for an interview question that they will ask me.  After talking with her I felt much better about the whole situation.  Tonight my softball game is a night game.  I am excited to play on a field with lights.  Perhaps my true skills will finally come out.  Either that or I will not be able to see the ball and make contact.  Either way it will be fun to do something new.  Well, I will tell you how it all goes tomorrow.
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So work has been very CWAZY this week.  All of the contracts are being reviewed and wages figured out.  Pretty much that means there is a butt load of work to be done.  Also, I have been having my position weighing down on me.  I have an interview finally set up for next week, but there are also interviewing three other people.  I am freaking out.  Plus, if they do not offer me the position, there is no way in Hell that I am training my replacement.  I think it is one thing when you are choosing to leave, but if you are being kicked out that is completely different.  Today, the interview questions were on the printer, and you do not know how hard it was to not look at them.  Ok, so hoopfest is this weekend.  My favorite weekend in Spokompton.  And this year I have to work the swing shifts.  Thank goodness I only have to work at 5 each day.  That means I can still catch a lot of B-Ball.  Well I will fill you in on more on Monday.  Talk to ya later!
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well in regards to a car I am leaning towards getting a 2004 GT Toyota Celica.  It will be pretty much the car that is shown below, but the new one.  After looking at rates and talking to my oh so informative friends I have come to the conclusion that it would end up costing about the same for a new one as this one.  In the end I might even come out on top.  And my fingers will be the only ones to drive around the precious beauty.  So now I am going to wait and sell my car next month and try to get at least $2,500 for it.  We will have to wait and see.  That way I can use that as a down payment and talk the dealer down.  I still want it to be pretty much loaded, but do not need the 6th gear for that extra umph.  I can't wait to have a new car.  I think I will go get the door fixed on my car this weekend.  I sure hope it doesn't cost much to fix.  But then again I will feel like an idiot if it doesn't, for I should have gone and got it fixed a lot sooner.  This weekend, just a bit of work and a bit of play.  Almost everyone is out of town this weekend so I will have to be creative.  Sean is taking on the task of teaching me how to drive a stick.  Open parking lots here I come!  Well, I better go, the sun is finally here and I am excited to play in it a bit this weekend.  Bye! TIFF :-)
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Here's my baby!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I haven't had much time to update you lately.  It was good to go out for John's birthday.  I had a lot of fun, and I hope John did too.  Karen was in town and it was great to hang out with her again.  On Saturday Karen, Brooke and I went and test drove cars.  It is official, I am in love with the Toyota Celica.  I have been searching the internet for this car and I found the one I want just outside of Portland.  I wish I knew if I was getting this HR job for sure.  I got in trouble today for coming to work late, so who knows.  Maybe that was God's way of keeping me from jumping into buying a car until I know that I will have the funds.  But let me tell you as soon as I have this job securely then I will be purchasing my new vehicle.  I still have to see how much more insurance would be on my new little sports car, but I'm sure it can't be all that much more a month.  What is another $30 or $40, when you get better gas mileage and you are in a great car.  Anyhow, I spent the rest of the weekend working.  All was going good until last night when one of the boys decided to throw Ranch dressing all over the kitchen and sprayed water everywhere.  Ah, good times courtesy of Excelsior!  Well, I am off tonight to do some damage at Northtown.  There are some good sales, and it is payday.  Don't worry, the car is in the back of my mind so I will hold myself back a bit.  Hope you have a great night, bye!  :-)
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I can't believe our little friend John is having a birthday today.  John are you sure you weren't hatched?  Either way I guess we can still celebrate the day you came into the world.  I hope you have a wonderful night!  Today has been another oh so fun day at the office, strike that it has been a crazy not so fun day.  Poor Brooklyn is sick, I sure hope she starts to feel better soon.  Karen is in town, so it is going to be good to see her again.  It has been awhile since I got to see that girl.  Well that is about it, let's get the show on the road.  I can not wait for the weekend.  Wait strike that again, I really do not want to have to work at Excelsior this weekend.  Friends in town, and plus it was so nice to have a few days off last weekend. Perhaps I will let Excelsior know that I want to take most of the summer off.  That way when the weather starts to get bad again I can fill up my time.  We will see.  Well Talk to you later!  Hope you have a good weekend! Love- Tiff
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So we all know that I have a lot of patients, but I am on my last straw.  Today I had visions of yelling at Judy across the way and throwing her plant off the counter.  I can't take any fucking more.  I will probably hear it soon that I am rolling my eyes all the time.  My radio doesn't even have the ability to drown her out.  Ok, with that said I am going home for the day.  It has been the longest day today.  I have been entering data all day at lightning speeds to make up for taking two days off.  Payroll needs it all to be entered and there is just not enough time to do it.  It was fun last night at Sean and John's house.  Eating delicious chicken tacos and drinking Korona's.  Yummy was the name of the night.  Well I am out, talk to you later!!!!!!!!
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So here is the trip rundown:  Vacation had a slight delay and I did not get out of town until Friday.  So I spent much of the day Thursday preparing my car for the drive over to Bozeman and then I got a lovely call from Papa saying he would like to join me.    So we were finally on the road at 1:30.  Scotty would like to blame me for the long delay in our taking off but do not let him fool you, he had a part in it.  The road over was dry, and filled with road construction.  I swear there was three times as much road cut down to one lane than they were actually working on.  Whatever, we made pretty good time and finally arrived around 8:00.  It took awhile because some people can not count lights and we got a little off our route.  When we got to Sean's house his parent's prepared a lovely steak dinner that was delicious.  I was stuffed and that lead to a hard time getting drunk.  We first headed to the Bermuda to get drinks.  When we ordered our first round we got about five drinks.  I was prepared to hear a cost near 20 dollars.  Much to my surprise it came up to 12 dollars.  Scotty's and my mouths dropped open at the sound of the price.  Most of the bars in Bozeman have these cheap prices.  I swear I am not telling a lie.  I must say that the Molly is my favorite of the three bars.  Then it was off to a few more bars in downtown Bozeman.  Same great prices, and each place with its own unique atmosphere.  After we put back a few drinks, keep in mind I have had two sipper drinks, four shots, and a Yager Bomb.  Still not feeling very drunk, much brought on by the hefty meal.  Then we were on our way to the KO aka Meat Market USA.  We wanted to get our groove on and so we did.  I put back two more drinks and had a few shots when the train song came on.  Get this for the whole song the waitresses poured drinks in your mouth for free.  We bumped and grinded until closing and then headed home.  We started the next day with wonderful bagels and then headed to see the horses.  Ahh, I love horses so much and can not wait to own some of my own.  Then we went up to ?Highlight? to go see a waterfall.  The altitude was killing some of the hikers, but I will not name names.  I was a little winded myself.  It was beautiful, but I was bummed when my camera would not work.  Then we headed back to the house to take a nap and ended up watching the Last Samurai.  After the movie ended we headed down for some beers on the roof of a bar I can not remember the name of.  But it was fun and we all decided that Spokane definitely needs one.  I was starving and we finally caught up with DJ at the restaurant to have dinner.  There was almost 20 people there for dinner and I did not want to repeat the big meal from the previous night.  But you know how it is when the baskets of chips keep coming and you are starving.  Then your food finally arrives and what are you going to do, you must eat it.  Then it was off to go listen to DJ's band, and man are they good.  I love it all night long, the songs kept coming.  We ended up drinking a bit more, and had fun.  The best part of the night was when Casey was completely drunk and doing all kinds of crazy things.  Such as peeing in the road and then the biker cops came by.  Somehow he managed to sneak that by.  We ended up heading home before closing but it was a fun filled night.  Before bed the boys decided to have some fun and we watched Reno Cops.  That show cracks me up.  The next day we had a wonderful breakfast provided by Mama O'Conner and then we packed our things.  We didn't get out of the house until one due to Sean O loosing his checkbook.  Good times!  Then we had a little pizza lunch that was great and we were out of town.    It was so much fun to meet all of Sean's friends and see his town.  I do not think I would have the stamina to live in that town and keep up with the night life.  It would be fun for a summer though.  We made it back to town in five hours, and Bubbles (Sean's new car) made it just fine.  Do not let Sean fool you on the name, he loves it and wishes he came up with it himself.  Oh yes he might give it some other nicknames.  But nothing will outlast her first name.  Well there you go, a breakdown of the trip!  It was so good to get out of town, and then I was hit with the reality of work.  Ah, the real world.  Talk to you later!
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        It's FRIDAY!!!!!!!!!    Well at least it is in my working world.  Tonight I must pack for the first vacation that I have taken in almost a year.  The last time I got out of Spokane was when I was heading to Breacta's wedding and ended up having to come back to Spokompton due to a car wreck.  With the passes being clear, hopefully, we should be able to dodge this fate.  We will have to wait and see if any bad memories pop up when we drive past that point on our little road trip.  I am so looking forward to some days off without any work.  I swear I need it and can not wait to get this show on the road.  The weekend plans go as follows: Thursday night - getting lost in the Bermuda Triangle (three bars that share a parking lot); Friday - horseback riding; Saturday - BBQ and watching DJ's band; Sunday - coming home.  There you go, pretty much we have a lot of time to just see what life in Bozeman is like.    Well, I will let you know how the weekend goes when I get back.  This was probably the worse weekend to go due to the fact that my little brother is graduating from high school on Friday, and there is a wedding this weekend that I should be going to.  But I am going gosh dangit!  Hope your weekend is fun and I will talk to you later.  Tiff-A-Roo :-)
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The word "work" and "movies" pretty much sums up my weekend.  I worked a split shift on Saturday, a morning to 1 shift on Sunday and a 8 to 5 shift on Monday.  Let me tell you I am pooped after my weekend.  All was going well until Monday came along.  The boys were little shits and pretty much made my work day a living hell.  Just because I am a relief staff must mean I do not know what the hell I am doing, well according to the boys anyways.  I was happy as a clam when I was able to get out of there only 15 minutes late.  It could have been way worse!  At home the only thing I wanted to do all weekend was watch T.V. and movies.  I ended up buying a few flicks this weekend and a new romance novel.  But here is the kicker, the book is from a guys perspective and written by a guy.  I have been wanting to read something that dove into the male mind and the world of love and romance.  Pretty much guys are confusing and I do not understand them.  One would think since I have three brothers I would have the upper hand.  As far as I can see the major influence this has played on my life is the fact that I am not a typical emotional girl.  I pretty much take life as it comes and do not have many highs and lows.  But having three brother has shown me that guys are just as complicated and unique as girls.  In the words of Emma " what is the point in me being three and twenty and still so much to learn "?  Well, I hope your weekend went well and I will talk to you later!  Tiff!!!
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           Since blog has changed their posting abilities my scripts are all out of wack.&nbsp; I will have to mess around with it when I get some extra time next week.   This weekend I was pretty much sick the whole time.&nbsp; Let me tell you it is not fun to have a fever, especially when it is near 100 degrees outside.&nbsp; I didn't even make it in to work on Monday because I felt like crap.&nbsp; Though I found enough energy to play the last softball game of the season.&nbsp; But no one wanted to talk to me since I had no clue what kind of a bug I was carrying.   Tuesday at work I was confronted by my coworkers and they finally got me to go see the doc.&nbsp; No I did not have strep, but some virus.&nbsp; I hate viruses, but after work I started to feel a bit better.&nbsp; The best I have felt in almost a week.   Today I have been entering all the pay increases for the upcoming year.&nbsp; Let me tell you my eyes are going crazy from all the different screens I have to check.   Well I am off, I will fill you in more when I have a few minutes to blog.&nbsp; I've got to get home and get out of this place!!!&nbsp; I KNOW!!!!!!!!!                
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
            So as you can guess I didn't win the Sarah tickets.&nbsp; But if you never try you will never win any thing.&nbsp;     &nbsp;   Other hightlights: I still  LOVE  my car!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!     &nbsp;   Tonight Brooke, John, Jen and I are all going kayaking.&nbsp; Sadly Sean is out of town, but he was able to go home to Bozeman.&nbsp; I guess that is a good excuse to not be here with us.&nbsp;     Other weekend plans: work.&nbsp; That is about it, and to hopefully not melt away from the heat.&nbsp; Which as John put it so elegantly last night "we looked like cancer patients".&nbsp; So our house is pretty damn hot.&nbsp; Oh yeah we forgot that we have AC, but we really do not want pay for it.     &nbsp;   Well I hope you have a great weekend!&nbsp; I will fill you in next week.&nbsp; Bye Tiff! :-)                 
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So today on the radio it was announced that I won free ice cream from 103.1 KCDA.  I signed up for this contest a few months ago, and they actually drew my name.  So today around 11:45 the ice cream team brought about 30 or 40 Dove ice cream bars.  I always sign up for contest, but I hardly ever win anything.  I guess that I am now qualified for the free trip to go see Sarah McLachlan in Philly.  It would be sweet to win that trip.  Plus I have been wanting to see Sarah in concert for a while now.  Here's to hoping!
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Our BBQ was a success!  There was a bit of drinking, a bit of eating, and a lovely amount of dancing.  Then it was off to Downtown, but we just weren't feeling the Pub Club.  Scotty wasn't feeling the ride down, and ended up decorating the inside of Brooklyn's car.  Not a pretty site.  We headed home shortly after arrival and after partaking in some grub at the ?Blue Satalite?  The next morning I could not sleep in, big surprise, not really!  I cleaned up after the party, because our house was trashed.  And then I washed my lovely new car.  Ahh, it is so pretty when it is all cleaned up.  Then I was off to work until 11:00.  Then on Sunday I got up early and went to work.  After I got off work I made my last trip to the dealership, and hung out with my fam.  I went to see The Anchorman with my brothers.  My movie review is two thumbs up.  I was laughing the whole time.  I would and will probably go see it again.    Well there you go, you are probably mad that you were holding off for that review.  Not a very eventful weekend.  But then again that is just assuming someone reads my blog.  Peace! Tiff-a-roo!!! :-)
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So here are the rules for the ever so popular game of Shotgun.  Who knew that there is a website with the rules and amendments.  Here you go!  http://shotgunguide.com/  I'll fill you in on my weekend adventures later!  Stay tuned.
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ahh, I finally have a hair appointment tonight.  I am so excited to get rid of the shaggy mop on my head, and get some shape back.  After my haircut I am going to run home to our little BBQ party.  I love to hang out with people, especially a BBQ in the summer.  I have no clue how many people are coming to his little shin dig, but it could be a lot and it could be a few.  Only time will tell.  I'll fill you in on the weekend festivities on Monday.  Hope you have a great weekend! Tiff :-)
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Coming soon to a neighborhood near you.  Would you use it?&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This very well could be the best music video ever produced.  Check it out!  Make sure to watch it all the way through, it gets Crazy in the end.  http://www.hellonetwork.com/demo/toysclub/video.asp?speed=hook300  Let me know your feelings towards the vid!
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes everyone I have finally taken the plunge and bought a new car.  It was so much fun, lots of paperwork, and two hours at the dealership but I finally had the car that I have wanted for months.  I didn't end up getting the silver car.  But I think I like this color even more than a silver.  I will have to get Brooke to take a picture that way I can get it on my website.  It is a 2002 Toyota Celica and it is Midnight Blue.  When you look at it you would think it was black.  But it isn't, in just the right light you can see that it is in fact blue.  It is so fun to have a new car!  I still do not feel like it is really mine.  But my little Baby Blue grandma car is no where to be found.  I actually have to run out to the dealership to swap out my CD player with the original cassette player that was in my car.  I must say that if you are looking to purchase a car I would go with Parker Toyota.  They are a great dealership!  Plus if you get a car with them I will get a $200 bonus.  Just a little incentive if you are thinking about buying a car.  So pretty much that was the highlight of my weekend.  I did not work at Excelsior and it was wonderful.  I had a whole three day weekend and did not have any thing I had to get done, but accomplished a lot of errands that I haven't had time to do.  I went out to Liberty Lake with Brooke and that was pretty fun.  The fireworks were nice, though Brooke didn't see any of them.  A waste of a 4th of July if you ask me, some stupid bet.  Yes yes that is how I feel since I thought that I had this one in the bag.  Well, back to work.  Oh yeah, I got offered the job at Whitworth and they are paying me what I wanted and then some.  It has been a great couple of days.  Now I just have to find a place to live after next month and I will be set.  I think I am leaning towards a Studio apt. Downtown.  That way I can keep my monthly payments low.  Especially since I now have this car payment to make.  Ok, I will fill you in on more when I have more to tell.  Oh one more thing about the car it is a stick.  So 1st is a little sticky, but it is getting better.  :-) Tiff
    
</post>


</Blog>