<Blog>

<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I wonder if most epiphanies occur in the restroom.  Strange thing to say really, but this whole day has been out of routine.  I’m a bit baffled as to where Fen the independent girl went and why I’m left questioning so much.  I mean, I realize what caused all this and it’s not a bad thing really, it’s just strange.  This all may sound strange, I may just be going crazy but today I haven’t felt myself.  I’ve watched the phone ring repeatedly but have found no reason to answer it. This is not to say that I didn’t know who was on the other line and what the call was for, I knew all of that but chose not to pick it up.  Rather I watched it, watched it ring, watched the icon on the phone blink in a fast flashing black arrow and the usual annoying tone that it makes.  All I could think of was what’s going on with me.    THE AFTERNOON:  I’m writing in hopes that it will alleviate some uncertain feelings that I’m having.  There are many paths that I’m working on navigating back to.  Such as independence vs. relationship.  It never occurred to me that both can be balanced, and with my recent realization that my SO may not be here  in the next year or so, I’m learning to balance my independence with our relationship, something that may not have occurred to me before.    In learning of my soon to be or so feels like it, departure of my so, I wondered all the things that staying in the relationship could bring and then I pondered the negatives.  For example, when you both are faced with the realization that it is really over.  My friends have provided a wealth of opinions as to what I should do, and though I value their opinions greatly, I did end up doing what I believe is best for me.  A friend said that, I should live for now, because you can never know what will happen in the future.  To just enjoy the relationship and not let the uncertainties of tomorrow cause any ill feelings or cautions in how I am. I think her advise has carried over these last few days.    I’ve taken a few steps of my own to put myself back on the path, which I veered from months back and am looking yet again to where my next chapter in life will begin.  I love this city and the people I’ve met here and I have no doubt we will continue to stay in touch and hold onto the bond that only friendships and family can, but I need to plan for something better.  I’ve always known that, and I’d like to think that maybe this is god’s way of saying that there are better things to come.    Patience is a virtue.   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      TGIF!!! I'm in such pain, from god knows what...Actually I do know. I've spent the last few days back into my usual Yoga routine and my body is in pain.  Who would think that an hour and a half session of stretching would cause unbearable pain.  I will not give in though, I'm heading yet again today to yoga class as usual.  Let the pain continue, at least my mental state will be at peace.  On to other things...My friends are going through so much right now, it's just incredible.  One is venturing back into the life of singlesville and the other is beginning another chapter in her life with her job, the other who has been single for a few months is dating again and the one who is my mirror image in terms of relationships is in a serious relationship now, and me?  I'm rethinking many things.   It's just strange how you move in all these directions and eventually you have to stop and take a moment to ponder if that's the direction you want to go in.  I spent several years of my life knowing the direction I wanted to be in but having it shattered in an instant.  I eventually managed to build the strength within myself to get up and do it yet again, with a different plan in mind, but the plan was interrupted.  In a good way, I guess one could say.  Now I'm fully aware of the direction I'm leading myself into, fully aware and as prepared as I can be.  Life is funny like that I guess.  I'm hopeful of many things though and realize that life has its ups and downs.    Perhaps the coffee, loads of sugar and tea are getting the best of me.  Anyhow, nothing can really upset me today.  I have an unusual feeling of peace within myself now-a-days.  Perhaps it is the yoga :)
     

    
</post>

<date>09,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm three classes from graduation and feeling the anticipation of what's to come.  The last several months has felt like both a strike of luck and a disappointment.  My friends are traveling down their paths as I am going down mine and it appears that at some point, you hit a wall.  I realize this makes absolutely no sense but I think to the very few of you who understand, I hope you found a way out.  I think with time and much contemplation I'll find my way out of where I am.  I can however be very thankful that life has brought me to this point and that the next chapter in my life will be held with great anticipation.    We shall see...
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It has been an amazing week. It didn't occur to me that my blogger account was still active, but I've got so much to say that I think now is the time to start keeping my thoughts recorded. My week has been unbelievable. I spent the early part of last week at a photo shoot. The photographer is awesome. Without making me looking unlike myself he took some very good photos. With that said, I'm coming out of my shell and will be auditioning within the month for a a few bit parts. We shall see...Wish me luck :)  Other than that, my friends threw me an amazing surprise birthday party at one of my most favorite restaurants, 67 at the Edgewater. My boyfriend was in the loop on it the whole time and I had no clue!  Then as my week ended, my sweetie took me to LA for a birthday getaway. We spent three nights at a trendy LA hotel, toured the walk of fame, and made a trip to Disneyland. He doesn't know how much that trip meant to me, but I felt for once in my life that everything was perfect.  So I dedicate this most amazing week to P. Nick. Love you much my teddy bear. 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    This photo was taken from a photoshoot take in early August.  Enjoy!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>