<Blog>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This "Pardon Me" lyric speaks my thoughts...     So pardon me while I burst into flames I've had enough of the world  And it's people's mindless games So pardon me while I burn  And rise above the flame Pardon me, pardon me I'll never be the same  
    
    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today marks the THIRD time I left my handphone at home as I rush to work this morning. Is age and forgetfulness creeping up with me or is it pure clumsiness? Or is it coz I just have too many things on my mind that I'm losing memory space to include the usual wake up routine: bathe, dress up, put make up on, blow dry hair, take your hand bag, laptop, handphone, and car keys, kiss Angel & Daisy, start the engine and off to work.... could it be due to the cigarettes I've been smoking all these years? Or can I conclude that, there it is again, one of those days when "shit happens".   I'm having a new theory that was inspired by my friend the SECOND time I left my handphone at home... My handphone's no longer a priority to me.... No more I come up with a statement "gosh, cant live without my mobile, cant imagine a life without it in the first place" I'm beginning to feel I CAN live a normal life without it... Without people calling me and bugging me... Without my mom checking on my whereabouts... Without my friends calling me out for lunch... Without stupid tele-sales marketer calling me up to annoy me with their much wasteful services. My mobile is no longer my pride and joy which it used to be... It's just another device to reach other homosapiens....Or for others to reach me...Be it a call or SMS or MMS. I do admit one thing for sure... With the existence of my mobile since I was 18, I haven't remembered any of my friends or families phone numbers! So surely this has emptied some memory space in my brain.... Therefore, I'm sure I have a little space in my mature brain to remember my handphone with that normal wake-up routine I've setup.   Perhaps it is true that my handphone IS no longer my priority... Come with the subsequent curiosity, what happened? What changed and made my mobile no longer a priority? Has my life changed so much that I don't need to keep constant contact with other homosapiens and do not mind not being able to contact friends and families? I don't use the office phone for personal calls for sure.... No one calls me thru my office phone as well.... Except for Citibank... Even my boss gets me thru my mobile!   Sheeeshh.... Hopefully by end of the week I can figure this thing out... Right now, other priority awaits... Incubus concert!! Gosh.. I cant believe they're coming here to perform!! Cant wait to go to the concert tonite...Wait for my review on it tomorrow! Now if only I can figure out how to call my "twin" to confirm the time to meet up and go for the concert... 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       DC played this song over and over again in the car when we went out the other day... the day I told him I want this to officially end, before I get hurt really bad... Before things get worst than it already is... I cant believe that once again I'm at the happiest moment of my life, having the chance to meet someone so special like DC and yet I'm just filled with sadness and hurting deep inside knowing that he'll never be mine...  I found this article on Soul Mates...I'm pondering upon this paragraph:  Remember that every relationship we share is a way for us to become enlightened. They come to us to teach and help us remember that God has sent us only angels.      If I Ain't Got You - Alicia Keys-   Some people live for the fortune, Some people live just for the fame Some people live for the power yeah, Some people live just to play the game Some people think that the physical things, Define what's within I've been there before, but that life's a bore so full of the superficial  Some people want it all But I don't want nothing at all If it ain't you baby If I ain't got you baby Some people want diamond rings  Some just want everything But everything means nothing  If I ain't got you...yeah  Some people search for a fountain, Promises forever young  Some people need three dozen roses, And that's the only way to prove you love them  And in a world on a silver platter, And wondering what it means No one to share, No one who truly cares for me  If I ain't got you with me baby Nothing in this whole wide world don't mean a thing If I ain't got you with me baby 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I've met someone... someone who is just amazing! If things didn't happened the way God intended it to be.. I wouldn't have met this special someone at all! And the miracle happened just as I was thinking of making some major changes in my life...  The Sabah trip was a VERY much needed break for me.. I was given 2 weeks to work in Sabah, a place I've never been to before. I planned that this trip was a great get-a-way for me to decide on certain things in my life, which I didn't had the chance to think about before due to my workload.   Here are the list of things I want to change in my life before 2005:-  1. Quit smoking - eventually, one step at a time I guess.. 2. Cut off contact with stupid jerks - Toy-Boy, Asshole & Naim (my ex) 3. Get over my ex...Focus on my career more than my love life 4. No more "PMS"  Now these might sound easy to achieve if I put all my heart and determination into it, but knowing ME....I'm quite fragile, easily influenced by my evil, negative surroundings and I can be very indecisive... It makes those things unachievable eventually. And so I'm keeping these things in mind and if I can change 3 out of 4 items, that's an accomplishment!:)  Funny how life works... Here I am trying my hardest to rectify my flaws and the negative things in my life... Making things work better for me, be happier and more content... Just as i got things figured out, comes BIGGER challenges...one after another!!!   Let's glance through my complicated love life for the past 7 years. I only started liking someone really bad, as in having a HUGE crush, back in high school. I was never "inlove" with anyone then... unlike many of my gurl frens. When I turned 19, I met my first boyfriend, but things didnt work out between us (he just disappeared) and i figured i shouldnt be wasting time looking for love. The only thing on my mind at that time was to be the top student and get into university. As i went to uni, i met my soulmate, RT. I knew he was my soulmate because, heck, he's the only person in this lifetime who can read me and have 'magical moments' happening between us everytime we're together! Fact is, he felt the same sparks as i did. BUT ofcourse, he was attached, i was just another temporary game. I loved him dearly, though things we're not meant to be between us, as my heart aches everytime he's with someone else, I believe i've loved him and i felt the real thing called love. It was pure love, nothing physical, just pure emotions...and i missed that...the emotional rush.  As time passed by, after 3 rebound relationships to replace RT, i concluded and made a public announcement to my friends that i could never find anyone else like RT. Until the day i met DC at KK airport... It all happened by chance. I felt a connection with DC, things I only felt 5 years ago with RT.   THE PROBLEM: Five bloody boring years to actually find someone by chance and then KNOWING that he's everything you've been asking for from God... But unfortunately he belongs to someone else. Damn... Blessed and cursed at the same time.. How F**Ked up is that?!!   Seriously, this shitty feeling of meeting someone so amazing and knowing the existing of chemistry but WITH restriction is just DEJA VU! Why cant things just work out for me.. For once at least. I just cant figure this out anymore... Keep meeting someone SO right but the situation SO WRONG.... Please God.. I'm not asking much... Just someone to love...Someone that's mine...  And so.. The story of my NEW adventure begins with DC... How bad is this "new, unlisted" change in my life you're wondering?? Trust me... It's the worst ever! But for sure, with this change, I've managed to eliminate item no. 2 :)  Honestly, I just don't know how long this one's gonna last. I don't know how far this relationship/affair/game is gonna go. DC tells me  "I'm not gonna end this... Only 2 things that will end this thing we have... One is when you get married... Two is only if you want me to go"    I told him the two things aren't gonna happen... Or will it ever?  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Whoaaa... Soooo many things have happened in my life during the past TWO months!!! My Goshh.. how time flies!! I've got tonnes of NEW happenings around me since i last updated this site! To summarize, here's a list of the NEW, wonderful, most memorable things that happened in such a short time frame up till today:-  1.  4 days trip to Salang, Tioman with Nabilah - a whole NEW adventure by itself! 2.  Road Tax & Insurance renewal - got myself a NEW Insurance Company. 3.  Primary school reunion at DU!! My goshh... 14 years we haven't seen each other!! 4.  My brother's wedding...Got a NEW member in the family - a lovely sister in-law! 5.  My Project Implementation Track 2A went LIVE - New SAP system for the live companies! 6.  A Go-Live celebration at A'Famosa, Melaka for the project team!! 7.  13 days trip to Sabah for system support - Unbelievably FUNTASTIC! 8.  A NEW project implementation Track 2 - same system but a new team, new users. 9.  My Car temperature rose!! New important stuff to take note of, ALWAYS! 10. My grandma admitted to hospital for 5 days...   Seriously, looking at this list, i'm surprised i can even find time to digest everything in one go!   Trip to Tioman left me with bitter sweet memories... I managed to do my Intro Scuba Dive, got to catch up with Nabilah, got to a new theory "that one must differentiate between LUST and "CASE" and that a person who talks bad about others might NEVER realize that he himself is the WORST being itself"... and the existing theory: "If you are a wonderful person, you will bound to meet and attract more wonderful people" is SO TRUE!  Road Tax & Insurance renewal... doing it all by myself wihtout troubling my dad has added more boost to my sense of independence. Many thanx to my aunt & uncle for guiding me on handling this yearly chore. Now i'm left to properly organize my important documents, piling up fast on my study desk in the room...  Primary School Reunion... was just AWESOME!! It was just exciting and overwhelming to meet up with old classmates that i havent seen in YEARS!! Turns out the gurls are looking more and more babelicious compared to the men....why am i not surprised..hahaha! Met my first ever ex-best friend, Zanne... cant believe some things never change. I had the courage to chat up with an old crush, finally...tho he dont seem that impressive no more...must have been out of my mind to have had a crush on him 14 years ago...kids!!  Brother's Wedding day!  A memorable day indeed... i hope they live hapily ever after.  Hahh.. this is tiring.. i'll just summ up everything else lah since there's just too much to write with so little time and patience on my side. As my project went live on 12th April, everything was fun fun fun for a month! The celebration in Melaka was outtathisworld, stayed in bungalow with the AJKs, cowboy line dancing, paintball combat and karaoke, wic i never knew i had the guts to do..with my ED too!! Then the trip to Sabah... sighh.. i'll dedicate a column just for Sabah tomorrow...one word, AMAZING.  So right up to now, i'm a concentrating on my new project Track 2 and so far it's just time consuming. Not that i mind, it's even greater after the wonderful changes that came after the Sabah trip...i've got myself a NEW distraction... :)  And here's to the NEW ME: as of today, I QUIT SMOKING...looking forward to healthier lifestyle... CHEERS! 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I went out for dinner with my ex-colleague last night. He told me before he had some personal life problems and I was the only one who could understand the situation... Because it involved a "soulmate".  And yes, anything to do with soulmate, I am THE person to talk to about. And so after catching up with our working life and achievements... We went straight to his problem. His soulmate problem wasn't as bad as I thought.. Just needed someone to tell him to not be a bad person by being selfish, but to look at the other person's perspective and think about her feelings as well.  A lot of men tend to forget and be very selfish... It's all about what he wants, what he feels and what he expects out of a gurl. Apparently too, there are some goody-two-shoes men out there that have this burning desire to be a devil for a day or a night and go for a kinky one-night stand to let of his steam. If this person wasn't my friend, I'd straight tell to his face "Go jerk off somewhere u fucked up bastard" But since he was a dear friend and looked like he needed help... I gave him a point to ponder and think for himself.  By the time we all reach a mature age, say 25 plus (this does unfortunately vary depending on a person's intellectual level), we should be able to differentiate things in our life, the rights and the wrongs, the good and the bad...We made a good point last night that we are  UNIQUE  people, due to our balanced values and mixed upbringing (me being 1/4 Pakistani, not any typical Malay family, and him not from any typical Chinese family).  But somehow, with that perception, I just CANT quite comprehend why he wanted to be that devil. It's only fair to let out your "steam" to someone who deserves it and not just find a nice innocent gurl (or a friend for that matter!) to let it off .. just because you are having the burning desire or urge to do so.    Come on, how selfish is that??  Logically, why would you want to have sex with someone you dont love? Too much PORN maybe? I dont understand... dont think ill EVER understand!  What if someone does the same to someone very dear to you... Your partner? Or your sister? Unfair isn't it? Seriously, I don't know why people have less compassion for others like I do. I guess I learn that from RT.  He used to tell me this and I treasure it for life:  "If some one truly loves you, he wouldn't hurt you or treat you like trash or even use you. Those who do, must get rid of them. He who loves you will only want what is best FOR you."   Sigh... I wish RT and I got married and lived happily ever after.  I probably wouldn't have to go through life with these issues so much. Oh well, since I am a good-hearted person, I'm just happy for RT's current girlfriend. I hope she treats him as nice as he is and I wish them well. Anyways, back to my friend's problem... I just told him not to be selfish and must think of the consequences of your temporary desires. Bad things and bad intentions always comes back with bad consequences.  It's just pure LOGIC. And you know how we ended the day? Before we left he said "I'm still up for the kiss you told me...anytime."  OKAYYY.. That was just too much! Fine, I did say I fancied him the last time we were working together. I WAS ON A REBOUND! And I SOOO know he wanted to take advantage of my fragile phase. The nerve of a man!! I truly endure our friendship and wouldn't want anything physical to ruin it, but I just cant believe some men who ARE friends would think of such things of ME! It's just disappointing! And heck, I told him I wouldn't go all the way with him, ever, because he's got a wonderful girlfriend and I was on a rebound and we're not from the same religion. And I told him that maybe I'd kiss him but it probably wont mean anything because I'm not in love... Meaningless just like Mint and my ex. But of course... how silly of me, he wouldn't mind!  See here's the thing. How can men out there treat women like me... Like trash. Gurls like me have our values, are worth the respect and just coz we look hot and sexy doesn't mean we are CHEAP and EASY. We look good on the outside coz we ARE great on the inside, and just because I don't wear a   tudung   doesn't mean I'm sleeping with everyone I meet. To these men with such narrow mindset, unlike tudung gurls who potray innocence, I somehow potray a social lifestyle, like pre-marital sex is OK.  How narrow minded can a person get?   Why do men have to generalize me based on the outside?! It's very disturbing and upsetting for sure. This is why I want things to end between me and DC...Apart from the relationship not being right and all. I don't know for sure if he's not trying hard to get in my pants and that's all he wants from me because most men are like that.   And that is why I told DC:  don't mind me if I generalize men for being pricks and bastards because I've met more than one who treat me like dirt because you men generalize women like me based on our appearance. And I don't even generalize men based on appearance!"   It's sad that it's really hard to find good-hearted Malay men for keeps these days. And I haven't even narrowed down this topic to the aspect of religion itself! My colleague mentioned this morning that I should go find a matsalleh (foreigner) who would understand my perspective and who is not so narrow minded like the Malay men.  If only finding THE ONE is  as easy as buying a new CD for keeps at Tower Records... Worth the effort and money too.  Anyways, I guess meeting up with weirdos and psycho men taught me one too many lessons on narrowing the criteria I want in my life partner. I'm gonna go home now and do just that list. Here's my theory for the day:   "Too many people care more about always doing things the right WAY, rather than doing the right THING."   So yes, I shall do the RIGHT things very much soon to re-organize my life into a much, much better one. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Gosh... Work has been pretty hectic these few days. Finally I got the time to blog my thoughts.  Let see... I had a fantastic weekend!!! Managed to go out with my uni buddies to OU on Saturday afternoon for late lunch at this superb laksa restaurant!! I love the Laksa Johor!!! Had a wonderful conversation with my girlfriends about my problem with DC... I didn't expect the warm logical advises really but I guess being close friends and caring ones too, they saw that I needed some help on trying to figure things out. Perhaps my misery was pretty obvious that afternoon since I was feeling kinda down when I saw the surroundings at the mall before I met them. I poured my thoughts and along our conversation, I somehow regained my confidence to tell DC that it is over between us... That this has got to stop.  Later, I accompanied my mum to catch the movie 'Days after tomorrow' wic wasn't all that good la... I think Armageddon had better script and drama compared to this one... Quite lame actually. But since I had so little sleep the night before and after falling asleep a few times during the movie, I had to disappoint my mum by not being too enthusiastic about having dinner with her. I guess it wasn't right of me to make face and wanting so much to go home and hit the bed since (Monday was just a few hours away!) What came to my conscious mind was that I wanted some things to go my way... And if my mum wasn't happy with that, she has to just accept the fact that  I  wanted to go home since I was very much tired and it is  what I wanted ... afterall, I have been tolerating the things SHE wanted...Like me accompanying her to the movie and last week's Shrek 2.  So yeah.. tha's when I thought.. Actually been thinking a lot about it since last week la... I've been getting feedbacks from friends, colleagues, and my readings that I've got to set some things in my life and identify the  THINGS I WANT IN MY LIFE... The things I want to achieve in my career...The criteria I want in my life partner...The things I want in a relationship with friends, with my life partner, with my family... The things I want for myself, physically and spiritually.  And then my friend suggested I try this horoscope website and this is the most outstanding remark for my Personal Horoscope:  Give yourself an edge by clearly defining what you want and going for it.  You have to live your dream, you cant just dream your dream.   - How coincidental is this??!!! -  It's not very easy to clearly define the things that I want. Just last week I did the list of the things I wanted to change and so far... I still haven't changed any one of it....Bummer!  I guess it's not an overnight change, dats why I gave myself till end of this year.  but seriously, at this point of my life, I'd like to focus on things I want for me and my life more than what others want.  I've been pleasing my parents and giving them what they wanted out of me since I was born! Leeysha the obedient child, studied hard to get good grades, make my parents proud by being top student, get my degree in uni, get a good job. Never once did they cared to ask me what I wanted. I guess even if they did, I don't think I can tell straight-out what I wanted because I'll just pretend that I don't know what I want and suggest things that they would want me to be or have so that they would be happy and proud parents.  Is it coz I'm just not selfish? Keep putting others first? Why is it so hard for me to come out with the things I want for ME? I'm gonna be on leave tomorrow and I think I'm gonna have that list out by then.   Here's a great advise I got from the net this morning at  urlLink MSN Women:    Realize the worth of logic. Dare to reduce your problem to the simple elements of an equation. See it for what it is: a problem, and your objective is to resolve it.  Remove the hostage from the equation. It is simple logic. Now all you have to do, is to DO it.   Anyways, DC called Sunday night when I made my mind up... I just told him that I want this to end. I guess it took him by surprise, again for the 3rd time... And I was crying the whole night coz I said that... It wasn't what I wanted but it's something I have to do. And when I told him about it over coffee the I want it to end... Cant seem to do it straight to his face. I tried reasoning things out, put everything into perspective that whatever we're having right now is just not right and I want it to end before things get out of hand.... But hell, he reasoned things out even better! I just cant seem to get over him can I? I guess I really really want his friendship and the comfort feeling of finally meeting someone truly amazing and I do not want to lose this special relationship...That's what I really want right now.... But I'm gonna tell DC again this weekend and I'm not going to give up telling DC that "This has got to stop. I'm doing this not because I WANT to... But because I HAVE to..."  "Nobody gets too much heaven no more...it's much harder to come by.. i'm waiting in line.." 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       They say  "Time flies pretty fast when you're having fun" . I woke up this morning in disbelief that it was already Sunday. I managed to squeeze a few chores and pamper myself with a great hair-cut yesterday before a meeting up with my L friends at a cozy cafe in TTDI. I felt like I need to help out my friend CC who was having trouble with her ex.. She's finding it difficult to move on when she found out that her ex have moved on and found someone new, a friend of hers too. The tragic things that happens unexpectedly in everyone's life.   Sometimes you keep telling yourself that you're strong and you're able to move on and live a better life after a break-up. I wonder if anyone can really really get over their ex in a matter of months. For me, it's NEVER that easy.  Especially when I really really love that special someone. I've always wondered how easy is it for my ex to just go on and have a new relationship with someone new after we breakup. It takes years for me to actually have the courage to get into another relationship although I regard myself as a strong and mature woman. I've always had the fear that my relationships just don't last, that shit might happen one day to break us up and that I might never settle down with anyone due to the reason that the next person I love will eventually leave me one day. Perhaps I have to change this negative theory into some kind of challenge.  This is where DC comes in. I'm thinking and challenging myself that I should just pursue this much forbidden relationship just to prove that shit IS GOING TO and WILL happen sooner or later. Just so I can tell to him and myself: 'I told you so'. The more I get to know DC, the more content I feel with myself. I haven't laugh and smiled as much as I did before I met him... I'm terrified at the thought that this happiest moment in my life will just end abruptly due to circumstances..  I HATE IT!    My heart aches and my soul screams for explanation from God when DC asked me:  DC: Tell me baby, do you feel for me? ME: Even if I give you my sincere answer, things will never change between us. DC: I know, but do you feel anything for me? ME: Can you answer that if I asked you the same question? DC: No...I can't. ME: Then you know how I feel.  But I'm sure between those lines, our hearts we're communicating about our true feelings for each other... Because the look in his eyes, it was just magical. I'd love to shower him with all my love, give him the best of me, showing him how lucky I feel to have him in my life... But I cant.. .And that just sucks....Nothing could be worst than this. I just hope my heart is strong enough to endure all the complex emotion and situation. I just want to be happy and that's what I feel when I'm with him... When we part, that's when my heart starts to cry... How do I justify the hurt or happiness I feel inside?     Perhaps time will tell and make things less complex than it is right now. Maybe I should start praying for time...  
    
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I had a  CRAZEE  weekend! Having fever didn't stopped me from having too much fun with my life. I went for a stunning makeover session on Saturday and ended up with blonde highlights!! After meeting up with my long lost friend at One Utama, I went back home to get ready for Zouk's party. Picked up CC and the party at Zouk was much as expected... Boring rave music. I'm still a sucker for RnB music when it comes to partying I guess. After coming back home at 3am... I called my ex.  Damn... I was having fever and all...It made me realize about why we were never meant to be together in the first place anyways. After the 2 hour conversation, having my phone barred today because of it... I realize that I still haven't done the list of "What I want..." Just yet. I'm still flipping thru my pass... Clinging to something... I cant quite figure out what or why. DC didn't even cared when I told him I was sick. That's when I decided MT ought to be given a shot... Don't ask me why.. I just needed to get over my ex, DC, RT... everyone!!! I'm just sick and tired of being lonely, being so hard on myself... forcing temporary temptations on me just to forget things... Just cause I believe in fairytales...I'm really tired of the bullshit around me. So i began SMS MT and his respond is just overwhelming! I hope i dont get carried away again...  So, as of today, I managed to ignore DC... To decline his coffee invitation for the very first time....More to come,perhaps. I know it's just cruel of me to ignore... But I wish I could disappear instead, like how Frodo disappeared when he wore the ring. I'm taking time to think things over about what I want. Something good might turn out from all of this insanity. I took my parents to dinner last night. I felt really good that despite my troubles and depression, I managed to make my parents happy. And my cats are just as adorable themselves... I love them so much! It feels wonderful to wake up to Angel or Daisy in the mornings.. Knowing they are there for me thru my good and bad times and never once deny my love nor not give me their sincere affection. Even if my parents don't show me as much love as they ought to, I'm still thankful for the love they have for me.  All this grateful feeling coz someone SMS me late last night:  Bersyukur itu adalah tanda2 orang beriman.  I used to be very grateful of the things I have in my life. It's been a while since I thank God for everything he has blessed me with. This should be a good week ahead. I'm just gonna be friends with DC, hope things will be good for him, I'm looking forward to see MT again and perhaps, not hoping anything but just to give it a shot, perhaps we can be friends again...    "Everyone falls in love sometimes... sometimes it's wrong, sometimes it's right. For every win, someone must fail... But there comes a point when, when we exhale"   
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I've been listening to the Simply Red songs this past two weeks. I think it's such a classic band with such soulful tunes that I just have to appreciate each and every song on every album. Who can say no to Simply Red's music...Sometimes with a touch of reggae, sometimes R&B, most times jazzy..Lovee 'em!  It's been a tiring two weeks for me. Running here and there just to be sure I won’t miss one bit of happy moment in my life. Works been crazy as usual, I can’t believe these accountants cant figure out their finance management and reporting since the company started its business!!  It's all haywire and we have to help them figure it out.  Imagine their own people can’t even figure their own financial system and process...how bout us outsiders trying our best to figure it out for them. CHAOS!   I'm wishing for time off to go to the beach and expose my skin to some sun, sea and fresh air right now. Traffic's like shitty these days, it's killing my patience! Need some peace of mind...but where can one find some peace of mind here in the heart of KL??? Back in Penang I could go to the beach anytime I wanted to and it's just 2 bus rides away from my apartment. Here...I’m just stuck. it's traffic everywhere, no sign of the ocean; it's the office, crowded shopping malls or home. I don’t mind the city really, but it's just suffocating at times for me. Being so used to be near the beach, seeing the horizon, finding peace of mind while listening to the waves...man, where does one find such peace of mind here in the city?  MT came back in my life out of no where...and proposed. Man, I think he could have done better than what he did. a shock to me without doubt but I don’t really care anymore since I’ve got no feelings left in me for him. I’m assuming it's the distraction and attraction to DC that has caused me to feel nothing for anyone else, which means I might end up alone as always for denying other men and giving my all to DC...just like how I did with RT. What is the difference between what I have now with DC and RT? the difference is that DC reveals his feelings for me, and RT didn’t. but hey, in the end of the day I’m just going to be all alone by myself anyways, so why bother worrying about shitz like that. For sure I don’t think I can pretend and accept MT's proposal just coz everyone's getting married and having babies of their own. I can’t even pretend and live a superficial lifestyle just coz it's convenient for me...let alone with reasons to get back to some bitch out there. I'm not that kinda person.. so yeah, rationally, don’t think I’ll be marrying MT anytime soon or ever.  DC and I are in our second month now. feels like I’ve known him for ages tho and yet discovering something amazing every single time I’m out with him. it's just been a magical journey of course, all day everyday. am predicting some change toward mid next month since he's gonna move to a different location. I’m gonna miss him so much, too much. I'll keep holding on...to whatever than I’m suppose to hold on to. DC speaks to me of   FOREVER...IMMORTALITY  ..I hope I’ll live to see the ending of this twisted episode in my life. Never was there a time that my heart does not ache every time he speaks of the other half...after all, I am the fool in love...    "loving you is easy... comes so naturally..." -MisS KEyS-    
    
    
</post>


</Blog>