<Blog>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hmmm, to start us off, how are you? i hope you are good. how is your bf. hope he is good too. me and you should hang out sometime, possibly. if you want. you dont have to if you dont want. well i guess you can post her with your response or what not. 
    
</post>


<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There are moments in life when you miss someone so much that you just want to pick them from your dreams and hug them for real! When the door of happiness closes, another opens; but often times we look so long at the closed door that we don't see the one that has been opened for us. Don't go for looks; they can deceive. Don't go for wealth; even that fades away. Go for someone who makes you smile, because it takes only a smile to make a dark day seem bright. Find the one that makes your heart smile. Dream what you want to dream; go where you want to go; be what you want to be, because you have only one life and one chance to do all the things you want to do. May you have enough happiness to make you sweet, enough trials to make you strong, enough sorrow to keep you human, enough hope to make you happy. The happiest of people don't necessarily have the best of everything; they just make the most of everything that comes along their way. The brightest future will always be based on a forgotten past; you can't go forward in life until you let go of your past failures and heartaches. When you were born, you were crying and everyone around you was smiling. Live your life so at the end, you're the one who is smiling and everyone around you is crying. Life is not measured by the number of breaths we take, but by the moments that take our breath away!
    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The Moment You Said Hello    I don't know what it was About the word you said, Which on that certain day Caused me to turn my head.  When I looked into your eyes I could see my hopes and dreams, And each time I hear your voice I know what forever means.  There isn't a star I wouldn't give you I'll say the sweetest words you've ever heard, Not a day will pass, when I won't be there I know all this from your one simple word.  Your smile tells the truth And I know without a doubt, In my heart, from the start You were the one I couldn't live without.  What is this word you said Which gave me the greatest love I could know?, I've loved you from the moment you spoke 'The Moment You Said "Hello." 
    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this is a poem i wrote this morning and yeah. It's not quite finished so bear with me.  "Why Live Life"  Why live life from day to day, When all it's filled with is miserary, Filled with sadness pain and sorrow, Each day is like this even tomorrow.  I always thought life was filled with love as precious and sweet as a dove but now i can see it i've opened my eyes  Life is just a shit hole surrounded by flies.  Now don't get me wrong I was in love once I dated this girl for quite a few months It wasnt untill i saw all of loves lies we broke up, i left her, with tear filled eyes  Maybe it was wrong, I'll never know was all of our love just a soap opera show Why did i let myself get so involved Now there are many things that need to be solved.  I was cherrished but now I'm jaded I was loved but now hated I was carefree and Joyfull but now i 'm worried and fearful  Why you ask i do not know, Maybe life is just a painful show.
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Shhh... I have a secret.. If you wanna know ... I'll tell you!!!   You are the Best and i luv ya !  I got your back  You got mine,  I'll help you out  Anytime.  To see you hurt  To see you cry,  Makes me weep  And wanna die.  And if you agree  To never fight,  It wouldn't matter  Who's wrong or right.  If a broken heart  Needs a mend,  I'll be right there  To the end.  If your cheeks are wet  From drops of tears, Don't you worry, Let go of your fears.  Hand in hand  Love is sent,  We'll be friends  Till the end. 
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      EVER WONDER?    >have you ever wondered which hurts the most?   >Saying something and wishing you hadn't? or saying nothing and wishing you had? I guess the most important things are the hardest things to say. Don't be afraid to tell someone you love them. If you do, they might break your heart...if you don't, you might break theirs. Have you ever decided not to become a couple because you were so afraid of losing what you already had with that person? Your heart decides whom it likes and whom it doesn't. You can't tell your heart what to do.   >It does it on its own....when you least suspect it, or even when you don't want it to.Have you ever thought, "This relationship won't last because we live too far away..." That ISN'T true! In fact ,most relationships could work out BETTER that way! Have you ever wanted to love someone with every thing you had, but that other person was too afraid to let you?   >Too many of us stay walled up because we are too afraid to care too much...for fear that the other person does not care as much, or even at all. Have you ever denied your feelings for someone because your fear of rejection was too hard to handle? We tell lies when we are afraid... afraid of what we don't know, afraid of what others will think, afraid of what will be found out about us. But every time we tell a lie, the thing we fear grows stronger. Life is all about risks and it requires you to jump. Don't be a person who has to look back and wonder what they would have done, or could have had. * What would you do if every time you fell in love you had to say good-bye? *What would you do if every time you wanted someone they would never be there? *What would you do if your best friend died tomorrow and you never got to tell them how you felt? (even if it is that you don't care anymore)*What would you do if you loved someone more than ever and you couldn't have them? *What would you do if you never got the chance to say I am friends with all of my family and they know I love them?* People live, but people die.   >LoVe iS frIenDShiP tHaT haS cAuGhT fiRe 
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey, if anyone who reads this is interested in online gaming here is a link to a really fun game, http://cc-game.net/signup.php?ref=2964  use referance code 2964 when signing up
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I wrote this poem for one of my best friends who moved the first part of July, she is one of the coolest people i know, and i love and miss her alot!!!!!   "Saying Goodbye"  Saying goodbye, going away Seems like goodbye's such a hard thing to say Touching a hand, wondering why It's time for saying goodbye.  Saying goodbye, why is it sad? Makes us remember the good times we've had Much more to say, foolish to try It's time for saying goodbye.  Don't want to leave, but we both know Sometimes its better to go  Somehow I know, we'll meet again Not sure quite where and I don't know just when  You're in my heart, so until then It's time for saying goodbye.  Somehow I know, we'll meet again Not sure quite where and I don't know just when You're in my heart so until then Wanna smile Wanna cry Saying goodbye 
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey i didnt write this but it hit me very hard when i read it.  Mommy.. Johnny brought a gun to school,>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; He told his friends that it was cool,>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; And when he pulled the trigger back,>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; It shot with a great crack.>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Mommy, I was a good girl, I did What I was told,>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I went to school, I got straight A's, I even got the gold!>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; But Mommy, when I went school that day,>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I never said goodbye,>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I'm sorry Mommy, I had to go, But Mommy, please don't cry. When Johnny >shot>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; the gun, He hit me and another,>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; And all because Johnny, Got the gun from his older brother.>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Mommy, please tell Daddy; That I love him very much,>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; And please tell Chris; my boyfriend; That it wasn't just a crush.>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; And tell my little sister; That she is the only one now,>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; And tell my dear sweet grandmother; I'll by waiting for her now, And >tell my wonderful friends; That they always were the best; Mommy, I'm not >the first,>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I'm no better than the rest.>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Mommy, tell my teachers; I won't show up for class,>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; And never to forget this, And please don't let this pass.>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Mommy, why'd it have to be me? No one deserves this,>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Mommy, warn the others, Mommy I left without a kiss.>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; And Mommy tell the doctors; I know they really did try,>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I think I even saw a doctor, Trying not to cry.>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Mommy, I'm slowly dying, With a bullet in my chest,>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; But Mommy please remember, I'm in heaven with the rest. Mommy I ran as >fast>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; as I could,>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; When I heard that crack, Mommy, listen to me if you would,>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I wanted to go to college, I wanted to try things that were new,>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I guess I'm not going with Daddy, On that trip to the new zoo.>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I wanted to get married, I wanted to have a kid,>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I wanted to be an actress, Mommy, I wanted to live.>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; But Mommy I must go now, The time is getting late,>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Mommy, tell my Chris, I'm sorry but I had to cancel the date.>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I love you Mommy, I always have, >I know; you know it's true, And >Mommy all>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I wanted to say is, "Mommy, I love you." 
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is a poem that i wrote for one of my best friends, she has always been there for me i just wanted to be there for her   >It wouldn't matter if you told me  >That you wanted me to die  >It wouldn't matter if you hurt me  >Bad enough to make me cry  >  >No matter what you do or say  >I will always love you  >No matter what you do or say  >I will always help you  >  >I wish that I could ease all pain  >Make it not so bad  >I wish that I could stop the rain  >So you wouldn't be so sad  >  >I know we had our ups and downs  >And just a few twists and turns  >But no matter what happens  >We can always patch the burns 
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I wrote this poem last night, ive been going through a really rough break up. i love this girl with all my heart but she causes me unbearable pain.   Im sick of your shit and im sick of you Sick of the world i am through Im sick of this pain sick of your lies Sick of Hellos sick of Goodbyes I'm sick of you and sick of love Sick of The world ive had enough Im sick of Pain and sick of sorrow sick of today and sick of tomorrow 
    
</post>


</Blog>