<Blog>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Karma Fool's modest library&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Blog Central&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>


<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Karma Fool watched an episode of  Queer Eye for the Straight Guy  tonight.  The straight guy was a forty year old who wanted to change--to "improve"--himself.  But on one condition.  That he not look like an ordinary forty year old--by which, I think, he meant button down shirt, tie, dress pants . . . the whole tragedy.  Needless to say, the QE fellows accomplished that goal.       But what captured Karma Fool's attention was that the straight guy considered himself a Buddhist.  Yet because he was married and a relatively new father, he admitted that he had little time to practice his Buddhist ways.  His spiritual space had been taken over by baby toys.  He rarely meditated anymore.  He accepted this fate by spinning it as a spiritual sacrifice for his wife and enfant.    Obviously he was misguided.  Just as is Karma Fool much of the time.  Sacrificing one's "spiritual" time is apt to create resentment over time.  It's like my doctor told me several years ago:  "You have to be selfish when it comes to your own well-being."  This does not mean hurting others.  It means making a conscious, daily effort to take time for one's self.  And only for one's self.  For Karma Fool this can be as simple as taking ten minutes in bed in the morning to follow my breath.  Or taking ten or twenty minutes in the afternoon to do the same.  And, as always, it means trying to be mindful.   Send an E-Mail to Karma Fool at:  misterzen@gmail.com
     


    urlLink Link 



    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Karma Fool has begun reading  Living with the Devil:  A Meditation on Good and Evil , expecting to read only the first chapter before falling asleep.  But it was too well written and interesting to stop so soon.  Here's a sample from the first chapter of why I am impressed:  "Letting go, even momentarily and unintentionally, of that desperate and obsessive grip on self does not obliterate you but opens you up to a fleeting and highly contingent world that you share with other anxious creatures like yourself."  Karma Fool likes the way in which  Living with the Devil , without preaching or patronizing, creates a connection between the reader and everyone else--whether they are theistic, non-theistic, or, presumably, atheistic.  Send an E-Mail to Karma Fool at:  misterzen@gmail.com
     


    urlLink Link 



    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The July issue of  Scientific American  has an interesting article that argues that the currently fashionable books that aim to show that god's [purposefully not capitalized] existence is statistically probable or otherwise "scientifically" verifiable are misleading and fallacious.  Karma Fool has a problem, however, with what appears to be a cop out at the end of the article.  The article ends as follows:  "In my opinion, the question of God's existence is a scientifically insoluble one. . . .  This is faith's inescapable weakness. It is also, undeniably, its greatest power."  This statement, it seems to me, is simply intended to placate those  Scientific American   readers who consider themselves to be theistic.  The fact is that the "scientifically insoluble" nature of god's existence is faith's "inescapable weakness"--period.       Karma Fool agrees that faith is undoubtedly a comforting factor in the lives of many people.  But it is still a superstitious factor--and, as such, hollow.  Send an E-Mail to Karma Fool at:  misterzen@gmail.com
     


    urlLink Link 



    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Karma Fool is tired.  Having spent four days painting and redecorating two bathrooms, Karma Fool is ready to do nothing.  I am not sure if I approached the bathroom project in a properly mindful manner.  But I am determined to approach doing nothing mindfully.     The  Tibetan Heart Yoga  book that I am reading states that it is essential to track the breath by starting with the out breath and finishing with the end breath--just the opposite of what I have been doing for years.  The stated justification is that when we are born we begin by taking air into our lungs--and when we die, our last breath will end by expelling air from our lungs.  So we should follow our yoga/meditation breath by ending with a "in" breath--so we do not associate this yoga/meditation time with the final death breath.  I like this idea.  I also notice that tracking my breath in this manner requires me to pay more close attention to my breath than I is normally necessary.  In short, it helps me (or forces me) to be more mindful of my breathing.  And this is a good thing.  Send an E-Mail to Karma Fool at:  misterzen@gmail.com
     




    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Karma Fool drives part of the way to work each day.  A basic Huffy bicycle is stuffed in the trunk of my car, but the trunk can't accommodate the entire bike.  So its front tire protrudes precariously out the back of the trunk, daring any tailgater to get too close.  The bike has no gears.  No hand brakes.  It's bare bones transportation.  Once I get a few miles from my office, I park my car and peddle the rest of the way.    But before I can ride, I must drive.  At a certain spot on the road that I travel, two lanes become one.  Every morning I see the same thing.  People who I can only assume must be half-way polite in most respects become aggressive, death mongers as they approach the merge from one lane into two.  These drivers come in three types.       First, there are the V.I.P. drivers.  Those people who speed past those drivers who form an early line in the right lane.  These people approach the merge as if they are somehow entitled to get to the point-of-merge before those who wait patiently in line.  In so doing, the invariably drive at unsafe speeds, endangering themselves and the rest of us with whom they "share" the road.  Second, there are those drives who drive into the right hand land well before the "point-of-merge."  But rather than move entirely into the right-hand lane, they split the difference, positioning half their cars in the right-hand land while leaving at least half of their cars in the left-hand land--thus blocking (or attempting to block) the drivers above-described V.I.P. from passing them by and beating them to the point-of-merge.  Third, there are those drivers who simply wait there turn to merge, by gracefully accepting their lot in the admittedly slow-moving right-hand lane.  I like this group.  I am often in this group.  I aspire to be in this group more often.  I am never in second group--the suicidal lane blockers.  But I have, from time to time, joined the V.I.P. group.  Karma Fool is not proud of this.  But I am that I am.   Send an E-Mail to Karma Fool at:  misterzen@gmail.com
     




    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Karma Fool is very much a believer in evolution.  In fact, to me it is not so much a matter of "belief" (which has a ring of "faith" to it) but a matter of self evidence.     So I regularly read Carl Zimmer's blog.  Zimmer is a popular science writer who writes books on evolution and other interesting topics.  Today, I read a June 3, 2004 entry on Zimmer's site in which he informed his readers that someone had used the "Comments" section of his blog to post a press release.  Zimmer requested that his readers not use his blog in this manner.  The press release posted on Zimmer's site, Karma Fool thinks, is another example of bad karma.  As it seeks, apparently, to lead the reader of Zimmer's blog to believe, or assume, that Zimmer himself had endorsed the content of the press release.  If true, the comment writer's technique is more insidious than that of a spammer.  But here's the karmic rub:  Karma Fool posted a comment on Zimmer's blog, in which I agreed with Zimmer.  What was my motivation for doing so?  To use Zimmer's blog to encourage his readers to read Karma Fool's blog?  Or just to let Carl Zimmer know that I support his blog?  Or both?  Or neither?     Send an E-Mail to Karma Fool at:  misterzen@gmail.com
     


    urlLink Link 



    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Karma Fool was listening to  A Prairie Home Companion  when Garrison announced that Ronald Reagan had died.  I was a little surprised, and a little disturbed, to hear what appeared to be at least one cheer in the background. To his credit, Garrison ignored the outburst and went on to respectfully, and thoughtfully, announce that he wished Reagan's family well, and then went on to praise Reagan--not the man's policies or politics--but simply Reagan's "charm."  This, to Karma Fool is a solid example of an act of good karma and an act of bad karma.     How does Karma Fool feel about Reagan?  Well, there's a lot of water under the bridge.  So I no longer feel the hostility that I once did toward him.  Reagan was born in 1911.  In the same year as my grandfather (who died in 1996--also of Alzheimer's).  So today, as I think of Reagan, I think:  Not bad for a kid from Dixoon, Illinois.  Were his policies wrong?  Yes.  Many of them horribly wrong.  Was his heart in the right place?  I don't know.
     




    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It seems to Karma Fool that Buddhism is amorphous enough to accommodate a wide range of individual spiritual (and more on the term "spiritual" later) inclinations--even for an atheist.  Buddhism also offers a unique opportunity to explore conceptions, and misconceptions, about the nature of "reality."  Karma, for example, is misunderstood, misapplied, and overly simplified term of art.  And by that, Karma Fool means that he does not understand Karma; he misapplies the term karma, and he overly simplifies the concept of karma.     Here's an example:  I am driving in my car, and someone rudely and impatiently honks at me for not accelerating at a green light in what the other driver thinks is an appropriately aggressive manner.  My immediate response is to want to retaliate in some manner--give it a vulgar hand gesture or, perhaps, driving very, very slowly in order to really annoy the other driver.  My secondary response, however, is to likely think to myself:  "No, do no retaliate.  That's what karma is far."  Meaning, the other driver's rude and aggressive behavior will be appropriate;y punished through the mechanism of karma.    This is Karma Fools common thought process about karma.  It is likely misplaced.    This blog will explore Buddhism in all its manifestations:  Buddhist text and superstitions, meditation, yoga, "real life" karma in action--as taken from headlines, and anything else that is somehow (to Karma Fool's twisted perception anyway) related to the concept of Buddhism.
     




    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Karma Fool is mostly bored by politics.  To me, there are some fundamental party differences, and maybe that partly explains why I have no interest in watching the debates, the conventions, the pundits, the negative ads.  To me, these things are basically the same every four years.  Most people are going to vote one way or another--or not at all--regardless of the media blitz.  And so I generally have little interest in throwing in my personal opinions.   But enough is enough.     Today, the day after the  urlLink Democratic National Convention,  President W's team announced his latest tag line:  "We've turned a corner."  This, of course, immediately conjures images of W landing on the air craft carrier last year with the giant banner hanging in the background proclaiming:  "Mission Accomplished."  What a crock of karma crap.    So W's "We've Turned a Corner" is more aptly equated with "We've Gone Over the Edge" or "We're a Deer in the Headlights" or "We're Despised Around the World" or, at the very least, "we've Really Gotten Ourselves in a Fix This Time."  That said, Karma Fool hereby lends his modest karmic support to  urlLink Kerry .  God speed.  If only there were such a being. 
     




    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Karma Fool has never been the type of driver who slows down to look at the carnage of an accident.  Similarly, in high school, whereas most of my classmates would eagerly form a circle around a fight between two testosterone maddended guys having a slug fest, I would walk the other way, sickened not just at the fighting and violence, but at those people who were so anxious to watch and cheer it on.  So I was faced with a dilemma when I checked out the web site  The Memory Hole  after reading about it in the August 2004 issue of   urlLink Wired   magazine.     The Memory Hole claims to be, and indeed apparently is, decicated to publicizing all sorts of information that our government, the media, corporations, and other entities and individuals likely would not want available for mass consumption.  For example, the site contains a five minute video of President W sitting in front of grade schoolers AFTER he learned on 911 that America was apparently under attack.  Watching it, I was left wondering (1) how could he remain so apparently calm (or oblivious) and (2) why would the Secret Service have permitted him to remain in one arguably soft-target location for so long under such dire circumstances.  But The Memory Hole also contains some graphically disturbing material.  For instance, it contains images of one of the beheaded victims in Iraq--his head posed grotesguely on his back.  The site also claims to have video footage of the beheading.  I did not watch it.  And therein lies the dilemma for Karma Fool.  This is obviously a site that I will return to often, now that I know it exists.  But is it the type of site that I should include on the Karma Fool blog "Links" list.  Ultimately, I decided to include it.    Why?  Because I think its an important site for all kinds of reasons.   The violent images on the site are "hidden" on separate links--and they do not appear to have been placed there gratuitously.  And  I have to admit that sometimes it may be important to take a look at just how cruel some people can be--and not to just read about it.
     


    urlLink Link 



    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Krama Fool purchased some bagels today.  Sitting indiscreetly on the counter before the cash register was a tip jar.  And taped to the tip jar was a piece of paper with the word "karma" written upon it     The implication, I guess, that the bagel shop employee hoped to convey to me and other customers was that if I put some money in the tip jar, I would be acting skillfully, and thus generating good karma--or rather, "purchasing" good karma.   Well, that's not the sort of logic that motivates Karma Fool to cough up a tip.   
     


    urlLink Link 



    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Karma Fool read an article recently in   urlLink Scientific American   that discussed how the sheer number of choices with which we are faced can--far from freeing us up to a world of opportunities--can, in fact, paralyze us:  urlLink Scientific American: The Tyranny of Choice         One partial solution that Karma Fool has to the information overload dilemma is scanning, and if then adequately intrigued, reading, news, blogs entries and other Internet site information through a so-called "news aggregator."  News aggregators come in many forms, but what they all, in essence do, is collect information for Internet sources into one easily accessible location on your computer.  The aggregators scan the Internet sites that the user designates and looks for new information.  When it finds new information, it collects it.  Karma Fool then needs to only open his aggregator, instead of visiting countless Web sites.   I found that not all aggregators are created equal.  You van easily find them through a simple Google search.  After trying any of them out, Karma Fool found that the one that is easiest to use and best serves my purpose is an free aggregator program called  urlLink Tristana .  Take a look.  You may like it too.  And it just may free up some time for meditation or some other positive activity.
     


    urlLink Link 



    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Some people are so blatantly unreasonable and, well, ignorant, that it is difficult to know how to respond to their lunatic ravings.  And, of course, Karma Fool is talking about creationists.     There are a number of fantastic books that appropriately take creationists to task.   Richard Dawkins'   urlLink The Blind Watchmaker: Why the Evidence of Evolution Reveals a Universe Without Design   stands out as one of the best.  There are also some excellent articles, like those written by Michael Shermer, editor of   urlLink Skeptic   magazine and the author of a monthly column of the same name that appears in   urlLink Scientific American  .  Here's an example of Shermer's writing:   urlLink Scientific American: God's Number Is Up    Karma Fool was delighted to recently find a thoughtful, non-hostile manner in which one evolutionist blogger has elected to respond to what was proving to be a veritable Noah's flood of creationist spam-like comments on his blog site: &#147; urlLink Pharyngula .&#148;  The blogger has developed and posted what he calls an "email policy for creationsists."  In it he informs the creationist spammers that he will respond to their blog comments--but only if the creationists agree to two simple conditions:  (1) his responses will be made publicly on his blog and (2) the creations must give him permission to publish their email addresses.   So far, he reports, there has not been a single taker.
     


    urlLink Link 



    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
          Karma Fool stumbled upon some interesting news in the "Editor's note" of the June 2004 issue of  urlLink  Psychology Today  . The "note" compares two lottery winners: Clifford Turner and Michael Carroll.   Turner, a Buddhist, won a $50 million lottery jackpot. And he elected to  maintain his simple lifestyle and share a chuck of his new found wealth  with his community. One news clipping about Turner referenced " urlLink lottery karma ."   The other jackpot winner (Turner)--in a dufferent lottery--showed up to  collect his $18 million winnings wearing an electronic monitoring  bracelet--having pleaded guilty to charges of drug possession.   And which lottery winner do you think was the happiest?   Yes, it was Carroll. And no it was not because (or just because) he won $32 million more than Turner.   Okay this morality fable is trite and predictable. But Karma Fool thinks there is a viable lesson in there, just the same. 
     


    urlLink Link 



    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Karma Fool does not have a practice cushion--that is, a cushion on which to meditate.  Maybe I should.  Maybe I would meditate more often and more effectively if I used a cushion.  In fact, I know would.  Virtually every book that I have read on meditation recommends a cushion, a regular schedule of mediation, sitting straight and so on.  But that's not the way Karma Fool does it.  Maybe someday I will.     More often than not, my meditation time is when I first wake up in the morning, but before I get out of bed.  The house is still quiet, the day's activities have not yet begun.  I'm not sitting up straight.  I have no posture at all, really.  But it's a convenient time to watch my breath.  To count the ins, the outs.  To feel the air moving at the edge of my nostrils.  And sometimes convenient meditation is enough. 
     




    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      There's an interesting article in the  urlLink New York Times Magazine  today about graphic novels.   [Note:  To read it online you will need to complete a complete a FREE and easy NY Times registration form.  It takes less than a minute.  And you need not give accurate personal information].    The article discusses how graphic novels (which is the term that is now generally accepted to refer to book length stories that are told, well, graphically) are becoming more and more popular, more and more mainstream.      Karma Fool does not read many graphic novels.   Hardly ever does so, in fact.  But that may change.  In fact, years ago, I purchased and read (with amazement, horror, sorrow, and did I say amazement), Spiegelman's   urlLink Maus   and  Maus II .  In fact, I only own a few novels (having elected some time ago to acquire primarily non-fiction):  such as Gilbert Sorrentino's   urlLink Mulligan Stew   and Richard Adams' wonderful  Watership Downs .   But among my sparse fiction collection are the two Maus graphic novels.  Karma Fool has also read and enjoyed   urlLink Ghost World  --which, as the Times article discusses--was also turned into a film.  There are also graphic novels focusing on Buddhism, but Karma Fool has only read (skimmed, really)  urlLink one of them --and it just did not hold my attention.  Despite all the favorable reviews, I was bored with it.  But maybe you will like it. 
     


    urlLink Link 



    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Joseph Campbell's admonition to find one's bliss has become a cliche.  But seventeen years after his death it is more than that.     Karma Fool thinks that the word "find" in "Find your bliss" could--and should--be greatly broadened:  Find; Do; Live; Share; Covet; Redo; Expand; Narrow; Refine; Explore; Abandon . . . All of these acts are necessary, at times, to make one's life blissful (or, rather, Bliss- Full ).  It's odd, really, how simple the "find your bliss" concept is--yet how complicated.  It's complicated because many of us are not used to looking inward.  It's complicated because it seems self-indulgent--and that can seem wrong, or selfish, or shallow.  It also can seem impractical, because many of us assume that finding one's bliss is inconsistent with earning a living, taking care of one's family or tackling the myriad other responsibilities that accompany adulthood.  But Karma Fool would argue that finding one's bliss--and then pursuing it--can free one up for all sorts of "responsibilities."  Once you find your true bliss, it is no longer necessary to waste time chasing after false bliss.    And, ideally, it may even be possible to find connections between one's bliss pursuits and one's responsibilities.  Joseph Campbell apparently did it.  He was blissfully interested in mythology--and that interest sustained him financially  and  "spiritually."  Maybe you can do it to.  Maybe Karma Fool can as well.  Send an E-Mail to Karma Fool at:  misterzen@gmail.com
     


    urlLink Link 



    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Karma Fool's Scottish great, great, great grandfather fought in Revolutionary War.  In fact, the then new American government gifted him land in Kentucky as payment for his services.  So, on this Independence Day, a tip of the hat to Grand Dad James ------, Sr.     But, this same grand dad, and his son, also owned slaves.  Hardly worthy of a hat tip.  I have a copy of a will in which these men, my forefathers, leave their human "property" to my younger ancestors.    So from a karma perspective, how, if at all, is Karma Fool supposed to respond to this wart on his family history?  Does battling the British excuse owning humans?  Is it a wash?  I think not.  Can it properly be excused as merely acceptable conduct for  that  time?  I don't think so.  In an ideal world, my ancestors would not have participated in slavery.  But they did participate.  Did they ever question their own conduct?  I wish I knew.  And now, approaching two centuries later, and karmically speaking, should I attempt to somehow make amends for their misconduct?  I think not.  My perspective on Karma is fairly simplistic--and not at all supernatural.  Simply put, my ancestor's karmic debt is not Karma Fool's to pay.    One of the goals of at least one type of practicing Buddhist is to have accrued just enough karma at the end of his or life to extinguish that life utterly--but not so much karma as to permit for rebirth.  In other words, a blissful death is the ultimate lights out.    I do not believe in rebirth.  I believe that my death will be the "ultimate lights out" for me regardless of what my conduct is like while I was alive.  That said, I do "believe" in karmic-like consequences while one is alive.  Something akin to "what goes around comes around."  These karmic consequences are not caused by a supernatural force--but by the conduct itself.  These consequences can manifest instantly (i.e., you drive in a careless manner and you have a accident) or may build up over time (i.e., you consistently treat your co-workers with contempt and you may eventually be terminated).    Yet I also believe in so-called "brute facts"--things without cause.  How does this all tie together?  I don't yet know.    Send an E-Mail to Karma Fool at:  misterzen@gmail.com
     




    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Karma Fool does not wish to remain blissfully ignorant of happenings around the world.  That said, Karma Fool no longer watches local or national news shows (i.e., Dan Rather).  Nor do I listen to NPR's  Morning Edition  as I drive to work.  Why?  Because every time I take a peak or give a listen I am assaulted with "news" of a Palestinian blowing up an Israeli; an Israeli helicopter taking out a Palestinian; two or three US soldiers killed by a roadside bomb; dozens of Iraqis killed by a bomb; a school shooting; a missing child found murdered . . . well, you get the idea.  Maybe this all came to a head for Karma Fool with 911.  I really cannot remember.   This "news" tips Karma Fool's emotional balance.  Does seeing or hearing about this information assist me in any way?  I do not think so.  Maybe it did the first or second time I saw it.  But the news is always the same.  And after thirty or forty it merely makes me feel dull and discouraged.    Do I avoid this news altogether.  Not at all.  Indeed, I probably check the  urlLink CNN  website ten times each day.  That said, having scanned the headlines ("Three US soldiers Charged with Abusing Prisoners"), I do not normally read the entire article.  Instead, Karma Fool will scan the major headlines, and then head to the portions of the CNN that I find interesting and uplifting--like the Science and Space portion of the CNN.  For example, today there is an interesting article a  urlLink newly found hominid fossil .  For more information on this fossil, Karma Fool suggests you take a look at  urlLink Karl Zimmer's blog entry .  Does Karma Fool think that our news sources should change and report only--or mostly--or more--"good" news?  Not necessarily.  In fact, probably not.  But I am glad that I have other news options.  And I am glad that I have learned that I do not need to listen to or watch the "traditional" news sources in the same old manner--or at all.     And thank god [small "g", because there is no supernatural God entity] for  urlLink  The Onion   and good ol'   urlLink Grit  .  And for that drive to work, thank god for Stephen King's books on tape.  At least there is no mistaking King's brand of horror for "reality."  Send an E-Mail to Karma Fool at:  misterzen@gmail.com
     




    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Karma Fool was pleased to find The   urlLink Tibetan Book of Yoga: Ancient Buddhist Teachings on the Philosophy and Practice of Yoga   listed in the Books section of the July-August  urlLink Utne Magazine .  Why?  Because I am reading it.  Actually, I have been reading it in fits and starts for months--which is shameful since the book is quite thin.  It's part philosophical treatise, part how to manual.  And it is a very good book.  Karma Fool recommends it heartily.  What was surprising, however, is the book that was featured by  Utne  directly above  The Tibetan Book of Yoga .  It's a book called  The Executioner Always Chops Twice:  Ghastly Blunders on the Scaffold .  Frankly, while Karma Fool used to enjoy movies and books in  The Silence of the Lambs  genre.  But I have changed.  I no longer enjoy this type of story.  Yet I still like Stephen King--and I suppose it's because Stephen King's fiction is so obviously just that:  fiction.  But despite my change of heart, how can I resist taking a closer look at  The Executioner Always Chops Twice .   Utne  describes it thus:  "Reading Executioner is like watching a car wreck--you can't take your eyes away even though you feel wrong for staring."  Actually, Karma Fool is repulsed by car wrecks.  Yet I must take a gander at this book, if only for a few pages.  Karma Fool has placed it on hold at his local library.  Send an E-Mail to Karma Fool at:  misterzen@gmail.com
     


    urlLink Link 



    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Karma Fool just received  urlLink  Discover   magazine's "Special Einstein Issue" in the mail.  One of the articles, entitled "A Tangled Life," notes that Albert was "indifferent to material comforts in general."  And, by way of example, the article quotes the beloved brainiac as stating:  "What more does a human being want?  Manuscript, violin, bed, table and chair, that is enough."  Well, not even the tragic comma misuse [ Punctuation Help ] in this quote diminishes the zen-like flavor of Einstein's observation.       Indeed, replace the violin with a foot stool, and maybe add cushion for that chair, and I could not agree more.  
     




    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      When Karma Fool was a kid, he enjoyed camping because it represented a complete escape from the "responsibilities" of my normal, civilized life.  Taking out the trash and helping my sister wash and dry the dishes was wonderfully transformed into simply burning used paper plates and cups in the camp fire     The campground my family usually went to when I was a kid was only two hours away from my home in central Illinois--just one state over to Turkey Run or Racoon Lake in central Indiana.  But for me, it was the same as if we had traveled to another planet.  It never occurred to me that for my parents, a two hour drive was probably not much of an escape for them at all.  But for me, the tent, the campfire, the horseback riding, the lake swimming, the ability to take a walk --sans parents--in the woods, was invigorating.  Then, as a college guy, camping was a cheap way of escaping my studies.  Yet it was also a way to stare up at the sky and contemplate the new knowledge that me and my friends were  acquiring in philosophy and other classes.  The world was, indeed, an oyster.  Now, at 42, camping has changed again.  Last night, Karma Fool took his 7 year old daughter on our first camping trip for the two of us.  We went to a small lake up on Mount Hood.  There was no time for staring at stars and contemplating the cosmos.  I was too busy living in the moment with my daughter--playing checkers, catching frogs, walking barefoot in the mud of the lake, making and eating somores--just hanging out together.  I'm not sure that I like the "camping" part of camping as much as I did in earlier days.  In fact, I'm sure that I do not.  Setting up a tent is work now.  It no longer feels like I'm a pioneer constructing a new home.  I'm no longer entirely indifferent to the smell of camp fire smoke in my hair.  Truth be told, Karma Fool would probably rather hike during the day and return to a hotel room at night.    Camping no longer transports me into a pioneer mind-set.  I know that civilization is as close as my cell phone--even if  there is no reception at my camp ground.  But camping cannot be matched for placing a dad and his daughter together in an uninterrupted way.  If we camp, we must talk.  We must listen.  And so I'll keep on camping.
     




    
</post>


</Blog>