<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      went to great america, beat some groper up...and had a fucking hilarious convo with shannon:  AbstinanceroX: aw AbstinanceroX: shanny is bored FranklenIsMyFrog: hi FranklenIsMyFrog: FUCKING HELLA BORED AbstinanceroX: im trying to get all my fav bands and shit together AbstinanceroX: it takes so long FranklenIsMyFrog: lol FranklenIsMyFrog: when do u come back AbstinanceroX: like ive been looking at other peoples to see who they like and im like O YEAH THEM AbstinanceroX: saturday AbstinanceroX: the third FranklenIsMyFrog: lol FranklenIsMyFrog: kk FranklenIsMyFrog: well we gotta chill when u get back AbstinanceroX: lol k FranklenIsMyFrog: soo FranklenIsMyFrog: get any tanner? AbstinanceroX: haha yeah AbstinanceroX: like a corner of my shoulder is burnt AbstinanceroX: it looks so weird AbstinanceroX: but i am still white lol FranklenIsMyFrog: lucky! the other day i got soooo burnt AbstinanceroX: haha FranklenIsMyFrog: im like a red thing AbstinanceroX: lol AbstinanceroX: tomato! FranklenIsMyFrog: haha thats what i look like, my arms and face and back are like this AbstinanceroX: AW AbstinanceroX: poor shannon FranklenIsMyFrog: lol its hurts soo bad AbstinanceroX: like a triangle on my shoulder is red,  a teeny one AbstinanceroX: lol FranklenIsMyFrog: lol AbstinanceroX: ok got some more bands AbstinanceroX: but there are so much more i like FranklenIsMyFrog: lol FranklenIsMyFrog: ahhhhhh FranklenIsMyFrog: what should i do AbstinanceroX: hmm AbstinanceroX: tommy FranklenIsMyFrog: i wish AbstinanceroX: lol AbstinanceroX: he wishes too AbstinanceroX: hehe FranklenIsMyFrog: lol AbstinanceroX: i am listening to punk rock AbstinanceroX: yey FranklenIsMyFrog: wooh yay AbstinanceroX: yeyeyeyey FranklenIsMyFrog: what are you listening too AbstinanceroX: rancid AbstinanceroX: and lars alskfjdslk and the bastards AbstinanceroX: really long name lol FranklenIsMyFrog: lol AbstinanceroX: lars frederikson and the barstards lol FranklenIsMyFrog: awesome AbstinanceroX: and no fx AbstinanceroX: and the drop kick murpheys... FranklenIsMyFrog: cool AbstinanceroX: lol AbstinanceroX: yeah AbstinanceroX: i am bored too FranklenIsMyFrog: fuck me too FranklenIsMyFrog: i havent done anything this summer, it fucking sucmks FranklenIsMyFrog: i wanna get drunk AbstinanceroX: aw FranklenIsMyFrog: with you! AbstinanceroX: lol! AbstinanceroX: that was so fun! FranklenIsMyFrog: i knowww FranklenIsMyFrog: man i wanna see tomy AbstinanceroX: aw AbstinanceroX: call him AbstinanceroX: its.. FranklenIsMyFrog: lol i dont wanna call him AbstinanceroX: 351 8746 AbstinanceroX: lol FranklenIsMyFrog: lol AbstinanceroX: lalala AbstinanceroX: im bored too AbstinanceroX: trying to stay up cuz justen gets on like at midnight FranklenIsMyFrog: haha AbstinanceroX: like omg AbstinanceroX: i think im gonna die im so bored FranklenIsMyFrog: fuck me too FranklenIsMyFrog: i havent done anything this summer. i havent even drank once, and thats a BIG thing to me AbstinanceroX: lol AbstinanceroX: then GO AbstinanceroX: lol AbstinanceroX: run hurry AbstinanceroX: albertsons! AbstinanceroX: lol FranklenIsMyFrog: hah FranklenIsMyFrog: liek my moms gonna let me run out of my house FranklenIsMyFrog: but you know how i was groundeD! FranklenIsMyFrog: im not anymore FranklenIsMyFrog: yaya AbstinanceroX: HAHA AbstinanceroX: YEY AbstinanceroX: then you can spend the night at my house.. FranklenIsMyFrog: YES! AbstinanceroX: lol AbstinanceroX: brb FranklenIsMyFrog: k AbstinanceroX: b FranklenIsMyFrog: hu FranklenIsMyFrog: hi AbstinanceroX: lol AbstinanceroX: hi shannon how are you? FranklenIsMyFrog: fucking bored. what about you sarah? AbstinanceroX: same smae AbstinanceroX: same same er yeah FranklenIsMyFrog: lol FranklenIsMyFrog: ur comments on myspace make me laugh AbstinanceroX: lol FranklenIsMyFrog: haha make me think about the old days in love-n-care AbstinanceroX: lol! they were fun AbstinanceroX: omg i have this old country song stuck in my head AbstinanceroX: "i like it i love it i want some more of it" FranklenIsMyFrog: AH i used to love that song!  FranklenIsMyFrog: haha when i was little, i would always have my sister play it when i was with her AbstinanceroX: who wrote it? FranklenIsMyFrog: i donno i forget AbstinanceroX: lol AbstinanceroX: ill look it up on amazon. com FranklenIsMyFrog: haha ok FranklenIsMyFrog: tell me when u find out his name AbstinanceroX: lol k AbstinanceroX: tim mcgraw i think? FranklenIsMyFrog: lol k FranklenIsMyFrog: it is FranklenIsMyFrog: lol im downloading it AbstinanceroX: lol! FranklenIsMyFrog: haha this is such a good song! AbstinanceroX: lol! AbstinanceroX: i know AbstinanceroX: lets be cowboys! AbstinanceroX: punk rock cow boys! AbstinanceroX: er ...girls FranklenIsMyFrog: haha FranklenIsMyFrog is away at 10:03:59 PM.  AbstinanceroX: HEY  Auto response from FranklenIsMyFrog: brb  AbstinanceroX: omg no AbstinanceroX: you have to go see tsunami bomb with me and britney FranklenIsMyFrog returned at 10:06:29 PM.  FranklenIsMyFrog: haha i was just listening to them FranklenIsMyFrog: whens the show AbstinanceroX: july 24 at the graceland FranklenIsMyFrog: alright ill try to goo AbstinanceroX: its ten bucks man you have too AbstinanceroX: ooo AbstinanceroX: lol FranklenIsMyFrog: haha ok AbstinanceroX: er wait maybe that says ten oclock AbstinanceroX: hmmm AbstinanceroX: dunno? FranklenIsMyFrog: haha ok AbstinanceroX: haha its 4 o clock AbstinanceroX: ten dollas FranklenIsMyFrog: 9. THE FIRST THING YOU NOTICE ABOUT THE OPPOSITE SEX? FranklenIsMyFrog: haha sorry i had to ask FranklenIsMyFrog: lol ok AbstinanceroX: hmmm AbstinanceroX: hmmmm AbstinanceroX: justen? AbstinanceroX: HMMM AbstinanceroX: his lip rings AbstinanceroX: man those are hot FranklenIsMyFrog: ohh fuck i know FranklenIsMyFrog: i love them... haha tommys AbstinanceroX: o fuck peircings drive me liek AbstinanceroX: omg AbstinanceroX: orgasmic FranklenIsMyFrog: and nipples too! FranklenIsMyFrog: fuckk me tooo AbstinanceroX: O FUCK FranklenIsMyFrog: HAH AbstinanceroX: AAAAH AbstinanceroX: I LOVE THEM FranklenIsMyFrog: ME FUCKING TOO FranklenIsMyFrog: there soo hot AbstinanceroX: omg i know AbstinanceroX: we should get shirts that say "show me all your peircings" AbstinanceroX: hehe AbstinanceroX: ALL of them FranklenIsMyFrog: haha that would be awesome! AbstinanceroX: lol AbstinanceroX: lalalaaaaaaaaa FranklenIsMyFrog: man FranklenIsMyFrog: lol you got me thinking about pircings FranklenIsMyFrog: making out with guys with lip pirced is soo much nicer than guys with out them AbstinanceroX: oooh shit AbstinanceroX: i know AbstinanceroX: oooh shit omg AbstinanceroX: lol FranklenIsMyFrog: ahh FranklenIsMyFrog: hott AbstinanceroX: im all giddy now AbstinanceroX: lol FranklenIsMyFrog: me too!! FranklenIsMyFrog: I WANNA MAKE OUT WITH TOMMY AGAIN! FranklenIsMyFrog: lol AbstinanceroX: LOL AbstinanceroX: AH i miss my justen FranklenIsMyFrog: aww!! AbstinanceroX: fucking lip rings AbstinanceroX: omg AbstinanceroX: nipples AbstinanceroX: lol AbstinanceroX: and his TONGUE! FranklenIsMyFrog: AH HOT AbstinanceroX: I KNOW FranklenIsMyFrog: hahahaha im like laughing, smileing now AbstinanceroX: hehehe me too FranklenIsMyFrog: hah FranklenIsMyFrog: man we gotta get drunk together, and tommy must be there FranklenIsMyFrog: lol i dont give a shit about getting abck with him, i just wanna fuck around with him AbstinanceroX: LOL! AbstinanceroX: im telling him that! FranklenIsMyFrog: haha DONT AbstinanceroX: no way hell be like AbstinanceroX: FUCK YEAH FranklenIsMyFrog: haha AbstinanceroX: LETS GO FranklenIsMyFrog: LOL! FranklenIsMyFrog: lol but really, i dont want a boyfriend right now, i donno maybe later AbstinanceroX: haha AbstinanceroX: i looove justen as my bf AbstinanceroX: i dont think i could take him fucking around with other chicks FranklenIsMyFrog: lol well you guys are good for eachother AbstinanceroX: lol yeah AbstinanceroX: lol AbstinanceroX: we are so funny FranklenIsMyFrog: haha i know AbstinanceroX: like freaking out! AbstinanceroX: omg peircings! AbstinanceroX: lol FranklenIsMyFrog: haha FranklenIsMyFrog: I LOVE THEMN FranklenIsMyFrog: and tom has one!! TOM DELONGE! AbstinanceroX: LOL FranklenIsMyFrog: ah u should see my wall.. its coved with him FranklenIsMyFrog: im obessed AbstinanceroX: justen has...4 there, 2 there, one there and one there...EIGHT FranklenIsMyFrog: lol AbstinanceroX: lol FranklenIsMyFrog: i have... 5 big posters, and one little one, and the big atticus poster that has them on there. and then live pictures of them AbstinanceroX: lol FranklenIsMyFrog: FUCK U SARAH FranklenIsMyFrog: OMG  FranklenIsMyFrog: haha u put that convo AbstinanceroX: LOL FranklenIsMyFrog: in ur myspace AbstinanceroX: did you read britneys comment? AbstinanceroX: lol FranklenIsMyFrog: brb let me read aobut how much u put in there FranklenIsMyFrog: hold up AbstinanceroX: lol AbstinanceroX: not the tommy part AbstinanceroX: i took that out FranklenIsMyFrog: haha ok good AbstinanceroX: lol! AbstinanceroX: i wouldnt do that lol! AbstinanceroX: not to everyone FranklenIsMyFrog: FranklenIsMyFrog: I WANNA MAKE OUT WITH TOMMY AGAIN! FranklenIsMyFrog: fucker FranklenIsMyFrog: lol FranklenIsMyFrog: its ok AbstinanceroX: oops AbstinanceroX: lol AbstinanceroX: sorry FranklenIsMyFrog: haha its ok FranklenIsMyFrog: i dont caer FranklenIsMyFrog: its true AbstinanceroX: lol not like noone knows... AbstinanceroX: lol FranklenIsMyFrog: alteast u didnd put the rest it FranklenIsMyFrog: in* AbstinanceroX: omg no no tthat AbstinanceroX: god FranklenIsMyFrog: lol AbstinanceroX: lalala AbstinanceroX: tsunami bomb! AbstinanceroX: ten bucks! AbstinanceroX: lol FranklenIsMyFrog: yaya FranklenIsMyFrog: haha  AbstinanceroX: lol AbstinanceroX: im so hyper FranklenIsMyFrog: lol me too FranklenIsMyFrog: i gotta pee, im to lazy to get up AbstinanceroX: LOL AbstinanceroX: er AbstinanceroX: lol AbstinanceroX: lol? FranklenIsMyFrog: lol AbstinanceroX: i seriously need to update my pictures FranklenIsMyFrog: brb AbstinanceroX: k FranklenIsMyFrog: k hi AbstinanceroX: went pee? AbstinanceroX: lol FranklenIsMyFrog: nope talked to kat for a sex FranklenIsMyFrog: sec AbstinanceroX: LOL! AbstinanceroX: you pervert! AbstinanceroX: must be all that talk about piercings AbstinanceroX: lol FranklenIsMyFrog: haha AbstinanceroX: lalalaaaaaaaaa AbstinanceroX: lol AbstinanceroX: so bored and so hyper AbstinanceroX: everyone is asleep AbstinanceroX: so i gotta be quiet AbstinanceroX: AND ITS FUCKING HARD FranklenIsMyFrog: haha AbstinanceroX: yeah AbstinanceroX: im like AbstinanceroX: bored AbstinanceroX: you know that velvet revolver song is really hot AbstinanceroX: even though they are a bit scarey FranklenIsMyFrog: haha FranklenIsMyFrog: his pants are sooo low AbstinanceroX: lol god i know AbstinanceroX: YEY AbstinanceroX: I JUST MADE MY OWN NIGHT AbstinanceroX: i can light a lighter! AbstinanceroX: lol.. FranklenIsMyFrog: haha FranklenIsMyFrog: brb AbstinanceroX: k FranklenIsMyFrog is away at 10:50:55 PM. 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      at least ten year old skater punk boys think so. actually i think they were more like thirteen and fourteen, but anyways...played skate bball...where you skate and play bball at the same time! tried to catch the ball while i was like pivoting and i landed on my finger while it was strait. it got like the size of i dunno...about twice its normal size, and then in the middle of my shower it popped back into place. that hurt so bad. so all the kids are like "can sarah come out and play". i should have seriously said no. but they are so nice and cute and i was like ok why not?...and then BAM. i found out why not.  so there is matt, going to be a freshman, teeny and blonde, reminds me of a younger matt dooley actually, kinda freaky. then peter, asian, also going to be a freshman, friendly but a bit over cautious. and then ryan, who is going to be in eigth grade, a bit chubby, freckled, almost annoying. but not as bad as his younger brother jason, who almost killed my six year old cousin/niece/sister in our RV party. and kelly, seven, cute and freckly, very sweet little girl, and her older brother johnny, who is about as tall as justen, looks like he is 15 or 16 too, but is 11. no kidding. 11. but he is really annoying and stupid...you know, hello 6th graders are still 6th graders. and i swear all these little skater punk boys have a crush on me, they come over and ask me to play and go to the pool and want to help me with my skate techniques. its rather funny. but thank god i leave saturday. admirers tend to get on my nerves...i love the attention, but from...[counting] five guys at once?! its crazy.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      o jesus. mom went home today. thank god! i do love the woman...but she is either fawning over how pretty im getting or how tall i am or how old i have grown, or finding someway to twist a really minor situation into something gigantic and seemingly intolerable. is our life really that dull that she must lie to make it interesting? she does have her mothers qualities, inculding overdoing things, overdramatizing teeny weeny issues and my favorite: making her life seem either ten tiems better, or preferably, ten times worse, than it genuwinely is. o well. porn. what a great topic. i swear to god i am the only girl who can admit she enjoys watching some woman getting fucked with her feet in the air and her ass on the cherry stained desk of a well paid lawyer, or perhaps the chilly counter of a downtown drug store, or the vynil seat of a lower class coffee shop. lord knows i cannot spell at these hours of the night, but he also knows that this is when my fantasies really kick off.[not to mention, kick ass] if it werent for playboy, i dont know what i would do with myself. id be dry of the lush ideas, and probably dry in my nether areas as well. thank god for the fountain of youth. all i need to do is turn it on. anways! and the last, most familiar topic to me, okay second to porn...the mall. what genius thought up this gathering place? i love wasting away money, rather, my mothers money on stores and stores and stores and miles of stores full of rich, vibrant clothing. o it is joy. and then, arms loaded with cheap paper bags decorated with fancy, gleaming, desperate logos, you plop down and enjoy your coffee at starbucks. happy happy happy days like these. oh yes, i love them. goodnight ladies and gentlemen. i have masturbated twice in the past ten minutes, and now i can say, i feel truley satisfied.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey kids! i am in the sweet californian sun right now. taking it all in. okay so i really am not that tan am i? o well. friday we went to the board walk, i road a few rollercoasters, nothing special, but i looove santa cruize. pretty sandy beaches and all. great shit. then saturday we went to the gym. omg! they had a tv connected to every cardio machine and a station at every weight lifting section. i was like in love. we went shopping yesterday too, got a jimmy hendrix tshirt, pink bracelette, three bikinis and two pairs of flip flops. joy. and today we went to a little kiddy park. it was cute, but really really hot. i am kindof worried cuz i havent heard from justen, which might mean he is at my house, which also might mean he is dead because ed is prally just landing in seattle about now. so god. please help me. i dropped the key on the roof, ed i swear, and thats not justen, its his evil twin. with the same peircings. and all. anyways, yeah im a bit freaked...but i am sure he is just at his grandmas. O RIGHT, thats where he prally is. cuz now he like helps with her landscaping! OOOH. silly sarah. i still have this feeling i am dead though. o god. well anyways, i love cali! and even if i am still ghostly...i dunno, nothing more to say. ah fuck. my crotch itches. ciao!
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      got a new blog majig cuz people keep finding it out and reading my personal shit you know?! them bitches! summer has been going pretty good. monday went to ride my bike around with justen, tuesday went to mall with my wife, and out that night to hang with justen, today went to skate barn with justen...im such a pussy. i cant even drop in. o well, i will learn, i was thinking, the days mom works i could move like the tables around and screw with my board to learn somethings. i feel like it right now but mom is here. cant wait to go surfing. man! remind me to send in my skate legged creature to lib tech, and to tell sister about justens board, and i think thats it. california in two fucking days. rad! i think ill bring my board there too, even if i dont ride it. its mostly flat where my cousin lives though so if we go on a walk or something i should be alright. i think? i am so tan! i have the best tan line ever! yey! my ass is tomato red though, and the tan line is like half thong half underwear. lol. gtg step dad is home. toodles.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      cuz you never know what your kids might want to read when they grow up.   &nbsp;  Monday, July 05, 2004  well...  i dont like name acronyms...i am sensational, accurate, raw, accurate again, and handy. i sound like a vibrator.   urlLink 3:39 PM  -  urlLink 0 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   Sunday, June 27, 2004  oh  this is what i sent to thomas. just because i feel like puttin it in hurrr.TOMMY?! you gotta my space huh? so you can talk to shaaanny huh?! hows it going pimpsicle? hey justen is not a whore biatch! he is MY whore. like hecks yeah. when i get back to warsh-ing-ton...mmm mmm. you know what...so anyways. how are yall?im bored as a mother fucker!woohoo! one handing typing at the moment.aka: masturbation time. happy moment.   urlLink 8:43 PM  -  urlLink 3 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Monday, July 19, 2004  this thing i found.  you of the moment:they call me: sarahsex: vaginaeye: greenhair: brunetteskin: pale as caspernails: blacktoenails: pinkrings on your fingers: justens, christiesmusic of the moment: ah, you caught me listening to blink 182, but it doesnt count cuz its on the radiomusic want of the moment: i just bought it: rock against bushfav feature: hmmm. not my ass, not my lips, not my hands. my tan line!your opposite of the moment:turn on: piercings, skate skills.turn off: being a dickhead about blow jobs. youre not getting one.love that: quirk, when you talk you form a shocker with your right hand. [justen you perv]hate that: isnt this like the same as what turns me on...o no i guess not. hate that over protectivenesswant that: roman guy buttneed that: tongue piercinghad that: oral HAHAHA!looks like: jesus with lip rings, maybe they put you on the cross wrong, justenwishes:you wish you could outside: skateyou wish you could inside: none of your buisnessyou wish you could in the kitchen: cook periodyou wish you could in the bedroom: what odd things this person thought of.you want right now: havent i told you all? digital camerayou wanted and you got: tight pantsyou wanted and you couldnt get: a blazer to go with my tight pantsfavs:drink: ginnon alcoholic: tomatoe juicefruit: pineappleveggie: carrots?meat: i dont really like much, chicken is good and bacon. mostly i like copper river salmon.carb: potato breadcolor: pinkshoe: my converse :) they are so cuteshirt: ummm. god. i had a shirt but it got stolen, my lib tech one. *cries*pants: yey for gap jeans. my butt looks good in themshow: this show called blow out, about a bitchy guy who owns a salonband: omg. jesus. way too many. but i know all the eagles songs so them.solo artist: uuuh. tom petty, eric claptin or van morrison. one of them kids.movie: rocky horror picture show! so creepy.radio: kgrg, its always on, i never change it.your odd quirks:what is it: i have alot: not admitting i like blink, cuz i fucking dont; stopping to think in the middle of walking somewhere, like on the stairs going to class; just calling people names not knowing where they came from: like jesus, or lover.people think youre: loud, violent, annoying.but sometimes you can be: completely serious, quiet, and omg...MATURE.the side no one sees: and the side you will never see: me unhappy, cuz i always find a way to be when people are around. or me completely serious. this only happens in the depths of my room when im hard at work on some unsuccessful failure of an art project.one comment to add: you ask the wierdest things, whoever made this.   urlLink 8:45 AM  -  urlLink 0 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   fucking old!  this site is so old. i never go there ne more:http://www.xanga.com/home.aspx?user=rohrforsonicare   urlLink 7:57 AM  -  urlLink 0 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   Friday, July 09, 2004  700 dollers...  mom...i am so sorry i broke the window. see it all started when i wanted to go play with my friends...and no body could so i decided to call justen so we could take pictures of my hair. o and get away from donovans stupid comments...lalala ignoring you donovan lalala...anyways...well then... see we were joking around and i put my key somewhere and BAM forgot to take it home...so his mommie gave us a ride up the hill. and my window was locked. well look says i, the bathroom window is open all i have to do is jam my arm in and pull a bit and we can hop in. no says justen, not a good idea. well. we went for it anyways and yanked and then...crack says the window, and all over flew teeny bits of glass. so we laughed, said fuck more than a few times, went downstairs and waited for you to come home, mom. i deeply appologize, and will gladly repay you. it will only take me about a year and two months based on the allowence we have agreed on.   urlLink 5:49 PM  -  urlLink 1 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   Wednesday, July 07, 2004  moments of desperation.  perhaps...if you people...who think you understand how i feel...but really dont...cuz you never will...read this...you would see?Dongcicle: What?Dongcicle: Nevermind.AbstinanceroX: what what? you imed meDongcicle: I just read the emails.AbstinanceroX: oAbstinanceroX: wellAbstinanceroX: yeah nvm thenAbstinanceroX: haha i forgot i had blocked you so...i unblocked youDongcicle: You blocked even Ben, Chris, Me, everyone?Dongcicle: All my names.Dongcicle: Even the new ones huh? lolAbstinanceroX: no...Dongcicle: Did you have your settings so you could just talk to a few ppl or something?AbstinanceroX: i blocked just oneAbstinanceroX: no thats how my space isAbstinanceroX: you have to invite them to be your friend and they have to agreeDongcicle: Did you block ben?AbstinanceroX: no..Dongcicle: OhAbstinanceroX: i havent been on for a while alsoDongcicle: On the one thing, it says that you are always online.AbstinanceroX: on myspace yesAbstinanceroX: but not online like aim or msnDongcicle: Ok.Dongcicle: The thing I was talking about On MoDeLsLuStDongcicle: Was the swimming thing the 3rd.Dongcicle: Or something.AbstinanceroX: was the swimming thing the third? o with justen?AbstinanceroX: what?Dongcicle: Dunno.AbstinanceroX: k...Dongcicle: Dont mind that.AbstinanceroX: uh and you were models lust right?Dongcicle: Yes.Dongcicle: You wouldetn talk to me on this name.Dongcicle: SO I went undercover.Dongcicle: lolAbstinanceroX: ooooohAbstinanceroX: yes i forgot i had blocked youAbstinanceroX: but just dongcicleAbstinanceroX: i didnt make it that hard lolAbstinanceroX: and i was pretty sure it was youDongcicle: Why did you block me in the first place..AbstinanceroX: uhAbstinanceroX: hmmmmAbstinanceroX: well i had to go a few times..but after that i didnt feel like really talking to youDongcicle: Whatever, I guess.AbstinanceroX: your profileAbstinanceroX: needsAbstinanceroX: workDongcicle: My profile?AbstinanceroX: my space?AbstinanceroX: lolDongcicle: OHDongcicle: It sucksDongcicle: lolAbstinanceroX: hahaDongcicle: I dont even use it yetDongcicle: Ive been reading justens thoughAbstinanceroX: did you just get one to try to like talk to people?Dongcicle: Its interesitng.AbstinanceroX: yes...Dongcicle: sarah this is for you.............listen Dongcicle: Who knows.AbstinanceroX: i heard you laughed at his pictureDongcicle: So/so.AbstinanceroX: you mean bastardAbstinanceroX: lolDongcicle: WellDongcicle: He is mean to meDongcicle: SO I will be mean to him.Dongcicle: It works both ways.AbstinanceroX: yes so i guess you have your reasonsAbstinanceroX: i amDongcicle: Who told you that?AbstinanceroX: felt just grandAbstinanceroX: chris brownDongcicle: That ass hole.AbstinanceroX: haha!Dongcicle: He is going down.AbstinanceroX: awAbstinanceroX: he told me lots of thingsAbstinanceroX: todayAbstinanceroX: and jrAbstinanceroX: them bothDongcicle: Yeah..Dongcicle: How much was it about me?AbstinanceroX: haha ..the bit that you laughed at justen and the bit where chris said you were worriedDongcicle: ehDongcicle: lolAbstinanceroX: dont worryDongcicle: Im glad I got friends to tell ppl what I think.AbstinanceroX: i only cut myself twenty one times! and i ate today! and...i feel happier about myselfAbstinanceroX: hahaAbstinanceroX: how gay am i?AbstinanceroX: GAY.Dongcicle: Really?AbstinanceroX: really? no i am not gay. yes i ate. yes i sliced.AbstinanceroX: bummer huh?Dongcicle: Sure...Dongcicle: Why do that?Dongcicle: Its dumb.AbstinanceroX: well...duh. but i have my forms of release and you have yoursAbstinanceroX: mine is just...specialDongcicle: Yeah.AbstinanceroX: my profile is sortofAbstinanceroX: blindingDongcicle: YeahDongcicle: Sarah, next time you feel like doing that, can you please call me or something.Dongcicle: Cause that is just crazy you doing that.AbstinanceroX: well...no not really. i did not want to talk to you don.AbstinanceroX: cuz you were like freaking outAbstinanceroX: and so was iAbstinanceroX: so i just got offDongcicle: You lied to me again sarah.AbstinanceroX: well yesAbstinanceroX: i didDongcicle: Thats why.Dongcicle: Im good now, I guess.AbstinanceroX: and i totally think that you had a reasonAbstinanceroX: or have reasonsAbstinanceroX: to be angryAbstinanceroX: or whatever and not trust meDongcicle: Lol, why did you get drunk with Justen again? hahaAbstinanceroX: i feel like...in this not real worldDongcicle: After you dumped him.AbstinanceroX: o m gAbstinanceroX: that was absolutleyAbstinanceroX: the dumbestAbstinanceroX: fucking thingAbstinanceroX: i have ever doneDongcicle: The more you hang out with him.. the more he still likes you.AbstinanceroX: and i honestly can sayAbstinanceroX: because i am insecureDongcicle: You are chillin with him too much. And the fact you almost had sex with him.Dongcicle: Stay away lol.AbstinanceroX: haha that was a lieAbstinanceroX: needed dramatics for my blogDongcicle: OkDongcicle: WellAbstinanceroX: i wasnt like even closeDongcicle: Close enoughDongcicle: NevermindDongcicle: Thats good.AbstinanceroX: i was more of...dont touch me you sick bastard i am a virgin and its mine and you cant have it lalala!AbstinanceroX: i have ringworm. :-)Dongcicle: You also did the swimming thing again. And good job.AbstinanceroX: swimming thing?AbstinanceroX: o why yesAbstinanceroX: another dumb thing to add to my listAbstinanceroX: along with inviting amberAbstinanceroX: because later roxanne ate her outDongcicle: Justen was there.AbstinanceroX: gag gagDongcicle: wtfAbstinanceroX: im telling youAbstinanceroX: i need better friendsAbstinanceroX: HAHAAbstinanceroX: no actually you told meAbstinanceroX: lolAbstinanceroX: but just pretendDongcicle: OkayAbstinanceroX: if only christie lived nearerAbstinanceroX: i think i will marry herAbstinanceroX: lolDongcicle: HeheAbstinanceroX: because your best friend lasts longer than your boyfriend alwaysAbstinanceroX: and she doesnt cheat on youAbstinanceroX: and she doesnt influence bad thingsAbstinanceroX: and she loves you foreverAbstinanceroX: even if you get uglyDongcicle: Yeah.Dongcicle: Or maybe you are going for the wrong people.AbstinanceroX: well see...my new therapist has this theoryDongcicle: your new.Dongcicle: lolfinished convo...in next blog.   urlLink 1:21 AM  -  urlLink 1 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   moments of desperation second half.  AbstinanceroX: people who dont know me think i am nice...because usually i am...sorry i have to rule out your case don...lol...and so they cling to me cuz they know i will let them walk all over me...like you said...HAHA...and because they need love and care and blah blah blah more like a mother and special attention and i give that to them...i attract needy peopleAbstinanceroX: and needy people are ones with issues...AbstinanceroX: like self esteemDongcicle: I would make a good phycologister\AbstinanceroX: haha...no you wouldntDongcicle: What do they do anywayDongcicle: I dont even know what I am talking about.AbstinanceroX: there is knowing what is best...and there is letting one find out on their own what is best.Dongcicle: The thing I want to do when I am older is help people.AbstinanceroX: parents also forget...that you never learn from someone elses mistakesAbstinanceroX: never.AbstinanceroX: you either are terrified of them, or learn on your ownAbstinanceroX: donDongcicle: yoAbstinanceroX: you are rather offensive sometimesDongcicle: YesAbstinanceroX: well at least your attempts to be are...and it hurts my feelings...i would tell you to fuck off if you were my phsyciatristAbstinanceroX: and then i would kill youAbstinanceroX: likeAbstinanceroX: not kidding.Dongcicle: Am I saying you are?AbstinanceroX: haha..he also mentioned something about anger issuesDongcicle: I think I should stay away from you. You are saying you will kill me.AbstinanceroX: lolAbstinanceroX: noAbstinanceroX: only if you were my phsyciatristDongcicle: ahAbstinanceroX: well...anywaysDongcicle: okAbstinanceroX: you are concerned about justen...rephraseAbstinanceroX: aboutAbstinanceroX: me AbstinanceroX: with justenAbstinanceroX: well...AbstinanceroX: hmmmAbstinanceroX: i do not think you realize some thingsDongcicle: OkDongcicle: Maybe I dontDongcicle: ActuallyDongcicle: I am sure I dontAbstinanceroX: it is very very hard to let go of someone...after five months...of happynessAbstinanceroX: especiallyAbstinanceroX: when they are not an asswholeDongcicle: You think I dont understand that?AbstinanceroX: dont talkAbstinanceroX: listenDongcicle: NoDongcicle: I wana say somethigAbstinanceroX: no don i am not donAbstinanceroX: fineAbstinanceroX: but i am not fucking doneAbstinanceroX: and i will block youAbstinanceroX: becauseDongcicle: EhDongcicle: Go onDongcicle: jesusAbstinanceroX: have i said im not done?AbstinanceroX: o thanksAbstinanceroX: it was very stressfull...and i felt very attatched. i am not sure about love...because i dont even know what that is anymore...so confusedAbstinanceroX: still not doneDongcicle: kAbstinanceroX: and for me...letting go of him...was like setting him up for something really hurt full. and it was most hard because he never had done anything to piss me off. he always tried to like be the best...sounds gay but it is true. and i do not like hurting people...i have the biggest guilt issues for people who i feel deserve them...like i cried when i skipped choir, but not scienceAbstinanceroX: and i cry when i hurt momAbstinanceroX: but not edAbstinanceroX: its just how i amAbstinanceroX: and that was so hard for meAbstinanceroX: to say goodbyeAbstinanceroX: and everyone knew he was good to me..and so did iAbstinanceroX: i felt like a fucking bitch...and people thought i was just dumping him because i was cheating or somethingAbstinanceroX: but i wasntAbstinanceroX: it was so hardAbstinanceroX: and everyone was pressuring meAbstinanceroX: EVERYONEDongcicle: Cept me.AbstinanceroX: saying things i did not like...because they were not in my relationship, they just assumed they knewDongcicle: WaitAbstinanceroX: bullshit donovanAbstinanceroX: you wereDongcicle: OmgAbstinanceroX: i didnt like that eitherbAbstinanceroX: but you were helping in a wayAbstinanceroX: cuz i was ballingAbstinanceroX: and you were thereAbstinanceroX: but i still was angryAbstinanceroX: i felt like you were also trying to make up my mindAbstinanceroX: and right nowDongcicle: SarahAbstinanceroX: well no...back to those daysDongcicle: I told you to choose yourslef!Dongcicle: I got the conofAbstinanceroX: i just wanted to make him feel betterDongcicle: LOok.AbstinanceroX: of course you did goddamnitAbstinanceroX: but when you are telling me what he is thinkingAbstinanceroX: that is fucking pressure donDongcicle: When did I do that?Dongcicle: wait waitDongcicle: back upAbstinanceroX: THE WHOLE CONVOAbstinanceroX: but anyways...i felt bad so i kept hanging with himAbstinanceroX: but that hurts him moreAbstinanceroX: and when i dont he is still sadAbstinanceroX: there is nothing i can doAbstinanceroX: right nowAbstinanceroX: i feel i cant make any one happyDongcicle: hehAbstinanceroX: nobodyAbstinanceroX: is happyAbstinanceroX: everDongcicle: That is a lie.AbstinanceroX: if i took him back...mom would not be happy...you wouldnt and neither would iDongcicle: Thats not true at all.AbstinanceroX: if i didntAbstinanceroX: ever one thinks i am such a bitchAbstinanceroX: DONT TELL ME ITS A LIEDongcicle: omg..AbstinanceroX: you think you understandAbstinanceroX: but u have no ideaDongcicle: fine i dont sarahDongcicle: u got meAbstinanceroX: how i feelAbstinanceroX: no idea!Dongcicle: CALM DOWNDongcicle: pleaseAbstinanceroX: i cant anymoreAbstinanceroX: this is tearing me apartAbstinanceroX: i am in piecesAbstinanceroX: everdayAbstinanceroX: i get worse donovanAbstinanceroX: i am spiraling into insanityAbstinanceroX: cuz i cannot make people happyAbstinanceroX: they are never happy!AbstinanceroX: no decisino i can makeAbstinanceroX: will please someoneDongcicle: You cannot make people happy? What is this.AbstinanceroX: and they say they want me to be happy...bullshit...they want me to be happy with their ideasDongcicle: they whoAbstinanceroX: donovan. listen to what i just saidDongcicle: mim trying tooDongcicle: lolAbstinanceroX: there are choices i can makeAbstinanceroX: but nomatter what oneAbstinanceroX: someone is attacking me on the other sideAbstinanceroX: and it hurtsAbstinanceroX: and i am going madDongcicle: SO you are talking about me?AbstinanceroX: i am tlaking about everyone around meAbstinanceroX: everyoneAbstinanceroX: i want to run away...get a new lifeAbstinanceroX: its not working right nowDongcicle: WellDongcicle: Who is a problemn in your life right nowDongcicle: besidsed meAbstinanceroX: GODDAMNit...i am trying not to be angry..but EVERYONEDongcicle: cause i know I have just been a blockAbstinanceroX: everyone who affects meAbstinanceroX: or talks to meAbstinanceroX: friendsAbstinanceroX: familyAbstinanceroX: they tell me to move on, get away from justen, they tell me to go back, he was so good to meAbstinanceroX: and justenAbstinanceroX: godAbstinanceroX: i have never seen him like thisAbstinanceroX: he is so hurtAbstinanceroX: and i just cant do anythingAbstinanceroX: i am stuck at a place where i am trappedDongcicle: I feel right now, that if I say something. I am going to get yeled at.Dongcicle: So, go on.AbstinanceroX: yeah you are rightAbstinanceroX: i am trying not to make noise as i cry donovanAbstinanceroX: its too hardAbstinanceroX: i cant handle thisAbstinanceroX: thats why i have cut myselfDongcicle: :-(AbstinanceroX: its likeAbstinanceroX: if i feel something...at least that will healDongcicle: So, me talking to you about anything.. dident help at allDongcicle: It just hurt yoiu?Dongcicle: Cause when you drank, I was mad at you?Dongcicle: About lieing and everything.AbstinanceroX: no not thatAbstinanceroX: about justenDongcicle: And that I "forced" you to dump himAbstinanceroX: when i was thinking about dumping himDongcicle: Cause I told you to do what you thought was best.AbstinanceroX: i know you didnt donDongcicle: And you did thatAbstinanceroX: you didnt forceDongcicle: SO, I dont like the fact you said I did that.AbstinanceroX: i felt pressure!AbstinanceroX: pressureDongcicle: Pressure?Dongcicle: HehAbstinanceroX: it attacks mmeDongcicle: You thought I was pressuring you to dump justen?AbstinanceroX: yes...but i never meant that you meant toAbstinanceroX: its likeAbstinanceroX: i just feel like you didDongcicle: Well I dont think I didAbstinanceroX: well stopDongcicle: okAbstinanceroX: this is where people make me madAbstinanceroX: stop getting defensiveAbstinanceroX: and understandAbstinanceroX: how i feltAbstinanceroX: at that momentAbstinanceroX: i was under complete stressAbstinanceroX: you telling me to GO GOAbstinanceroX: and him telling me NO I LOVE U so onDongcicle: Why did you say, that I dont know whats its like to give something up?Dongcicle: I was gana say that earlier.Dongcicle: Because, I do know what it is like Sarah.AbstinanceroX: because you have never been in a relationship quite like this...you dont handle things like i do either...obviously nobody thinks the smaeAbstinanceroX: nobody thinks the smae is more like what i meantAbstinanceroX: and one person can feel seomthing entirley differentAbstinanceroX: im sure you doDongcicle: Just because I have never been in a relationship, doesent mean I dont know.AbstinanceroX: fuck donovanAbstinanceroX: youre getting defensiveDongcicle: Im actually really calmAbstinanceroX: this is why i do not like telling people thingsAbstinanceroX: because they come back and try to prove something...its like...sorry but werent you trying to help me? i thought this was about me? you wanted me to be happy right?> well good job.;AbstinanceroX: and then! they tell you that you are self centeredAbstinanceroX: well no...actually all i can think about is other peopleAbstinanceroX: because no one is ever pleasedAbstinanceroX: ....AbstinanceroX: I cannot win these daysAbstinanceroX: and they wonder why i am so insecure?!AbstinanceroX: life truley sucksDongcicle: yeah..Dongcicle: Idont want to say anything else about your relationships anymore cause maybe your right.Dongcicle: Maybe I dont know what you are talking about.Dongcicle: And when you say they.AbstinanceroX: i know you have lost thingsDongcicle: SAounds like you mean me.AbstinanceroX: but likeAbstinanceroX: you dont feel the same as i doAbstinanceroX: nobody feels someone elses emotionsDongcicle: I know.Dongcicle: I agree.AbstinanceroX: thats what people should understand about meDongcicle: But.. sarha... why, why do you think you dont make people happy?Dongcicle: You make me happyDongcicle: You make allot of people happyDongcicle: You shouldent feel that way about yourself.AbstinanceroX: well...everyone is pulling and pushing me...be with him you bitch, no stupid girl dump himAbstinanceroX: but i doDongcicle: Who is saying..Dongcicle: Be with him you bitch?AbstinanceroX: deven?AbstinanceroX: walkerDongcicle: Deven is an ass holeAbstinanceroX: and tommy sortof hintedDongcicle: All friends of justen?AbstinanceroX: haha of course!AbstinanceroX: and the othersDongcicle: I am telling you to do what you want.AbstinanceroX: mom says i need to do whats best for me...but not to break HER heart...uh mom...its my heart you should be worried about...Dongcicle: So you want to go out with him again?AbstinanceroX: o wowDongcicle: Or what do you want to do.Dongcicle: SarahDongcicle: ha\Dongcicle: ah*AbstinanceroX: i dont knowAbstinanceroX: lalalaAbstinanceroX: i wish someone would except that tooAbstinanceroX: I DONT FUCKING KNOOOOWAbstinanceroX: if i do..i have to promise myself it is not out of guiltAbstinanceroX: god you know what is frustrating?!Dongcicle: huhAbstinanceroX: him telling me to use him all i want...LIKE OMG!!! can you not see that is just stupid?! i dont feel that way for him now! and he wants me to like lie...to be there...because it would make him happyAbstinanceroX: it makes no senseAbstinanceroX: godDongcicle: I read that.AbstinanceroX: justen omg....hes going to kill himself if he goes onAbstinanceroX: liek thisAbstinanceroX: no i will not use you!AbstinanceroX: goddamnAbstinanceroX: that is cruelDongcicle: He is trying his hardest to gbet you backDongcicle: trying everythingAbstinanceroX: i hate thatAbstinanceroX: i cannot handle his emotions along with mineAbstinanceroX: he shouldnt depend on meAbstinanceroX: i cannot handle thisAbstinanceroX: goddamn!AbstinanceroX: sldjkfadslkjfDongcicle: yeahDongcicle: Yeah...Dongcicle: exactlyDongcicle: You read all his blogs right?AbstinanceroX: o godAbstinanceroX: yeahDongcicle: when will i wake up form this nitemare....when will everything go back how it use to be..i found a girl i rally like but i guees i am not good enouhf for her i dont know anymnore Dongcicle: Sounds like he is trying to make you feel bad.AbstinanceroX: wellAbstinanceroX: even if hes not tryingAbstinanceroX: hes very successfullDongcicle: YeahAbstinanceroX: if this doesnt turn subjects my blog is going to be too longAbstinanceroX: hahaAbstinanceroX: i hope you dont mindAbstinanceroX: but even if you doAbstinanceroX: ...too badDongcicle: Lolok...so i think we moved on. am not sure. thats where we are right now.   urlLink 11:38 PM  -  urlLink 0 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   Monday, July 05, 2004  about mwah  i stole this from someones myspace that i totally dont know, heh. but hey, im allowed.LAYER ONE:--Name: Sarah Jeanne RohrBirth date: 4/27/1989Birthplace: Auburn, WACurrent Location: Auburn, WAEye Color: green some days, blue some days, gray some days.Hair Color: brunette.Height: 5’4"Righty or Lefty: Righty.Zodiac Sign: Taurus.LAYER TWO:--Your heritage: mostly italian and german.The shoes you wore today: sneaking home with justen, uh i think blue converse, on a walk, red c's.Your weakness: piercings.Your fears: drowning...some heights.Your perfect pizza: olives, pineapple, bacon, canadian bacon, pepperoni, lotsa cheese.Goal you'd like to achieve: uh? not being so insecure sometimes.LAYER THREE:--Your most overused phrase on AIM: "omg"Your thoughts first waking up: i suck.Your best physical feature: none today, but yesterday i liked my ass. until it itched.Your bedtime: nine, or 4-5 am...never in between.Your most missed memory: certain boyfriends...with pretty lip and nipple and tongue rings...LAYER FOUR:--Pepsi or Coke: coke.McDonald's or Burger King: no in and out burger? fine then.Single or group dates: uh? im single...but i love dates ;)Adidas or Nike: Adidas.Lipton Ice Tea or Nestea: Lipton.Chocolate or Vanilla: chocolate...def.Cappuccino or Coffee: Cappuccino.LAYER FIVE:--Smoke: ew.Cuss: bitch never.Sing: yes. very well on good days.Take a shower everyday: sometimes two.Have a crush(es): right now, boys make me gag. im after your piercings! watch out!Do you think you've been in love: o yeah.Want to go to college: yeah.Like(d) high school: uh. not really.Want to get married: someday.Believe in yourself: Yep, no one else does.Get motion sickness: no.Think you're attractive: actually, yes. okay...no. well, sortof.Think you're a health freak: hahahahaHAHAHA! no.Get along with your parent(s): haha again! no. again.Like thunderstorms: hecks yeah, they scare my kittys, and they run all over and pee on things.Play an instrument: piano.LAYER SIX:--In the past month have you...Drank alcohol: yes.Smoked: like i said. ew!Done a drug: nope. cept for mydol.Had Sex: no.Made Out: yes.Gone on a date: not really...Gone to the mall: yes.Eaten an entire box of Oreos: i tried.Eaten sushi: o yeah!Been dumped: no...dont make me feel guilty.Gone skating: ish.Made homemade cookies: nope. thank god.Gone skinny dipping: wanted to.Dyed your hair: i wish.Stolen anything: depends on what you consider "stealing." heh heh.Sex with a dead horse: fuck yeah! that bitch was good too. have you seen a horny horse? my god they have big penises!LAYER SEVEN:--Ever...Played a game that required removal of clothing: haha. never...If so, was it mixed company: yeah.Been trashed or extremely intoxicated: ME?!Been caught "doing something": oops...Been called a tease:haha yeah...Gotten beaten up: please...i will beat the burgers out of you.Shoplifted: no.Changed who you are to fit in: i dont even remember who i am...i tend to change anyways. but not intentionally...LAYER EIGHT:--Age you hope to be married: at least fourty.How do you want to die: in the middle of a really good fuck...perhaps with the nurse who thought he was gay...at least until he worked at my nursing home :).Where you want to go to college: anywhere, as long as its california.What do you want to be when you grow up: a prostitute. no really. sounds fun...okay maybe a teacher.What country would you most like to visit: italy.LAYER NINE:--Best eye color: green?Best hair color: blonde! them blonde bitches rule. o wait, pink!Short or long hair: on who? me? fuck i dont know.Height: o this is about guys...heh around six feet ish.Best weight: buff kids weigh alot, and really, i dont know what that is.Best articles of clothing: your lacies.Best first date location: anywhere, like under bridges. with vodka. and increased sexual energy.Best first kiss location: first kiss? uh...well...somewhere where everyone can see. you know, like witnesses.LAYER TEN:--Number of scars on your body: four that i notice.Number of drugs taken illegally: none.Number of people I could trust with my life: i dont count these things, because that often changes.Number of CDs that I own: i dont count that either, jesus.Number of piercings: ear and ear. tried nipple. not going there.Number of tattoos: none.Number of times my name has appeared in a newspaper: once or twice. im good! famous!Number of things in my past that I regret: o god....too many.   urlLink 7:52 PM  -  urlLink 1 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   well...  i dont like name acronyms...i am sensational, accurate, raw, accurate again, and handy. i sound like a vibrator.   urlLink 3:39 PM  -  urlLink 0 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   Saturday, July 03, 2004  wondering.  is it a crime that i feel really hot today? that i touched myself in inapropriet places this morning? that i am not sure if what i have is what is right? that i am damn sure i am damn cute...that i laugh at my own jokes? that i even tell jokes? that i want to party and be free without the chains of something so serious weighing me down? something so committed? i love you kid, but i cannot handle such things, such jealousy and accusations. is that a crime too?   urlLink 8:48 AM  -  urlLink 1 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   all i want for christmas  is a long board and a digital camera. for now.   urlLink 6:41 PM  -  urlLink 0 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   Wednesday, June 30, 2004  ME AND SHANNON CONVERSATION [u must read this]  wanna see how retarded we are when we think about guys with peircings:FranklenIsMyFrog: 9. THE FIRST THING YOU NOTICE ABOUT THE OPPOSITE SEX?FranklenIsMyFrog: haha sorry i had to askFranklenIsMyFrog: lol okAbstinanceroX: hmmmAbstinanceroX: hmmmmAbstinanceroX: justen?AbstinanceroX: HMMMAbstinanceroX: his lip ringsAbstinanceroX: man those are hotFranklenIsMyFrog: ohh fuck i knowFranklenIsMyFrog: i love them... haha tommysAbstinanceroX: o fuck peircings drive me liekAbstinanceroX: omgAbstinanceroX: orgasmicFranklenIsMyFrog: and nipples too!FranklenIsMyFrog: fuckk me toooAbstinanceroX: O FUCKFranklenIsMyFrog: HAHAbstinanceroX: AAAAHAbstinanceroX: I LOVE THEMFranklenIsMyFrog: ME FUCKING TOOFranklenIsMyFrog: there soo hotAbstinanceroX: omg i knowAbstinanceroX: we should get shirts that say "show me all your peircings"AbstinanceroX: heheAbstinanceroX: ALL of themFranklenIsMyFrog: haha that would be awesome!AbstinanceroX: lolAbstinanceroX: lalalaaaaaaaaaFranklenIsMyFrog: manFranklenIsMyFrog: lol you got me thinking about pircingsFranklenIsMyFrog: making out with guys with lip pirced is soo much nicer than guys with out themAbstinanceroX: oooh shitAbstinanceroX: i knowAbstinanceroX: oooh shit omgAbstinanceroX: lolFranklenIsMyFrog: ahhFranklenIsMyFrog: hottAbstinanceroX: im all giddy nowAbstinanceroX: lolFranklenIsMyFrog: me too!!FranklenIsMyFrog: I WANNA MAKE OUT WITH TOMMY AGAIN!FranklenIsMyFrog: lolAbstinanceroX: LOLAbstinanceroX: AH i miss my justenFranklenIsMyFrog: aww!!AbstinanceroX: fucking lip ringsAbstinanceroX: omgAbstinanceroX: nipplesAbstinanceroX: lolAbstinanceroX: and his TONGUE!FranklenIsMyFrog: AH HOTAbstinanceroX: I KNOWFranklenIsMyFrog: hahahaha im like laughing, smileing nowAbstinanceroX: hehehe me tooRETARDED!!! but you gotta have something that makes you quiver right? besides cheesecake...   urlLink 10:16 PM  -  urlLink 3 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   Sunday, June 27, 2004  oh  this is what i sent to thomas. just because i feel like puttin it in hurrr.TOMMY?! you gotta my space huh? so you can talk to shaaanny huh?! hows it going pimpsicle? hey justen is not a whore biatch! he is MY whore. like hecks yeah. when i get back to warsh-ing-ton...mmm mmm. you know what...so anyways. how are yall?im bored as a mother fucker!woohoo! one handing typing at the moment.aka: masturbation time. happy moment.   urlLink 8:43 PM  -  urlLink 3 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   Wednesday, June 23, 2004  at justens  oooh its 12:18! im such a bad kid! rar! well you know how it is. hey i made up this song on my way down the hill. its pretty stupid but i was bored.damn i forget how it goes. it was like ish:im sarah rohrim a fucking whorei can screwcan youi like to screwdo youmaybe one or twothree or fouror even morecuz im whatim sarah rooooooooooooooooooooohr[uh repeat i guess?]it was the shit when i remembered like the beat and stuff. but i forget these things. yeah. o well.   urlLink 12:18 AM  -  urlLink 1 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      im funny. and i love myself. so im going to make a list to cheer my self up.  ten things i like about me...NO ten things i love about me...no that sounds gay. I GOT IT: ten things i adore about myself:  one: hmmm. im funny two: i am passionate! in an odd...obsessive way three: i am a great thinker, weee four: i am not perfect, i mean...that is great... five: i CAN keep a secret. if im payed six: i dig my shoes seven: i complement people, even if it is after i sortof dis on them... eight: i listen to good music! and that makes me even cooler! says thomas nine: i have great respect for people who earn it... ten: i dunno, im not embarrassed that i made this gay list  okay...one more  eleven: i look really hot today, in a scrubby mis matched way, but god... i would do me. 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so i asked justen back out. it went something along the lines of...  so do you think we should...you know...maybe...uuuuuuuuh....GETBACKTOGETHER. there, i said it.  i dont really remember, but i guess it was funny. i mean, its not like we dont fuck and seriously adore eachother or anything. and its not like we dont fuck. did i say that? 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      had sex on the top bunk. im still waiting for the bathroom counter. hmmm, doggy style wouldnt be bad either, ya know?  some shit from myspace, cuz im deleting it all!   Monday, July 26, 2004  oops  omg. last night, we snuck out, made a video [me justen and tommy] and then tommy left and we got nachos at like four in the morning...then...i woke up, passed out and "went to school' haha ok so i skipped...AND THEN...i went to the skate park with justen and zach. oops gtg BYE GROUNDED   urlLink 5:52 PM  -  urlLink 1 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   people are dumb  like sarah leveing her thing log in just for me too play with hehehehe......she's in the shower right now naked :P will i am off to do somethings.   urlLink 11:31 AM  -  urlLink 0 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   hmmm.  what is the point of a mosh pit anyways? hehe. all i saw was push shove squish squeal almost die stage diving shit. but hey, its all fun. besides you get all hot and sweaty and excited and you jump and dance and make funny jirating movements with your whole self and head bang and scream out lyrics you might not even know! def fun. so so fun.   urlLink 8:01 PM  -  urlLink 0 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   o so much entertainment.  tsunami bomb was awesome last night! i jumped into the pit eventually. weee, i almost died. then we went to a party, i was pretty drunk. watched some guys skate around on this dudes ramp in his BACK YARD! haha! but surfing was awesoooome. def going again! so tired, but i want to see everyone tonight, god two and a half days and i already feel disconnected. hmmm, justen is nowhere to be found. arg.   urlLink 7:59 PM  -  urlLink 0 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   Friday, July 23, 2004  OMG. again.  okie dokie. i cannot decide whether i want people who come strait to my profile to read this, or only those who look at my blogs. i was going to put it in my about me, but i think i would scare the fuck out of some people. so lets just post as a blog for now. :) personality: i am great fun. i tend to be a ditz, more out of habit than genuwine stupidity. i love art! especially music, but then again i love films, and visual art...hmmm. lets just stick with i love art. im a definate people lover! i try to get people to add me, but i think i come off as too obsessive. it must be my million compliment messages: "youre a doll, you have lovely taste in music, i dig those plugs!" o well. i will hump anything with piercings [obvious rephrase right there]. so beware! i can be violent, and i deeply apologize to my future children, who i have large worries will end up in foster care. i can be emotional, but i get so lost in my thoughts. i am not sure whether i truley feel it, or if its just pms or dramatics overtaking my complex subconcious brain! i fear the drama in myself, and the fact i might overdo everything. and i fear my fear. errlack. i love romantic things. but dont&nbsp;like it too much in my own relationships. i am almost too tomboy to be mushy gushy. but o the italians. those sexy accents, find me a man like that and i will melt beneath his tan palms. i love movies that are mushy. modern mush sucks though! give me something with audrey hepburn. now there is a classy lady. old movies where men treated their sweethearts like a glass vase. and yet the women adored the men, the charm in those movies. thats what i love. i have tons of nicknames, i can try to remember them: sars, sarsicle, honey bunnie, wifie, henrietta, sarah the rohr, sally flaxx, sweet cheeks, chomper, omg. i give in. too many! on food: food is wonderfull. someday, i will weigh 343984309 pounds, and still enjoy and good meal, triple chins or no. on school: i love the people at my school, especially some of the freshmen next year. little boys are so entertaining. god i think most girls hate me. i am not sure why, i am really friendly and i love to by my chick bitches presents :). it must be that i dont really wear makeup or care to straiten my kinky hair. on habits: mine include: stopping in the middle of everything to think, biting my nails, loud and violent, taking one or two or three showers per day, indulging in a half gallon of ice cream, snooping around in closets and medicine cabinets, correcting peoples spelling mistakes, spending my day on the internet, dreading to drop in! on anything else: random things i like or love: tea, oh them piercings, pineapple, different cultures, italian shoes, sparrows and kittens, feeling loved, declaration. what i love about me: my many faces, i do like my ever changing eyes, i am truley a great thinker-even if i do have to stop in the street to accomplish it, i can ignore the idiots in the world and accept the fact that there will always be people who hate you. realize youre brilliance, and move on. what i hate about me: i cry so easily, my hair sucks, i am too lazy to do much of anything, i dont always believe in myself, and the fact i even care about all of those. what i wish people knew: i may seem shallow or apathetic, but i think very much about all i do, except for when the temper gets going... the slightest thing effects me greatly, so i try to teach myself to move on. sometimes, it really is about making yourself happy, especially in cases where nobody else WILL be. i am an intellegent person, but i rarely show it because i think subconciously i fear people knowing i am smart. o well, thats how it goes! life is so damn short, stop dreading, and get what you want done with already! [and to end the bit of "about me"] the last bit: i am proud of you who read all that! leave me a comment that says "sarsicle owes me a dollar" and ill be sure to send one your way for being such a good sport. [rather, that was me paying for popularity. im a sneaky little whore!] not really, thanks for reading all that, but no dolla gangsta! end.  urlLink 12:07 AM  -  urlLink 3 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   ugh.  what an hour for my hair to be truley perfect.   urlLink 11:44 PM  -  urlLink 0 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   weee.  haha. i recieved a really funny email from some guy that read something along the lines of : punk rock girl you are hot and sexy and marry me! blah blah blah, and he must have stumbled upon my blogs or realized i was agnostic...cuz this guys profile made him out to look like a high believer, and he got scared away. silly little boys. so easy to intimidate them. at least there are a few true dudes out there i can count on. i love you all :).   urlLink 11:40 PM  -  urlLink 0 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   surfing and a show.  woo. i am gonna go see tsunami bomb, pipedown, and this other band i forget who this saturday. tomorrow though, i will be drowning :). surfing! i am so weak, im gonna die. i dont think my ten pounders will match ocean currents. o well, i am a tough kid. sorta...all i can say is: i hope this fifteen bucks is enough to afford a tshirt, hmmm. maybe i can scronge around for another ten or so and get brittany something too. i think she would like that, shes such a doll, this girl :).or would she just be happy with an autograph??? hmmm. i got it! if i somehow get beaten up or drugged or die, and cannot make it to agent m, i will buy her something. i gots it all planned out. :) wee.alright...so! i am going to die surfing, then die during the show, and come back with loads more hot effin pictures. o jesus, but nobody show them to roger roberts. i swear he went into boner land at the skate park. effin perverts!so...what a great blog. end.   urlLink 8:20 PM  -  urlLink 0 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   *yawn*  eek. three nights in a row. one to just hang, one to watch fireworks, and one to return batteries. SO...hmmm. i am bored! woo!   urlLink 8:22 PM  -  urlLink 1 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   Monday, July 19, 2004  omg!!! OMFG!  Looking at your pics..you have a great look!...very photogenic..Hard Edge...hope your modeling. Take it Easy... Aaron ah. i love this dude.   urlLink 10:09 PM  -  urlLink 1 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   im over it.  ok..so i was a bitch about that whole religious thing. i just cannot stand this whole idea of a higher power...and my oppinions take over me. but honestly, religious people can be such hippocrates. it pisses me off. i cannot even give you the list of examples i have, because the last four convos i had were full of them. if youre going to be defensive about god, shouldnt you do it in a "godly" way? do you get me? not be so...what they think just involves being an athiest. well actually i am more agnostic. but today the bitterness was revealed. omg. this is like. at least fifteen posts today.   urlLink 9:21 PM  -  urlLink 4 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   get over it again!!!  Boobalu3689: hiBoobalu3689: SO you deal with your problems by blocking ppl?Boobalu3689: Figures..sexnpineapple: omg dont even start. its a joke, sorry if you attend church every sunday, but this has nothing to do with the real god...it has to do with justenBoobalu3689: then why did you say all that shit?Boobalu3689: exampleBoobalu3689: sexnpineapple: he will liveDongcicle: You dont fucking relize Jr do you?sexnpineapple: tell him to cry and pray to god donovan.Dongcicle: Thats really pissing him off sarah.sexnpineapple: god will make it alright.Boobalu3689: and so u blocked donovan?Boobalu3689: because you know he is right.Boobalu3689: that you are being fucking disrespectfullBoobalu3689: just change your namesexnpineapple: psh dude, i dont give a fuck.Boobalu3689: im not asking you to kill someone for meBoobalu3689: thats cause you are a bitchBoobalu3689: ofcourse you dont give a fuckBoobalu3689: heyBoobalu3689: ahBoobalu3689: nmBoobalu3689: i give upsexnpineapple: you can live with it. damn strait! go smoke some weed or somethingand then jr calls me. and my mom hung up on him. my mom kicks ass!   urlLink 8:23 PM  -  urlLink 1 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   get over it.  Dongcicle: Are you seriously trying to piss me and jr off?Dongcicle: Dont you fucking relize that Jr is really religiouse?Dongcicle: That offends him.sexnpineapple: well dude! it has nothing to do with the actual jesus...he can deal with itDongcicle: Stop being a bitch Sarah. Please change it.Dongcicle: Have you completly lost your mind?Dongcicle: Just cause you dont belive in God doesent mean you have to be a bitch about other people doing it.Dongcicle: Who cares if it is a joke.Dongcicle: Change it.sexnpineapple: no! stop being a retard donovan. i get offended when people preach to me, and i deal with that...so he can deal with this, why doesnt he just delete me? sexnpineapple: it is a joke about justensexnpineapple: he will liveDongcicle: What the hell is your problem Sarah? How am I being retarded?Dongcicle: You dont fucking relize Jr do you?sexnpineapple: tell him to cry and pray to god donovan.Dongcicle: Thats really pissing him off sarah.sexnpineapple: god will make it alright.Dongcicle: Well you are talking to him.Dongcicle: Now anyway..i am honestly sorry if i truley offended anyone...but its a joke about justen! if youre going to be an ass hole about it, of course im not going to do what you say. isnt that in the bible or something?   urlLink 8:07 PM  -  urlLink 0 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   beauty is a crime.  some chicks are so pretty i want to chop off there heads and smack them down on my neck. its not fair. why cant i have cute little freckles or pouty lips or high cheek bones or a button nose or perfect hair! AH THAT GETS ME!!! perfect hair. why cant my hair be perfect? or my skin flawless. this obsession has to stop. haha.   urlLink 8:06 PM  -  urlLink 2 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   rock out til you cock out.  this is my eleventh post today. i rock. that quote up there i stole from liz, even though i am posative she is not the creator. but i love her! shes so smart, and says everything i have tried but failed...so well! liz if only you would comment. maybe ill call you and see if we can go to a show together.   urlLink 10:04 AM  -  urlLink 0 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   Monday, July 19, 2004  little story.  since i have absolutely nothing to occupy my time, im going to write you all a story.my grama was a bitch. seriously. she grew up with eight bros and sisters. she raised the young ones after her mom died [having her tenth kid]. my grama was only thirteen. her father, was mario carmen ferraro. i think i spelled that right. he was an opera conductor, who i believe might have been famous, but that was in the early nineteen hundreds, even late eighteen hundreds. her father, moving on, went a tad nuts after his wife passed away, and sortof faded off. grama grew up in chicago and sang [sung?] in a nightclub at sixteen, and i think she used her earnings to support her family during the depression...so you see, she had a really hard life, but she picked up vanity and jealousy from her older sisters. they beat grama sometimes, telling her she wasnt pretty enough...and so on. grama did the same thing to my mom, and this is what makes her a bitch: she stands my mother, so young, in front of a mirror and tells her: look at your big nose, your short legs, youll never be as pretty as me. or something like that...and mom grew up to be a softy. much better than grama, who constantly "knew" that women hated her because they were jealous of her dainty figure and good looks. but i think most of moms personal issues came from the way she was raised. mom went on to marry a man, glen, my sisters dad. he cheated on her and left one day, i hear, without saying much to mom at all. my sister was really little, i remember mom saying, and she would cry because glens girlfriend would show off her young boy infront of my sister, and not pay much attention to jeannie at all.mom married nelson next. i loved this guy. she had my brother i think when my little sister was six. he grew up to love trains...but when nelsons father passed away, he grew deppressed, and soon that marraige had ended.and then...my dad. he conned my mother, he cleaned up for her, pretended he was a good jahova wittness...followed his morals, but soon his habits snuck back in. he sometimes would get violent...he left one day, took her credit cards, bought things, the good car, o god everything cost mom so much. and i dont even remember this dude. i was two.lets see...im terribly awefull at writing stories like these. i truley suck. but now that you have succeeded in baring through my bad spelling and prose...i congradulate you. haha. but im not done...so mom married ed. he can be a bit of a dick. but thank god hes not like the other men...she finally followed good advice: never marry a man out of guilt, and never marry a man to change him.OK NOW IM DONE. bored bored bored. lalala.   urlLink 9:49 AM  -  urlLink 0 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   sugar.  how am i supposed to watch my sugar intake if mom keeps buying me chocolate graham crackers?   urlLink 9:47 AM  -  urlLink 0 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   the shoes.  fucking converse. too many cute shoes. can anyone tell i have nada to do?http://converse.com/zproductmatrix.asp?zcatid=2&zsubcatid=&amp;zgenid=2&exclusiveid=&amp;zstyleid=&page=0&amp;leftnavid=1&leftnavsubid=   urlLink 9:40 AM  -  urlLink 0 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   effin effer.  my blog is effin up and making me effin mad. it says i posted o what a night and random stuff today. hello?! loser?! i did not you effin effer.   urlLink 9:25 AM  -  urlLink 0 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   this thing i found.  you of the moment:they call me: sarahsex: vaginaeye: greenhair: brunetteskin: pale as caspernails: blacktoenails: pinkrings on your fingers: justens, christiesmusic of the moment: ah, you caught me listening to blink 182, but it doesnt count cuz its on the radiomusic want of the moment: i just bought it: rock against bushfav feature: hmmm. not my ass, not my lips, not my hands. my tan line!your opposite of the moment:turn on: piercings, skate skills.turn off: being a dickhead about blow jobs. youre not getting one.love that: quirk, when you talk you form a shocker with your right hand. [justen you perv]hate that: isnt this like the same as what turns me on...o no i guess not. hate that over protectivenesswant that: roman guy buttneed that: tongue piercinghad that: oral HAHAHA!looks like: jesus with lip rings, maybe they put you on the cross wrong, justenwishes:you wish you could outside: skateyou wish you could inside: none of your buisnessyou wish you could in the kitchen: cook periodyou wish you could in the bedroom: what odd things this person thought of.you want right now: havent i told you all? digital camerayou wanted and you got: tight pantsyou wanted and you couldnt get: a blazer to go with my tight pantsfavs:drink: ginnon alcoholic: tomatoe juicefruit: pineappleveggie: carrots?meat: i dont really like much, chicken is good and bacon. mostly i like copper river salmon.carb: potato breadcolor: pinkshoe: my converse :) they are so cuteshirt: ummm. god. i had a shirt but it got stolen, my lib tech one. *cries*pants: yey for gap jeans. my butt looks good in themshow: this show called blow out, about a bitchy guy who owns a salonband: omg. jesus. way too many. but i know all the eagles songs so them.solo artist: uuuh. tom petty, eric claptin or van morrison. one of them kids.movie: rocky horror picture show! so creepy.radio: kgrg, its always on, i never change it.your odd quirks:what is it: i have alot: not admitting i like blink, cuz i fucking dont; stopping to think in the middle of walking somewhere, like on the stairs going to class; just calling people names not knowing where they came from: like jesus, or lover.people think youre: loud, violent, annoying.but sometimes you can be: completely serious, quiet, and omg...MATURE.the side no one sees: and the side you will never see: me unhappy, cuz i always find a way to be when people are around. or me completely serious. this only happens in the depths of my room when im hard at work on some unsuccessful failure of an art project.one comment to add: you ask the wierdest things, whoever made this.   urlLink 8:45 AM  -  urlLink 0 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   im calm now.  ok but this was kind of funny:emo emo everywhere,emo emo dye my hairbuy some glassesblack and thinthrift shop stealing?thats a SINemo emo make me cryemo emo kiss goodbyelisten to those whiny boysand play with all those emo toysso slap on a sweaterand join the clanBecause im emo's number one fan!!some chick posted that...hahaha. i mean, you have to laugh right?!   urlLink 8:40 AM  -  urlLink 0 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   the internet is stupid.  what is up with people who make sites like: how to dress emo...?!?!?!?!?!? do you have nothing better to do than catagorize your "scene" shit?! arg. things like that piss me off. why cant you just wear what you want and not be labeled? like...wtf. it is so dumb. are we not old enough to get past this? if you arent "emo" you arent "emo". why would you want to be something your not cuz its the "scene"?! its so...dumb. idiotic. naive. i mean sure, we all have a look we go for, but for some reason, that pushed my anger button. dont even get me started on the "non conformist" thing.   urlLink 8:28 AM  -  urlLink 0 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   fucking old!  this site is so old. i never go there ne more:http://www.xanga.com/home.aspx?user=rohrforsonicare   urlLink 7:57 AM  -  urlLink 0 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   BAM.  somehow i lived through 61 pages of people who live five miles within 98092, only have pictures and are between 18 and 100. i am so fuckin bored.   urlLink 7:22 AM  -  urlLink 0 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   ah fuck.  some person called me sexy last night. im feeling pretty good. and uh i did that damn thing where i mean to post a blog but i post a bulletin. so not good. so dumb. well here you go:i hooked up my computer, from my room, onto moms monitor, in the office, WITH THE INTERNET...so i can sit here until normal people wake up. i am good. i seriously never thought of doing that...maybe cuz my computer weighs like fifty pounds? thats ok...im a strong chick. sorta. whatever, its just mom takes the main computer...well laptop to work..and i NEED this thing. i am just...good.end.   urlLink 6:46 AM  -  urlLink 0 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   random stuff.  i want a digital camera. so i can take naughty pictures of myself... ah, not really, just good ones. someone should take photogrophy with me so we can make bad ass pictures and put them on things. i dunno, it sounds fun. i want to cut my hair again, shorter and sexier. and i need a better straitener. my curling iron is getting angry at me... its hot, i need to clean my mouse cage, i need to take a shower, i need to get rid of my head ache too! eick. crappy day. its like a late reaction hangover or something. what are you kids doing tomorrow!? i am going to wake justen up, and we are going to learn me to skate. perhaps ill even ollie more than like a half inch off the ground! woohoo. im bored as fuck.   urlLink 4:08 PM  -  urlLink 1 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   o what a night!  woo. got "grenaded" last night with my best buddies justen and shannon and thomas! and ok...first, when we were sneaking out...shannon tried to jump off the fence and almost killed herself, and i was laughing so hard i tried to pee in someones yard, and their dog barked...and i didnt want them to wake up and find me so i grabbed my pants and ran for what we used to call the fort. and then...i peed! and then we went to justens and popped open a bottle, and sat around and talked, and some how we all ended up getting naked...i dunno it was really hot in justens room and BAM we were hanging out all over the place. and theeen...shannon and i drew pictures when we were drunk, and we made a video tape of our non sober idiocy. and theeen...OH, they wanted to go on a walk, so we were going to albertons, and tommy was skating justens board and fell and diondre grabbed it. so i chased him and smacked him really hard in the face and tried to grab the board...but since im all white he was like threatening to beat me up...so he like threw the board to daniel and dan like ran with it, and i was fucking you know, being stupid and pissed off...and who knows where tommy and shannon went, and i dunno where justen was either, so they were both like coming at me and i freaked and was like JUSTEN and then...he showed up and somehow i got hit in the back with a watermellon. ok so THEEEN...we went into albertsons and had to go, but there were cops everywhere...so we went the back way...but by the time we got there, diondre and his like..black posse people were all together and they were all really pissed cuz "some white bitch" hit him...lalala...wasnt me...and THEEEN, we finally went home. or well, to justens, and stayed inside. and i get angry when im drunk so i kept getting mad at justen for touching me...but he said he wouldnt do it and then he did again...and i was like AH. so then he like crawled out his window cuz he was pissed off at me...and i felt bad but i was too drunk to cry. so moving on...eventually it was time to go home and me and thomas ate some pizza and drank some juicey stuff...and we walked up the hill...we had to keep stopping cuz lazy ass shanny and tommy were taking for like ever. but yeah, we got home and i almost died trying to get on the roof...and shannon got up there alright...and...we went to bed. TADA.   urlLink 4:42 PM  -  urlLink 2 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   Thursday, July 15, 2004  the continuation.  sexnpineapple: GEEZFranklenIsMyFrog: hiFranklenIsMyFrog: lolsexnpineapple: and whats your damn excuse?!sexnpineapple: lolFranklenIsMyFrog: my computer fucked upFranklenIsMyFrog: lolsexnpineapple: o ok lolsexnpineapple: has it been fucking other computers again?sexnpineapple: hello...that thing needs birth controlFranklenIsMyFrog: hah ayeasexnpineapple: your gonna have little baby computers all over the placesexnpineapple: omg im bored!FranklenIsMyFrog: lol me to!sexnpineapple: nothing to dosexnpineapple: well tomorrowsexnpineapple: this timesexnpineapple: my parents will be heading off to hit the sheetssexnpineapple: and we will be dressing ourselves all pretty...and sneaking outsexnpineapple: and BAMFranklenIsMyFrog: YAY!sexnpineapple: fucking our brains out! ok maybe not...but close!FranklenIsMyFrog: lolFranklenIsMyFrog: im exciteddddddddsexnpineapple: AH ME TOOsexnpineapple: lalalasexnpineapple: lalalalasexnpineapple: lolsexnpineapple: hahasexnpineapple: justen has a camerasexnpineapple: like a real onesexnpineapple: huge too!sexnpineapple: we should video tape ourselvessexnpineapple: lolFranklenIsMyFrog: haha awesomesexnpineapple: and watch it when we are sobersexnpineapple: and see what idiots we aresexnpineapple: like singing songssexnpineapple: and asking where we aresexnpineapple: lolFranklenIsMyFrog: lolFranklenIsMyFrog: its gonan be so funnysexnpineapple: haha i knowsexnpineapple: god..i want to pierce my tongueFranklenIsMyFrog: fuck me toFranklenIsMyFrog: my mom would kill me thoughsexnpineapple: we should have justen do it...yeah but we can hide it...its not that hardsexnpineapple: lolFranklenIsMyFrog: haha we couldsexnpineapple: just talk slowly and with your mouth semi closedsexnpineapple: lolFranklenIsMyFrog: lol it would hurt soo badFranklenIsMyFrog: but it would be so cool!sexnpineapple: i pierced my nipple shannon. i know pain. its not that bad...FranklenIsMyFrog: haha go sarahsexnpineapple: it hurtsexnpineapple: but...it would have been better if we used a clampsexnpineapple: it would have gone faster and hurt lessFranklenIsMyFrog: lolsexnpineapple: yeah it isnt in though..cuz like the ring wouldnt go in and it closed upsexnpineapple: stupid lol!FranklenIsMyFrog: haha FranklenIsMyFrog: lol that would be so awesome, if we did ours tomorrow (tounges)FranklenIsMyFrog: i would be nervise about my momsexnpineapple: lolsexnpineapple: fuck me toosexnpineapple: but like...sexnpineapple: o wellsexnpineapple: lol]FranklenIsMyFrog: hahasexnpineapple: hmmmsexnpineapple: i am seriously considering thisFranklenIsMyFrog: i am toFranklenIsMyFrog: lolsexnpineapple: lolFranklenIsMyFrog: i would love to have mine donesexnpineapple: ill prally cry though hahasexnpineapple: but o wellFranklenIsMyFrog: lol i probally would tosexnpineapple: lol i am such a wimpFranklenIsMyFrog: me to!sexnpineapple: i cried when he pierced my nippleFranklenIsMyFrog: i hate painFranklenIsMyFrog: lolsexnpineapple: eick me toosexnpineapple: but it would be awesomeFranklenIsMyFrog: I KNOW!FranklenIsMyFrog: hahasexnpineapple: like hmmm...saturday and sunday i will be home though...eek lolFranklenIsMyFrog: ill probally be home saturday, not sunday thoughsexnpineapple: what r u doing?FranklenIsMyFrog: lol i could some how get out of my hosueFranklenIsMyFrog: going to katssexnpineapple: lol me toosexnpineapple: prally i could like... hmm just do chores all daysexnpineapple: and not talk to them muchsexnpineapple: and then monday they go to work and by tuesday i think you can take it out for a whileFranklenIsMyFrog: yeaFranklenIsMyFrog: ah i want to so fucking bad, but if my mom sees shell be fucking pistsexnpineapple: AH mine toosexnpineapple: shit and think of ed...sexnpineapple: omg lolFranklenIsMyFrog: hahahaFranklenIsMyFrog: he would flipsexnpineapple: we should stop at bartells and buy that numming stuffsexnpineapple: for you teethsexnpineapple: lolsexnpineapple: see if it worksFranklenIsMyFrog: but then if she did see it, i think she would be pist at me, and like ground me and tell me to take it out. but if i didnt i think she would get over itFranklenIsMyFrog: hahasexnpineapple: it might work?sexnpineapple: it worked for my lips lolFranklenIsMyFrog: lolsexnpineapple: god i want tooooFranklenIsMyFrog: lol when tomorrow comes, ask me when im drunk, haha see what i say thensexnpineapple: lolsexnpineapple: kFranklenIsMyFrog: haha ill end up saying yes thensexnpineapple: haha me toosexnpineapple: but you dont feel as much pain when youre drunk...sooooFranklenIsMyFrog: lol thats goodsexnpineapple: yepsexnpineapple: so im thinking more of a yessexnpineapple: but even when i pinch my tongue it hurtssexnpineapple: lolFranklenIsMyFrog: i knowsexnpineapple: lolFranklenIsMyFrog: i think i would like sream and then start cryingFranklenIsMyFrog: lolsexnpineapple: lolFranklenIsMyFrog: then freak outsexnpineapple: i screamed when he did my nipplesexnpineapple: lolsexnpineapple: i was like ah ahaAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAHsexnpineapple: lolFranklenIsMyFrog: hahaFranklenIsMyFrog: lol that would be so cool. lol it would be a memory between me and u!sexnpineapple: yeah!sexnpineapple: me and shannon pierced our tongues together!FranklenIsMyFrog: YAYFranklenIsMyFrog: lolFranklenIsMyFrog: while we were drunkFranklenIsMyFrog: !@!sexnpineapple: yey!sexnpineapple: its hard to eat though..like...the next daysexnpineapple: ill ask mom to make uhh pudding or something for breakfastFranklenIsMyFrog: hahasexnpineapple: be like...mom we are having pudding...hehe (ow)FranklenIsMyFrog: hahasexnpineapple: amber loves hers though so..FranklenIsMyFrog: im thinking i could just tell my brother to come and get me, and then i could stay with him all day... and then go to kats.. and then it would be monday and my mom would be at work so yeasexnpineapple: yeah! lolFranklenIsMyFrog: ive been wanting mine done for a long timesexnpineapple: and i can just suffer haha kiddingFranklenIsMyFrog: lolsexnpineapple: we totally shouldFranklenIsMyFrog: haha we shouldsexnpineapple: hmmsexnpineapple: yeah!sexnpineapple: lolFranklenIsMyFrog: dude im so nervise but so exictedsexnpineapple: me tooFranklenIsMyFrog: haha and then all of us would have our tounges pirced! u me justen tommysexnpineapple: tommys tongue is pierced? wow..sexnpineapple: i did not noticesexnpineapple: lolsexnpineapple: O YEAH THATS RIGHTsexnpineapple: justen did itFranklenIsMyFrog: lol yeasexnpineapple: its way better making out with guys with tongue rings toosexnpineapple: way funnerFranklenIsMyFrog: lol oh funnFranklenIsMyFrog: cant waitFranklenIsMyFrog: lolsexnpineapple: i have so many bands on my my spaceFranklenIsMyFrog: lolFranklenIsMyFrog: guess who im listening to!?sexnpineapple: uhsexnpineapple: blink 182?sexnpineapple: lolFranklenIsMyFrog: nopesexnpineapple: ummmsexnpineapple: i dont know...FranklenIsMyFrog: TSUNAMI BOMB!sexnpineapple: tsunami bomb!FranklenIsMyFrog: lolsexnpineapple: O second guess im goodsexnpineapple: i am going to see them...sexnpineapple: r u coming?FranklenIsMyFrog: proballysexnpineapple: you should get tickets like soonsexnpineapple: cuz my mom only bought two! lolsexnpineapple: shes like fuck no im buying two and thats itsexnpineapple: i was like oh ok..FranklenIsMyFrog: lol kFranklenIsMyFrog: i donnosexnpineapple: they are only ten bucks sexnpineapple: you should lolsexnpineapple: or like...bring tommy with yousexnpineapple: lolFranklenIsMyFrog: lolsexnpineapple: bored so boreedsexnpineapple: lalalsexnpineapple: alkjsdlfkjsexnpineapple: brbsexnpineapple: god i hate justens brothersexnpineapple: such a dick head!FranklenIsMyFrog: lol whysexnpineapple: he hangs up on mesexnpineapple: lolsexnpineapple: no hes not clicksexnpineapple: lolsexnpineapple: fuuucksexnpineapple: justen was supposed to go home and sleep tongihtFranklenIsMyFrog: lolsexnpineapple: called your house. you are not there. too effin bad if you pass out tomorrow night huh?! i wont feel sorry for you. i can pierce my tongue by myself. yeah. so there. sexnpineapple: comment hahaFranklenIsMyFrog: who is that?sexnpineapple: justens thingsexnpineapple: lolFranklenIsMyFrog: ohh justenFranklenIsMyFrog: from usexnpineapple: hahasexnpineapple: yeahFranklenIsMyFrog: lolsexnpineapple: omg im so boredsexnpineapple: i think im gonna go to bed soonFranklenIsMyFrog: lolsexnpineapple: like hmmmsexnpineapple: nowsexnpineapple: lolsexnpineapple: night shannonsexnpineapple: lolFranklenIsMyFrog: hahaFranklenIsMyFrog: nightFranklenIsMyFrog: call me tomorrowsexnpineapple: ksexnpineapple: bye   urlLink 9:24 PM  -  urlLink 1 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   another convo to add to my list.  its really not that exciting...but im bored. tada:FranklenIsMyFrog: yosexnpineapple: heysexnpineapple: tell me about your dream!sexnpineapple: lolFranklenIsMyFrog: lol read ur commentFranklenIsMyFrog: i wrote it in theresexnpineapple: ooohsexnpineapple: okFranklenIsMyFrog: lolsexnpineapple: haha thats a huge commentFranklenIsMyFrog: lolFranklenIsMyFrog: it was a big dreamsexnpineapple: HAHA oh powder vodka not power lolFranklenIsMyFrog: haha yteasexnpineapple: hHAHAHAHA sarah bellomy!!!FranklenIsMyFrog: lolFranklenIsMyFrog: it was a cool dreamsexnpineapple: hahasexnpineapple: freakysexnpineapple: with all those kidsFranklenIsMyFrog: wooh tomorroowwwwsexnpineapple: AAAAAAAAAHsexnpineapple: fuck fuck fucksexnpineapple: i am so excitedFranklenIsMyFrog: me to!sexnpineapple: but this time, we cant let the boys seperate us, unless we want to go screw or something...BUT EVEN THEN, we are going to have fun together lolFranklenIsMyFrog: haha YES! its gonna be a good good time!sexnpineapple: YEYEYEYEYEEEEEEEEEEYsexnpineapple: YEYEYEYEYUAsklfjdslfkjrsexnpineapple: lolsexnpineapple: FUCKsexnpineapple: i have to give him money though....uhsexnpineapple: SHITsexnpineapple: lolFranklenIsMyFrog: lol i think i have somesexnpineapple: fuck fuck fucksexnpineapple: well i do too butsexnpineapple: he needs it soon...sexnpineapple: hmmmsexnpineapple: maybe i can get him to walk his ass up the hill tonightsexnpineapple: i skipped school today lolFranklenIsMyFrog: lol bad sarahsexnpineapple: and the lady called in...and i pretended i was my mom!sexnpineapple: i was like "oh shes throwing up all over" and thinking...would mom say that? lolsexnpineapple: but she believed me so hey!FranklenIsMyFrog: hahasexnpineapple: fuck i might get disconnectedsexnpineapple: brbFranklenIsMyFrog: ksexnpineapple: the phone cuts me off sometimes...sexnpineapple: o yeysexnpineapple: it didntFranklenIsMyFrog: yayFranklenIsMyFrog: what are we gonna do in the day tomorrowFranklenIsMyFrog: ?sexnpineapple: uhsexnpineapple: mom is making me be her slave!sexnpineapple: i have to fucking clean like everythingsexnpineapple: for an eight doller cdsexnpineapple: lolFranklenIsMyFrog: lol that sucksFranklenIsMyFrog: what cd?sexnpineapple: rock against bush!FranklenIsMyFrog: lolFranklenIsMyFrog: awesomesexnpineapple: ysysexnpineapple: ersexnpineapple: yes.sexnpineapple: lolsexnpineapple: woo i love itsexnpineapple: such good shitFranklenIsMyFrog is away at 8:26:48 PM. sexnpineapple: o yeah shannon...brb to you tooAuto response from FranklenIsMyFrog: brb   urlLink 8:35 PM  -  urlLink 1 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove   people write funny things.  Everybody loves an emo girl,With thick framed glasses,And cute choppy hair,And teeny little asses.Everybody likes a punk rock girl,With colors in their hair,That rocks and rolls,With studs everywhere.What about girls who cant make up their mind?Who toss and turn,When they dream of boys,And their stomachs churn.What about girls who like a little lace?Who dig short hair,Who want tight jeans,And not to care.What about girls who don’t fit in?Who listen to rock,And try to skate,And don’t suck cock.What about girls who wish they could?And gulp down gin,And paint their nails,And just can’t get in.What about girls like me?Who have very little friends.And try to make more,But the girls are all bitchy,And the guys are all busy,Just trying to score.So lost in the crap everyday.I don’t know who I am,So I tell my mom to fuck off,And the doors I slam.What can I do to stop this all?I will just calm down,And smile,And not frown.And what all this just never works?Then I’ll try to relax,And if I can’t,I’ll chop your dick off with an axe.tada. im bored. and congrats on not making any sence. like, am i the only one who understands that even "non-conformists" conform?   urlLink 8:55 PM  -  urlLink 0 Comments  -  urlLink Add Comment  -  urlLink Edit  -  Remove    i think it automatically deletes the super old ones. o fucking well. 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      right, yeah we didnt get back together, i am such a jealous bitch, maybe thats the only reason i wanted to. i am fucking lost. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      we didnt have sex that night but we did end up having it on my bed the next day after he woke me up. there was blood like everywhere, so we took a shower and shaved half of his&nbsp;ass. so funny.&nbsp;and then we went to go get some food after we did all of my chores. haha, we did my chores. such a sweet kid. and then we talked to roger and dillan and went home. and i couldnt sleep so i was on myspace like all night. finally passed out on the floor.&nbsp;woke up, went to wallmart to get a sleeping bag :) weee. and theeen, saw roger and dillan there, it was weird. so i am excited to go surfing, glad our ac is working again. i feel so, unvirginly all of a sudden. haha. poor justen, he felt bad cuz he came too soon. i dont really care, it still hurt, so i was actually more on the happy side. but sshh. maybe next time we can go for like, a whole five mins haha. only kidding.   
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i like it i love it, i want some more of it, o i try so hard to get a little of it! but my momma is a gay freak! and she wont let me! arg. fuck if the edit i made in my last blog doesnt work im gonna have a hissy fit...it still says "he go being a dick head..." when i wanted it "he wouldnt go being a dick head." reDICKulous. im so deprived. can anyone tell im horny?! jesus christ. 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      thats it. we are getting back together haha. this is gay! we still act like were together, and its not like i would want us to actually be apart... so yeah. he wouldnt go being a dickhead and say no right? hmmm...i dont think he would...i can always cry and make him feel bad. :) i want to have sweet sex tonight. ill bring a condom. woo!   
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       got drunk with tommy, justen shannon. it was fun cept for shannon moaning above us lol. damn again. so none of us our virgins...not amber nor justen nor shannon nor thomas nor i! how young are we? haha. young enough to get away with being stupid. did blogspot change its settings...it looks different. wow it did!  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      it hurt like a mother. i was drunk. zach, tommy, deven, amber, christie know. well yeah justen does too. lol duh. well...yeah. nothing feels different, why do people make it such a big deal?
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      summer school is odd. so we got back together and broke up again. for now we are just "fuck buddies". i laugh at that. how could i not? im a virgin. neways. i am over the guilty but donovan is being a total asswhole so poo on him. gtg mom
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      MoDeLsLuST: ? AbstinanceroX: ? MoDeLsLuST: ? AbstinanceroX: do i know u? MoDeLsLuST: no AbstinanceroX: ok MoDeLsLuST: y? AbstinanceroX: dunno MoDeLsLuST: did u see what justen put in his blog thing? AbstinanceroX: yes AbstinanceroX: i did MoDeLsLuST: o AbstinanceroX: so wait i really dont know you? MoDeLsLuST: not really MoDeLsLuST: i know u though MoDeLsLuST: u know MoDeLsLuST: this morning MoDeLsLuST: :-) AbstinanceroX:  this morning... AbstinanceroX: hmmm AbstinanceroX: i saw lotsa people like thismorning/lastnight AbstinanceroX: there was uh...justen and tommy and charlie and joe and spoon and chancey MoDeLsLuST: hehe AbstinanceroX: AH AbstinanceroX: im scared MoDeLsLuST: i luvd it AbstinanceroX: u luvd what? MoDeLsLuST: :-D AbstinanceroX: LOVED WHAT?! lol MoDeLsLuST: u never even asked for my name hehe MoDeLsLuST: hey MoDeLsLuST: do u know devon ryder? AbstinanceroX: no.. MoDeLsLuST: oh MoDeLsLuST: ok AbstinanceroX: so are you saying i should ask for your name? MoDeLsLuST: shouldent matter MoDeLsLuST: i wont tell u AbstinanceroX: o alright AbstinanceroX: so why are you talking to me? MoDeLsLuST: cause i am having this problem AbstinanceroX: ok MoDeLsLuST: and i got no one to talk too AbstinanceroX: does it have to deal with justen and i? AbstinanceroX: o alright AbstinanceroX: then it has to deal with you? AbstinanceroX: but i dont know you.. MoDeLsLuST: can u still help me?.. AbstinanceroX: sure i guess... MoDeLsLuST: well.. MoDeLsLuST: i did something bad MoDeLsLuST: and lied to my parents and friends about it AbstinanceroX: ok... MoDeLsLuST: and i dont know what i should do about it MoDeLsLuST: like... MoDeLsLuST: like talk to them about like it or something MoDeLsLuST: wut do u think AbstinanceroX: i am not sure AbstinanceroX: lol MoDeLsLuST: lol AbstinanceroX: i dont know you! AH MoDeLsLuST: so MoDeLsLuST: wut would u do AbstinanceroX: i guess i would tell someone? AbstinanceroX: i am not good at telling people things though so.. MoDeLsLuST: wut do u mean AbstinanceroX: i tend to keep things to myself AbstinanceroX: secrets AbstinanceroX: i guess MoDeLsLuST: o MoDeLsLuST: u still going out with justen? MoDeLsLuST: or am again or whatever MoDeLsLuST: like u know AbstinanceroX: yeah...but no im not AbstinanceroX: i am very very confused MoDeLsLuST: bout what AbstinanceroX: about like how we are MoDeLsLuST: o AbstinanceroX: i love the kid...but i felt like so attatched you know? MoDeLsLuST: ya AbstinanceroX: so i didnt want to get that serious and i broke it off AbstinanceroX: but we still like stayed together...and he is really upset about everything and i feel guilty...but you cant just date someone cuz you feel bad AbstinanceroX: you have to feel like you love them the same AbstinanceroX: wow i like not knowing you MoDeLsLuST: lol MoDeLsLuST: its okay MoDeLsLuST: i have no one to tell anyway heh MoDeLsLuST: i found you at myspace AbstinanceroX: really? MoDeLsLuST: ya MoDeLsLuST: thought u could help  MoDeLsLuST: cause we do the same things MoDeLsLuST: drink and lie to our friends AbstinanceroX: but how did you get my sn? i didnt think it was on there.. MoDeLsLuST: under instant message AbstinanceroX: o AbstinanceroX: O AbstinanceroX: haha MoDeLsLuST: lol MoDeLsLuST: ive been reading your blog thing for a while now MoDeLsLuST: i wanted to talk to u lol AbstinanceroX: o lol ok MoDeLsLuST: c we can be best friends MoDeLsLuST: and u can lie to me over and over and tell me you wont do that anymore MoDeLsLuST: it will be fun MoDeLsLuST: hehe AbstinanceroX: not really...i dont like lying to people... AbstinanceroX: i just feel like i have to AbstinanceroX: im an insecure kid MoDeLsLuST: why though... AbstinanceroX: i dont know? people will hate me if i break it off completely with justen...thats hard enough...and i dont know actually MoDeLsLuST: why did u want to ditch him in the first place lol MoDeLsLuST: wut did he do AbstinanceroX: nothing AbstinanceroX: i just wasnt sure i felt the same as he did AbstinanceroX: which made me feel like i was using him AbstinanceroX: so i let him go MoDeLsLuST: o MoDeLsLuST: makes sense MoDeLsLuST: i guess MoDeLsLuST: wasent justen everything though? MoDeLsLuST: u sur talked about him allot and he is pretty hot MoDeLsLuST: *saw pictures* AbstinanceroX: lol AbstinanceroX: he was great! but i wasnt ready for that much commitment MoDeLsLuST: did u do what u said u did in your last blo MoDeLsLuST: g MoDeLsLuST: one sec... let me find it lol MoDeLsLuST: AND GET DRUNK!!! AND FUCK KNOWS WHAT WE DID. MoDeLsLuST: after that i belive MoDeLsLuST: u just say that for attention or something? AbstinanceroX: no not really...i was worried that i messed around too much. but we didnt have sex...just it almost went too far MoDeLsLuST: o lol MoDeLsLuST: thats good AbstinanceroX: yeah AbstinanceroX: how come you did not invite me? to be your friend? MoDeLsLuST: want me too? MoDeLsLuST: i guess AbstinanceroX: sure MoDeLsLuST: i dont really use my thing that much MoDeLsLuST: i just look for buddies AbstinanceroX: o ok MoDeLsLuST: who are like e MoDeLsLuST: me MoDeLsLuST: i have to go MoDeLsLuST: bi AbstinanceroX: bye..   something makes me want to think it was don..but o well.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink http://profile.myspace.com/users/3870815 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      broke up with justen. how fucked is that? stupid...but i had reasons...and i dunno. i just did. but then, last night...i felt so alone, so i caught up with him...and we got really drunk, and were together just like old times...its weird but it feels normal i guess. sortof like best friends with benefits? i think? well yeah...then today my rents went to the property to hook up some shit with the RV and i talked to amber and we left, met at the bridge, and woke up justen. so then...we all went to the river...after hanging in his room, and wanted to go swimming but it was really fucking cold. so that didnt go down, and like the hangover returned, and i realized i hadnt eaten in a long ass time so justen bought me subway, such a good boy. such a good good boy. a good good good boy. with cheese. and god...i like being like this...apart...but together...and it makes no sense at all to me...uh the convo is right here: tada:  fuzzypinky0: r you there fuzzypinky0: now AbstinanceroX: uh yes fuzzypinky0: ok fuzzypinky0: so you still going to the see the fire works? AbstinanceroX: uhg AbstinanceroX: yes fuzzypinky0: what timr fuzzypinky0: time AbstinanceroX: uh AbstinanceroX: ask stupid mom "uh when it gets dark out?" AbstinanceroX: LIKE WTF?! fuzzypinky0: :-( AbstinanceroX: that could be 9 pm til 4 in the morning AbstinanceroX: lol fuzzypinky0: dont be mad fuzzypinky0: get glad fuzzypinky0: i got some if you want to baorw some fuzzypinky0: lol AbstinanceroX: lol what? AbstinanceroX: you retard AbstinanceroX: lol omg AbstinanceroX: that was weird justen fuzzypinky0: what AbstinanceroX: nothing lol nvm fuzzypinky0: ok AbstinanceroX: OK! AbstinanceroX: READDY! OK! AbstinanceroX: rah rah rah AbstinanceroX: rah fuzzypinky0: ?? AbstinanceroX: nvm AbstinanceroX: being a cheerleader fuzzypinky0: ya that is what i thought fuzzypinky0: so did you have a nice ride home fuzzypinky0: on the scary pain fuzzypinky0: :-) AbstinanceroX: haha AbstinanceroX: no AbstinanceroX: i felt sick fuzzypinky0: hehe fuzzypinky0: i do righ tknow fuzzypinky0: and dezzy fuzzypinky0: for now reason AbstinanceroX: too much junk food fuzzypinky0: no AbstinanceroX: not enough vegatables AbstinanceroX: YES AbstinanceroX: lol fuzzypinky0: no fuzzypinky0: i eat lots of them fuzzypinky0: too meny fuzzypinky0: and pineapple fuzzypinky0: ewwwwwwwwww fuzzypinky0: :'( AbstinanceroX: haha AbstinanceroX: yey AbstinanceroX: i am proud fuzzypinky0: ya you should be fuzzypinky0: lol fuzzypinky0: what are you doing tommaorw fuzzypinky0: ?? AbstinanceroX: uh AbstinanceroX: FUCKING A AbstinanceroX: going to the fucking property! AbstinanceroX: for a fucking bbq! fuzzypinky0: :'( AbstinanceroX: AND TOMORROW NIGHT AbstinanceroX: we are going to PARTY! AbstinanceroX: BITCHES AbstinanceroX: YES YES YES fuzzypinky0: you and me fuzzypinky0: ?? fuzzypinky0: or youmom AbstinanceroX: i am "staying the night at shannons" AbstinanceroX: well uh AbstinanceroX: everyone fuzzypinky0: o AbstinanceroX: no fuck the kids justen! us teenagers fuzzypinky0: my mom wanted to know if you wanted to cuomme over for dinner fuzzypinky0: tommarow fuzzypinky0: but... AbstinanceroX: but? fuzzypinky0: ya fuzzypinky0: you wont be here AbstinanceroX: OK JUSTEN AbstinanceroX: um AbstinanceroX: listen! AbstinanceroX: k?! fuzzypinky0: ok fuzzypinky0: k AbstinanceroX: god ok i think....that we are kindof getting attatched...and that we are really serious and that we need to slow down a little ok? fuzzypinky0: ok fuzzypinky0: meanig AbstinanceroX: lol AbstinanceroX: yeah i wanted to like get this down in person, but at albertsons there were alotta people AbstinanceroX: i think like AbstinanceroX: hmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm AbstinanceroX: like god AbstinanceroX: ok fuzzypinky0: ya  AbstinanceroX: WE ARE LIKE WAY IN DEEP AbstinanceroX: k? fuzzypinky0: ya fuzzypinky0: ok fuzzypinky0: and y is that bad fuzzypinky0: ? AbstinanceroX: uh AbstinanceroX: i feel like AbstinanceroX: pressured into commitment with you AbstinanceroX: sometimes fuzzypinky0: o will iam soory fuzzypinky0: but who's pressurding you AbstinanceroX:  no one in general AbstinanceroX: but  AbstinanceroX: see AbstinanceroX: we are serious AbstinanceroX: and AbstinanceroX: i feel like i want to be a kid and be free AbstinanceroX: and sometimes AbstinanceroX: you make me feel like i am married to you fuzzypinky0: how fuzzypinky0: i let you do what you want AbstinanceroX: nooo thats not it fuzzypinky0: o fuzzypinky0: well iam dory fuzzypinky0: soory fuzzypinky0: if its my falt AbstinanceroX: ok..............hmmmmm AbstinanceroX: i just feel like we need to slow down AbstinanceroX: step back fuzzypinky0: ok AbstinanceroX: do you get me? fuzzypinky0: ya fuzzypinky0: how far back fuzzypinky0: ? AbstinanceroX: god i dont knwo AbstinanceroX: far enough to where i feel like we are just a happy couple AbstinanceroX: not so AbstinanceroX: attatched.. fuzzypinky0: o AbstinanceroX: ok so like tell me what you think i am telling you fuzzypinky0: so your not happy anymore fuzzypinky0: ? AbstinanceroX: ummmmmmmmm AbstinanceroX: no AbstinanceroX: ok AbstinanceroX: uh fuzzypinky0: ok AbstinanceroX: no i just AbstinanceroX: need some air? fuzzypinky0: so your not dummping me  AbstinanceroX: no fuzzypinky0: are you AbstinanceroX: lol no fuzzypinky0: ok fuzzypinky0: ok fuzzypinky0: good fuzzypinky0: you want to know what i think AbstinanceroX: ok AbstinanceroX: go fuzzypinky0: about this fuzzypinky0: ? AbstinanceroX: yes go fuzzypinky0: ok fuzzypinky0: aaaaaaaaaaaa fuzzypinky0: lol AbstinanceroX: JUSTEN fuzzypinky0: i cant out it in words AbstinanceroX: TRY fuzzypinky0: put* fuzzypinky0: ok fuzzypinky0: it might take a wile fuzzypinky0: ook AbstinanceroX: ok GO fuzzypinky0: aaaaaaaaaaaaa AbstinanceroX: justen AbstinanceroX: omg AbstinanceroX: comeon fuzzypinky0: you should do what you have too AbstinanceroX: what is that supposed to mean? fuzzypinky0: atjatjsafgjmsg fuzzypinky0: i dont know fuzzypinky0: 6 fuzzypinky0: :'( AbstinanceroX: lol yeah you do AbstinanceroX: justen fuzzypinky0: iaqm sorry AbstinanceroX: justen AbstinanceroX: come on please AbstinanceroX: tell me AbstinanceroX: do you want to break up? fuzzypinky0: hell no AbstinanceroX: ok then tell me AbstinanceroX: what it means fuzzypinky0: ok fuzzypinky0: what do you want to do fuzzypinky0: ? fuzzypinky0: is up too you fuzzypinky0: it's* AbstinanceroX: k... fuzzypinky0: i want to be with you fuzzypinky0: but if you dont want to be with me just tell me AbstinanceroX: no i do fuzzypinky0: ok fuzzypinky0: ok AbstinanceroX: i just want to back off fuzzypinky0: like how AbstinanceroX: like AbstinanceroX: uh AbstinanceroX: hold on AbstinanceroX: im thinking AbstinanceroX: not be so AbstinanceroX: uh fuzzypinky0: ok AbstinanceroX: uhhhh AbstinanceroX: uuuuuuuuuuuh AbstinanceroX: uuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuhhhh fuzzypinky0: ? AbstinanceroX: not be so together? no fuzzypinky0: i dotn get it AbstinanceroX: me neither AbstinanceroX: like AbstinanceroX: hmmmmmmmmmmm AbstinanceroX: just take it slow AbstinanceroX: do you get that much? AbstinanceroX: thats all i want AbstinanceroX: take it slow fuzzypinky0: i thought we were AbstinanceroX: well AbstinanceroX: fine AbstinanceroX: but AbstinanceroX: whatever fuzzypinky0: so like dont be around eacher  AbstinanceroX: no fuzzypinky0: or something fuzzypinky0: lol AbstinanceroX: GOD THIS IS HARD fuzzypinky0: help me AbstinanceroX: not be so serious fuzzypinky0: i knoe AbstinanceroX: lol im trying but i cant explain fuzzypinky0: ya fuzzypinky0: serious???? fuzzypinky0: in like what way AbstinanceroX: everyway AbstinanceroX: lol fuzzypinky0: and that is AbstinanceroX: uh AbstinanceroX: every way AbstinanceroX: lol fuzzypinky0: lol fuzzypinky0: i know that fuzzypinky0: but  AbstinanceroX: like every part of our relartionship AbstinanceroX: lol fuzzypinky0: how meny part's are there AbstinanceroX: HAHA fuzzypinky0: no really AbstinanceroX: there is sex, ummm, support? ummmmmm AbstinanceroX: im sorry i think its funny AbstinanceroX: im laughing cuz i cant explain AbstinanceroX: dont get pissy im trying to help fuzzypinky0: what about sex fuzzypinky0: iam not getting pissy AbstinanceroX: what about sex?! AbstinanceroX: JUSTEN AbstinanceroX: omg AbstinanceroX: no you didnt fuzzypinky0: what AbstinanceroX: JUSTEN AbstinanceroX: take it slow jesus christ fuzzypinky0: AbstinanceroX: there is sex, ummm, support? ummmmmm AbstinanceroX: i am still a virgin fuzzypinky0: i know AbstinanceroX: ME TOO fuzzypinky0: i am  fuzzypinky0: ant i fuzzypinky0: ? AbstinanceroX: justen you are not AbstinanceroX: stop it fuzzypinky0: ok fuzzypinky0: ok fuzzypinky0: iam sory AbstinanceroX: its not funny seriously fuzzypinky0: i know it not funny fuzzypinky0: iam not laugfing AbstinanceroX: omg AbstinanceroX: the first thing you say!!!! is what about sex!!!!!!! fuzzypinky0: ya  fuzzypinky0: that is what you said AbstinanceroX: BUT JUSTEN AbstinanceroX: THAT IS NOT COOL AbstinanceroX: I AM NOT YOUR WHORE fuzzypinky0: i dont caer about that fuzzypinky0: i know AbstinanceroX: sorry i never gave you head jesus but GOD fuzzypinky0: i never said that fuzzypinky0: it ok fuzzypinky0: you dont have too fuzzypinky0: it you chose AbstinanceroX: BUT JUSTEN AbstinanceroX: tell me honestly fuzzypinky0: ok AbstinanceroX: if you thought that i wouldnt fuck you when you first met me...would you have continued like being with me? fuzzypinky0: yes AbstinanceroX: justen AbstinanceroX: seriously AbstinanceroX: you are a bit of a man whore fuzzypinky0: iam fucking serious. AbstinanceroX: ok AbstinanceroX: but what if i said all sex has to stop AbstinanceroX: what would you do? fuzzypinky0: yrs fuzzypinky0: yes fuzzypinky0: as long as iam with you fuzzypinky0: i wood do what you want me too fuzzypinky0: do fuzzypinky0: is that is nothign fuzzypinky0: then nothing will happen fuzzypinky0: ok AbstinanceroX: but sometimes i dont feel that convinced fuzzypinky0: if you tell me no then i wont fuzzypinky0: i swer AbstinanceroX: havent i? AbstinanceroX: like AbstinanceroX: i have fuzzypinky0: ok fuzzypinky0: iam sorry AbstinanceroX: but somehow i am easily pressured fuzzypinky0: about that AbstinanceroX: you know that fuzzypinky0: i wont tery to do that fuzzypinky0: any morer fuzzypinky0: ok fuzzypinky0: sorry AbstinanceroX: hmmmmmm AbstinanceroX: justen AbstinanceroX: i dont know fuzzypinky0: whaterver it take to still be together i will do it AbstinanceroX: well see AbstinanceroX: and thats kindof scarey AbstinanceroX: its like AbstinanceroX: you seriously are attatched fuzzypinky0: so AbstinanceroX: but we are just little kids fuzzypinky0: that is me fuzzypinky0: you dont have to fell the same AbstinanceroX: what if it wasnt me though? AbstinanceroX: yeah but then that is wrong AbstinanceroX: that is like AbstinanceroX: using you fuzzypinky0: how AbstinanceroX: if i dont feel the same way about us as you do AbstinanceroX: its wrong AbstinanceroX: its like fuzzypinky0: on it nor fuzzypinky0: not AbstinanceroX: using you because you love me  AbstinanceroX: BUT IT IS AbstinanceroX: you dont see justen fuzzypinky0: yes fuzzypinky0: i know i dont  AbstinanceroX: justen that is why i feel guilty AbstinanceroX: because i dont always feel the same way AbstinanceroX: and sometimes i think i do AbstinanceroX: i am unsure AbstinanceroX: and if i ever broke up with you AbstinanceroX: youd be really hurt wouldnt you? fuzzypinky0: ya fuzzypinky0: so AbstinanceroX: that is not so AbstinanceroX: that is mean AbstinanceroX: and i dont want to be mean justen AbstinanceroX: i want to be honest AbstinanceroX: but they dont go hand in hand fuzzypinky0: you are AbstinanceroX: but justen, if i stayed with you and didnt feel the same its also not fair to me fuzzypinky0: some time you have too be mean to be hounest fuzzypinky0: rember the turth hruts fuzzypinky0: .... AbstinanceroX: i dont like hurt fuzzypinky0: but you have too tell the truth AbstinanceroX: i am trying fuzzypinky0: well tell me the teuth fuzzypinky0: so you want to be with me still fuzzypinky0: right AbstinanceroX: sometimes yes and sometimes no fuzzypinky0: y sometims no fuzzypinky0: ? AbstinanceroX: i am just not always ready AbstinanceroX: for what we have fuzzypinky0: ok fuzzypinky0: then if you not redy i can wate fuzzypinky0: if you can AbstinanceroX: but justen AbstinanceroX: i dont know if you would wait if i ended it with you AbstinanceroX: what if we never came back AbstinanceroX: or one of us didnt want to AbstinanceroX: the other one wouldnt be very happy fuzzypinky0: hold on AbstinanceroX: ok fuzzypinky0: 1 at a time fuzzypinky0: AbstinanceroX: i dont know if you would wait if i ended it with you fuzzypinky0: meaning fuzzypinky0: what for what fuzzypinky0: wait AbstinanceroX: what if we broke up? AbstinanceroX: or i broke up with you  i guess... AbstinanceroX: you couldnt wait AbstinanceroX: you know that AbstinanceroX: you would want to move on  fuzzypinky0: no fuzzypinky0: i woodent AbstinanceroX: justen AbstinanceroX: be honest AbstinanceroX: you think you wouldnt now fuzzypinky0: you my last gf i will have AbstinanceroX: but think realistically fuzzypinky0: no fuzzypinky0: your my last chancs on girls AbstinanceroX: why is that? AbstinanceroX: did i turn you gay? fuzzypinky0: becasue  fuzzypinky0: on fuzzypinky0: iam just not going to go out with girls again AbstinanceroX: justen AbstinanceroX: seriously AbstinanceroX: you will fuzzypinky0: unless it wood e with you AbstinanceroX: dont say that fuzzypinky0: iam fucking seirous AbstinanceroX: i dont believe you! AbstinanceroX: god justen AbstinanceroX: alright AbstinanceroX: but even then AbstinanceroX: that would make me feel like shit fuzzypinky0: i can prove it too you fuzzypinky0: go to hot mail fuzzypinky0: and go to my account AbstinanceroX: no just AbstinanceroX: nvm AbstinanceroX: justen AbstinanceroX: dont worry about it fuzzypinky0: ok fuzzypinky0: but if you dump me AbstinanceroX: JUSTEN STOP fuzzypinky0: ok AbstinanceroX: DO NOT MAKE ME FEEL WORSE AbstinanceroX: THIS IS HARD ENOUGH OK? fuzzypinky0: i sory fuzzypinky0: ok AbstinanceroX: i dont want to stay together because i feel bad for hurting you and leaving you alone, i want to stay together because i love you, but right now i am not sure if i do AbstinanceroX: do you understand me? fuzzypinky0: yes AbstinanceroX: ok AbstinanceroX: because right now AbstinanceroX: this hurts me alot fuzzypinky0: mee too AbstinanceroX: but i think its what i am trying to say fuzzypinky0: it's over fuzzypinky0: ? AbstinanceroX: god AbstinanceroX: i hate those words fuzzypinky0: ya me too fuzzypinky0: but it you chouse AbstinanceroX: god justen AbstinanceroX: i dont like it AbstinanceroX: but i think i have to fuzzypinky0: ok fuzzypinky0: just y fuzzypinky0: do you have too AbstinanceroX: i sortof spent like an hour explaining that to you... fuzzypinky0: lol fuzzypinky0: i know fuzzypinky0: ok fuzzypinky0: iam sorry  fuzzypinky0: for wasting your time AbstinanceroX: no AbstinanceroX: god dont say that fuzzypinky0: it was the best 5 mounth of my slfe AbstinanceroX: justen fuzzypinky0: i dont know who long i can type ofr AbstinanceroX: see why i didnt want to? fuzzypinky0: ya AbstinanceroX: you dont know how bad i feel god fuzzypinky0: but y live a lie fuzzypinky0: no fuzzypinky0: no fuzzypinky0: i do fuzzypinky0: so we  fuzzypinky0: are fuzzypinky0:  over fuzzypinky0: ? AbstinanceroX: yes........ AbstinanceroX: for now i guess... fuzzypinky0: ok fuzzypinky0: if tht is what you want fuzzypinky0: but  fuzzypinky0: just if you get a nouther b f fuzzypinky0: and do stuff with him fuzzypinky0: like sex fuzzypinky0: dont cumm back fuzzypinky0: ok fuzzypinky0: please AbstinanceroX: okjusten AbstinanceroX: ok fuzzypinky0: and we could still be frinds fuzzypinky0: right AbstinanceroX: yes god AbstinanceroX: yeah fuzzypinky0: just frindes fuzzypinky0: or moer fuzzypinky0: or  fuzzypinky0: .... AbstinanceroX: ok AbstinanceroX: justen i have to go fuzzypinky0: no fuzzypinky0: whte fuzzypinky0: like 5 moer min fuzzypinky0: please fuzzypinky0: iam thinkg AbstinanceroX: i only have like two AbstinanceroX: k? fuzzypinky0: ok fuzzypinky0: shot i for got fuzzypinky0: wha ti was going to say but fuzzypinky0: i still love you just want you to know that and i guees i will go find some one to talk too or try too fuzzypinky0: ok fuzzypinky0: by AbstinanceroX: bye fuzzypinky0: i will miss you AbstinanceroX: you too fuzzypinky0: oya and you only say by to the one that you love fuzzypinky0: i hrud that some were fuzzypinky0: ok fuzzypinky0: by AbstinanceroX: what? AbstinanceroX: ok.. AbstinanceroX: bye fuzzypinky0 signed off at 9:06:15 PM.  fuzzypinky0: o ya AbstinanceroX: what? fuzzypinky0: tell you mom she is cool too AbstinanceroX: ok AbstinanceroX: lol fuzzypinky0: :-) fuzzypinky0: whit a:'( AbstinanceroX: haha me too fuzzypinky0: hey AbstinanceroX: yeah? fuzzypinky0: one more fuzzypinky0: lol fuzzypinky0: sorry AbstinanceroX: k fuzzypinky0: but  fuzzypinky0: wood you take me back  fuzzypinky0: if have done some things with a diffrent gilr AbstinanceroX: um AbstinanceroX: that makes me really want to say no AbstinanceroX: but probably fuzzypinky0: ok fuzzypinky0: i will try not too fuzzypinky0: but..... fuzzypinky0: iam sorry if i do AbstinanceroX: yeah well you have your hand...but then again so do i AbstinanceroX: gtg AbstinanceroX: ok? AbstinanceroX: bye fuzzypinky0: ok fuzzypinky0: by fuzzypinky0: and AbstinanceroX: JUSTEN fuzzypinky0: i dont think i wood belev too go thought  with that anyways fuzzypinky0: and plese dot cut you r self fuzzypinky0: too AbstinanceroX: haha ok.. AbstinanceroX: yes dad AbstinanceroX: I GTG fuzzypinky0: no AbstinanceroX: lol fuzzypinky0: daddy AbstinanceroX: lol! AbstinanceroX: bye justen!  AbstinanceroX: bye fuzzypinky0: 8-) fuzzypinky0: by sarah    yeah i know...fucking long...but whatever...uh, tonight there is a big ass party under the bridge...justen better find his camera cuz i am gonna do some wild shit! cuz i feel like it! RARRR! and gtg...shannon emailed me woohoo! no more crying you bad sarah. stop it! o well...ill just cry it all out.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>