<Blog>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I wasn't gonna run today but pt saved me and called so I ran 3.2 with sun valley cut it. Which is 4 miles making my milage for the week in 3 days around 14.5... YAHOO
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went running with longo rich pt and I we ran 3.9 from rich's house which turns into 4 miles. After the pool felt SOOOOOOOO good. I got out and then jumped back in a couple times. Pt had to walk and as soon as he dropped back I picked it up b/c I wanted to go in the pool!
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Thought I was done huh... well i just ran another 2.5 miles with P.T. so there ran sun valley totaling milage for the day is ... 6.505...YAhOO
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Rich ran to my house. We ran 3.2 saw the girls running the other way I grabbed my swim suit and ran to Rich's house with Rich. We swam and then Rich drove me home. Total of 4.005 miles
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Easy day today ran 2 miles sun valley with the girls as girl pace... only sweat because of the heat outside. Nice to get out and run though Note to self
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I ran 3.5 miles yesterday. I ran to the highschool ran 6 laps ran an apple then ran home. I ran it with erika. It was fun
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       &nbsp;i have been running this week and finished with 51 miles ending with 9.2 around the res. So yea i havent really updated this because its been a busy week. O well. Maybe next week it will turn out better.   
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I  woke up at 8:30 and ran 5.7 with P,T. Then I played tennis ALL DAY. Then at 6 I ran .25 to memorial then 5.1 with Rich. It was a long day and I have blisters and hot spots from tennis. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I wanted more but am starting to get lazy. Ran 3.2 with the peeps this morning. Then ran 6 miles with rich this evening...i'll work my mileage up  
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       today i ran 2.8 then 3.2 then 2 miles with .25 totaling 8.25 for the day. I wanted more. O well 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ran 5.7 in the morning with pt. and then this morning ran a 15 mile run 3 laps at the resivouir  at rogers. It was long but very long. So yea 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ran 6 miles with rich today.... only run for the day! 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       yesterday i ran 3.7 miles at the night run before i went to the driving range! 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I ran sun valley then to kevins and back for a night run with pt fun stuff 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Rich and I ran a 5 mile 3.9 this morning at the 8 oclock run. It was fun! 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       summer runs have started! there were lik 24 people there. I ran 5.1 with condrin and lemonadeface richie! i pushed the pacea a bunch and it felt really good to open our strides! It was really really fun. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       rich wanted to run 3.2 again so ... wtf i ran it with him again ... 6.4 but i sill have practice tonight. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       3.2 block with PT today... easy a little sore from yesterday but still easy 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today I went on a really long run. I felt bad about not running saturday. So I ran the springlake road then hooked up with flanders and then went straight to st. dominics. Then I turned left onto random street then left again onto pleasent then when i got to the high school I ran sun valley then range p.ts doorbell and ran another one with sunvalley and this one included debby dr so it was 2.5 miles. Then I ran home totals...   3.9, 5.1 combo =6 sunvalley      =2 sunvalley with debby =2.5  6=2=2.5=10.5 the longest run i have ever ran at one time! 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I asked rich online and he sounded up to it so I ran from stephs to his house to the high school and back then to stephs house thinking it was 4 but it was actually 5 fun stuff.! 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today I woke up at 6 again and run 5.1 block with p.t. that was fun then I also ran home from the house I babysat at which is 1.35 miles away. Hopefully more to come. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I rode my bike down to laurens got lost then found her house and ran 5 miles slow pace with her and erika. Fun stuff then I rode home 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ran this morning 3.2  block... slight pain in leg... dono whats up prolly just from sitting in car so much on vacation. Running again tonight. 
    
    
</post>


<date>31,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       wahoo kimmy is helping me type my blog for the day b/c i'mbabysitting her. i love my kimberly. We made a fort and then it fell down so we made it again and it fell down so we made it again and it worked. yea so today i had track and i got to run 4 miles in the freaken rain, i think i'm still wet, it was so gross. I dont like practice b/c i get the feeling that some ppl r pretending to be injured when they're not just to get outta workouts *cough cough* o well their loss in teh end, well i really should be actually be babysitting now so i'm out 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I want it to be summer again or atleasr spring. Today is gonna be great yea right. I have church tonight so not cool then I have a little homework I don't want to do it :-( O well Track was good today because I am hurt. Tomarrow I will be back. I hate people who fake being hurt to get out of workouts.. It gives REAL hurt people a bad name...Hmm Lets see anyother issues... o yea... one of the people I used to like likes my best friend.. He is such a lucky kid hehe... I hate it when it rains .. I wanted to go to kevins house but I guess i can't ride my bike. WHen i can drive I will NEVER be home..I don't understand my parents They won't let me take PLTW next year and it makes me so mad because i could do it. But the heard so many bad stories and that it is a waste of time. They make me so mad. THey say it is the best for me not to... but i know they are just dumb.. Erika never had time to do everything. She is always babysitten thats cool I guess maybe I just have no life and that is why I am always home on the computer and never out with friends... heh.. O WELL>.. I wanna see kevins puppy.. I am done now...   EDIT -Yea.. by the way if you are reading this blog and are like hey that is me whether it is good or bad please don't get mad at me... :-D yea so i am just going to keep posting my mind whether your in it or not! 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I slept so much today. After the second part of pre-CAPT testing, I just put my head down and I slept for about 30 minutes. Then during Science, we were watching an extremely boring movie on geyers. I put my head down, and next thing I knew, Mrs. Dunn was next to me saying, "Becky... Becky, wake up." I have Ms. Delfino for Spanish, but she's been absent for about two weeks. We have Coach Bob for a sub, and as you all know, he's freaking awesome. In Civics, Alisha was telling me how she asked Coach Bob to go to the cafe, and he said no. So she asked to go to her locker, and Coach Bob responded, "Yes... but if you somehow wander into the cafe and get caught, then it's not my responsibility." or something like that. So I got the idea to go to the cafe during my Spanish class. Lauren L. and I were eagered to go, and we asked Coach Bob if we could go to our lockers. He said, "Wait until I start the class and hand out the worksheet." So we waited. Then he said, "Wait until you finish the worksheet." So I quickly conjugated the entire worksheet (afterwards, we checked it and my worksheet was all right... damn I'm good!), and Coach Bob allowed Lauren L. and me to go to our lockers. He knew, of course, that we wanted to go somewhere else, because he said, "Just be back in 15 minutes." So we quickly went across the library and down the stairs. I was excited to see Kait, Eliz, Helene, Jamie, yadda yadda. By the time we got to the cafe, the freshmen and sophomores had already went down to study, grr. So Lauren L. and I are hoping Coach Bob will be the still sub and that Ms. Delfino won't be back tomorrow. I hate indoor practices, they suck a lot. We did plyometrics, and then the freshmen went over the rules of the game. Afterwards, we did TAE BO! It was uhh... interesting! Practice ended around 3:30 (SUPER early), and a bunch of us just hung around and talked. Oh... and guess who's the backup goalie?! That's right, MEEE! Kait S. is good though, but I just want to play goalie and make all the damn right handed people of going through the difficulty of shooting with a left handed goalie. After all, I go through the difficulty of shooting about 99.9% of the time (I encountered a left handed goalie only  once . Believe me, my shots went through, mwhaha) with right handed goalies. It's not like it's impossible for me to shoot, it's just more difficult. And I don't like people making things difficult for me. So... bring it on, biznatches! 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       You ppl-meaning becky never use titles... o well... I did mine last so it would be on top hehehe Today i got to skip practice pretty much i cleaned the pole vaulting pit thing since i am injured and pole vaulting... It was discusting BUT pretty fun hahaha... I have botics AND boy scouts tonight. I hate how i have an assignment for a class due today even though i won't be in the SCHOOl  until fri... DAMN EMAIL.. O well hrmm lets see my blogs are always so random and breaky because of the dots.... o well... I can't wait until...summer yea thats it I CAN"T wait until summer and then yea. I hate school Never get to see friends EVER and yea its just plain dumb. capts suxxor as usual. It is lots more ppl when more ppl are here.   EDIT (by Becky):  The ... are called ellipses. :D So you learned something new today, woohoo. 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       BLOGGER IS BEING A BIZNATCH. PUBLISH MY POST, DAMN IT! I SEE LAUREN'S, BUT I DON'T SEE MINE. WTF IS YOUR PROBLEM, BLOGGER?! WHY MUST YOU BE SUCH A BUTT MUNCH!? Oh, and Lauren, look on the bright side... if you live in a cardboard box behind Wal-Mart, you'll live near me. So we can hang out all the time, haha. Nifty, right?  EDIT:  Wow... look at the counter. The majority of the hits were from me refreshing over and over trying to see my post, lol. Oops, my bad. 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Even after my nice, hot shower, I am still very numb. Practice was so unbelievably cold today... Well, knowing me, you know I'm a problem child, and problem children have (duh) problems. Today's problem concerns lacrosse. Yessireebob. Well, during English class today (when I was wearing Rita's sweatshirt because it was so cold, haha), I was working on my vocab when Mrs. Consic (also my lax coach) came over. She knelt down next to me and told me she wanted me to play center for the first game. The first thing that came into my mind was something between an "UGH" and an "EW". Hopefully it's only for this game though. Because I don't understand why she would want me to play that position. First of all, sure, I'm a semi-decent runner but I believe I absolutely  suck  at lacrosse. I get beat up so much during the games... like during our drills today, I already got knocked down and got so many cuts. I have this cut shaped like the Nike sign above my knee, it's actually pretty nifty. Anyways, when I fell down during the drill, the field hockey people started laughing, because I fall down all the time during field hockey season. I'm determined not to have a song about me falling down get created or get carried over from field hockey season, lol. I'm keeping track of how many times I fall down this season. So far...  one . Kait's the forgetful one, lol. She owes Mrs. Consic $4.50 so far. And this is the first week of practice. I've realized my blogs are always about lacrosse. Wow, people are right, I  am  obsessed. :X 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       wahoooooo, I'm so excited b/c i've always wanted to blog but i never knew how..now i do thanx to becky and josh. Today we had CAPT. it sucks! i know i'm gonna fail it when i'm a sophmore. then i wont graduate, wont get into college, never get a job and i'll live in a cardboard box behind walmart for the rest of my life. After school today i had a dentist appointment. Scariest moment of my life, cuz i had to get my first cavity...eeeek i almost peed my pants i was so scared. my mouth is still numb lol. I didn't mind it though since i couldn't feel anything and my dentist gave me "happy gas" and that was fun. At least i got to miss practice today. I felt bad though cuz i had to leave right after school and i culdnt' see Mike, i feel bacd cuz i dont see him a lot. When i got home i went to the mall so i could buy niki a present for making varsity. I managed to get a shirt for myself at weathervane. Then later tonight i have to babysit for my neighbors, fun fun. o yea i finally got my ipod working. i love it to death. grrr english essay 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The weekend was ever so boring. The highlight of my weekend was Sunday. I got to skip chinese school... with my mom's permission. Skipping with a parental consent... isn't that just hilarious? I'm sure I'm the only one laughing now (I'm not really laughing...) Lauren and I went to a million stores, like Sports Authority. At Sports Authority, we were walking by when we saw the bowling part of the store and it reminded us of our traditional weekly bowling thing. So we found pins, set them down, and we bowled. At one point, I didn't really catch the ball, and it rolled over my toe. It killed... I was wearing flip flops. Today, I was walking down to my 3rd period class (which was really 8th period...) when I heard someone calling my name. At first, I thought I was imagining things, hah, since I usually do. But it was Josh, and he was going to PLTW. And I just found out he's going to be going all week! Woohoo, another person to talk to in PLTW... I don't really have anyone to talk to anymore, since I got moved so far away from Steph and Cecelia. Saddening, I know! Right now, I'm willing to talk to anyone that talks to me, lol. Practice was so great today. We didn't have to run an apple, hallelujah! I love being lazy. We were supposed to run two laps around the field at the end of practice, but since I was the first to hit the far cone when we were practicing shooting, I only had to run one lap. Eliz only had to run one, too. The bad thing was, I had so much energy towards the end of practice... I was so hyper. At practice, Kait and I were just doing the little clap shot trick for fun. The thing is, I always have to have the ball to begin with. Same with Eliz and me. So I can never end up with the ball. I'm going to stop talking about it now, since I don't think anyone has a clue what I'm talking about. Oh, and CAPT testing sucks, I think I'm going to end up going to the wrong period class at least once this week... more than once, I bet. 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok soo... sunday was boring day not quite I went to church and had to read the lessons. Then I went home and got ready to fly rockets.. Dad was being dumb do didn't end up flying until like 3:30ish then I had to go to my violin lesson at 4:45. So not as much time as a wanted but it was a blast. We blew up mountain dew cans. We blew up rockets. It was just a fun time. I wanna do it again. Then I got to sleep in  and go to school later because i don't ahve 1st period yipee! Anyhow then I went to school and made stuff in inventor on my laptop during 4th period. Helped this girl out with a lab report 5th period then had civics english and then audited the PLTW class. That was fun. I even got permission to go all week YEA! I made the same thing they were making. Inventer doesn't look THAT hard. Mr. Carpenter said I could go for just next year as long as someone drops out. I think someone is so that is a good thing! :-D. Umm hrrmmm let's see what else. O yea I went to track and my leg was killing me. THis is the first time I haven't ben able to run -through an injurey. I hobble-limped the entire way. Then I cut the course to finish faster and got lost. I am soo stupid. O well. I stoped and got to break a little. Coach says it is just a muscle thing so it should go away soon. I can't wait to try pole vaulting. I will suck  but it looks so fun. Time trials are wed. I better be good by then or I will be mad. O well coach now's how I can run. Being number one in your class suxxor. People say it is good, but if you ask me it is just another way to make good enemies. Or give people bad impressions of you. O well. Hmmm I think I am done. Going to change the site a little bit. See what i can do. Peace out ^ This is pretty long Josh your getting better at this whole righting thing... To bad capts still have writing on them. I am gonna fail it. Who cares! 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hah. I knew it. I'm not even part of the group anymore... I had the feeling that as soon as I started lacrosse and everyone started track, I would be left out of the group. The thing is, I don't think I really mind that much, because I don't think I was  ever  part of the group to begin with. They're all doing stuff together this weekend and leaving me out. Surprise surprise. When I call people up and ask them if they want to go to so-and-so, they're always like, "Nah, I don't feel like it..." And why am I always the one calling people up? I give up. It's a waste of my time attempting to be in the group. People are really driving me crazy now... ::cough:: parentals ::cough:: and friends... one of my friend's going to a purse party. WHAT THE HELL is a purse party? I think after I finish up my conversation with Mario, I'm going to take a walk in my woods. Hopefully I'll get molested and murdered so I don't have to deal with any of this crap. I think my theory that  PEOPLE SUCK  should be official by now. Goodbye, folks.  edit:I know how you feel. Life suxs sometimes. But there are always people you can turn to and then things are so bad. So bex I love ya and you'll always be part of OUR Group so yea... hahaha i love the power to edit hehehe (by josh since he is almighty administrator) 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey I am Josh Debner and I am the kid who sits home and does nothing on fri. nights.. If I do do anything, It will be going to the mall with my family FUN FUN FUN :-/ two weeks in a row now. Ok so today was an alright day. I had ALL my academy classes... It is block scheduling so having 4 45min classes is much better than 2 1.5 hour ones... I found since i was absent I don't have to make up a lab YAHOO. Hmmm Bus ride home ate lunch. Went and had a sub while I FAILED a civics test.... actually is was  true false but she could have made it hard. Teachers are so stupid sometimes. Anyhow hmm Then i went to this REALLLY stupid romeo and juliet that was boring and fake and a waste of money, BUT we missed class so it was ok. Then went to track IMPOSSIBLE workout today i can hardly work. Lauren and Steph went to movies with Mike and Joe.. yea they had fun. Busy day tomarrow. I am going to walmart for botics then glowas to help with ipod then erikas for supper yea... write more later peace crackerz 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hallelujah. My cold and cramps are gone now. Too bad I'm so sore right now, and my right ankle hurts. Geez, I'm such a problem child, I can never be 100% fine at once. Jackie, Alisha, and I wanted to cut Civics so we could go to the Romeo and Juliet thing. Okay, I lied. Jackie and Alisha wanted to cut. I was freaking out, because I was afraid of getting caught, lol. If Jackie and Alisha did leave, chances are I would have gone with them. Mr. Murphy came though, and closed the door. I'm sort of glad he did, because I don't think I would have lasted through the Romeo and Juliet thing twice. It was  so  boring. Oh my, my sister's really scaring me. I don't see her for a couple of months, and the next thing you know, she's eating the fish she used for bio labs... ick. (Sorry it's long...)   my sister:  guess what i ate today?  laxerbex  x:  rice?  my sister:  ok...so for bio lab...we had experiments on summer flounder, and we were only using their brain and otholiths in their skull...  laxerbex  x:  do i want to know the rest of this story?  my sister:  and the rest of it we saved  my sister:  and we had a fish BBQ today, hahahahaha  my sister:  i ate nemo  laxerbex  x:  EW, WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT?!  laxerbex  x:  wait... nemo is a CLOWN FISH  my sister:  because...it was free fish??? it was soo good too  my sister:  and get this  laxerbex  x:  ew, it was edible?  my sister:  our lab coordinator's name is Jamie TROUT haha...  my sister:  and she was the one filleting the fish  my sister:  yum i haven't had good fish in so long  I edited this blog and took out my sister's screenname so people like BRIAN MOCCI doesn't freaking im her and tell her that I'm their bitch... Jesus Christ. 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey I am home. Practice was ok today. I am  STARTING to get in shape. Glad that becky could join us. It raining tonight.. NO FUN!... My mom is gonna be gone the WHOLE WEEKEND! I AM So excited.. i didn't say that though hehe. Anyhow I am glad i am not a girl becky. I am going sat to help fix loreli's ipod.. yipee.. anyhow yea.. I am a boring kid.. good thing becky is here and lauren is coming. Umm not much else headed to robotics we are having a car wash coming up not this weekend but next.. 5 bucks.. tell EVERYONE to come. We are like 1500 in the whole... O well yea see ya later Hope you feel better Becky We ALL LOve ya 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I got major crampage during 8th period. With my luck, it lasted throughout lax practice. I hate being a girl, ugh. I sucked so much during practice today becaues of cramps. While running the apple, at least 10 people were ahead of me - way ahead. During shuttles, I missed so many catches. A lot of people told me not to get so frustrated, because I got worse as I got more frustrated. Cramps suck. Of course, when I got in the car, my mom told me I needed to deal with a situation concerning my sister and her college. I wish they wouldn't shirk off their responsibilities so much. I can't be a damn kid  and  a parent at the same time. To top it off, my dad's taking time off from work until Monday. His damn surgery was so long ago. He is fucking fine. And he needs to learn that the stock market has no damn secret. Afer losing thousands of dollars, you'd think he would learn by now, Jesus Christ. During Health, Jamie, Cecelia, Alex, and I were talking about our ages and birthdays. Jamie, Alex, and I mentioned we were 14, and Cecelia said she was 15. Cecelia was talking about how so many people had February birthdays, and I mentioned that I was one of those people. Jamie was like, "Wow, Becky, you're only 14?" But then it occurred to me that I'm  15  now. How sad is that?! I'm checking so many people's away messages now, and they're all mentioning how sore they are from lax. I might be sore, I don't know. All I know is that I'm feeling  nothing  compared to my cramps. 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am in Earth Science Again... Pretty boring were talking about heat and water and REALLLLLY boring. Anyways track shouldn't be that bad today. I have robotics tonight fun fun fun. Hmm I dono maybe I get to see the sexy ipod today who knows... haven't talked to erika in a long time. Maybe I'll call her  
    
    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       That is what this is for... righting randonm things. I love your jokes they crack me up like i dono i am not a funny kid but anyhow I am bored and i dono maybe lauren will help spice this blog up a little two.. 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey, Josh, no need to put our initials on the bottom! Hell yes, I don't have to announce that I'm BY all the time! (For those who don't get it, read that sentence out loud.) 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Aww, man, we have to put our initials? I remember when I was waiting for the bus with Amanda and Amanda during middle school one day, I noticed their intials on their backpacks. I said out loud, "Hey, you're Alm, you're Amp... I'm just BY!" and a lot of people turned around and stared at me. I was just stating the truth, it's not my fault people's minds are so corrupted. We had another day of lacrosse tryouts. This time, we were with the sophomores. At first, I was nervous that they were going to make me look bad, but I did fine. The apple was especially muddy, but it was fun. It went from 2:30 to 4:30 instead of ending at 3:30. It went by so quickly, I love doing shuttles. Not right handed though, hell no. I can't wait until my cold is gone. I swear my nose did more running than I did today. That was corny, I know. I swear, no more jokes and puns, alrighty? Or someone will have to  PUN ish me. Aghhh, I'll stop now, I promise. It's not fun blogging when you have nothing to say. Remind me never to blog when there's nothing new or good going on. It's like me writing notes to Lauren in Science class just to stay awake. They're so random, it's pathetic. But then again, I'm always random and going off tangents. 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       JJD: I think becky and lauren are now gonna right here so even though it says at the bottom for clearification we are going to put our initials in front of our message... easier to read ;-) 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey ... Today is wed. I made supper LASAGNA (sp) anyhow school wansn't too bad today. Not that much work and I can't wait for summer! LAUREN GOT A MINI IPOD!!! THAT IS SOOO FREAKEN COOL I want one really bad... Even if it was pink :-/ hahaha anyhow yea big lust object... O well Track was really easy today. Knee hurting so I only ran 2 miles. I wanna pole vault, I put that on my card lets see what coach says hehee Yea anyhow I am looking for potential writers here... So if you are interested Im me and i'll consider it. Didn't see steph or erika like at all today or even kevin... I feel so out of the loop... summer will be so much better! Peace homies 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey I just has an idea.. Maybe if i have more people write here it would be more interesting.. This is really quite boring.. 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey all, I am finally home. Today was pretty good. We had a short day so that was most definetly a good thing. We went to Stephs after school before practice. It was so great. EVERYONE went that included erika. I was so happy. They were pretty good. They are pretty good pretenders I think; BUT deep down i Know they both had fun. Becky was sad... I need to find out why. Makes me sad when ppl are sad. I wanna no because normally when i am sad i wish other people would just ask. So yea... I needa ask later when she comes back from away. TRACK WAS HARD TODAY! He gave us like an end of the season work out and I am so out of shape.. NOT GOOD O well. I am so sore yet a busy night tonight. Botics at 6 and then boy scouts at 7:30. I would prolly not go to the boy scout meetings if it weren't for the fact that I am incharge haha. Hopefully look good on my resume i guess. HMM I GOT MY CELLY back today. The bus driver saved my life by finding it. I am going to try and upload more links and add more stuff right now this is pretty boring. Lets see Maybe I should make a link to all the pictures I have.., HMMMM Time to get moving BUSY night tonight.. I'll write later if I am motivated enough 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       RIGHT NOW I am in earth science.. very boring. We are desalinizing water FUN FUN FUN .. I guess... Anyhow this is becoming quite a boring blog.. Maybe I should have more people write in it to get more interesting  
    
    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hello... I am at the academy.. We got here extra early today. Very little trafic. Woke up late again today.. O well what can you do about it. I should be doing makeupwork now but I a lazy. So SCREW that.. o Well 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       YAY! got the new look.. pretty damn sexy if you ask me.. Now to get the counter and chatterbox to work.. hmm... 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       YAHOO ABOUT TO UPGRADE TO A MUCH PRETTIER INTERFACE THANKS TO DENNIS HWANGS HTML WORK...i would do it but my lazyness excedes me... so check back later to see the pretty version of me... what i am talking about .. no one read this stupid thing anyhow.. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hello Today was hmmm.... interesting... Ok well i woke up and lets see I took shower at 5:30 then fell asleep by accident got back up at 6:17 and got on bus at 6:25... Slept on Bus.. Listened to Music on bus.. Got off bus...forgot cellphone on bus...got to school... called cell phone.. bus driver give celly back tomarrow...got to school.. did a stupid precapt science thingy all day.. very dumb...next i went to spanish took a stupid reading test damn i hate mrs ainsworth...went to track.. maybe just MAYBE i should run in between season... I SUXXOR at running now.. hahahahaha I WAS DIEING! (cold too I only wore a t-shirt and breakaway pants) lets see next i ate a ritual after practice choco-toco    :-P.... THen came home ate some really good mexican shit my sister made... then had to do bible study thing...   josh  
    
    
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       hey today i went to church... I had to play my violin and it didn't sound that great. O well i only practiced like twice. It really suxs to have your two best friends hate each other. You can never do anything together and if your in a spot and their both there you get all stressed and you'd rather just sit by yourself then create any trouble.. g2g write more later 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok... Well... Today we had a robotics competition. In the beginning of the day we were in 2nd from the day before. It was looking reallllllllly promising. We had alot of teams talking to us about picking them for alliances (teams). We lost one match because the other team we were with wasn't doing what they should have been doing and kept getting in our way. Then in our last match we were with the first seeded team. They flipped over and couldn't get back up wich left us by ourselves and so we had to fend for ourselves but still lsot 115 to 100. This bumped us down to 11th place which put us out of the picking. We then were at the mercy of the top 8 teams. You would think that because we were in the top 15 we would have gotten picked quickly. Teams forgot about us and well we didn't get picked. This ended the regional for us and we were VERY dissapointed. I have to say at that point I felt like going home. O  yea this was then put on that when i was on the way home i called to see what time we were going somewhere. But that had already left.. FUN!!! o well maybe another time. SOOO i ended up going to ems best buy and the mall with the parents sister and sisters friend.. WOW i am a loooser. Well something to look foreward to I guess.. HOMEWORK! This is a long enough blog. I think this is going to be usful I never EVER thought I would enjoy righting. But getting my thoughts down is really helping I think. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       hello... I am not good with this whole online journal thing so bear with me. I will write down my thoughts passions and feelings whenever I write here... So if for some reason or another I say something.. that is proably a spur of the moment this. Take no offense. If your in here.. and it is bad don't worry ... I will forget in about 5 min... 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It all started when I called Lauren. There's this guy that I have liked for a while, and I think that he might like one of my friends. I have this (guy) friend who likes this friend... a lot. And I was thinking that if the guy that I like asks my friend out, she would say yes without a doubt. And it would hurt me a lot. So when I called Lauren, I was really angry because it made me upset how someone could just do something without thinking of their actions. But when I got on the phone with Lauren, I started crying, because I realized that I wasn't angry, but I was  upset . Of course I would be upset over the fact that the guy I like for a while would be going out with my girl friend, but I was crying over the fact of how hurt my guy friend would be. I don't even care how hurt I get anymore. I hate seeing other people so sad. Especially one of my friends. My guy friend just likes my girl friend so, so much. And I hate the fact that my friend doesn't even consider how she makes other people feel. So I got off the phone with Lauren and I was sitting in my chair, crying and thinking. And it made me realize that sometimes  I  do things without considering how other people feel. And how I haven't been exactly the nicest person in the world sometimes. Then I started thinking about other things, and my mind just became a whole swirling jumble of mess. I started crying even more. Like, how could I regret giving my mom $1500 so she could have a chance at being an actual citizen and seeing her family again? I feel so guilty for actually regretting that. She deserved that money, and now I'm really glad I did that. She might be able to go back this summer and see her entire family again. It would be the first time in over 20 years. I really hope she'll be able to. Also, I used to do this 'Random Acts/Compliments Of Kindness' thing with Lauren... I would give out compliments or do nice little deeds for people that I don't normally talk to. And I would list what I did daily and stick it in Lauren's locker. How could I just give up doing that after 2 weeks? How selfish am I? I mean, how much does it take to talk to a person who's sitting all alone in class or to compliment someone you usually don't bother talking to in class? Sure, it may take a little effort being nicer, but it may really make someone's day one day. I felt really disappointed in myself. How could I be so hypocritical? How could I be upset over my friend not thinking of her actions when I don't feel upset when I don't think before I act myself? I just wish I could turn back about 6 years of my life and relive it. How could I have been so mean in the past? And why have I been? After all this, I don't care if the guy I like likes my friend anymore. I just don't want my friend going out with him because I don't want to see my (guy) friend get hurt. My feelings have been all wavy today. First, I was acting really happy, oblivious to what was going on. Then I was angry, and then I was sad. And now I'm just... I don't know anymore. But I just read over this blog and I sound so emo. I'll probably change my mind after I publish this blog and delete it... so you're lucky if you get a chance to read this. 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am exhausted, bruised, cut up, sore, and all that fun stuff. And I am confused as to why Josh has about three of the same blogs. We had yet another game today. We lost. This sucks, because we really are a better team than Newington. The thing was, we were all so tired. I know that's not a good excuse, but that's why we didn't play our best. The first game, I only got put out for about 5 minutes towards the middle of the second half. The second game, the only time I got put out was when I got that yellow card. Today, I kept on looking over to Consic to see if she was going to sub me or not. I got put out for about five minutes towards the end of the first half. For the first two games, I started as center and played left attack wing as well as center. That is a lot of running... I am so tired.  Today, I started as left attack wing and stayed left attack wing until Consic switched me to d-wing to defend #7 of Newington. God damn, that girl is weird. I checked her stick when she had the ball, and she said, "Get away from me." That's so gay telling a defender to get away. Seriously. And if that defender actually LISTENS, that's just plain pathetic. #4 of Newington, she is so nice... she plays field hockey too. She's so little, her head is to my shoulder, I think, haha. I'm really pissed off that I have not scored ONE goal yet. I made so many damn shots towards goal. Of course, that sweet shot yesterday... arghhhh, $^#%#@#^asdf*. I whipped my shot towards the upper left corner and it rebounded off the goggles of this girl who was standing in front of goal. At first I thought it was my fault, and I felt so damn bad. After that ref gave me a yellow card, everyone was telling me that I had already shot when that girl jumped out in front of me. If that girl didn't run out, that shot would have made it in. I wasn't sure, but that's what someone said. So I got pissed, because that should have been a call on her for shooting space, and I should have been able to get a free shot on goal. Instead, I got a yellow card. Yayyyy, not. AND THEN, afterwards, people were telling me the other team was bitching about how I broke that girl's goggles. I highly doubt it, since goggles were designed to save your head from getting hit. They wouldn't break after you get hit just once. Believe me, I know, haha. Mercy was seriously a one person team. This girl, Kait DelCampo, #47 (this is pathetic that I actually know her name) shot the majority of the goals. One time during the face off, the ball flew up and I was getting it. She dug her cleat into my foot and I fell flat on my stomach. Grr. We're not playing against them again. I don't know if that's a good thing or not. I sucked at today's game. I made shots towards goal, but none of them went in. And yes, I fell (got knocked down, same thing... either way, I ended up on the ground) at least three times today. The sweetest fall was the first one... when the girl I was defending ran into me, I went down on the ground all sprawled out. Then I leapt back up and blocked a pass towards my girl right after I got up. Unfortunately, that was about the only good thing I did today. Next game is home, vs. Chesire on Tuesday, May 4th. Hopefully, I won't be as tired that - woah, I just yawned. Anyways, hopefully I won't be as tired that day. And Josh, I don't know why my posts are always so long. I just have a tendency of typing a lot. It's not like anyone reads this, because my posts are always about lacrosse. 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       today was pretty awesome. i gave a flower to someone (i was told this someone doesn't read these so i can talk about it lol). first time i have ever given a flower to someone at shs and it was way better than expected. yes it was difficult and needed moral support from josh and other friends but i did it woo hooo. it was cool. my mom is callin me now so i have to cut this blogg short.. there will be a continuation............  but im glad i did 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today since we had that bomb threat thing I had time to waste waiting for lunch so I was in the attendance office right...and i saw this AWESOME motorcycle helmut. It is cool colors with spiked coming off it everywhere. I want one. So i took some pics. Here they are:      
    
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hail Sepko....Hail Sepko... Ugh this is so stupid. I have pole vaulted a total of 4 times (including a meet) and We have not practiced pole vaulting in 4 FREAKEN WEEKS! That sure isn't cool. Anyhow yea not to much else happened since I blogged last tues. On wed I went to school then came home after running 6 miles really tired then my parents made me go to bell choir but it wasn't that bad because a bunch of people didn't show up so we didn't play. I just rode around the church in the wheelchair (funtimes) then today which is thurse was alright. I woke up and got ready for school and when i got on the bus i felt prepared and actually like I had everything for ONCE. I got to school took an INSANELY hard Earth-Science test which i DEFF aced I hope. Then I worked on and completed our group physics project by myself... ( I did the whole thing at 1:45 Thurse morning) Then I went to track expecting to pole vault since he said either wed or thurse we would. But chilinsworth wasn't there and since neither greg or I were vaulting sat. We didn't need practice... WTF O well when we loose it is now HIS FREAKEN FAULT. LEts see I don't understand how girls can right such long posts. Mine turn out to be so short. O wait I watched the Pirates of the Carribean and have determined that I want to be a pirate and then I went to robotics and made a yearbook and tried to hang our robot. Then came home and watched CSI! and then watched an hour thing on TV about cheating....with my parents.... It was AMAZING! they have this website called turnitin.com or sumthing and if a teacher submits your work it will find if any of the words 8 or more match any website on the web. Talk about finding your out!!!!!What can you do. It was a really interesting show. Then we wwatched this special about like drunk driving and sumthing and how this girl lost so much and the driver walked away without a scratch. Now i am sitting here writing this blog about to start spanish homework. I highly doubt anyone actually reads these posts 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I went to school---> went to track---->ate dinner---->went to scouts---->sat on my @__ and talked to people---->started homework------>finished homework  ran a 11:50 for two mile today.. that SUXXOR... but it felt so good running distance again. I felt free like a little birdie in the sky. Then I did nothing else and went to sleep. Yea not much to write about today and I am=Lazy 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
            man, i feel special getting to write on here  
    
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       hello i threw 160 today which is an unheard of distance....today was pretty cool i had fun. i watched josh do his blogging from his palm pilot while i sat there and looked into space doin nothing. 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Attention: this is going to be a blog about the lacrosse game... so if you can't stand me talking about lacrosse, I suggest you x out now. ;) The bus ride was fun, and when we got there, I started getting nervous. Lauren S. pointed out that this was the field Coach Ann got in a fight with the refs... ahh, good times, good times! During warmups, I could not catch a thing, and I was freaking out. In the middle of warmups, they called for captains, and Kait, Lauren S., and I went over to the ref. Afterwards, we got our sticks checked, and then it was time for the game. I walked over to the center of the circle, and I nearly had a heart attack. My opponent had to be almost 6 feet tall. It had got to be funny watching a short little person and a super tall person doing the faceoff. Of course, she had the advantage. I was leaping to get the ball and she didn't even have to raise her arms straight all the way. After about 2 face offs, Consic made Eliz and me switch positions. Oh... bless her, bless her. Simsbury scored like, 3 times and I was thinking in my head, "Oh shit, we're going to lose this game by a landslide." Then I got the ball, made an assist to Kait, and she shot it in. Wahoo. The damn baseball team was there watching, and they were making (really mean) comments. They called our goalie fat and they were saying shit like she couldn't block a thing... I mean, wtf. Were those comments really necessary? Thank god they left towards the end of the first half. I was in the first half the entire time, and I seriously felt like falling on the ground and going to sleep. Running 25 minutes (sprinting some parts) is not what I call fun. So the first half ended, and the game was 1-4, yikes. Consic told us that 11 of their players are SOPHOMORES. That's not fair. Plus, they had like, twice as many players as we did. Okay, maybe not, I'm exaggerating. But they had a lot. Halftime ended, and I was hoping that someone could go in for me, but Consic said to stay in the positions that you were in. So I continued playing left attack wing. Simsbury's goalie constantly runs about 50 meters out of the goal. During one time, she cleared the ball and it went (way) out of bounds. The ref blew the whistle and was going to give the ball to our team. And the goalie was screwed because she was WAY out of her goal, and anyone could easily sprint past and take a shot at an empty goal. Sweet, right? Well... the ref gave the ball the other team. WTF. Even though it was the other team's penalty. So that damn goalie got lucky. When the ref had announced that the ball was going to go to our team, I saw the goalie slowly inching back to the goal. Wtf. What a cheater. What a sore loser. If we get a shot on an empty goal, that's her freaking mistake, so she shouldn't be trying to cheat. Anywho... at another time, the goalie ran far out again, and about five of us went over to defend her and try to check her. Well, she threw the ball, and Kait intercepted the pass. Sweeeet. Even sweeter: the goalie was TOO far out. She couldn't run back to her goal in time, so Kait ran by and just took a shot on an empty goal. That has GOT to be the shot of the season so far! The majority of us were like, "Mwhaha... sucks for you, goalie. That's what you get!" Eliz did an awesome job and scored another goal. The score was 3-4. Consic called me back and had Erin sub for me. After about 5 minutes, I was JUST about to say how I wanted to go back in when Consic told me to go in for Eliz for center. It was so funny, because when Eliz was running back so I could take her position, the ball came towards her, so she had to continue playing. I saw the expression on her face, and she was probably thinking, "Ugh, I was about 10 feet away from getting a rest! WHY?!" I got called for dangerous checks and hmm... what else? OH YEAH. At one time, I got the ball, and I was going in to shoot. I had four people on me. Wtf. I never heard of a quadruple team before. The ref called on ME. On ME. She said that I was trying to barge through them. Well, it's kind of hard to go somewhere when they're on all sides of you. Ali scored, and the game was tied, 4-4. I was hoping that we would get another goal, but time ran out. But still... we played REALLY good for the fact that 1/3 of our team has never played a game in their life. PLUS, we were against some sophomores. Anyways, what really ticks me off is that we tied. Why is it that we always tie with Simsbury, no matter what sport it is?! For field hockey, we won the last game against them by one goal. I'm hoping we'll do the same the next time we meet up with Simsbury. Mwhaha. Well, time to stop typing (I know it's long), but I have to go do civics and science homework now. Ugh. And then get on the computer and type out the responses to the book we were supposed to read over the break. Of course, I don't know how the hell I'm supposed to get on the computer when my dad will be on... and speaking of my dad, I better get off now because he wants to use the computer. Oy vay. 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok let's see. Today is Mon. April 26th. I am Josh Debner and as far as I know I am a Human. I am quite bored even though I have homework to attend to so I thought I might blog about my nothing day. I went to sleep last night like 1:45ish reading this really stupid book called, "The Good Earth". It is just about chinese sluts and how old 75 year old people get it on with 18 year olds. It is really messed up. Well so then I woke up at 5:30 and took a shower. I went back to bed and slept ten minutes. About now it was 5:50 and I went downstairs. Packed my backpack and then packed my lunch. I had my healthy breakfast of..Lucky Charms and then I realized I had to wear the Reel Big Fish T-shirt today so I quickly ran upstairs and changed. Then I went back Downstairs and brushed my teeth. I rode the bus and listened to beatles reading that same freaken book. Then I got to school. Made sure I did my physics lab report right then went up to my geometry class room and read that FRIKEN book until class started. We are doing stupid MAD easy trig Functions (sine. cosine. tangent) and stuff with vectors. DAMN is it easy. Then I went to Earth Science and typed up the questions for the whole class on the computer since I was the fastest and most Agile Typist. Then I travelled to physics and learned more about simple machines and how that all shiz works. I went on the bus and started reading that silly book AGAIN. (while listening to beatles) Then when I got to the school I realized sometimes I get carsick when i Read in the car. I suddenly felt really sick and there was a pain in my stoumache and I felt like throwing up. I went inside signed in and went to lunch and ate huriddly. I felt better Food is a Friend. Hmm. Then I went to civics and told about my current event witch was about radioactive mosquitos and how people die from malaria every 20s and so then I travelled to English and learned about the English books I have to read over the summer. In spanish we spoke english and learned about some weird language... I forget what it is called... something starting with span and ending with ish. O yea SPANGLISH! I went to track afterschool still no vaulting and so I ran Sun Valley and did the accelerations. I don't really want to run the 2 mile tomarrow. I have a feeling I am going to do REALLY bad. Anyhow I came home REALLY tired from this exciting hard day at school and so I eat food then feel asleep until 6:22. I got up put on my boyScout Uniform and went to some cross over thing for people turning into boy scouts. Then I walked to CVS sorry Straub it was closer than Rite-Aid. Bought three candy bars.. One for me...One for me... and One for my sister since she got straight A's on her report card. She did a HELL of a lot better than me. I came home ate 2 plate full of nachos I made and then came up to my room and decided I am bored lets BLOG! I am waiting for kevin and erika to blog and I though people might blog today but I guess I will be the first and only. I am downloading like 100000 CSI tv shows to watch and I LOVE that show. I am really bored so I should stop rambling. NO ONE wants to read this. I am a looser. I wish I had a girlfriend sometimes. I dono I just LONG for it then there are other time and I am like heh... Why WOULD I want one. But yea like I said I am rambling and no one likes me anyhow so I don't gotta worry about that. Sorry for boring you and wasting 5 min. Of your day hearing about my boring one. 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       should this be moved to  southington.blogspot.com shs.blogspot.com ____.blogspot.com I dono vote or give ideas in the shoutbox.. cuz josh debner.blogspot is just plain dumb So i will be waiting your request everything will be exactly the same .. just differnt address 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I can't believe vacation has gone by so fast. It's unbelievable... it seems like it was just yesterday when I was lying on the floor of my bedroom complaining about how bored I was. Hmm... well, lots happened, but I don't feel like bringing up past crap. I was on the phone with Lauren, telling her how I had been contemplating whether I want to play the guitar or the bass (because my mom is a butthead and wants me to not have so many instruments in the house... pftt). I was leaned more towards the guitar because it's so versatile. BUT NOW... damn, I am eagered to learn the bass. Even though the Ibanez SRX400MO is going to take me forever to save up for, it'll be worth it. So you're wondering what swayed my decision, eh?  MATT FREEMAN , the bassist of Rancid/formally of Operation Ivy. He has got to be a god. Or well, close to one. I was listening to my old MP3s today, and I came across Rancid's song, "Journey to the End of the East Bay". AWESOME bass in that song... go download it or something. Hmm... what else to blog about... well, you know that little picture that Josh drew? (Scroll down... it's on the left side of the screen) I'm  TALLER  than Lauren in that picture! Haha... that has got to be a first. And I'm wearing a skirt with no top... that has got to be a first, too. I have nothing else to say, so later kiddos. 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I dono wut do you guys think... colors sexy enough for you? If you find any good color schemes in a program or anything i can match the colors color for color with this new program I got. Not to much been happening. I got a new google just because i can and I REALLY like it. 1 gig FREE of ROOM that is incredible. so yea... i have jdebner@sbcglobal.net and josh.debner@gmail.com i dono which you think is easier to remember i also have jdebner@crec.org haha so yea w/e Hmmm Today was boring as you can see I even had time to work on the blog. I don't want to go back to school tomarrow. We got mario in here and soon kevin to. Umm yea not to much else i can think of. Erika and I were supposed to go to the mall... but my parents were SLEEPING AHHH! wut can you do right!? umm I am gonna go work on some more homework and who noez wut else so yea peace for now 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       this is mario, this is my first time bloggin wooooo. wait where did that word come from, but whatever here is my day...   well today i woke up and was very dissapointed because it is the sunday before monday which means school. i wasn't worried about school cuz i like school well actuallly the things that come with school. anyway im like shit i have to do a ton of homework. so i was like stupid italian class im gonna find a way to kill my italian teacher.  i called up a friend of mine who also shares the same italian teacher and hates her just as much as i.  so we said we wont kill her we will just do r homework and suprise her to death.  i went to do my hw and the directions r in italian and the questions r in italian and i was like fuuuuuuuuck i live in american gimme directions in english but no. that would be easy.  so im like screw that bitch im gonna bull shit everything she assigned me and thats just what i finished doin. so im happy cuz i convince myself that i actually did my hw even tho i really didn't. o well. this first blog was ok at best but there will be more and with enough practice maybe i can do it as well as josh.. yeaaaa.  heyy people in the little box down there stfu ur gay and u have no friends ok so eat shit.. bye bye 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       yay! i'm finally blogging, i dont think i've blogged in like 2 weeks. anyway so we went to the reel big fish concert and i swear it was the most fun i've had in a long time. We got really good spots right in the front and the bass player to lucky boys confusion is reaallllly hott. It was scary at the beginning though b/c of the moch pits. Then it got really fun. Now i want to go to another concert really bad. i was wathcing mtv last night and they were interviweing New Found Glory and it was so cool b/c they asked them some of their favorite bands and one of them was reel big fish. I was like yea i know them and i saw them! hehe, it was so exciting. After i saw the concert i really wanted to play my guitar because they made it look so easy, so i've been playing my electric non stop the whole vacation. I hope i can get a new one for my bday this summer. I had practice every morning this week and i had a meet on Monday. The meet went good. steph actually ran this one. She did the one mile and got like 7:2? i just know it was seven twenty something. Then the next day i went to dicks to go buy some spikes for track. It was the scariest thing. My dad and i didn't know the difference between the distance and sprinting spikes so we wanted to ask someone. Then all of a sudden i see coach whyte. What r the odds of seeing your coach there when u need his help. so we walke towards him then i realized that he was wearing a dicks shirt and handing out shoes. He works there! So coach whyte sold me my spikes, it was really weird. Then the next day of course steph didnt' go to practice suz she was too tired. Today i didn't go to practice but i acutally had an excuse. i had a migrain, its only the second practice i've missed though out of all 3 seasons so i think its ok, and steph didn't go today either. I really dont want to go back to school. Vacation is almost over!!! grrrr 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, after crying hysterically over my hair, I picked up the phone and decided to call Lauren. But when I picked up the phone, there was no dial tone. I got suspicious, so I paused and then said, "Hello?" And it was Lauren! Man, we are psychic! So I was on the phone with her, crying, laughing, and making fun of my hair. I realized I may be a tad dramatic... okay, so I don't look like a guy, but still, DAMN, it's short for me (and I realize that short for me may be considered long for other people, considering the fact my hair was really, really long). It's just BARELY past my shoulders!!!!! Lauren told me that vitamins make your hair grow faster... haha, I don't know if that's true or not, but I raided my dad's vitamins cabinet and I took as many types of vitamins as I could. Not a smart thing to do, I know. Is it possible to be overdosed on vitamins? Maybe as a side effect, I'll grow to be extremely tall overnight. Haha, I wish. I'm just hoping my hair will grow at least 1 inch before my first lacrosse game... or else I'll be standing in the middle of the field trying to keep my hair up instead of concentrating on the game. THANKS A LOT, MOM. I'm going to go edit my previous post now, as I was crying when I was typing it, and I might have not made any sense at all. Toodles, kiddos. Let's pray my hair will miraculously grow a lot longer, alrighty? 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I woke up around 8:00AM to get ready for going to New York. Sadly, the thing I was looking most forward to was being able to listen to the K Rock 92.3 radio station (The website is  urlLink here ). When I arrived at New York, I was all cheerful and happy. I was having happy thoughts like, "Man, I love New York... it's like a second home!" After a while, I started having opposite thoughts. I was thinking, "Man, New York BLOWS." Everywhere I turned, I saw Yankees baseball caps. I saw someone with an A-Rod jersey... ugh. When I came out of the restaurant, this guy was waiting by the door, he followed me, and whispered in my ear, "You're beautiful." EW. I wanted to sock him in the jaw. He followed me for a couple more seconds. He's lucky I didn't kick him in the crotch. And at the hairdresser's, I wanted my hair to be just 2 inches shorter, and layered more. But my mom came over, told the hairdresser, "Don't listen to her. Just cut up to here," and she indicated where she wanted it to be cut. I was just so shocked that I couldn't say anything. But I was screaming inside my head, "WOW, WHAT THE FUCK, MOM. WHOSE HAIR IS IT?" My mom was like, "Well, you have a lot of hair, and it's really thick. Plus, it must be difficult playing sports with so much hair." Um... yeah, Mom, sure. WHOSE HAIR IS IT? Yeah, SO WHAT if I have a lot of hair and it's really thick? YOU WANT ME TO BE BALD? Anyways, WHO'S WEARING THE HAIR, HUH? IF IT'S DIFFICULT, IT'S DIFFICULT FOR ME, NOT FOR YOU, GOD DAMN IT! I officially think I look like a guy now. I got like, 7 to 8 inches cut off... I feel like crying now. It's like I'm living with Hilter, I have no say in what goes on. I mean... a HAIRCUT. Don't I get a say in what I look like? Jesus Christ. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Okay, I lied, I didn't really blog about the Reel Big Fish concert the next day. I'm not even going to blog about it now, because I don't feel like it. Well, I'll talk about it briefly: We were about three rows from the stage the entire time. The opening bands were pretty decent. Suburban Legends had a lot of... ermm, interesting dance moves. I was kind of hoping someone would drop their trombone or trumpet while they were chucking it around all over the place, but no one dropped any instruments. I liked Lucky Boys Confusion a lot better than Suburban Legends. I purchased their CD for $5. When Reel Big Fish started playing, everyone got really crazy. Everyone was like, a foot taller than me, I swear I was going to die. I got separated from Lauren, Josh, and Steph so many times. Steph had to save me at least 10 times. And someone crowdsurfed and landed on my head, we don't get into that... and the security guard was just standing in front of the stage watching all of this go on and he was just smiling. What a crackhead. So I got the LBC CD, and I got a LBC shirt and a RBF shirt. I splurged, I know, but it's not like I'm going to be buying anything else anytime soon. Last night, I got a really bad virus. I don't know what happened, but my computer restarted and then it wouldn't even load the way it usually does. The screen turned all black and it said something like, "Cannot find SYSTEM.INI. Insert emergency boot disk and type scanreg /restore." I gave up, and I went to bed. Or at least I TRIED to go to bed. I was praying my dad would be called in early to work so he wouldn't go on the computer and notice that it didn't work. And guess what? HALLELUJAH, HE GOT CALLED INTO WORK EARLY. So as soon as he left around 8:00AM, I sprinted downstairs and tried to fix this. I called into the Dell Customer Service so many times, and the damn machine picked up, and it kept on going "Blah blah blah, please press 1. For blah blah blah, please press 2." Finally, someone picked up and GUESS WHO FIXED THE COMPUTER AND GOT RID OF THE VIRUSES?! Wahoo. Actually, I must give the dude over the phone some credit. He had a really cool accent, and he sounded like Apu from the Simpsons. I wanted to laugh, but I didn't want to be rude. Imagine Apu laughing and saying, "Hah. Yeah... exactly, exactly." That was what the guy kept on saying to me. What a nifty dude. Well, he helped me, and that's all that matters. I finished by 9:15... I danced around the house, jumped around, did cartwheels, screamed, cheered, and all that good stuff. I watched a movie, and fell asleep because I didn't get any sleep until... well, yesterday. I woke up, finally ate something for the first time today, watched TV, and here I am. I'm kind of disappointed. I should have gone outside, but the sun wasn't even that bright out today. HOLY SHIZNIT, and I just realized, I didn't pick up my lacrosse stick at all today. Dios mios, as my old spanish teacher would say. Hey... speaking of Scadden... Josh, did you ever finish that 1000 puzzle Scadden paid you to finish? Ahahaha. I must go back and visit her someday. I bet she'll get a kick out of that. Or err... a visit from me must feel like a kick in the HEAD for her. I don't think she liked me too much. Wow, I'm rambling a lot now. Anywho, I don't know if I should get my hair cut or not. It's about 13-14 inches right now. I want to get my hair cut, but I don't want my hair too short either. So I don't know what to do now. OR... maybe I should just get more layers so it doesn't seem like I have so much hair. Eh, who knows? 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This is the shirt lauren and I bought at the concert. Isn't it just AWESOME!    
    
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       by Eric R. Danton courant Rock Critic  Even the newest ska music sounds as though is was made at least eight years ago. If you're going to hang out in a mid-90's time warp, though, the guys in Reel Big Fish are a fun bunch to have around. The mid-90's is about when the latest ska revival peaked in popularity with bands like the Mighty Mighty Bosstones and early No Doubt adding an up-tempo twist to alternative music. The speeded-up, hornlanced form of raggae remains a live draw, however, judging by the  800  people who crowded the Webster Theatre Monday night to bounce along to Reel Big Fish's infectious songs.  The six-peice group played with impressive energy. Guitarist Aaron Barrett cranked out riffs while sprinting in place and jumping up and down (when he wasn't singing, of course), and the horn section at stage-right leavened the tunes with brassy blasts from a tumpet and trombone. Along with irresistible horn hooks and bringht vocal harmonies, songs like "Ban the Tube Top" and "She Has a Girlfriend Now" featured irreverent lyrics. "Sometimes love goes both ways," trumpet player/guitarist/singer Scott Klopfenstein said when he introduced the latter song about a relationship gone awry. As joyful as the band's preformance was, watching the crowd aws nearly as interesting. The area right in front of the stage became a roiling scrum of people swaying and hopping as once, in time with the punchy horn fills and punk-reggae guitar riffs. Ska also has its own dance accompaniment, known as skanking and few people in the mostly deserted bar area swung their arms and kicked their legs and spun about until even the people watching felt winded. Maybe it was the frenetic dancing, or maybe it was the band's over-long set, but Reel Big Fish started to loose the crowd by the end of it's 90-minute preformance. Half that amound of time would have been the perfect length. The group ended its regular set with a cover of A-ha's "Take On Me." 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       We went kayaking again today down on the CT River in Middletown. We paddled 1 hour upstream and it only took us 20 min to get back to the same place. I guess current helps a little bit.  This is My baby  urlLink SEXY KAYAK       Although mine is yellow faded to orange. I also have a skirt so I don't get wet. A Paddle and a bilge Pump.  I LOVE KAYAKING! Tell me if you know any good spots! 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       REEL BIG FISH WAS SOOO GREAT! I can't wait to go to another concert. I couldn't have imagined a better time. I had so much fun. 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I don't trust anyone anymore. I think it'll be the best if I move to another place, because I am just so sick and tired of everyone. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey How are you! I am happy o so happy. I am in a good mood because I went kayaking today. My parents are downstairs watching tv my sister has a friend over and i am trying to read this stupid boring, THE GOOD EARTH. Yea and hmm I got my laptop back and the parents are giving me a less hard time about things. I saw erika and amanda and called like EVERYONE! THen i sat on my ass and didn't run or do anything. Cept i did kayak in the middle of the day. I wanna go rock climbing this week. If anyone wants to come or w/e tell me because i don't want to go by myself. I think tues afternoon I am going kayaking with my Pops and maybe jessica gibb's dad. Then tomarrow is the concert. BUt i need to find something to do until then, (it isn't until night time) I g2g help make some robotics webpage I'll write later 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today is a total and complete bust. I wish I was at least at home so I can lay in bed and blast my music and forget about everything. But unfortunately, I can't, because my mom brought me to chinese school half an hour early today. Tingy's right... chinese parents really do expect too much. I don't even know what I should do anymore. I mean, I'm a three season sport participant and I manage to get good grades, I volunteer, I'm always trying my hardest... so what else can I do? I mean, my parents should be glad I'm not one of those people who get wasted every weekend, who carries around a Louis Vuitton or Coach bag or whatever, and who has a cell phone which the bill is up to be $100 every month. I... I don't know anymore. And to make matters worse, I got called fat by my mom today. I just feel really frustrated right now. I mean, I tell my mom that I want a job, and is she happy? No, she goes ranting on and on about how foolish I am to think it's easy having a job, etc. I think I should give up on life. I mean, I try my hardest all the time, and look where it gets me. So I might as well stop trying. Anyways, where would all this take me in life, anyways? Obviously not very far if I'll never be able to attend the college I want to attend. So I might as well attend New Haven college or whatever the hell it's called. Or not attend college at all. WPI, RPI, I never had a chance. :( 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yesterday was the last day of school until spring vacation, woohoo! During homeroom, we found out that the freshmen are going to have a picnic/cookout shindig thing... i don't really know. Well, Becca W. and I signed up to be part of the committee, lol. I'm pretty positive I failed the geometry quiz. Well, I calculated, and if I  ONLY  get points off for the ones I couldn't solve at all, I would get an 89. But I doubt I'll get an 89, so I won't even have my hopes up. We did the listening part of the spanish quiz and corrected them... I'm pretty positive I got a 94 on it. Not bad... I would have a 96, except I didn't see two of the problems were USTEDES, not USTED, so I conjugated wrong. I say she shouldn't have abrreviated (sp?) them. Practice was cancelled and I was mad because I really wanted to go out and play lacrosse in the sun. Oh well. I can always do that by myself, but it just won't be as fun. It was depressing when I got home. So many people were at that Record Journal meet (it made me wish I did track), and a lot of people had already left for vacation. So many people are going to Florida... I envy them. About 3 people are going to Arizona... that's a lot of people. I mean, you would expect people to go to California or something, I don't know! Kait called me from the airport, ahhh, I miss her so much already! I wish I could go somewhere. Stupid Southington. Well, Lauren, Corinne, and I are probably going to the beach one day. I have no idea which beach. I don't know the beaches around here... the beaches I go to are all in Taiwan, lol. So that means I haven't gone to a beach in around 2 years. My god, I'm deprived. Yeah, anyways, so I was depressed, bored, and I was just sitting on the couch flipping through channels. I can't believe I completely forgot about the Red Sox/Yankees game. Luckily, the game didn't start yet. I had the cat in my lap (she was sleeping), and my dad came over,  STOOD IN FRONT OF ME  and started petting the cat. This was when I was  WATCHING THE GAME . I wanted to scream at him. People should never do that to me! That lasted about a minute, but still. I wanted to pick up the cat and chuck it towards him and scream, "HERE, HAVE THE DAMN CAT!", but I stopped myself. If I get this ticked off just because my dad came over to pet the cat, man... imagine me driving. Can anyone say road rage? I can! Anyways, so the Red Sox won, woohoo! :) I have no idea what I'm doing today. I'll probably just spend the entire day outside, and get all nice and tan. People tell me I'm tan enough, but this is considered  LIGHT  for me, okay? Even though my tan has faded from over the summer, I still have damn tan lines. Short tan lines, sock tan lines, sports bra tan line, tank top tan lines... you name it, I probably have it. You'll never catch me doing that tan spa thing... I don't even know what they're called, I just call them cancer filled places. Tan and cancer... two for one deal. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Aww, I'm sorry you had such a bad day, Josh! :( Cheer up, because I'm sure a good day is right around the corner (Wow, I sound like a Hallmark greeting card or something). Surprisingly, I had a rather good day today. I don't know what made it good, it was just a good day. During my stupid orchestra quiz, I didn't care whether or not I sounded good playing in front of Mr. Shaw anymore. Of course, I played like crap, but it was still better than I usually play. We had Coach Bob for Spanish, woohoo! Gym was just hilarious. Jamie, Kait, Alex, and I got so into what we were doing. The whole class must think we're crazy by now, but that's okay... they're going to think we're even crazier after they hear Jamie, Kait, Steph, and I rap in Health class (for a project). Someone wanted us to sing a Beatles song instead ::cough cough:: but no thanks. As much as I hate rap, it'll be more fun rapping in front of the class than singing a ballad in front of the class. Practice was cancelled today, so I went down to PLTW to work on the train. Well, at least I (sort of) caught up now. I left a note for Lauren over by her bright pink bag when I headed into the cafe. I noticed Taylor was doing her biology homework, so I went over to talk to her. It's always fun talking to her... I think we disturbed the entire cafe because we were being so loud though. I talked to Mrs. Consic, and she wants to reschedule our game to Friday instead. I forgot her reason, but I want her to reschedule the game... that is, until I remembered that Kait isn't going to be here on Friday, and she's starting as Right Attack Wing. So I half want the game to be tomorrow, and I half want it to be Friday. I'm still a tad nervous about playing Center... I have a feeling I'm going to make a fool out of myself when I don't do face off right. Blegh, why can't I just play Left Attack Wing?!?! I really don't have anything else to blog about, so I'll stop here... wooo. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       hrmmm.. I realized something today   Life is just one damned thing after another.  --Elbert Hubbard    Ok let's see my grades are slipping so I am obviously not smart anymore or at least am doing good in school at all. I suck at pole vaulting or at least coach thinks I do that is why I am not vaulting tomarrow. I suck at running. My time dropped by 13 seconds from last meet. But 5:24 is still a really bad time for the mile when your are a distance runner. As my dad said, "What happened? Your sick and coach still made you run?" Well I am still kinda of sick but i wasn't feeling that bad maybe I am just not a good runner. No girls like me. Especially not the one I like. Just as a friend.. thats what i always get. I haven't played violin in weeks so I must be horrible at that. Wow... can I do ANYTHING good. I obviously can't type good today. Everyone is ignoring me today. Erika was sick from school so I didn't get to see her. O yea I wastalking to my mom and I borrowed money from my sister for the concert. Come to find out If report cards come out before the concert they may not let me go. They think I have mine now but am not showing it to them. Huh... such trust they have in me. Today they asked me if I still believe in God.. like my wizard cousin had all of a sudden changed my mind. Huh yea I can't really think of anything else to say I am kinda having a bad day as you can tell catch me later   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ugh...my dad lives in the stone age I am telling you. I am sitting at a table eating my chinese food and my dad comes in and asks would you like to watch the Presidential Speech thing for your political science class. I go no I am good I wanna eat my food. Then he goes, "O thats right I forgot your only an AVERAGE student now. You wouldn't wanna watch this". UGH my dad is so anoying. Ain't he supposed to be supportive here? I gotta ask money from my mom for the Reel Big Fish concert. It is going to be amazing. I am sick but I pole vaulted today and did sorta good. I just need to weigh more and get faster. Those things I CAN work on. but i won't be pole vaulting in a meet for a whole though. I don't think Sepko likes me. I am kinda an underdog. He doesn't think I can do it. But today during practice he couldn't find a single thing wrong with my jump... That is a good thing. I burned a couple cd's and yea i dono I am bored and mad so i thought I would write this blog. Peace out more later 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       YAY!! WE GOT THE TICKETSSSSS WAHOOOOOO!!! i just hope i can go 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So it was a typical boring school day... I stressed out in orchestra because I hate that damn Mozart piece, plus Jordan kept on playing that damn "Flying" song which got stuck in my head. Then in PLTW, Mr. Carpenter was talking for so long, and someone hit the main power switchoff thingamaroo. In geometry, I got shushed by one of my fellow classmates for being too loud. Like I said, typical boring school day. Then during practice, I find out that we have to run two consecutive apples. Of course, me being me (stupid) I decide to take it super slow and I ended up being one of the last people to finish. At least I didn't stop to walk at all though. I guess that's good. And I ran by Jake and some other people (who were also running), and I heard the words, "Japanese girl"... idk, I'll have to ask him about that tomorrow, lol. Jackie and I practiced doing face off, and Consic made us run after the face off drill (when no one else had to run). Then at the end of practice, we had to sprint and cradle at the same time. I sprinted down the field, but then I noticed everyone was taking it slow, so I took it slow too. You gotta love being lazy. So okay, here was a crappy day, crappy practice (oh, and I forgot to mention a crappy thing happened today... involves someone being a big fat hypocrite), and I go home. And what do I find? An envelope addressed to me! I ripped open the envelope, and I swear there was 'hallelujah' music going on in the backround.  IT WAS THE REEL BIG FISH TICKETS!  It's kind of funny, because it came with a letter, thanking me for buying the tickets in advanced from their website... and then it's signed, "Story of the Year". Ooookay, buddy. Sure. I felt super special getting a note from one of my favorite bands, and I see it signed, "Story of the Year". Psh, biznatch. It even said, "Thank you for your support!" Erm... I'm supporting RBF, not SotY, mkay thanks. I laughed at the mix up of the letters though. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I haven't blogged in such a long time. Anyway we had our first track meet the other day...it was ok, well actually it pretty much sucked. I got so mad b/c i was running the 4x800 and the 2 mile which is kind of a lot, at least compared to some people, and other people that weren't running were complaining, i wont mention any names though. then over the weekend we had another practice and this person decided to ditch me after saying she would go and slept in. When we actually did get to practice coach was so pissed that no one was there that he took it out on us and started yelling at us. THen we had the hardest workout ever. Todays practice was easy though since its pre-meet. I'm so exited b/c today i found out that Laura got a guitar and she wants to learn, so over vacation shes coming over and im gonna teach her. Then Jake also wants to learn now b/c he said he doesn't want Laura to know somehting that he doesn't lol. I can't wait. steph was like yea i can help teach u. i can't wait to see the look on lauras face when she actually finds out steph can't play a single song. Only 4 more days til vacation!!! which means REEL BIG FISH!! I am so excited about this concert, i just hope the tickets come in the mail to becky b/c she hasn't gotten them yet. I like havn't stopped thinking about this concert lately. Well time to eat, i'm out 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I know I haven't blogged in so long. My sister came back from college on Wednesday. I had to clean and all that fun stuff... I found out the majority of my averages in my classes. I think I'm going to get just one B this term. Stupid Geometry. On Thursday, the freshmen lax team  finally  got the uniforms. I was the first one to pick out a uniform. That was amazing, considering I'm almost always last, thanks to my great last name. I'm #35... woohoo, that's the number I wanted, because #5 and #3 are my two favorite numbers. When we ran the apple, some of us cut part of the apple, and Leahy saw and told Consic. Damn. Figures... the first time I actually cut a part of the apple since autumn, and Leahy sees. After practice, my sister picked me up and we went home. She was talking on the phone about how she was thinking about going over John's (her friend) house, and she was talking about how John had mentioned some of this brother's friends are gonna be there too. After my sister hung up the phone, I told my sister I was one of John's brother's friends, and asked her for a ride... mwhaha. It was nifty at Mario's... I learned that I suck at driving cars and ping pong. I also learned I never want to play polish ping pong... unless the person I'm playing against has horrible aim. I was still in bed yesterday morning when the phone rang around 9:50 (I went to bed around 2 last night). It was amazing how I just leapt out of bed when the phone rang. I mean, I was asleep and everything. Steph was calling to tell me that we were going out to breakfast. I got ready in 5 minutes... damn I'm good. Lauren, Steph, and I went to Gene's Restaurant to eat. Afterwards, we walked across the street to the vet or something... I don't really know what the place was called. It's sad how I've lived in Southington all my life and I still don't know the town. Clifford Ringo... awww, he's so adorable! Mrs. Demarino dropped me off at home, and my sister, mom, and I headed out to the mall afterwards. I really didn't want to go to the mall, but I just went anyways because I wasn't in the mood to be home alone. Hmm... let's see... what else happened? Well, I hate Bob, he can just go and die. The first lacrosse game is on Thursday. I'm really not forward to that game. It sucks that it's an away game, because we're all going to look like gigantic shiny blue blobs in our extremely large jerseys and extremely large skirts. Both the away jersey and the skirt are royal blue. Maybe the designer of these uniforms wanted the opponents to be blinded by the shiny, bright blue and to stand there and just gawk at us. Hah, that may actually be an advantage for us. 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Alright... So here is the deal I told my aunt about my three b's and how i was gonna have to start saying good bye to my friends and my computer and stuff and yea I guess she told my parents. Anyhow my parents flipped out and They took it worse that I thought they would. My Dad is ashamed to look at me. My mom is to frustrated to talk to me and everyone is pissed at me. If my cousin and aunt and uncle weren't here it would be a living war. All over an 87 an 86 and an 84. UGH wow i really hate spanish english and civics.. (by the way all level 3 and 4 but that makes no difference what so ever)I walk into my house and my dadi looks at me really seriously and mad and goes, "I am so dissapointed in you, You have obviously not been trying your best or telling us the truth, There goes everything we have worked for. All the scholorship money and colleges. RIGHT OUT THE WINDOW. All over because you don't want to try now." I just said ok you think that and say that I don't want to argue right now. Then I went over to the trailer and complained to Richard about my parents. Then my mom came in and was like good night and I was like no thanks. She came in and gave me a whole lecture on how my dad is looking at the big picture and I am only looking at right here and now. By the way I am ranked number 1 in my class so doing bad on grades in my family is like doing drugs in other. Its mest up. Then my mom left. I was feeling really mad and sad and bad at this point and wanted to call someone but it was pretty late so I called Erika's cell phone and Steph. But no one was home. I didn't want to call Lauren or Becky and wake them up and Kevin is at the apartment so i couldn't call him. So i walked into the chruch and went to the bathroom and decied I would see who is online at the church since I won't be able to go online at home any more proably. I found there were only a few good people to talk to so I decided I would write this and that is where I am now. I am going to work my ASS off this term. No AIM, No TV, No MOVIES, No Friends. IT IS GOING TO SUX but maybe my parents will be happy if I get straight A's again. Tomarrow I am going to do homework prolly all day, So I can maybe enjoy easter with my parents. If only people could understand. O yea track practioce tomarrow. MAYBE I will be able to go pole vaulting tomarrow. I sure hope my parents let me go to the REEL BIG FISH concert. I would be so incredibly dissapointed if i couldned. But HEY what can you do when you do bad for ONE FREAKEN TERM IN YOUR LIFE. (by the way those are my first b's ever on a report card and my parents blame it all on robotics and me not trying.) (they say that robotics isn't worth doing because you don't get a grade...I say they are on crack) 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       secret_dude99: you didnt even respond when i hit you lol Joshonhis laptop: i was having a dia de HORRIBLE today Joshonhis laptop: until I pole vaulted secret_dude99: why Joshonhis laptop: then everything has been going GOOD since then.. Joshonhis laptop: started off I had to wake up real early to finish an enlgihs project Joshonhis laptop: ok then I almost got to school late.. Joshonhis laptop: then the capts were SOO stupid today Joshonhis laptop: then my little led blinkythingy batter ran out Joshonhis laptop: then i sat in the library doing nothing Joshonhis laptop: then you weren't in your class Joshonhis laptop: then i had a test that i did bad in in civics Joshonhis laptop: and found that my quarter grade fropped 12! points since last term.. secret_dude99: o Joshonhis laptop: so i gotta figure a way to explain that one to my mom w/o blaming it on robotics Joshonhis laptop: then I sumhow got blue on my white sweatshirt Joshonhis laptop: then i had to listen to the Most BORING lecture today in english on antigenie Joshonhis laptop: then i went to spanish and found out we have a project Joshonhis laptop: and wwe did busy work all day secret_dude99: Antigone lol i loved that  secret_dude99: aww im sorry Joshonhis laptop: then i went to the teacher and talked about my grade found out its final and i just should done better or she like my work better Joshonhis laptop: then i went to track and found that for shirt there were not medium... Joshonhis laptop: or large.. Joshonhis laptop: so i have a XXL track uniform   
    
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Super quick blog... today was extremely boring. During the pre CAPT testing, I really needed to go to the bathroom, and the teacher was taking so damn long with the math problems. He said, "Alright... you multiply the numbers like this..." And everyone was saying, "No, you divide!". Then he responded, "Huh? What? You multiply?" And I got so pissed that he was taking so long with the problem, I shouted out, "NO! You freaking divide the numbers!" I thought I had muttered that to myself, but I realized I had shouted when I saw Cecelia and Mal cracking up hysterically. I had lacrosse practice (extremely cold), and then I had to leave early for an orthodontist appointment. I asked my doctor how long I have to wear my braces for until I can get them off, and he said they might be taken off around September or August.  AGH.  That's in about 5 months. That's too long. It's been  EXACTLY  10 years since Kurt Cobain died. Sadness. I was going to go to Wal-Mart to get one of Nirvana's CDs (so I can eventually own them all), but I'm going to watch Steph in the Passion play with Lauren instead. And that's why I'm in such a hurry. So toodles kiddos. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       hey wow I dono I feel sad for Absolutely NO reason dono why. today i did church then absolutly NOTHING i did homework and slept all day. It was nice to relax. To bad i didn't finish my only homwork assignment project thing. I'll finish it tomarrow. I hate daylight saving time and stuff. Its so stupid so confusing and just plain dumb. Yea. I have yet to use the spell check button on my posts yet heh hope people can read them. I HAVE to get a new cd reader so i can start ripping cd's that is all i am doing over summer. Actually I have quite a lot planned but yea. I needa borrow becky;s entire cd collection a couple cd's at a time. My network is so fuxxored. ugh it went down today and i almost died doing my hw without wireless. I got it half back up again. My dad is aLwayz so disssapointed in me. Everything is my fault and I shoulda done better. Whenever anything is missing he blames me. Half the time it is me but that is besides the point. Since my desktop is being gay I can't stream music to my room. So i have been listening to the same son all day since its the only one I have on my laptop. Good thing it is a good song. My laptop is being gay to it decided to stop playing dvd's or music or anything so i hadd play around with it.Hmm tomarrow i gottta finish my project before 7th period. My songs are.hmmm interesting and yea capts YEA no academy. I dono wut else I always think of stuff to write then go and start to type and am like what am i gonna write. O yea i got webspace so I might be upgrading if i have the time or engery or w.e. I dono we'll have to see Josh Debner i like to sign twice 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Before chinese school, I convinced my mom to bring me to Best Buy. I was mad because they only had one little section for Nirvana. And there were like, 3 rows just for the Beatles. I didn't get the Nirvana CD I wanted because they didn't have it... that made me mad. Then it took me around 15 minutes to decide on what CD to get instead of the Nirvana CD I wanted. I was going to get a Dead Kennedys CD, but they only had 3 CDs by them. They didn't have the one I wanted. I got a Led Zeppelin CD instead. It was $14.99, but it was two discs. It's a a pretty good deal. Afterwards, I went to the West Farms mall, since it was right across. My mom and I spent a little too much time at the mall... I ended up being late for chinese school, whoops. I need about 3 more Nirvana CDs to complete my collection. I just started on Led Zeppelin. I'm not going to get any 'Best Of' CDs because that's just a waste of my money. So I need 9 Led Zeppelin CDs to complete  that  collection. Plus, I have other CDs from bands I want like Alkaline Trio, Dead Kennedys, The Offspring, Powerman 5000, Tsunami Bomb, yadda yadda. Too bad I can't trade my CDs from when I was little (like Britney Spears... aghhhh) for CDs I actually  want  to have. That would be awesome. Time to go upstairs to listen to wonderful Zeppelin and clean the room (because my sister is coming back this week). Later kiddos. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ok todays sunday...lets recap on my "wonderful" weekend. Friday night after practice i just hung out at my house until like 8:45 at night me and my friend decided to have a sleepover. Saturday morning i brought my friend home, then i took a shower and Mike asked me to go to his house to like watch a movie or something, so i went there which was really scary but ended up being fine. Then right from there my mom and I went to steph's house before she went to prom. Her hair and everything looked so pretty and i loved her dress. I feel bad for Mario though since shes going to prom and doesn't really like him. O well she'll probably change her mind AGAIN. Ok so after that Matt and Kyle Belanger came over and watch freddy adu play soccer with me and my bother. Then all of us went to my neighbors house to watch the game. scariest game i have ever watched! so i didn't get hom til like 12 30 and of course we had to change our clocks back  so it was really like 1 30. o well. Becky just got me in this CD mode and i want to go to best buy and buy some cds lol, thanx becky. Its either gonna be Pnk Floyd or beatles. hmmm, probably beatles, i just got their Yellow Submarine CD yesterday. Im getting closer now i only need like 9 more lol. I think i have 10 total of their CD's so far. Today im actually going running which is a first on the weekend b/c even when coach tells me to run on the weekend i never do but i think the only reason i want to run today is b/c i want to test out my ipod, otherwise i probably wouldn't go. ok well i need to go eat my breakfast. wahoo 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am so incredibly bored. I hate staying home on a Saturday night. Lauren, Josh, and I were supposed to go bowling late last night, but we ended up not going. Instead, I slept over my friend's house. Then I basically spent the entire day online. I started getting ticked off at installing greymatter because... ugh, I don't know, it's weird uploading stuff without using an FTP program. So then I gave up. 12 days until the first lacrosse game (It's away, ugh), and 16 until the Reel Big Fish concert (with Lucky Boys Confusion and Suburban Legends). On Monday, it will be exactly ten years since Kurt Cobain died... There's this girl that I used to be incredibly good friends with, but I don't know anymore. My friend wants everything to be the way it used to be between all of us. I try my best to be nice and talk to her, etc. I don't know why I try so hard to remain friends with her, because she lies to me all the time, and always leaves me out of everything our group does. I don't trust her anymore, and I regret having trusted in the past, because I told her something no one should really know. My friend (who I shall not name) told me that the girl came up to her and told her I was leaving her out. WTF, when? The only time I know of (and it was the ONLY time) was this time during study hall... I sat with Jamie instead, because we needed to do our science lab. Pure evil of me, right? I'm sure... I hate how our friendship seems so fake. It's not even a friendship. I feel bad for not even being sad that we don't have such a great relationship like we did. I don't even get why I'm not upset. Am I really that mean or is the friendship just never that great? I think I should stop talking about this person now. Even though she talks crap about me behind my back, I shouldn't stoop down to the same level as her. I didn't say who it was that I was talking about... but still. She's not being a loyal friend towards me, but that's no reason why I shouldn't be a loyal friend towards her still. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok so here we go. It is friday night. Josh is Home.. alone.. again.. and yea. Um let's see we MIGHT go bowling tonight. I sure hope so. But we'll have to see. I have SOO much homework. I have to read the entire odessey. I am such a procrastinator. Practice was easy today because of injury but it sure hurt like hell. Between the wind and the pain I felt a couple tears. It was HARD! hahaha. Yea Mon. No academy so that is a good thing. And I get to go to PLTW YEA.. my only chance since parents won't let me take it next year. I dono i wish kevin could sleep over but he is doing something with is dad. So maybe another day. Ha... I set my sterio up again and networked my computer so i have streaming music anywhere in the house wirelessly then i hook it up to my sterio.! High wattage is FUN in ROOM! Tomarrow I have a car wash and boy scout clean up that reminds me i gotta call patrol leaders.. Hrmm I do that.. And blog later if i have time... 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm sitting here with my feet propped up, trying to think of something to write. When did life become so boring anyways? Jesus Christ. I wish I had my Canon Powershot A60 (it's a digital camera) already... then I can just amuse myself by taking pictures of my hands or something. Okay, not necessarily my hands, but  something ... or I wish I had my Ibanez GRX40NM (guitar) so I can teach myself nifty tabs. Why is it the only two things I want are so damn expensive? I don't even care if I don't go shopping at the mall in a million years... all I want are my camera and guitar, so I could never ever be bored or unhappy again. Goddamnit, I can't wait to  start working over the summer.  find a job for the summer. Hah. The summer... wow. It seems so far and close at the same time. I might be going back to Taiwan with my mom.  MAYBE.  It all depends on June 20 somethingth. I don't want to get my hopes up, but Lauren thinks that my mom will be able to go back to Taiwan. If I end up going to Taiwan, that will be amazing. I'd actually see my relatives TWICE in three years... instead of seeing them approximately once every seven years. The last time I went back to Taiwan was the summer of 7th grade. By myself, yeah biznatch. I'm surprised I didn't get on the wrong plane and fly to Jamaica or something. But if I go back to Taiwan this summer, I can bring my digital camera (if I get it by then), and take a million pictures... of my aunts' restaurants, of the lush green mountains, etc. I wrote a 3 paged note to Lauren (mainly) about Taiwan. Hah. Sorry to put you through that torture, buddy. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok lets see I got up late when to school slept basically through capts. Went to PLTW then went to civics. OO yea i got 3 donuts for breakfast and lunch this morning. It was YUMMY. Then I went to english and did nothing like usual. Then I went to spanish and took a freaken impossible test. THen i went to track and limped the warm-up. THen I told coach i don't care i am still running. So I ran sun valley. Then I got back worked out for a bit. Went upside. Listened to some whining. THen saw lauren and then got a ride went home. Got online talked to lauren and becky about someone then thought about poor mario. THen played a car racing game vs mackenzie for like 10 min. then went to robotics. Got home checked to see who was online. Got invited to a chatroom and in ti was rich cahill pat and a bunch of people. Talked in there for a little bit then got fed up with their gayness and Then said hey lets see whos on still no-one fun to talk to and then decided hey josh lets go blog. Yea So I can't wait till tomarrow then i can work on homework and clean my room. I need more time Time is not in the lots of quantitiy right now and I am mad at someone. Lauren sounds board and becky sounds happpy. Kevin I haven't talked to and erika is busy as usual. I am just juicy because i went to robotics. Robotics is fun and makes me happy. I get to get away from everything and just have fun. I want to get better. I hate being injured you get called a slaker and stuff and you have all this bad rep. If only people understood how much i want to run. Hrmm yea that is my day so far I have a bunch of homework. I prolly won't do it like usual. I have to go to the academy tomarrow for the first day this week It will be heartbreaking seeing all the work i missed. So yea I  will write more when i have more time to think about what i am going to post. Until next time  Mood: Life is Sexy People Mad at: Only a couple Friends: Going pretty good Girls: Hey i am josh suxs as always... Song: Gonna listen to some yellowcard  Josh debner even though it says it underneath  PS This is a pretty long post   PPS I am Hungry like a hippo cuz food is good to eat 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Lauren kindly reminded me to blog. Okay, I lied. She said that she was going to blog now, and I decided to, too. Lauren L. and I  finally  cut Spanish. Well, not really. Ms. Delfino wasn't here today (and she hasn't been for the last two/three weeks). We didn't have Coach Bob for a sub, though. We had this other guy. Lauren and I just asked to go to our lockers, and he let us go. So we went across the library and down the stairs next to the girl's locker room. After we got to the second floor, we ran into the bathroom. Then we walked out of the bathroom and just pretended to be coming out of there. It wasn't that fun hanging out with my friends... the majority of them were unhappy, and I was too nervous about getting caught. It didn't help that there was this teacher who stood by the table almost the entire time. After around 10 minutes, Lauren said, "I think we should go to the bathroom now...", so we walked out and into the bathroom. Then after a couple of seconds, we ran out of the bathroom and sprinted up the stairs. Terms close on Monday. I'm really hoping my averages went up in all of my classes. My Spanish average went up 6 points from last term, Geometry went up 8 points, Science went up 3, but I don't know about English and Civics. My average in PLTW went from a 95 to a 91 though. Grr. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       hey hey. Today was possibly the most boring day of my entire life. I fell asleep once in school today but woke up like a min later and the rest of the day i was out of it. Practice today was really hard but so fun cuz we were out in the rain and i got copmletely soaked. some ppl still pretend they're injured and since they've been slakcing off so much today when they actaully try to run they cant even finish one 400 with us. Its really sad. I am still cold from practice and my brother and matt have really been pissing me off. All they do is make fun of me lol. I'm so bored i have nothing to even write about. My dads getting pissed at me so i'm gonna go play my guitar.  
    
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       -Stole from Tom..  FIRSTS First best friend: Proably Jordan First real memory of something: me and my sister playing in the snow First Job: babysitting First screen name: jdbaseball First self purchased album: Garth Brooks First funeral: forgot First pet: Fish First piercing/tattoo: none First credit card: none First true love: keighly (ha) First enemy: Robert Dilley First big trip: Iowa First concert: Reel Big Fish  LASTS Last big car ride: forgot Last good cry: often Last library book: Some Redwall book I think Last movie seen: James Bond 007 Last beverage drank:Water Last food consumed: Cookie as of Now Last crush: uh... Who do you think Last phone call: attempting to call stephanie Last TV show watched: the news Last time showered: last night Last shoes worn: hiking boots Last cd played: Yellow Card-Ocean Avenue Last item bought: School food Last ice cream eaten: at school fri. Last shirt worn: techwick hiking shirt LAYER ONE: -- Name: Josh -- Birth date: 01/29/89 -- Current Location: southington -- Hair Color: dirty blonde/brown -- Height: 5'?' -- Righty or Lefty: Lefty LAYER TWO: -- Your heritage: .5 german .25 norwegian .25 sweedish  -- The shoes you wore today: hiking boots -- Your weakness: i trust people to much -- Your perfect pizza: every meat available -- Goal you'd like to achieve: engineer and become successfull  LAYER THREE: -- Your most over used phrase on MSN/AIM: "nice" -- Your thoughts first waking up: Already? -- Your bedtime: Whenever -- Adidas or Nike: Nike -- Lipton Ice Tea or Nestea: nestea -- Chocolate or vanilla: vanilla -- Cappuccino or coffee: neither  LAYER FIVE: -- Smoke: hell no -- Cuss: maybe.. -- Sing: only when made to /or church -- Take a shower everyday: yep -- Do you think you've been in love: yes -- Want to go to college: for sure Layer Six: -- Liked high school: sure i guess -- Want to get married: yes -- Believe in yourself: sometimes -- Get motion sickness: no -- Think you're attractive: deff not.. -- Think you're a health freak: nope -- Get along with your parent(s): sometimes -- Like thunderstorms: maybe -- Play an instrument: violin  LAYER SEVEN:  In the 6 past months... -- Drank alcohol: no -- Smoked: No -- Done a drug: no -- Had Sex: No. -- Made Out: No -- Gone on a date: No -- Gone to the mall: Yes -- Eaten an entire box of Oreos: No, but I did other stuff -- Eaten sushi: no  -- Been on stage: no -- Been dumped: yes -- Gone skating: no -- Made homemade cookies: no -- Gone skinny dipping: no -- Dyed your hair: yes blue for robotics  -- Stolen anything: nope  LAYER EIGHT:  -- Have you ever: -- Played a game that required removal of clothing:yes -- Been trashed or extremely intoxicated: nope -- Been caught "doing something": nope -- Been called a tease: no -- Shop Lifted: no -- Changed who you were to fit in: prolly  LAYER NINE: -- Age you hope to be married: by 25 -- Numbers and Names of Children: 2+ one has to be called...? -- Describe your Dream Wedding: traditional/fun/hott/outside/ -- How do you want to die: sleeping -- Where you want to go to college: Mit RPI northwestern FIT  -- What do you want to be when you grow up: ENGINEER -- What country would you most like to visit: Eroupe LAYER TEN: In a boy... or girl: -- Best eye color?: anything -- Best hair color?: blonde :-D -- Short or long hair? about shoulder +/- a couple inches -- Height: no taller than me or not by muchg -- Best weight: w/e -- Best articles of clothing: w/e makes them feel good LAYER ELEVEN: -- # of people I could trust with my life: 2 maybe 4? -- # of CDs that I own: hmm.. i own? like 400.. i have? like 2000 -- # of piercings: none -- # of tattoos: None -- # of scars on my body: ALOT -- # of things in my past that I regret: mant but don't dwell on it  Ha/// you must be bored to read this... 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So anyhow at least we had today off from school or that would have been not fun at all. I went hiking today with my dad and it was nice to get out since yesterday my dad had to do confirmation and we went party hopping all day yesterday. We hiked 8 miles up talcott mountain in avon. It was pretty fun. Everyone comments on our dog it is pretty cool. So yea I came home I gotta finish this 300 page book before tomarrow. Erika send me a message she was getting her belly button pierced. I guess that is cool. W/e... What really pisses me off is that in her profile it talks about football guys but i am used to that. Then it says I need a boyfriend. Now I KNOW for a fact that she doesn't want it to be me. Now I dono if she noes but if she noes that i still like her I think that is just fucking cruel. But i guess she prolly doesn't no i have liked her forever. While we were hiking I was thinking about stuff and came to the conclusion I need to get to know more girls better b/c as of now even though erika will only like me as a friend i can't see myself marrying anyone other than her :-( pretty sad isn't it. Heh anyhow I should start reading me book now.  
    
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Lets see I haven't blogged since thurse. Fri my dad and sister and mom woke up extremely early and left to go to the air port so I was left to wake up on my own. I got ready and was outside but my bus didn't show up on time. So i figured we had a sub and she would show up late. She did but something interesting happened. She drove by me and didn't even stop.. huh WEIRD! anyhow so my dad drove me to school. I don't remember much from school except that I brought my laptop and during research block I played games and must have got yelled at a million times. Then I downloaded some movie and watched it on the way back to SHS. After school my dad picked me up and we went out shopping. I got some cool stuff. We went to sams club then up to compusa for some memorial moonlight sale. 4 hourse only. People lines up to get in. I got a tv tuner card fro 20$ a 120gb external hd for only 120 and 90cds for 10$. So it was pretty fun! After that we went to EMS and did not that much then TGIF. MANCHESTER has some HOT WAITRESSES... i was like DAMMMN so yea. We then came home and I got my tuner card installed then kevin called and asked if I wanted to sleep over and I asked my dad and he said yes even though we were gonna go hiking in the morning. This morning he called and was like I am leaving for hiking see ya later. I Felt So bad. I hope we can go hiking again sometime this vacation. I think he thinks I don't want to spend time with him. But I really do so I just don't know Today we just hung out then went to EmS and bought a hydration pack after I went to the mall with STEPHANIE! :-D that was fun. I know erika is camping this weekend. I hope she has fun but i am not going to worry about her. Church is gonna be boring tomarrow. no stephanie AND no erika. :-/ what can you do right. I bought a styx cd at the mall today and steph bought a hula hoop which I carried around the mall for her. I should proably start reading the book I have to read for english by tues. I really don't want to read it though. O well? So yea pics are below  
    
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Picture 3&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Picture 2&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    On the way home from Manchester after we went to TGIF and saw some BLAZIN watress's we saw this sweet looking truck drag race thing on the highway so I took a few pics through the window. That thing in the back is NOS. Pretty Cool huh.. I'll post a couple pictures&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    This is the line at compusa where I went and got a tv tuner card so I can watch and record tv on my computer as well as a external harddrive. It was a pretty good sale and it only lasted like 4 hours. People started running in the store it was funny!&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok so I woke up today very not easy. It took me forever and I almost missed the bus. I studied a little for my physics test today but not much and then fell asleep. In Earth Science w e did some pretty cool stuff. We made cold water boil by putting it in a vacuum and then we crushed stuff. I was tired but wasn't able to go to sleep on the bus. So I got to lunch and I made this AWESOME thing with a water bottle it was like a fountain and when you flip it over it bubbles and stuff. So that was the highlight of my day. Went to civics and got bored. Then I went to English and I got an A+ on my oral presentation but then I got a 73 on a research paper. :-/ Not cool. I went to spanish and got bored. I was so happy I didn't have to go to track today. So I went to kevins after school then I went to his ortho appt. We played wiffleball outside... I suck horribly. After school I talked to Erika afterschool and she gave me some attitude and obviously didn't want to talk to me. Steph on the other hand was real nice and we talked for a bit about track and other stuff. I need to work out tonight... that will be fun. My mom and my sister and my pops and me went to burger king. It was good eat'in. Hmm "I am starting to look into other pathways.." if you know what I mean.. I just don't see how this erika this is gonna work out. Maybe we were just meant to be friends. So. I am looking foreward to the beatles collection to finish but it is taking forever. I am watching jackie chan right now. This weekend my sister and mom are going to IOWA to see my cousins graduation. It cost to much money to send all of us out there. So I get to stay home with my Pops. I have a lab report due tomarrow I should proably start so i'll be off.  
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Obladi-Oblada... Two BEST beatles Songs. So anyhow I am tired So I will tell you my day in Josh version. Slept..Ate..Did Hw..Went to School...Whent to practice..went to home..ate krispy kremes...went to orthodontist...went to robotics...went to boy scouts...more detail later when i have time...   o yea I am going to take someones advice and give up but not loose hope!  
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        ::..:: Hello ::..::   I am Josh. U be know one We be dumb We be bored We feel Sad   So yea I am sitting here thinking about my day. I went to sleep this morning around 1:30 and got up @ 5:30 ..smart move you idiot josh. Then I went ready for school and ate my reeses peanut butter cereal.. It was inventive way of eating it. I ate some cereal then drank milk and swished in around in my mouth (wow...you should ...do something more better for the world because josh you are dumb) anyhow I got on the bus and slept listening to Elvis B182 the Beatles and Pink Floyd---GOod combo if you ask me. So then I finally got through half the day and got to civics and got an 81 on a test I thought i did AWESOME on. :-( o well that just ruined the rest of my day and it started getting bad and stuff and so I went running after school and of coarse it was a hard practice but it was short so it was all good yanno? After practice rich longo and I went to P.T's house real quick and we shot his airsoft gun and I really want one! :-))))))))))) Then I came home looked at them online pretty quick and got a call from erika and here I am thinking AWESOME SHE IS CALLING ME FOR ONCE ACTUALLY MAYBE THERE IS HOPE... SHe actually wanted to borrow some gay freaken tent for this weekend camping with Jordan wat a UGH! So yea... maybe I should take the advice that she gave me back in december and just get over her. She obviously doesn't care about me in that way and I should just move on and find someone who does. I just dono what to do anymore, just when I am about to do hope she'll do something to lead me on again. I am telling you it is horrible. So I don't feel good and I go upstairs and I fall asleep for like 4 hours wake up and kevin calls. We talk for a while about random fun shit and then I eat some food. He tells me his mom will let me get a airsoft gun. Now I just gotta work on my parents. So now I am eating and steph calls now this I think was actually just to talk and I felt good about it but I am not sure if steph feeels completely comfortable around me still when we talk it is just weird she ended up saying that she was tired and was going to sleep. She prolly wasn't but you never no. So now i am sitting here pretty depressed listening to music thinking aobut certain people and wondering what to do. So we will have to see. I will try and keep journal readers posted not that anyone cares. So yea thats about it. 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I woke up today before church got ready then went over to church. I read the lessons pretty good and then we had this thing after where we watched this movie about church. It was pretty boring but I got to sit next to erika so it was DEFF worth it. Then we came home and my sister made pancakes. I am telling you she makes the BEST freaken pancakes. Anyhow after that we went to best buy because I have a 50$ giftcard there but offcoarse with my expensive taste.. :-/ I couldn't find anything but I did find something I am going to save up for. A jukebox to play all my songs from my computer on. 20gb Phillips for only 250$. It looks really sexy to! The Link is the title. Um so yea i am gonna keep in the corner a little talley of how much more money I need... hehehe then I had some strawberries giftcards and we went there. I got TWO here that TWO beatles cd's Anthology 1 and Anthology. For only 15.99 each. THat is a swell deal because they are normally 32$ EACH! I bought them used.. Who really cares. I am so excited. I Want ALL the Beatles cds they are awesome. Well THen I came home and ate KFC and watched extreme house makeover and did homework. While doing my boring homework and helping Mackenzie with his geometry that he didn't understand I found that I have this AWESOME thing since I have sbc yahoo DSL. I have my own online radio station and I have all this cool stuff that I can listen to online and stuff. It is great. So i have been ripping cds since then and listening to music. And right now it is Led Zepplin so that is pretty cool. Talk to you later I gotta finish my lab report real quick.. 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Wow... Joshua James Debner is a looser. Right now he is sitting in his room watching veggie tales. I went to steph's tonight for a little while and erika was there. It was pretty cool we played rummio then when for ice cream then went to go and watch a movie called, "You got Served" it was pretty good for the little part I saw but my parents wanted me home at 9:30 :-( O well. All I am going to say about going to stephs is that is so bad because it is just so tempting. Wow when the cucumber veggie tale person holds paper it floats in the air. That is AMAZING! Today I woke up around 11 and had to do alot of chores today. Then I called Kevin and he came over and chilled for a while my house is really boring. Kevin left before dinner and yea thats about it. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    I Look Quite Disturbed don't I? This is what physics does to you. I am telling you. BEWARE OF SCHOOL! &nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Sitting home on a fri night with nothing o so nothing to do. I am sitting here on my coach watching CSI: Miami. Thinking about someone and no one. I am really bored but hey lets see what i did today. I went to school and while I was there I took a Earth Science quiz and got a bad grade. No I have to do a bunch of extra credit. I got to SHS and yea didn't do much else. After school I went to practice but all we did was put away hurtles and then eat pizza....YUMMY in my TUMMY. After that we went golfing (kevin mario and I) at timberlin.. that is a EXCELLENT golf coarse. RIGHT after that I went to a boy scout eagle ceremony and that was quite boring. All we did was give him his award and people talked forever.. Yea i am gonna go do somthing else so i'll write more sometime later 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Click on the title for those of you who don't know what song that is from. Well lets see today I woke up went back to bed woke up got ready got on the bus slept when to school then did a lab in physics and then did some weird sun thing in earth science. We hopped in the van got to SHS and then started my SOUTHINGTON day. I ate my lunch with peeps and then went to civics.. wrote the lyrics to "let it be" on the board and had a sub in english so we read the whole class then has a sub in spanish so we did busy work. I got changed and went to the bus got to the meet and pole vaulted (this is where it suddenly got cut off) then I ran not good but obviously good enough for confrences. O well I had kinda hoped on being done.. but w/e shit happens. I still won't letter. I was supposed to go to coffee house with steph and lauren but I got there to late and so I didn't want to interupt. I tried to call my parents but they were out so i walked home then did my homework and watched csi then without a trace..  umm yea that is about it I forget what I wrote the first time. I wrote more but then half of it got erased and replaced with that shit down therre        AHHHHHH-------->>>> I DIDN't WRITE THAT SHIT  ok.. so blogger mest.up I just half to rewrite half of my blog again . ok shuttup. i think i should be done by 7pm or latest 7.30 right?? So Mao..? Jamie..? anyone who wants to come down early can contact me.  oh and actually we don't have to go Liat, we can go elsewhere if you all wanna. Just somewhr in town perhaps? i only suggested Liat in the interest of you guys (you may get free drinks) and also for myself (cos i have no fucking money)..  So erm whatever you guys fancy..Coffeebean, Coffee Express, KFC, YaKun Kaya Toast, Khomala's Curry.. =X. whatever u fancy lah.i'll just tag along. see y'all laters!7s Curry.. =X. whatever u fancy lah.i'll just tag along. see y'all laters! 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    My alarm clock and this is what wakes me up. I am going to try and make a pad or Picture of the day album so get on my case if i am not uploading photos&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Jake Phillips making a fool of himself in lunch. Ins't he just a lovely princess? I know yea this is a pretty cool feature I like it!&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey. Wuts up dudes. It is about 12:07 and I almost forgot to blog today alot of nothing happened today but I will tell you since no-one actually reads this there is no one to read this and get bored. I woke up 5:30 must have turned off my alarm a MILLION freaken times. My mom FINALLY got me out of bed around 6:10 ish and I got ready for school and was on the bus by 6:20... (with a lunch josh made that morning might i add) I slept on the bus but listened to this EXCELLENT B-182 album and I forgot how awesome they are. I love there Take off your pants and jacket album. Anyhow I got to school and in Physics we did this wicked cool experiments with like tracks that worked like air hockey tables and air goes throught them then you have cars on them that are tracked on either side with these sonar things which send data to the computer wich makes a graph of the cars moving and then we analyze it and can find when the cars crashed and all this neat stuff. I love that kind of stuff. We are finishing it tomarrow. We are so far ahead of everyone. We are almost done with the extra credit. Some people are still on the first part.... tisk tisk... those slackers. I went to geometetry and was bored out of my mind then got on the bus and finished civics homework. I ate my lunch and had a exciting day at shs... NOT In civics we talked about the presidential candadates and what they look like... like that even matters.. WHO FUCKIN CARES... Yea and so then in English I was sOOOOOOOO close to falling alseep while taryn was doing her project that if she hadn't finsihed when she did I woulda been asleep. Then spanish was just plain gay as usual. Practice was so easy to DEPAOLO AND BACK HOLY SHIT THAT IS NOTHING. Tomarrow is the LAST MEET. I can't wait I will be FREE shortly. Then I came home and spent almost all night trying to get my computer working. I sorta got it working :-? I dono. It works the when I engage the wireless internet it gets the problem again.. so for now I said FUCK IT and it is just wired. I can't wait for my beatles collection to finish d/l that is going to be so off the hizzle. I like elvis presely I have been listening to a bunch of him recently. O yea I went to my room and started cleaning it like 11:45 ish and my parents got all mad and stuff and I was like  :-/ and they are like GET IN BED //// I think I am most productive at night as long as I am not tired... Yanno.. anyhow I g2g ttyl GOOD BYE MR> NO ONE! 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok so today I woke up and was pretty tired. I went to take my shower and almost fell asleep in the shower then I went back to bed and woke up right before I got on the bus through everything together and hopped on the bus. I was able to get lucky charms in a cup mixed with some milk though. I ate it very pleasurably on the bus. Then I got to school and was able to get all my homework done. That went well. Then I got to southington went to practice and got home early. I got home so early that in fact I was able to go to kevins play wiffle ball then go to my house and play baseball even with a load of laundry in between. I then came back and sat down at my computer gave steph a call but found she wasn't home. I called erika and she was, "Watching a Movie"  She said she would call me back. But I know she won't so its ok. Not much else new today. I am trying to get into the blog everyday habit. O yea I cracked open my country cd's I love them :-) 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Welcome to Gmail   Would You even guess. Such a big deal. I got a free account from blogger. People are selling them on ebay making TONs of money. That is insane. I wish I had a paypal or something so I could sell my two invites. O well. Yea I started my homework not like you care but I did. And I can't wait for school believe it or not. I just realized track is almost over and that means school is almost over so I can stand a little bit longer more of school so that I can get out. O yea realating back to this link If you REALLLY want these to invites email me. josh.debner@gmail.com Maybe we can work something out. I will be trying to arrange things on here to make it more homey now that everyone else abandoned me. 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Anyhow, I doubt anyone will blog here or even read here again so w/e I will just blog all I want and try and keep up on my thoughs myself. I dono if i am gonna keep this blog public or w/e we will have to see. Um lets see this weekend I went to a boyscouts campout till sunday. It was really boring. I mean REALLLLLLY boring. IT was all cubscout oriented. I got sun-burned pretty bad maybe it will turn into a tan. I wouldn't mind that. For ONCE summer maybe I won't be a white piece of paper. I worked with my dumbells today. I dono if it is helping but who knowes. Worth a shot. I have been listening to so much music lately. I don't know what I would do if i didn't have a stereo in my room. I use is all the time. Let's see friend wise I guess I am pretty good. I get fed up with things sometimes and just wanna quit. In my profile I had DYJLPWSTAYBF... and of course Erika asks.. she was the one it was about. She is always saying how we are best friends but we I know that we will never ever be more than that and it gets depressing sometimes. I guess I dono I am just lonely maybe. Can it be that I only have one best friend that is a guy? I dono it is kind of sad. But then maybe that is all a person needs. If they don't get mad at this person and enjoy spending time do you need more than one best friend to confide in? Anyhow school has been going a little better know i think . I have been trying a little more and getting a little better grades but i don't think they are going to be quite good enough. I have only a couple weeks to bring them up. I think I have a syndrom. I get home say i am gonna do my homework then put it off til late then it gets late and I give up and fall asleep then I wake up and don't understand why I didn't just stay up and do it. Maybe it has something to do with being tired. I need to clean my room and do my homework yet haha so I will be doing that. Peace OUt to the no one who reads this. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Sexy ain't it. This new blogger is kinda cool. Gotta figure out all these different function now. Go google. I think they did well. I gota upload a picture of me when i get home for the profile. They finally caught that guy who created that worm. Good thing my computer was prolly gonna get it sometime soon. So yea i am in eart science. I have todo a oral presentation tonight and a lab report damn o well. We will see if i have anything else to do tonight. I like this new interface by the way 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm bored, so I'll blog. Anywho, this weekend went by way too fast. It seemed like just yesterday I was sleeping over Lauren's house with Erika, Corinne, and Steph. Oh wait, it was yesterday. Never mind. Either way, this weekend went by too fast. This week, I have two games, one stupid orchestra concert, and one field trip. Agh. I hate weekdays. Now I can't wait for summer vacation. And summer fun runs, fuck yessssss. I'm supposed to be around half way done with  Animal Farm ... I think it's time I start reading it, so... bye. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I logged in to blog but as soon as I did, Mario was complaining about how I blog too much. Whatever. So bye. 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am so exhausted, that I'm actually typing this with my eyes closed. Blergh, anyways... so today's game was cancelled, and I was so pissed off. Even though approximately 1/3 of our team is injured and we have 2 subs, I still wanted to play. So we had practice, and Kait and I were sort of stranded at school. We had no way of getting to Randy's Pizza. A couple of my friends went to watch the freshmen guys lacrosse game. My legs are all cut up because I went in the woods to help look for missing balls because the team was going to have to run 13 apples and I felt bad. After the freshmen lax game, we went to varsity, but as soon as we arrived on the field, the game ended. So after that, we went to the varsity baseball game but as soon as we got there, THAT game ended. At one point, we went inside the school and met these volleyball guys from East Hartford or somewhere. We were playing this game (the guys called it shoe golf... err, okay) and there's a hole in the ceiling in the blue section now, thanks to me. Whoops, my bad. Like, six of us fit in one car and went to Randy's. I didn't get home until 8:30. Around 9:00, my mom and my sister came home from Villanova and I had to help bring all of my sister's stuff inside. So I was carrying bags that were almost as heavy as I was. Well, they weren't really, but they felt like it. I don't feel like blogging anymore. I'll blog again later or tomorrow. Bye. 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i walked downstairs and i saw my mom makin breakfast or something like that.. so i said mom im sick and she said ok stay home from school. i thought it would be great. and it was but only for like the first 4 hrs. now it is 2:42 and i have watched all of season 3 of family guy... well hopefully i can fool my parents again into letting me go out.. who knows. i feel like crap in more ways than one 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       There is this AWESOME show that some friends made  Watch it . ITs under media and it is pretty cool http://www.wtbtv.tk 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am a lazy freaken kid... I haven't blogged in almost a week. Anyhow um let's see. I pole vaulted today and didnt even clear a hight i suck then I ran a 2 mile really slow and so i don't wanna talk about that no more. I have to start and finish animal farm tonight then do a zillion page packet on it. SO I should maybe start that soon. I have ripped so many cd's this week. It is great. Becky you are AWESOME.. Lauren won't be awesome till tomarrow ;-) anyhow yea umm I dono wut else is happeneing. The other day some person talks to me and goes hey i heard you got a b and i go yea.. wut can you do and she goes O thats to bad. I said O well to tell you the truth i got 3 b's and she goes o well you see whats holding me down is chorus cuz i have a 97 but my other lowest grade is a 101. Wow what a bitch. Who cares i was first in my class for a little bit. Atleast i am sorta modest i think (i can hope) Um school sucks in the past 10 days of school have swear lemme count I have hadat least 20 test/quizzes no lie. It is so stupid. I can't wait for school to end. I wonder what i am doing tomarrow proably nothing anyhow yea gonna finish ripping cd's and then maybe i'll start reading animal farm 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Alrighty, quick blog time! I was on the phone with Lauren, looking through these twenty million pages of field hockey camps that Leahy gave out during the meeting. I was getting a really big headache just thinking of field hockey. Just thinking of how mean some people were to others who were on the same team... even though my friends were the ones being mean to people I hate, but still, no one really deserves to be treated meanly. I felt bad, and I would try to talk to the rest of the team. I'm considering quitting field hockey for cross country, but I don't know. There's obviously something about field hockey that I really don't like if this is about my third time considering quitting to join cross country. Plus, a lot of my really good friends are on the cross country team, so I know I'd love the team already. I don't know if I'll be able to run long distances that well though. Sadly, the most I've ever ran at one time was around 3 miles. I wanted to try the 5.1 with Lauren during inbetween season, but we never got to that because it was always snowing or something, grr. Hmm... what else, what else... well, Lauren's picking me up (tomorrow, not now, haha) and we're arriving at school around 7:00AM tomorrow (aghhh, too early) so we can decorate someone's locker for their birthday. I think I'm going to pass out in the middle of the hallway from blowing balloons and lack of sleep. Speaking of sleep, I should really get to sleep now. Or get my stuff ready for tomorrow then go to sleep, because I have a feeling I'm going to wake up around 5 minutes before Lauren comes to pick me up. Oh... and I have a new screenname, it's  ska rock it x3 ... just to let people out there know. I know a ton of people have my screenname and I don't know who they are/what THEIR screennames are... so you know, what the hey, they might as well have this screenname too. Later kiddos. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Half the team thought practice was cancelled today. It was a running practice, too. In the rain. Of course, the only day I don't bring a sweatshirt, Jesus Christ. I'm starting as center for tomorrow's game, woohoo. It's funny because I hated the idea of playing center when the season started, and now I'm all like, "WOOHOO, CENTER!" I can't wait until Thursday! Jamie, Kait, Steph, and I are doing a skit/rap for our health project... it's so awesome, haha. And I learned today that I cannot be ghetto to save my life. I am like, the least ghetto person in this town, I should not be living in this town at all. I think I need to move to MA to be with Clara, haha. Then I can sneak out at night and do grafitti and go watch the Battle of the Bands whenever I feel like it. I made a new screen name for AIM, but I don't know if I should use it... everyone will be like, "Huh? What's ska?" 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I got bored today so I decided to turn a pair of jeans into a jean skirt. The back looks like shit right now, so I need to find a way to fix that. That's Nikki's and my trend... you know it. The  urlLink day I'm supposed to die  is May 26th, 2093. Wow, that's interesting... ::cough cough:: LMAO. Not like I believe it, but it's nice to know they think I'm going to live to be over 100. Time to finish up my skirt, later kiddos. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       wow family guy is the coolest show ever. right now im watching it while blogging. tomorrow i go to school.  and im wearin my bristol centeral track shirt. i hope all goes well and nobody wants to fight me lol 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok so today i woke up around 9:15 and then took a shower and went over to collect and sort cans for the can and bottle drive for boy scouts. Next I went home and sat around for a little while. Then I went for a bike ride to hit tag sales because I was bored and no one was home. So we ended up runing 8 miles..My sister was all tired but I wasn't... I RUN TRACK haha... No but it was sorta fun. I got home and layed around some more washed up and got ready for the pasta dinner. The pasta dinner was pretty fun with erika and steph. Although poor erika wasnt feeling good. She'll feel better shoon though. We ate pasta then did the raffle then did bingo. It was so much fun playing bingo because at first I played with erika and steph at our table but then I started reading the numbers off. And it was so much fun. I was really good at it. Then erika ran out of cards and came up to help me spin. It was so great. We then finished that and cleaned up. That was pretty cool (haha yea sure) I jumped rope really good. (Some girl won a jump rope) Then i begged my dad to go to stephs for a lil bit. I hopped in the DEMORINOES car and drove off. We got their and steph had just won a hole BOX full of makeup. It was burning a hole in her pocket. And so she decided to use me as a specimen. She did EVERYTHING to me... liner...gloss...blush.....mascara... (it was scary and really uncomfortable) Then we decided to have FUN! We went all out and i put fake boobs on and a dress we took a couple pictures and then I took the make up off and we were watching a movie. Then the phone rings and my dad says that I should come home now and he is coming to pick me  up. Then i am sitting watching to movie and steph goes so i gues you wanna show your dad your RED NAILS.. I FREAKED.. i ran into the other room and told mrs demo i needed nail polish remover. Then We ran into her room and started srubbing. We got the bulk off but I have the bottle to take home for the little stuff. Yea that was about it I came home and decided to go online. So yea that was my day. I will NEVER wear make-up again ... and I will have a respect to all girls now for everything they go through... ( it really suxs to be a gay guy ... or a cross dresser) So yea. Not much else I guess.... excpt guys.. never go near girls with makeup when your outnumbered.. ( it was kinda a different experience though) 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Part of my forehead is green. I was wondering if I had some sort of disease, but then I went and pushed on the green area, and it hurt. It's a bruise. It must have been when someone checked me on the forehead during the game. Speaking of lacrosse, I should never talk about it ever again in the blog because Josh pointed out that the ad on the top advertises lacrosse now, since I talk about lacrosse so much. I wonder if I say NIRVANA NIRVANA NIRVANA NIRVANA NIRVANA over and over again, if advertisements of Nirvana would appear. It seems like I've blogged so many times in a row, but in actuality, I didn't. Lauren had blogged before, but she deleted her post because she didn't want someone to read it. I understand. My stomach really hurts now, because I was trying so hard not to laugh. I didn't want my dad to think that I was (even more of) a psycho. I had to call Lauren and share my tragic yet funny news. I love it when people are so clueless, but I guess it's better they're clueless than knowing the actual truth. I think I said too much, so I'll stop talking about it now. Hmm... what else... well, I can't wait until the summer, especially around August. A whole bunch of my friends are going to drive everyone down to the beach and celebrate Lauren's and Laura's birthday. It's going to be so freaking awesome. Then of course, Christine, Liz, Annie, and a whole bunch of us are volunteering at this camp as camp counselors. 8:30AM to 5:00PM every day... fun stuff yet tiring. I've decided not to go to any sport camps this year. MAYBE field hockey, but that's it. Then I want to go on fun runs with my runner friends, even though I'm not on the cross country team. Summer seems so far away... I know I'm longing for summer now, but when it comes around, I'm going to (sort of) miss school, because so many people are going to be away on vacation and I'm going to miss them so, so much. This was a pretty short blog (for me). 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i sent my first text message today and it was fun. it was about some random stuff that nobody carees about but that isn't the point. i took the sat's and then went to a track meet where i took 5th place out of like a billion people. and i wore my awesome hat that made me look like i was retarded. it was soooooo fun bye bye.. 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This Blog is gonna be really long because it should hopefully cover my entire vacation. But as it seems I will prolly miss some things so I will add additions when I think of them. Ok so it all started out way back ago on LAST monday. I woke up early sorta my parents were packing and so I finished up to. Then My dad dropped me off at the gentiles to babysitt. That was interesting. First timee for the summer and 6 hours... FUN! I made them pancakes. Then we played some lego creator game and then guess what  yes you know it I made them mac and cheese for lunch. We went swimming all day and I "graded" there dives.. it started out as 1-10 then ended up with the highest grade of.. 38.6 :-/ ... INTERESTING... So then i got to go home and we started our journey westward.... tired.. to be continued 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       two blogs in one day. I gues I am making up for the week that I am gonna be on vacation leaving tomarrow. I gave my dad some shirt my mom hooked me up with for dad's day. I had to play my violin in church which wasn't fun but at least i played my electric violin that was kinda cool. We are getting ready and packing and stuff so we had to set up the tents to make sure they worked yanno. Then we had to get our stuff around. I went to a meeting with the family I am babysitting for from 8-6 this summer. I am starting tomarrow before we leave and WOW that is all I can say. I would hate to be them. There mom is over proetective nurse.. what can get worse. They get 1/2 hour of tv a day...1/2 hour of computer a day and that is IT. They are 8 and 10 years old. They are only allowed to watch discover and disney. NO NICKELODEAN.. (they say words like stupid and looser and those are bad words to say). They can't eat breakfast until they have eaten 1 serving of fruit. If they have "junk" cereal which is all cereal they can't have a "treat" that day such as ice cream or brownies. If you ask me.. I thought cereal was good for you? O well. They have a pool so I can swim and hang out their. Its so funny She was like now Austin can you drink soda.. YeSSSSSS. How much? ONE A DAY. I don't know what austin does but he has a mom and a dad and he is a responsible kid if he wants to drink 3 sodas a day he will have to be responsible for himself.. WOW i felt so bad. I could easily drink 3 sodas in like 1 sitting. Anyhow I will try to make it fun at least they have so many toys and stuff. I gott wake up early and stay up late tonight to finish packing. FUN STUFF So yea if I don't blog anymore before my vacation PEACE! 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ok, So sat I woke up and I had to go help clean around the house and and we had this work day at the church so i had to help with that. After that I got my haircut and then I came home and I was really tired I dono why and just slept from like 3-5 so then I woke Up and walked over to kevins.. one bike is poped tire and another bike is at another friends house. So then I rode his bike while dan rode on his fake chopper and steve on his pocket bike and kevin on this scooter. WoW i really need to get somthing motorized b/c it is really hard keeping up on a bike. My parents doin't agree though :-( that leaves me stuck rideing my bike for the summer. O well. It was pretty fun although kevin is the only one who lets me ride anything. When we got to steve's house his brother was getting ready for a motocross race today. WOW that sounds like so much fun. I wish I could do that. Racing motorcycles? What could be more fun? So yea then I had to come home and it was boring so I ate food and then I think I am gonna start a website but I dono. Today is basically my last day here. Tomarrow evening we are leaving for vacation and not returning till I think like the 1st or sumthing. So I prolly won't be blogging for a while. I will try and check my email but we have to see. Tomarrow I have to babysit from 8-6 that is why we aren't leaving until evening otherwise we would leave earlier. Its all good I need the money I am like broke. My mom is making me play my violin for church today :-( so I have to go practice  JOsh 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink "Brian's Blog":  RAP-   "Retards-Attempting-Poetry"     He speaks the truth ladies and gents... read it and believe it! 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       BLOGGER IS BEING DUMB>>> IT TOOK ME AN HOUR JUST TO GET IT WORKING AGAIN>>>>BUT THANKS TO JOSH IT IS WORKING SO THAT IS GOOD 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today was the official first day of summer being as there is no school. at least for me some of my friends had one more exam but o well. Today I woke up to my parents fighting... ugh I hate that but its alright. since its friday its my dad had the day off. on his day off he always goes for a hike in the woods with the dog. But my mom didn't want him to today because she wanted him to clean out the basement so my dad was really mad. He woke me up like 9 o'clock ish saying If I can't do what i want to do then you can't do what you wanna do. GET UP! so i woke up and helped around the house. PT called but I couldn't go running because of the housework I had to do. Then we went golfing with kevin,jordan,eric and I. I did horrible. As usual. Then when we got done we took a few more trips to the garbage and then had to take the truck back. Now let me explain the truck really quick. Our car broke so we took it in and got a rental. But the only car they had was a huge Chevy Silvarado. My dad loves trucks.. So he was excited and we took so much garbage stuff from the basement while we had it but they fixed our car today so we had to bring the truck back. THen after that I was sitting around the house and I rode my bike over to stephs where we chilled and jumped on the trampoline and then after that we were gonna watch first 50 dates but I had to go to best buy with my parents. We went to find a portable dvd player since we had giftcards there and we are going on a big trip soon. SO we got one and now i am here sitting here writing about nothing everything and something. So yea my first day of summer wasn't bad. My mom is yelling at me to clean my room now so I will write later  
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Summer is here bizzliches! Yahoo... 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink summerrun.xls     This is the summer run in excel.. you guys SHOULD have excel 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok today was SWEEET....even though we had finals. I woke up like 7ish all worried about my english final....so I get up reread the story and the prompt and think about it then say wow damn that is easy... I DO know who the tragic hero in Antigone Is...So then I get to school and have a English Study group thing and I understand it a lil more. Then we hang with mario chandler jackie and taylor and it was pretty fun. By the time english rolls around I know it by heart. Then I get home and my mom is gonna bring me to a haircut and kevin and his gang arive at my hosue. So i grab my bike and we go down to family pizza. We order food then decide we wanna go to the fireworks store...WE head down in the direction of downtown and almost got runover a dozen times. We stoped in marcs dad's office and said hi. Then we went to adcanced auto parts and looked around. After that Marc Me Ryan Madore Steve Didomenico and Kevin went down to the fireworks store but the one near the breadmarket place was closed. So then we went to the one where eblens used to be and tried to buy stuff but he didn't believe we were 16 and so we got sold nothing :-(. THen we went to price chopper and looked around got free food samples and stuff. After that we hit petorama then got kicked outta Hobby Town USA. AND TAYLOR FUCKING CROFTON SAVED MY ASS BY GIVING ME A BLUE NOTECARD RIGHT IN THE NICK OF TIME AND YES THIS IS RANDOMLY IN THE MIDDLE OF MY BLOG... So anyway then we are sitting in the parking lot starting at some hott chicks ass and i spin my tire and PFFFFFFFFFFF it POPS... what a dissapointment. So the other guys leave and I am starting to walk up the huge hill in the direction of my house then I am like yanno I am gonna call richie maybe he is doing nothing and can give me a ride home. So he is like SURE and comes brings me home...THANK GOD FOR DABS!.  So I got home fixed my other bike then rode over to kevins again where we rode to steves and I rode kevins scooter... it is awesome he actually lets me ride it unlike steve. So then we finally made it back to kevins house and we chilled and shot the airsoft gun and then we drank sodas played wiffleball then went home. When I got home I chilled in my room then pt called and we ran 4 miles I went home and wrote this blog. Today was an excellent exciting day. I am gonna LOVE this summer  
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Leave a Comment with the answers.. PLease do it or I will think no one loves me :-( so yea answer them truthfully to.. so peace out  COMMENT BY CLICK ON THE LITTLE COMMENT BUTTON ON THE BOTTOM OF THIS POST AND THEN CLICK POST A COMMENT!!!!  1)Who are you? 2)Would you consider us friends?  3)When and how did we meet? 4)How well do you know me? 5)How have I affected you? 6)What's the fondest memory you have of me? 7)How long do you think we will be friends? 8)Do you love me? 9)Would you kiss me? 10)Would you hug me? 11)Would you do anything else to me? 12)What is my best physical feature? 13)What is my best aspect?  14)Give me a nickname and explain why you picked it. 15)Describe me in one word.  16)What was your first impression of me?  17)Do you still think that way about me now?  18)What do you think my weakness is?  19)What do you think makes me happy?  20)What do you think makes me sad?  21)What reminds you of me?  22)Who reminds you most of me? 23)If you could give me anything what would it be?  24)When's the last time you saw me? 25)Have you ever lied to me?   
    
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        THis Book i got an A+ for This is like my first and last a+ for the year        The Pattern Josh Friendly, Trustworthy, Loyal, Wishes to sleep forever, Dreams of making people happy, Wants to put a smile on everyones face, Who wonders why everyone is sad, Who fears of not being liked, Who is afraid of no one, Who likes ice cream, Who believes in God, Who loves running Who loves pancakes Who loves math and science Who loves hanging out with friends Who plans on going to collage Who plans on being successful Who plans on getting married Who cannot wait to grown up.     Justice Dept. Memo Says Torture 'May Be Justified'  By Dana Priest Washington Post Staff Writer Sunday, June 13, 2004; 6:30 PM  Today washingtonpost.com is posting a copy of the Aug. 1, 2002, memorandum "Re: Standards of Conduct for Interrogation under 18 U.S.C. 2340-2340A," from the Justice Department's Office of Legal Counsel for Alberto R. Gonzales, counsel to President Bush.  The memo was the focus of a recent article in The Washington Post. The memo was written at the request of the CIA. The CIA wanted authority to conduct more aggressive interrogations than were permitted prior to the terrorist attacks of Sept. 11, 2001. The interrogations were of suspected al Qaeda members whom the CIA had apprehended outside the United States. The CIA asked the White House for legal guidance. The White House asked Justice Department's Office of Legal Counsel for its legal opinion on the standards of conduct under the Convention Against Torture and Other Cruel, Inhumane and Degrading Treatment or Punishment. The Office of Legal Counsel is the federal government's ultimate legal adviser. The most significant and sensitive topics that the federal government considers are often given to the OLC for review. In this case, the memorandum was signed by Jay S. Bybee, the head of the office at the time. Bybee's signature gives the document additional authority, making it akin to a binding legal opinion on government policy on interrogations. Bybee has since become a judge on the 9th U.S. Circuit Court of Appeals.  Another memorandum, dated March 6, 2003, from a Defense Department working group convened by Defense Secretary Donald H. Rumsfeld to come up with new interrogation guidelines for detainees at Guantanamo Bay, Cuba, incorporated much, but not all, of the legal thinking from the OLC memo. The Wall Street Journal first published the March memo. At a recent Senate Judiciary Committee hearing, senators asked Attorney General John D. Ashcroft to release both memos. Ashcroft said he would not discuss the contents of the Justice and Pentagon memos or turn them over to the committees. A transcript of that hearing is also available. President Bush spoke on the issue of torture Thursday, saying he expected U.S. authorities to abide by the law. He declined to say whether he believes U.S. law prohibits torture. Here is a link to the White House transcript of the president's press conference, which included questions and answers on torture. The Post deleted several lines from the memo that are not germane to the legal arguments being made in it and that are the subject of further reporting by The Post.  Ok, so between all that legal garbage and the politics I think what this article is saying. Is that the CIA wants to interrogate the terrorists more inhumanly to get them to spill the beans. What is this world coming too? We are the country that is supposed to be fair and honest. We are supposed to treat everyone equally and even the accused has rights. Are we going to give up our rights in exchange for safety? How would you like to be an accused terrorist and get treated more harshly than all the rest? I think that this is not a good thing. We have rules for a reason. If for some reason those rules arent good enough then maybe the CIA needs to change or convince congress but there shouldnt be any bending of the rules. Everyone is equal and thats the way it should be.    Top 10 cafeteria table sayings -YOU DID WHAT? -YOU SAID WHAT? -SO HAVE YOU HEARD ABOUT (BLAH BLAH) YET? -HOW WAS THE PARTY? -SO HAVE YOU KISSED HER YET? -O WATCH OUT FLYING FOOD BEHIND YOU -YOUR ACTUALLY EATING THAT -HEY BUDDY ANYONE GOT 50 CENTS I CAN BORROW -CAN I SEE YOUR HOMEWORK I SWEAR I WONT COPY WORD FOR WORD -DID WE HAVE ANY (BLAH BLAH) HOMEWORK?    Harmony is his who can hear beyond sound. Laotse First of all I think someone mest up in the translation here. I mean come one his who hear? What kind of English is that? Skipping the weirdly placed pronoun yes I do know it is a pronoun and the verbs that make no sense hear beyond sound. I think that it means is when you are with someone you love you have perfect harmony. You can eat, talk, have fun together and you can talk the talk and walk the walk farther together than you ever could alone. You were meant for each other and that harmony will take you somewhere very special. Someday I hope to find this harmony Laotse speaks of.   My Bug list -People who think they are not as good as me -People who give lots of homework  -When people act different around different people -When someone is annoying   My first success has to have been when I was about 4 years old and I had my first violin recital. This is definitely not m biggest success but you have to start somewhere. I started playing the violin at age 3 and so I had been working hard all year practicing and trying to get ready for this recital. I got up there and played my twinkle and row your  boat in our group and I felt so proud then and I remember that day even now.  The word dawn. When I hear the word dawn I think of. -soap detergent -sunset -sunrise -baby deer (fawn) -A new dawn or like a new beginning   A silent mouth is sweet to hear- Irish Proverb This is NOT true. I can tell you that because I have heard non-silent mouths and they can be sweet to. I believe there is a sweet silence but I also believe in sweet words. Such as Shakespeare used such sweet words if he would have kept silent then the entire world would never have heard him. There are times to speak out and times to speak silently. I think that the speaking out times can be just as sweet as the silent ones if not sweeter. Would you like your teacher to tell you no homework or say nothing at all. Both mean the same thing but when she says the words no homework you are overjoyed and they sound sweet to your ear. If the teacher says nothing then this implies that there is no homework but you dont think about that until you get home and think did I miss something. A silent mouth is sweet to hear but sweet words are just as sweet.        The things I love! -walks on the beach -no homework nights -hanging out with friends -eating mucho food -sleeping in late -going to bed late -talking to people (internet + phone) -summer -spring, winter, and Christmas break -getting good grades -when things I make actually work    One way in which our school can be improved is how the day is broken up. I am one for block scheduling. I like it. I think it is the best way to teach. You can learn so much more when you have more time in one chunk then it is split up into tiny time periods. I go to two schools and my school in the morning has block scheduling. It works so well. We are able to get so much done and learn so much more. I feel that we get through the books faster and people understand things more since the teacher has more time to explain it. In all my classes at SHS teachers are almost always working right up to the bell.  I think the only way to fix this is block scheduling. Many other schools have adapted it why shouldnt we.                         My Nasty Letter  I have recently purchased a motorized scooter from your store on June 6th and it has already broken down on June 12th. I am so very disappointed with the quality of this piece of machinery. I had trust in your company and had chosen you because of your low prices and loyalty to customers. I spoke with your manager June 13th and he said that there was nothing you could do about it. I have heard many good things from my friends about your store, but by the things I have experienced I cannot say that you are even the same company. My friends spoke of excellent quality, superior service, and good prices. The only thing I have discovered for my self is low-prices and low quality. I have been shopping at your store for a while now. But if no action is taken I will have to shop elsewhere. I need this scooter either fixed or replaced immediately. Unless this is done I will be forced to shop elsewhere and tell my story to all I know. It is my hope that this confusion can be worked out and I can get a working scooter soon. Joshua Debner 517 Woodruff St Southington, CT 860-628-7131	Joshua Debner 	517 Woodruff St 	Southington, CT 	(860)-628-7131 	    
    
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok .... sorry i didn't blog yesterday but that is only because I was SOOOO FREAKEN TIRED. Sat after I blogged I went to kevins and Hanged out there all day. We rode bikes and then we went to pep boys and he returned the scooter. Then on the way home we orderded pizza from renaldos and then picked it up. While we were in meridan we saw this AWESOME chopper with pipes that went straight up then back it was sweet. The guy at pep boys said they would get a new shipment of scooters in wed cuz theres were all broken. So after we ate we chilled then I went home and cleaned convinced my mom to let kevin sleep over. Then kevin went to another pep boys and got a new scooter. This one should work good. When kevin got here we chilled in my room listening to music and talking to people. EATING JUNK FOOD. It was fun. We ended up going to sleep like are i dono 1:30 ish. Then we woke up at 7 for church. I got ready and then we ate breakfast. YUM YUM YUM (bagels donuts and cereal). Then I took shower and we made some cds. Kevin went home and I went to church [10:15AM] After church erika came over for a sec and i burned her some dashboard cds and we waited for amanda to come pick us up. We were chilling in my room. [which i later got in trouble for doing b/c she is a girl which is so fucking dumb] Then amanda came and we went to a play at the bushnell. The play was called. Starlight Express. It was about a boy playing with trains. Except all the actors were trains on roller skates. They had ramps going up the walls and stuff. It was awesome. I actually liked it!!!!. For the train races they had a screen that dropped down and they played a movie in 3d!! with 3d glasses. It was neat. Amanda said in London they actually have a track that goes around the audience so they have the races on that. That would be pretty neat huh? So after going to see the play I went over amandas and we chilled. Ate pizza... For the third day in a row. It was still yummy haha. Then we went outside and played basketball. I played barefoot. I stubbed my toe and took a  chunk  of skin off my tow and it started bleeding. It was pretty cool looking. We decided we should go home and start our homework. I went home sat on my bed and fell asleep for 2 hours. When I woke up I was still reallllly tired. I started writing all this randome stuff for english maybe i'll post it. I was so tired i started talking like i was drunk. I was talking to taylor and was making up words like mononic... and stuff and then I was gonna put in about how Fuck can be used in all the different types of words.. The Fucking Fucker Fuck the fuck out of that fucker. So yea i was pretty tired. I went to sleep then woke up and finished it this morning. Mine is pretty dumb. But its ok. I got everything done and in time to. Today classes seemed long but it ended quick. Since i only had to go to half a day of school. I can't wait until tomarrow. Then 3 finals and i am DONE!!!!! WAHOOO... So anyway that was my weekend. O today afterschool I walked to kevins and checked out his computer for somthing. Then my dad drove me home and I ran 4.005 miles wich rich (3.2 block then to rich's house) it was so humid. When we got to his house we jumped in his pool that felt so good. Then he drove me home we ate and thats about it... pretty boring ain't it...LIKE ME! 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    This is a collage of me that I made for this book I had to make for english :-(&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       OK so since my post yesterday was very brief I'll explain my past to days so far. Yesterday I wnet to school then after school I got a ride home from Kevin's mom. I sat home and talked to ppl for a little bit. Then kevin came by and he rode his new gas scooter to steves house where we hung out trying to fix it. (broke on the way there.) We called the marnufacture and they said that we could return it as long as it wasn't abused. After that I came home and ate supper. Next Kevin and I were supposed to go to chandlers but Kevins mom said he couldn't come so I went by myself. There were more ppl than I thought there would be. I called this one girl and she came cuz she lived down the street. When we first got their we show bb guns for a little bit. Then we went for a walk and got to see some cows. COWS ARE AWESOME. Then we met up with the girl who came. When we got back we started watching euro trip.. but it was a little weird watchin it with a girl haha. So we went and ordered pizza. But when we asked who had money only a couple of us so I ended up 15$ for like 1/4 of a pizza. O well. The kids who paid nothing ate the most. W/E that is fair. So when the pizza came. We didn't bring it down at first. We hung out in chandlers care. Then chandler walked the girl home. The other guys started chasing us for the keys since we locked the pizza in the trunk. So they took them. We took the girl home and chandler met her dad. He is so sweet... Anyhow by the time we got back there was no pizza those assholes. So we finished euro trip and started Texas Chain Saw Massacre but I am not a huge horror movie fan so i sat and talked on aim while i watched. Then we left. And this morning I woke up at 4:30 went to relay for life and then walked around the track will 6:30. It wasn't fun but i guess it was for a good cause 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       WRITERS BLOCK 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Been inspired to write a long journal entry thanks to Lauren from calumet. Ok so lets see. Today I woke up very very slowly. Took my mom 3 tries to get me in the shower. Then I finally got in and stuff. I got ready for school and went to school. When I got to school I asked my physics teacher about some leds i had found and what voltage they run at. He said to follow him. So we went in the robotics room and used a  variable power supply to find the voltage. Then he just gave me the power supply. How nice! :-D Ok so i'll post a picture when i get them in my computer. So lately i dono. Life has been ok. School is slowing down. Half my finals are over. I can feel summmer closer than ever before. Tomarrow at the academy all we are doing is watching movies for 3 hours. Then when i get back I sell flowers for robotics. I wish I could buy a flower for someone. But no one wants a flower from me. I talk ed to Lauren today from calumet pretty cool kid. Now i have talked to three people total from ma. They have a pretty cool town. Now much else really happened. Today I babysat annie and austin and made 20$ then went to a end of the year robotics party. WOW I is a looser. So yea can't wait tomarrow is fri. Going to school then i think partying at chandlers house.. Although i gotta wake up at 5:30 sat morning for freaken rellay for life. UGH WHY SO DAMN EARLY. Anyhow yea it will still be fun. I have to do a romeo and juliet play tomarrow in school. Some people are making it so difficult. I dono how it will turn out but I hope for the best. I could use a good grade. As much as I hate plays and sappy love stuff and shakespear he is a pretty creative guy. Kind of a hopeless romantic. Except much better than i'll ever be. I wish I had lines like his. Some are actually pretty good. but that is pretty geeky quoting shakespear on a date. So I guess not much else is happening. I guess this is a sorta long entry. I doubt anyone reads the whole thing anyway BYE 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Record-Journal   Quite an article...  "Rufus pimps three hoes. If the price is $85 per trick, how many tricks per day must each hoe turn to support Rufus's $800 per day crack habit?"  "Billy steals Joe's skateboard. As Billy skates away at 15 mph, Joe loads his 357 Magnum. If it takes Joe 20 seconds to load his piece, how far away will Billy be when he gets whacked"  I wish my spanish teacher did something like this ~!Wow Our School is Wack!~ 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
         urlLink   
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    This is a picture with the lights on....pretty cool I think ain't it?! You know you wish you had one.. I'll sell them.... 1 with plug ready to go for 20$... any offers&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Exit sign in my room on my computer desk plugged in my wall... It has a dead battery so the church couldn't use it so I said I would take it.&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It was cold outside  At the campfire last night Strangers all around Not a familiar face in sight.  We cam from home Discovered we are not alone God's here. We all found God here.  Found my family this morning My group seemed pretty good. We started having fun Running through the woods.  (Chorus) Bridge- Girls- Melody  Boys- Hey Hey Hey  As it turns out, God's not just at calumet You can see God in your friends, Or an evening sunset.  (chorus 2x)  Provided by a kool kid named Emily! Thanks muchos 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey,  Where do I begin... Wow what an unusual weekend. Fri, afterschool we had a xc meeting and talked about stuff. Like running in the summer. Fun stuff! Then right after that we went to my church and packed for CALUMET! It was a long but fun ride up. We stoped different places to eat and bought food. Then we bough pixie sticks and ate them :-D It was so great. When we got there we found our cabins and went to luther hall for some gathering thing with puppets... quite boring. We went to sleep and it was realllllllly cold. I was very uncomfortable. We woke up early the next morning. 5:30 took a shower and hung out just enjoying the lake beach and listening to the beatles. We had breakfast at 7:45. It was pancakes yummy. After that we went to luther hall and got our "familes" or a group of people that we would hang out with the whole trip. We broke off into our families, I was the only one from my church in my family and I thought this was going to be dumb. We got in our family and there were a couple cool kids i noticed right away. Everyone was just so damn serious though anyhow we started playing a wide game throughout the camp and everyone started warming up. We were getting alone and ended up winning. Then was lunch and freeeeeee time. I went canoeing with britney and steph and then played softball. It was alright. We ate dinner then went to this stupid vantriliquest concert. It was alright though because I just played war in the back with britney. Then we had a Piper concert and went into family time again. We started having fun and wrote a song. I'll put the lyrics up later because I lost them :-/. These ppl from gloucester ma were really cool and they made the family a little more talkative which was good.  After that we went and had a serious talk which was dumb but o well. We all decided we would have more fun next time and O WEE DID! Then there was the dance and the coffee house. THe dance music was weird and the ppl i was with could dance and i can't but it was still fun. Coffee house rocked when i was there. I went to campfire then to my cabin and fell RIGHT asleep. waking up sun was so hard. i went right to breakfast when i got up. Then left breakfast early to take a shower. it woke me up alot better. We when to family time and played frisbee and practied our song. We went to church and sang our song. Good times. Then we packed up and got ready to go home. Some people from my family got my s/n so we can talk somemore ;-) Then we headed home. The trip home was awesome. I bough a 12 pack of soda and found that i can down a soda in 21.29 seconds. Then we opened up someones backpack and found a bobble head jesus. That gave us an idea. We got paper and wrote honk for jesus then put it in the back window with gum. Then we wrote more signs and held them up on the side of the car. we got 3 trucks and 3 cars. One guy held up a bible and we just showed our bobble head and he lauged. We had a fun trip all around but i have finals mon. tues. wed. and so that won't be to fun. More to come later I am tired of writing. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey Hey Hey... AWESOME DAY DUDE! Ok so I woke up this yesterday morning realllly tired but I got all my homework done an was having fun in all my classes. After school I stayed after and helped this Rob Perez kid with a project and then I saw Erika, Lauren, and Becky..so i talked for a little while and then  I went to the track picnic and it was awesome we played frisbee which I love then we got food. What could be better? I love ultimate frisbee SO FREAKEN much. I got home and we were getting ready for our picnic for the church. Erika called and told me that she just got her belly button pierced. It is so awesome. You can see it if you want http://gmail.google.com/gmail?view=att&disp=inlined&attid=0.1&th=fce7d9399a932c2 After that Erika stoped over and we chilled it was pretty fun. Then I went and did my homework. My sister needed help with her homework at 12:30 :-( she is a slaker like me. So I helped her out until 1:30 then went to bed. I am so tired now in Earth Science 
    
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Ok soo a bunch of stuff has happened I guess... wed.. I babysat then rode around with kevin a little bit and thats it. THen THurse we went to the mall and that was a experience in it's self. We   were gonna meet kevins' girlfriend but it was all mest up. All in all we saw her about 15 min. THey never said one word to each other. Yesterday I babysat alll day then came home and went to kevins   house and slept over there. We'll have to see but Kevin's mom is thinking about moving... to burlington which is 30 min away. Kevin doesn't really wanna move but we'll deff just have to see that is all I can say. It is a nice house though.. you can see it ..   urlLink  HERE   .. I have to go run now so bye. I just got done clening the church today for the wedding.. hehe makes me 40$!   
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        So dudes...mon... hmm i slept in really late. Then I ran around town with brit. We like ran to the library and blockbuster then we got to my house. She walked to family pizza and her mom picked her up. Then after that I came home and ran with the ppl for xc. After that I hooked up with kevin and we rode to brits house. It took kevin like 1000000+ house of talking while i   wandered off to leave them alone to ask her out then they didn't even hug or kiss.. So anyhow we came back and I stayed home and that was my entire monday I think or at least what i can remember. This morning I woke up and hooked up with kevin. We rode bikes for a little while then my mom took us to walmart to buy my bike tire finally. We also went to Wendy's! I put the tire on my BMX bike and we hit a couple jumps behind his dad's house. Then we rode to chandlers house and were shooting bb guns int he fields behind his house. We&nbsp; shot turkeys but   they were to quick for us. THen we found this abandoned truck and started throwing rocks at it and shooting it.. All of a sudden this lady starts yelling you FUCKING KIDS GET OUT OF HEAR. I have to say i don't know if i have ever run that fast before. It was so bamfer. So after that we chilled and layed low in chandlers house then we rode home... but it started raining so we rode MAD fast.&nbsp; When i got to my house ppl were waiting to go on a run so i ran 7 miles and then ate dinner. I got ready for boy scouts and am headed there next. That is about all I have done.. Kevin might be getting a new computer he is excited..   
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Brit and her friend wrote this I guess why not give them a little publisity on my highly famous blog right? Hah yea write... its pretty good!   &nbsp;   I had on new clothes&nbsp; New sneaks on my feet.I was there for class on time Went to the back and took my seat.Yeah Im moving up Im already grown Soon Ill b graduating nd out on my own. I talked to some of my friends We were all having fun.&nbsp; Said some things I shouldnt have said&nbsp; Did stuff I shouldnt have done. I knew I was different. I felt God touch my heart I knew I should set a standard But then Id be set apart Walking to the bus I was not looking for strength.I heard the car tires screeching But now its 2 late.Im standing in this room nd I can see the heavenly gate Oh no I never prayed.I thought I had time to get it straight An angel walked to me,He had a nabook in his hand.I knew it was the Book of Life When would this dream end?I told him my name nd he began to look.Then he looked at me sadly and saidYour name is not in this book.Angel this is a dream, No I can't be dead!He closed the book and turned away, Ahead No.no this can't be real, Angel you can't turn me away.Let me talk to God Maybe he'll let me stay.He led me to the gate, Jesus came to me.He did not let me in but said Beloved what is your need? Jesus I cried please, Don't cast me away from you.Tears ran down his face as he said You knew what u needed 2 do. Lord&nbsp; please Im young&nbsp; I never thought I would die I thought Id have plenty of time Death caught me by surprise.Lord&nbsp; I went to church Plz Jesus&nbsp; I believe.He said you would not accept me My love you would not receive.Lord, there were to many hypocrites They werent being tru.He took a step back and askd What does that have to do with u?Lord my family claimed to be saved They werent real.u know.He said I died for u Now I have to go.I fell to my knees crying to Him Lord I planned to be real tomorrow.I couldnt make Him understand I had neverfelt such sorrow.Then it hit me hard I said Lord, where will I go?He looked into my eyes and said my child you already know.Plz Jesus I begged the place is so hot.It seemed to trouble nd grieve him He whispered DEPART FROM ME I KNOW YOU NOT.Lord your supposed to be love me, How can u send me to damnation? He replied With your mouth u said you loved me But each day u rejected my salvation.With that in an instant Day turned into night.I never knew such torture could be now its too late I know the Bible is right.If I can tell u anything, Hell has no age.It is a place of torture separated from God and full of rage.u know I thought it was a funny joke but this one thing is true.If you never accept Jesus Christ HELL IS WAITING FOR U!    &nbsp;  its pink b/c brit would appriciate the pink   
    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        OMG GUESS WHAT DUDES... josh just bought tims...   They are 6 inch high waterproof boots forest green color ;0)  don't worry I am not turning ghetto. They are 20$ and considering they are 139.99 I figured I   could get them and do whatever I want to do. So yea I went to the mall today and it was SOOO intense...&nbsp; I am gonna paste a convo I had with someone just so I don't have to retype   everything I did today at the mall. because it was BAMF intense fun! Brit CHandler ERika and I were there. Erika got her hair cut by brits mom and it looks fabulous now. and heres some more stuff we did...   actually it was more work putting the spaces fromt he convo in so i am just gonna retype it. I got their and we chilled and bought cookies .. it was buy 3 get one free WHAT A DEAL ... mrs. fields YUM.. so then we went and they went in vitorias secrets... while i help the food. Then we went   back and erika got her hair cut. Before i had come they hat bought jessica simpson shirts and cool stuff. Then athletes foot was having this intesne every pair of shoes in the store for 20$ sale. So i found a pair of 139.99 $ tims and bought them for 20$ :-P hahaha I don't care they   were 20$ that is nothing for tims.. Maybe I'll sell them or just keep them to play with. So that was intense we had to wait in line for&nbsp;like 30 min and then we were the last ppl to get in. We made friends with the sequrity guard and he gave us water. We also went into this furniture   store to buy furniture haha wink wink we just wanted to chill on the couches and stuff but this pakinstani guy came out and was like no you leave. Get out NOW. I try make livin. I have   customers leave now. I make living.. were like fine we wanted to buy a couch but tooo bad and so then we left.. we also went into the computer gamer place to pick up phone numbers haha yea right ...&nbsp;and everyone was staring and looking weird at us plus there were really strange stains on the floor so we left. We also went to weathervane today again but cahndler and i had fun with   this one. The sign outside the store had one side that said 7 days left and another one that said 6 days left.. I gues they are getting bought out or sumthing. So we went in with the girls and complained. they said we could fix it. we peeled off the 7 and underneath was a 9 OHHHHHH so   we flipped it around the nice guys we were to fix it. We went back and were like can we get something for it. She was like i would give you a giftcard but we are all out. SO she gave us   random piece of metal from some random shelf. Then a sensor :-D hehehehehehe this sensor makes stores alarms go off heheheh so that was fun. Brit got searched in footlocker when she   went in AND came out ha. We went and we also hugged this big plush dippin dots salesman and   chandler and i group hugged him then we ate dippin dots and spilled them all over one of those sticker maker machines. THen we called the number on the machine complaining we didn;t like   our picture... but they hung up on us :-(... so yea it was an intense mall visit. I also bought a 25$ football for 10$ talk a bout a bargain shopper. So can't wait for kevin to get back from maine. It   will be fun yanno. We can chill in our tims.. he has some he bought for like 80 .. mine were 20&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; :0D    &nbsp;  SO yea that was the mall    &nbsp;  I am gonna make this RAINBOW   
    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Ok I woke up this morning and then I ran 12 miles with rich. It was a weird 12 miles because we ran to laurens house then around the res to get the miles we needed. I got my cds back from lauren and I am&nbsp; feeling really good. I get home and my mom yells at me to go help over at the church for some babysitting thing. I get there and am like I am gonna make this more fun. So I call up brit and chandler ..(erika was bbsitting) so they come and my mom is being a BIG bitch today. So anyhow the kids were watching a movie and there was like 5 kids in the room watching it with them. So i went into the trailer and was gonna play n64 til the movie was over. Well my mom  FLIPPED  and told them to call there parents and go home. But they stayed and I got my phone taken away. It was gay. My mom is dumb. Then I went to church with brit and erika and help Val.. he is getting big.. Then after that I went home and waited for my mom to cool down up in my room. Then I went and did this fake apology stuff and she said i still couldn't go mini golfing. BUt my dad said yes haha so I went with brit erika and chandler and it was fun. Chandler one my one stroke. But we kept like cheering for this one kid in front of us. And then at the end he asked if brit was with anyone and she said yea cuz she didn't like him. and he put a piece of paper back in his pocket and walked off. I felt soooo bad.. but i am over it. heh .. no one wants to give me there number.. phhfff o welll. So then i came home and that was my day. What a freakin bore..    &nbsp;   &nbsp;  Start using the new word... its bamfer.. or bamf    &nbsp;  bitch ass mother fucker...   
    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Today was pretty cool. We woke up early and kevin rode his bike home. I went back to bed for a little bit. THen I woke up again and went hiking with my dad in ... don't laugh this old abaonded town called.."gaytown" cuz the "Mr. and Mrs. Gay" family lived there. We took the dogg it was it pretty fun. Then After We went to krispy kreme :-P. THat was EXCITING! So I came home and helped my parents set-up for this VBS thing tonight. Just chilled the whole day. Then when the program came erika and brittney showed up and we had so much fun together. All I can say is BAMF! (bitch ass mother fucker) so&nbsp;yea then after the thing.... we went to the mall and went&nbsp;to abercrombie & fitch and weathervane (&nbsp;being bought out... good sales) and since i was with them it was a blast~&nbsp;GOOD COMPANY MAKES A GOOD TRIP~&nbsp; O I forgot to mention the kids this week were soooo fucking cool. It was more fun than i thought. the prep work sucked but i had to littlest.. They were 5 and so they were realllly fun.      Funny Moments in VBS:      A&nbsp;kid was jelious that another kid was hugging me so he bit the kids arm.  The same kid did a PERFECT headstand in the middle of the program with all the parents.  The Same kid told me he loved me 100 no not 100 he loved me 105... 105 what i dono~?  -Thomas R.     A kid that SCREaMED becauase he didn't want to leave his mommy the first day but sat with me during the program thing at the very end.  The same kid that erika had a crush on since he was so adorable and had long eyelashes.  The same kid that painted the most perfect flower i have ever seen.  -Matthew D.     A kid tat is deff gonna be number one in his class  The same kid knew every word to every song  He pained a sea coral... i didn't even know what that was when i was his age...  -Michael M.     A kid that cried when she didn't get the ball.  The same kid argued that she had the biggest crayon  The same kid that was the first to enter the "stripclub"  -Kristin C.     A kid that was the biggest trouble makes  The&nbsp;same kid that blew on another kid when we said hands to yourself  The same kid that the arts and craft teacher said would have a VERY short life ;-)  -J.T. T.     Other good memories...   pizza after thurse..  calling chris's pizza..  the stripclub...  erika          
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Today was intense! I woke up. rode my bike to babysittting. GOt my 232$ Pay-Check! and Babysat all day. Then I went to vacation bible school and taught ... LAST LESSON!! HELL YEA! So then after is when the fun started. Brittney had come to help and then she called kevin and then he came. So it was me chandler erika brittney and kevin. We ordered 2 pizzas. Then we chilled and drank ice tea. I think kevin and   We were able to convince my mom to let kevin sleep over and that was amazing. We hav been talking to brittney and her and kevin are gonna hook up! So this is intense stuff going on. I wish kevin the best of luck and brittney....      BITCH ASS MOTHER FUCKER!!!!!!!!!!!    !its what we say when there is an awkward silence. You should try it works wonders.!      
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Sun...&nbsp;&nbsp; The title of this blog is based on long time no see but you don't really see here on blogger so. Hence the change of the phrase. Its been a LONG time since i have blogged last. Alot has happened. That I am going to write about so hang on and we will see what we can do. Alright so&nbsp;on sunday let me think what did I do.... hmm...... O yes.. I went kayking with jordan. He and his dad got kayaks.   urlLink  This is Jordans    and   urlLink  This is his Dad's   !   urlLink  (my kayak ...)&nbsp;   So anyhow that was pretty fun. I also mowed a lawn so i got 20$. It took like two hours to mow the lawn. I got grass stains all over my kacki shorts. I hate bagging the grass. It is a pain in the gr ass  haah get it. Ok i will stop. So then I went to sleep like that I guess. Waiting for kevin to get home since he was in freaking cape cod all week. Erika and Amanda were up there too so i was mad bored. Finally He got home. BUT we couldn't do anything mon.  &nbsp;  Mon...&nbsp; Because I had to babysitt from 8:30 am to 5:30 am. That was interesting.&nbsp;i made them chocolate chip pancakes. burned them but they ate them because they love me! we didn't go swimming but we played with legos and ps2 and tv and read books and did summer packets and stuff. It was ok. At 5 right after I finished the dished ICKKK dishes.. we had to walk down to vbs *vacation bible school* since there parents were back from work, and of coarse I can't drive. It took 23 min. To walk their. By the time i got their my class was almost all there. I am teaching a class with 11 yes thats right 11 going into kindergarden kids... They are soo cute and little and funny. BUT they can be a pain and after a whole day of sitting it was realllllly tiring. I did an awesome lesson with them on the creation. They Love me so much it is almost a problem. Then after vbs I went running with rich and then went home and went to bed.  &nbsp;  YESTERDAY... I had to get their by 6:15 to babysit because there dad was in NY on a buisness trip and their mom goes into work early. It was easy money cuz the kids were asleep and so I slept. WHen One woke up he came down and was like JOOOSHHH!!!!?????!!!! I think he thought I was dead! we had a big pillow fight and played hide and go seek. it was a pretty good day. We went in the pool and I made pretty good meals for them. Can't wait till tomarroow it is P-DAY!!!! yess PAY DAY! So anyhow we rode our scooters to vbs yesterday and it was better maybe we will do that tomarrow. Sooo then at vbs one of the kids was giving me a hug and another kid wanted to but the kid didn't want to share me so he bit the other kids arm.. Like I said they love me so much it is almost a problem. He goes jossss I luv you 100 no 105. They are so cute but so much work. The lesson only went ok but it worked. After I went running with rich and they had oppened the fire hydrants and so it was like a river in the road it was so much freaking fun. I could play in the water all day. We played while we ran. Then I went to kevs and brought him a monitor because his was broken. So then we chilled in his basement talk to ppl on aim and watchin some tvizzle. We decided to make a milksake. It was an interesting mix. Cofffeee icecream and a banana but it actually tasted pretty good. I was impressed. So yea then we went up and like slept  &nbsp;  Today!!!! and woke up ate breakfast. We played some good old wiffle ball this morning. THen I had to come home and do freaken chores :-( After that kevin stoped by and we chatted then i went to my room and slept from lack of sleeep. I got my vbs lesson ready and labed a couple cd's for my mom. Then I went to vbs. only 10 showed up today they seemed pretty good. Erika came to help!!! it was exciting. The kids were cute as always and so yea. Then after vbs I went running by myself b/c rich had already gone running. I ran 3.2 block then ran to kevins house chilled drank a coke then ran home. That is all the activities going on in the debner summer of 04 for these couple days..      O yea i worked on the youth group website a little bit i need more info on what i should do with it. Suggestions would be appreciated....  &nbsp;  http://www.zionlutheranct.elca.biz/youthgroup.htm      
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    I took this picture on vacation and meant to put it up I thought this was an appropiate picture when i was on vacation  Copyright Josh Debner 2004  
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       A bunch of things have happened since the last time I blogged but its ok since I can explain them. I got my new phone. It is a samsung sch-a530. I Love it So much. Thurse was like a waste of a day I basically did nothing and wed I forget what I did but Fri. I went to the beach. I got really sunburned but I hope it turns into a tan. I fell asleep in the sun. It is really red but it doesn't hurt so that is a good thing. I ran 9.2 today and it was really tough. I am tired and so glad for my day off tomarrow. Everyone is starting to come back from their vacations so that is good. I like spending time with friends. Today I went on a 1.5 hour motorcycle ride. It was so much fun. I want one so bad. I know it won't happen. But we can always dream right? I also went to brit's today. That was interesting. We worked on a website but we really didn't we just chilled it was cool... so yea that was my day.   
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today I woke up 8:30 to got runing at 8:30 with P.T. Wow I am one cool cat waking up that early to go runing. When we got back I helped my mom with vacation bible school stuff for a little bit. Then I took a shower and jordan picked me up. We went to mountain grove i dono what to call it but it has like a pool and stuff. I went to his tennis lesson. Then we played tennis. Worked up a sweat then ate lunch. After we were gonna go in the pool but it was too FUCKING COLD. SO then we played the game with the ball that is on a string atached to a pole and you hit the ball. After loosing 7 staight games to jordan i finally beat him.. (he agreed to play with his eyes closed... it was a close win.) Then he beat me a couple more times then we played some basketball. We were hott again so we jumped in the pool and it felt really cool. We swam for a while then went and played tennis for like 4 more hours. I got blisters and hot spots on my feet. While we waited for his mom to come. We played bocci ball and then horshoes.. I won horeshoes and he won bocci ball. Then I came home and went runing. I came home then i ate dinner watched tv and that was my day. My days are so much more boring in the summer. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Most of my friends are gone on vacation so this southtown this is bullshitin boring! Today i slept in till 10 had an ortho app. Came home chilled around and watched tomb raider 2 then went and got my hair cut. After that I came home and chilled some more. Then we ate dinner and that was my day. Interesting things about today, I found out i have a higher average than matt. Not that it mattered, but just i know. Also the ppl who mowed our lawn must have kicked up a rock that went through our the window in our back porch door. It was shattered when we came home and unless someone through the rock we dono how else it coulda happened. Maybe tomarrow will be less boring. OOO after i got my haircut i walked down to strawberries and bought two brand new cds. Queen platinum 3 cd collection and also the styx millenium collection. I love older music. So yea that was my boring day 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    My in my kayak this afternoon...  Copyright Josh Debner 2004  
    
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Isn't this a cool picture! I like the water and the coolio perspective from the yak  Copyright Josh Debner 2004  
    
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So this was my fri and sat. Friday I woke up at like 9ish which was really hard then ran with pat 5.7 miles. It was nice and easy so then I basically came home and cleaned like ALL day around the house my room and such then we went to the malll and my dad bought a gps unit for his b-day and they were gonna check out to buy new cell phones but they threw him off when they said my mom couldn't get a 100$ coupon two since he was the main person even thought they had both had their phones for 2 years. So he walked out mad. We came home and i "contacted" kevin. We picked him up and then went to toco bell... fun stuff. We then met dan and steve at the movie theater and saw spiderman 2. It was an intense movie haha. LoTS of slow boring parts. Some good action though. Kirsten Dunst DAMN very fine. So then we chilled at my house playing counter strike virtual pool and stuff. I stocked up on food for my long run today. We talked to ppl and by the time we got to bed it was already 5 oclock IN THE MORNING! So then i had to get up at 8 to get ready for the 9 o clock run at the orchards. we were both tired. We droped kev off then I went. I ran 15 fucking miles today. IN one run. It took 2 hours... 2 hours of constant running. TOUGH STUFF! So anyhow the guy i ran it with drove me home. can't wait till i can drive. Then after that I chilled around the house and then i called jordan and we played tenis. He of course won. Then he rode to my house and we drank lemonade and we raced on our bike. I won most of the time.. boo ya... so i am soo beat right now. I had supper then decided to fill out that survey thing... thats about all that happened. I am not running tomarrow. SO that will be a nice break. I doubt anyone reads this ppl don't leave comments! 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Just So You Know   I am not big into policitcs.. but i am not a bush fan. I saw this in someone's profile i thought it was funny! 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       WHAT IS YOUR FULL NAME?: Joshua James Debner  -NICKNAMES?: ugh josh is the only good one... (debs, debner, debby,) -WHERE DO YOU LIVE?: Southington, CT -SEX OR ICE-CREAM?: definetly ice cream! -WHAT COLOUR UNDERWEAR ARE YOU WEARING RIGHT NOW?: umm maroon boxers -WHAT ARE YOU DOING RIGHT NOW?: filling this survey out talking to glowa about running -WHAT WAS THE LAST THING YOU DID? eat supper -WHAT IS RIGHT NEXT TO YOU?: computer stereo bed couch -WHO WAS THE LAST PERSON YOU ATE OUT WITH: hmm kevin.. toco bell ! -IF U WERE A TOY, WHAT WOULD YOU BE?: hmm tough one... monkey in a barrel! -WHERE WOULD YOU WANT TO GO ON YOUR HONEYMOON?: exotoic, romantic, or foreign -WHO WOULD YOU WANT TO SPEND THE REST OF YOUR LIFE WITH? if I knew that i wouldn't be waisting my time with some survey thing i would be with them -HOW MANY BUDDIES DO YOU HAVE ON YOUR LIST?: 179 -HOWS THE WEATHER RIGHT NOW? mid 70's evening -LAST PERSON YOU SPOKE TO ON THE PHONE? kevin -LAST PERSON WHO TEXTED YOU: kevin or erika -LAST PERSON YOU TEXT: kevin or erika -WHATS YOUR RING TONE? ocean avenue -yellowcard WHAT DO YOU THINK A TOBLERONE IS:chocolate with yucky nuts in it..  AGE?: 15 HAIR? dirty blonde turning brown :'( WOT R U WEARING RIGHT NOW? globe shoes,kacki old navy shorts.. grey t-shirt DO YOU WEAR CONTACTS? Nope WHAT SCHOOL DO YOU ATTEND: Southington High School ~ Hartford Academy of Math and Science WHO DO CONSIDER YOUR CLOSEST/BESTEST FRIENDS?: kevin-erka-steph-lauren-jordan WHAT WAS THE BEST ADVICE EVER GIVEN TO YOU?: be you DO U OWN A VEHICLE?: no HAVE YOU EVER WON A SPECIAL AWARD?: school stuff and running WHAT ARE YOUR FUTURE PLANS?: loved married in good shape smart sucessful FAVE FOOD: pancakes FAVE FILM : seen too many LAST FILM YOU SAW AT CINEMA?: spiderman 2 FAVE DAY OF THE YEAR?: changes... whenever the day school ends DO YOU LIKE TO DANCE?: i would like it if i could :'( ARE YOU TOO SHY TO ASK ANYONE OUT: nope.. have done it b4 DO YOU SLEEP NAKED?: hell no? WHAT IS THE MOST STUPID THING YOU HAVE EVER DONE?:i dono i have done to many stupid things   DO YOU LIKE SCARY OR HAPPY MOVIES?: happy CHRISTMAS OR EASTER?: christmas  LUST OR LOVE?: love KISSES OR HUGS?: hugs COLOUR ARE YOUR PYJAMAS?: usually plaid i think :-/ WHAT COLOUR'S YOUR TOOTHBRUSH?: blue WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THIS SURVEY??: its a survey WORST FEELING IN THE WORLD: rejected shot down or helpless WORST SOUND?: awkward silences and toothbrush ( i dono i get chills). WHATS THE FIRST THING YOU THINK OF WHEN YOU WAKE UP? a;ready? ROLLER COASTER, SCARY OR EXCITING? both HOW MANY TIMES DO YOU LET THE PHONE RING BEFORE YOU ANSWER IT?: as long as it take to get there MEET ONE PERSON, DEAD OR ALIVE, WHO WOULD IT BE? the beatles ZODIAC SIGN: no clue IF YOU COULD HAVE ANY JOB IN THE WORLD WHAT WOULD IT BE? engineer or physician IS THE GLASS HALF EMPTY OR HALF FULL? Half full WHATS YOUR FAVE NUMBER? 2 NO GIRLS, FOR GUYS TO FILL OUT: THONG OR KNICKERS: depends on the gall  LONG OR SHORT HAIR: shoulder or a lil longer TALL SHORT: my height ( so i can look them in the eyes tell them they are beautiful) BREASTS OR BUM? w/e floats your boat its the person... looks will come later  FOR GIRLS TO FILL OUT ON GUYS:  BOXERS OR Y FRONTS:  DARK OR FAIR?  TALL OR SMALL:  SIX PACK OR NICE ASS :  DOES SIZE MATTER :   (FOR BOTH TO FILL IN)  MOST IMPORTANT PHYSICAL FEATURE: eyes CHOCOLATE, WHITE OR MILK? ? ROOT BEER OR DOCTOR PEPPER : Dr. P MUD OR JELLY WRESTLING? MUD! SKIING OR BOARDING?: boarding.. DAY OR NIGHT? Night SUMMER OR WINTER? Summer...and snow CAKE OR PIE? cake SILVER OR GOLD?? silver DIAMONDS OR PEARLS? Diamonds SUNRISE OR SUNSET?: Sunset HAVE YOU EVER BROKEN A BONE?: not a one  DO YOU HATE ANYONE?: a couple ppl but i don't talk to them DO YOU BELIEVE IN FIGHTING? why would you wanna? WHAT DO YOU DREAM ABOUT? stuff i usually forget DO YOU HAVE A HUGE CRUSH ON SOMEONE RIGHT NOW!: i dono.  WHO DO YOU TURN TO FOR ADVICE?: my handy girl friends and kevin WHO'S THE FIRST TO ASK IN COLLEGE/WORK IF YOU'RE ALRIGHT: don work YOU COULD HAVE 1 SKILL IN LIFE WHAT WOULD IT BE?: flying WHERE IS YOUR FAVOURITE PLACE TO SHOP: ems, american eagle, cabelas, many more - T h e E x t r a S t u f f - - WHAT ARE YOU SCARED OF?: no one likin me, bad grades WHAT ARE YOU LISTENING TO RiGHT NOW?: seether DO YOU WANT TO GET MARRIED: for shizzle Yes  - - F a v o r i t e s - -  COLOUR: green or blue CD or TAPE?: CD ANIMALS?: my weimaraner   - - HAVE YOU EVER - -  GIVEN SOMEONE A BATH: No BROKEN THE LAW??: not that i know of GONE SKINNY DIPPING? nope  FIRST THING THAT COMES TO MIND:  GRASS: yummy ZEBRA: stripes  SOCKS: where's the other one?  DUMB: fuck  HOUSE: clean BOB: bert FISH: boring SPACE: cold HUG: heaven  stole this from lauren's live journal!~ 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       What O what o what did I do hmmm... Ok so tues I babysat all day basically. Ran in the morning and then sat until like 6 oclock. The kids were realllly fiesty. THey fought back and forth the ENTIRE time. I had to tell the parents... they were not good. I felt so bad though because now they are going to get in trouble. :-( So that was an interesting time. My dad took me to "Ritas" it was so great they have custard and italian ice. It was excellent stuff. Then I got up wed and hmm... That day i ran with pt in the morning. Then I chilled at kevins house all day and it was cool. We went swimming and stuff. Then at 6 I went running then had to eat dinner with my parents and I went to the driving range with kevin then slept over kevins house. Then we woke up early this morning went golfing. I shot a 55. All day I been working in my room and around hte house and also we worked on my eagle project. My dad really wants me to get it. All I need is my project. I am starting to think so one else reads this because no one comments... O well 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So this is what we did. I woke up sun and then went to church. I came home and decided to run 10.5 miles in one shot witch was pretty stupid. Then I came home and drank like a gallon of water. Then we went to boston market. It was soooooo good. I love it there. My sister had went to camp in the morning so it is just me and my mom and dad for the week. Then my parents and i all went to see the terminal. It was such a good movie I was really impressed. When we got back we went to "Ritas" it was soo good. Italian ice and real custard it was good stuff. We came home and then I went to bed. This morning I went running once with pt then again with rich. It was ok. Then I went to practice at night. I ran a fast 5.1 and it felt really good. All we did today was clean and stuff so i just kind of hung around the house. It was fun so yea. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       UGH! ...  ok.. so today I woke up at 6 and was supposed to go running, but I was SOOO tired even though I went to bed relativly early last night because I had went running right before bed. So I decided that I would go running tonight. So I slept and that extra hour and a half sleep before chandler got here was awesome. Then we went up and got his boat ready. We cleaned and fixed the fridge and stuff. Then we came home went to walmart and picked up taylor and maura then after that we went back to the boat and went to some islands. It was really run and by the time we got back it was like 9 and then we chilled at Taylors... I called my mom at about 9:45 and asked if she wanted me to go home  or if I could have some pizza since I hadn't eaten dinner. She was in a really good mood. I said chandlers dad could bring me home and she was like thank you so much for calling. At about 10:40ish chandler said how he had a 11 oclock curfew. Then I felt bad about him bringing my home so i called my house and asked if they were awake and could bring me home. My mom is like sure. Then i tried to give her directions and she handed the phone to dad. Then my dad goes why you gotta make it so complicated and then I told him where and asked to come around 11. Then about 10:50 i see a car pass so i go out. THere is noone there and I wait out there then it comes back and it is my dad. He SCREAMS AT ME... I've gone back and fourth 4 times. Where were you. I am not gonna just pull in someones driveway at 11 oclock. Then we have this long awkward silence and he goes. So you didn't run today, there goes that disipline. That cut me really deep, and we didn't talk the rest of the time. I am gonna like like 18 miles tomarrow. Ugh I talked about running all day and even said at taylors i should leave so i can go run but they talked me out of it. O well what can you do. anyhow yea so now i am in my room and gonna go to sleep soon cuz i am in a bad mood and I want energy for all the running i am gonna make myself do tomarrow. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Here the jist of my vacation. We left monday mid day. That night we drove like 6 hours then spend a night in a hotel. We were supposed to stay in another hotel but they were all booked. So then we woke up and drove some more. We reached our campground and set up the tent. THen we went to cedar point for evening and the roller coasters were awesome one went 120 mph one went 96 mph check it out at cedarpoint.com. THen we came back to the campground went to sleep. We spent the entire next day in the park then drove a couple hours and got to the ford museum. We hit up a red roof in and took a rouge ford factory tour. That was so much fun. We got to see ford trucks being built then we went in this cool museum and i bought a gyroscope. Then we kept going and we got to the hotel where we stayed the weekend and then we spent the weekend in the pool and hottub and then we had the wedding. THe hotel suites were really nice. THen we drove through canada to NY and slept at a campground in Niagra. THen we spent a day at niagra falls took awesome pics. Went back to the campground then the next day drove the 9 hours home.  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       blog i need a mental break 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        I will stop with the :  C  O L O  R  S !!!!  ( ppl are complaining about how hard it is to read.) SO yea yesterday I bought golf clubs played tennis with kevin ran while he rode his bike next to me and then went to stephs for a movie night :-D. Today I sat around the house all day and did chores and then I went to boy scouts and Then when i got home chilled at kevins house for a lil bit. Tomarrow I am going to the beach so that will be fun. I don't feel like writing that much now b/c not much happened... and I am lazy SO maybe if somthing happened in my life I could right more.!   
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Later that Saturday I am trying to think of what I did.. I remember now. I got back from  running and went to kevins. We chilled for a little bit Then his dad picked him up and he went to mow lawns and his dads g/f's house for supper. I came back to the house and cleaned up after   the first wedding to make 40$~ THere were lots of rose pedals I had to vaccum then I had to sweet the corn that was thrown outside. It was boring. Then My mom got home from the wedding reception and I went to J. C. Penny and bought some new cloths for school. I love them   SOOOOOO much. I spent 107$ and got 5 shirts... 5 jeans.. THAT IS AN AWESOME DEAL. I got a rolling stones shirt and a ac/dc shirt and a dukes of hazard shirt, and the doors shirt and another ac.dc shirt. I think i also get a free mp3 player... but i gotta mail it in. So then after that  I  came home and cleaned up after the second wedding. THis one was just rose pedals and the runner. Then I hooked up with kevin and we went and played tennis.. I WON of course.. That was my Sat. Today I woke up and then went to church. Got to see stephanie for the first time in   like a MONTH! Then me and my dad went to lunch and he took me on a surprise... We went shopping for GOLF CLUBS!!!! We went to this Play it again sports but didn't find any. Then we went to Golfers warehouse and he got a set for 29.99!~~~~~~ and I didn't find any under   299.99! THere was a right handed pair ( i am lefty) for 80$ that were nikes and 799 dollar clubs.. but my dad didn't believe me that they were a really good deal. So he got the cheaper   ones. THen   I came home and we got KFC and ate it. After kevin and I went to play tennis at the High SChool and he beat me.. I dono what is wrong with me soo maybe next time. MY    parents went to a movie together, ain;t that sweet. I want kevin to sleep over when they get back.   
    
    
</post>


</Blog>