<Blog>


<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Here we go with the whole  urlLink chicken or the egg argument.   The  urlLink FDA  is asking the makers of ten different anti-depressant drugs to add or strengthen the warnings on their labels about potential suicidal side effects.  The primary drugs pinpointed are:        Prozac ( fluoxetine )   Zoloft ( sertaline )   Paxil ( paroxetine )   Luvox ( fluvoxamine )   Celexa ( citalopram )       Lexapro ( excitalopram )   Wellbutrin ( bupropion )   Effexor ( venlafaxine )   Serzone ( nefazodone )   Remeron ( mirtazapine )        This strikes me as an interesting philosophy, one based upon the ever-growing legal liability suits.  A more invasive big brother, it appears, wants to treat it subjects as sheep in need of exuberant pampering.  Anyone hear the call of the  urlLink Illumanti?   Chicken or egg, which came first?    The applicability of this philosophical dilemma, the so called chicken or egg conundrum, maybe actually be a  urlLink fallacy,  but this is why this policy is relevant....  These drugs are generally used for the treatment of  urlLink depression,  for which a symptom is, that's right kids, suicidal ideation, plans or attempts, according to the DSM-IV.  How could a researcher feasibly have any real statistics about how prone an individual is to suicide on a medication, when that very tendency (i.e. the dependent variable) is what put them ON THE MEDICATION?    &lt;breathes&gt;   I'm alright.  So everyone, remember to read your labels.  The side effects might be symptom... er... the symptom maybe be a side eff....  Whatever, you figure it out.   By the way,   HAPPY BIRTHDAY GRIFE!!!!!!!!!!!!!  
     


    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's coming, and coming soon.  The dreaded smoking ban begins  urlLink April 1st in Connecticut , and I, for one, am upset.  Yes, I'm a smoker.  That states the obvious reason, but in reality, there are so many others.  I have no dilemma with not smoking in a restaurant.  I can fully understand the aggravation of a non-smoker trying to eat and chewing down a large cloud of carbon monoxide.  I don't have a problem with it at all, but I do find it odd to ban it in a bar.  New York City has done this.  I've been there numerous times since the ban, and it sucks.  I've read all kinds of articles about the economical windfall following the law, with losses, on average, of 30% of customers according to  urlLink NYNewsday.     This brings to mind the days of Prohibition and the Speakeasy.  Making a law that forces people to give up something they enjoy generally doesn't go well when they already have a well established lifestyle.  The motivation, is of course, the health of non-smokers and employees.  First of all, half the people that don't smoke light up at a bar.  I've seen it, and many times.  I'd say that at least half of bartenders in the places I frequent smoke themselves.  A good bar owner will have an impressive ventilation system that removes the majority of smoke.  Besides, come on, booze and cigs are like bread and butter.  But what kind of precedent does this set?  If I'm allergic to perfume, is it going to get banned from a bar?  I have sensitive ears, hooting and hollering and laughing loud: banned.  I'm agoraphobic, so when I go to a bar, everyone has to leave.  Ridiculousness.  I would say there are much smarter, slower methods.  Consider, perhaps, taxing smoking bars.  Let the owners decide what kind of losses they want to take, and let employees pick where they'd like to work.  Already you have a financial option that the government might be a bit more interested in.  Make a law that these bars also have to have a ventilation system that rotates through the air  n -times per hour.  Stop selling packs of cigarettes at bars.  There are many options that are seemingly ignored.  Even if you wanted to be really drastic, implement a law that cigarettes cannot be sold to anyone born after April 1st, 2004.  Phase things out slowly... it's the way to institute change without rebellion.  I considered writing my congressman, governor, etc., but I know it isn't worth the time.  Perhaps business will be the ones who really control the attention of the aforementioned representatives of the people.  But I'm betting against it.
     


    
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Welcome to our slowly evolving discussion blog.  We will be conducting discussion about various topics in everday life here as the site evolves and the formatting works out.  We hope to create enlightening and inspiring debates and talks, and eventually allow others to add to our dialog.  As time evolves, we'll let you know more about us, and introduce you to the fun little game known debate.  More on this later.
     


    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      In the Renaissance era, which started in the 14th century in Italy and the 16th century in Europe, a Renaissance man was a person considered to be interested in and a master of many differing fields of “work and knowledge.”  However, as  urlLink Wikepedia  points out, “during the Renaissance, it was easier to be an expert in all fields, as the total sum of knowledge was considerably smaller than it is today.”  I begin this discourse because I believe that I’m a  modern-day  Renaissance man.  This is  NOT  a pat on the shoulder: I say this not as a justification of my existance, but as an edification for those of you who feel mired in mediocrity, swathed in situational stagnation, or cantankerous about commonality.    Bare with me here.    The modern-day Renaissance man is a lost soul, when juxtaposed to those men of yore.  Consider Leonardo da Vinci, whose birthday is a mere 5 days after mine.  An expert in art, math, engineering, and other sciences, he was a day dreamer who rarely ever completed his projects.  I read a fictional book that runs around Leonardo’s life and works a lot,  The Da Vinci Code  by Dan Brown is a really interesting read, though not always a hundred percent accurate.  He takes a lot of very complex ideas and breaks them down into an easy read.   One of the things Brown discusses is Leonardo’s invention that was perhaps the earliest form of public key encryption, a cylinder that required the write sequence to open.  I’ll cover cryptography and encryption basics in another post.  Back from my digression, the modern-day Renaissance man: one who is knowledgeable in many fields on a superficial level, but excels in none individually.  Let me give you an example:  I can sit down with a theoretical physicist, a personal trainer, a mortgage broker, a computer scientist, a business manager, a writer/journalist, a musician, a photographer, a medical doctor, a theater director, an engineer, a CEO, a financial analyst, a geneticist, a psychiatrist, a sales associate, a boat captain, an aspiring film director, a teacher, a waitress, a veterinary technician, a masseur, a webmaster, an aspiring speech therapist, an actress, a bartender, a “nanny”, an aspiring advertising executive, and an EMT (not necessarily all at once), and I can discuss their professions on more than a layman’s level.    This is important, because almost all of these cover the friends that I have, and I often help them to intermingle.   I read a lot of books, have a lot of discussions, pursue grand conquests of knowledge through the extensive internet, and daydream of entrepreneurial achievement.  I can manage finances and find answers to complex questions quickly, and digest that for others to understand with relative ease.  I can advise and help people to see themselves in an entirely different light, and I’ve taught myself most of what I’ve learned in college.  I write a blog.  I can’t graduate college on time, pick something I want to do, or follow the path that’s easiest.  I can’t figure out what a normal sleep schedule is.  I often can’t find my keys.  I forget to feed my dogs twice a day.  I’m a Renaissance man.  I have no grand illusions of being a reincarnation of Leonardo.  I’m still working on my stick figures.  But I know he worshiped the Golden Ratio (1.618:1, found in almost everything we consider beautiful, and almost precisely in our bodies, too much to get into here, read  The Da Vinci Code  to find out more), and I know he was a daydreamer.    I’d bet money that he had ADD.  The irony of being a modern-day Renaissance man is that there is no glory in it.  In fact, one is nearly forced to revel in mediocrity.  Others excel in fields, make money, and enjoy doing what they do.  They are consummate citizens, contributing to the world in their own way.  I applaud them, and I envy them.  But to argue, our world is one of specialization.  Like an exponential function, we increase precise knowledge at such a drastic rate that we approach an asymptote of the larger picture.  This could cause trouble down the line if we keep outsourcing with greater frequency.  Besides, what if you had a team of people building a house that were each so specialized and talented that they could create amazing pieces, but no one knew how to put it all together?  Your bedroom might have a porch in it with a swimming pool holding the refrigerator in the bathroom.    It would be a little odd, to say the least.  So I say to those who are like me, in this frame, ensnared and confused, there may be hope for us yet.  Maybe I adhere to false hopes, or maybe I’m entirely disillusioned about what I am and my aforementioned definition.  Regardless, I hold hope for where my mind takes me, and the interesting ways I generally arrive at conclusions or new questions.  I live an atypical life, and I enjoy it.  I hope that holds.  I’m a modern-day Renaissance man, and I hold good company.  
     


    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It seems to me that there are a few incontrovertible truths in this world--a few aside from all those many "everything is everything" and "the only constant is change" type dictums.  One truth is that truths of the nature about which I'm talking are somehow quite difficult to digest, and further, to practice.  The other truth is that sometimes, not all the time, but sometimes, admitting the error of your ways is ONLY a positive thing, for everyone.  When President George W. Bush got up for his press conference on Tuesday night and fielded questions (for only the eighth time, I believe) in a scripted order from the White House press corps, it could have been a good time to own up to some of the failings of his Administration's way.  When asked almost point blank if he'd do anything differently--such as, like, NOT initiate a wild goose chase for Saddam's purported and still-unfound WMD's; such as, like, NOT completely alienate a great majority of the international community that had been, in the months after September 11th, rallying behind us with all their sympathies, etc. etc. etc.--he just put on his figleaf cowboy machismo and snickered that he just couldn't come up with a mistake he'd made.  He's "confident" he's made a mistake, but he "just can't" come up with one.  Let's take a minute and bring this down to our level.  One time, a number of years ago, I was seeing this girl and completely blinded to anything but me and her.  I was militant about my health, my lifestyles, evicting any old bad habit I could imagine, disowning friends by the busload, oftentimes with a big kick in the ass and derisive, scathing remarks on their way out the door.  My compatriot on this page is one such buttkicked hombre.  I was, with hindsight in tact, just one depressed guy who thought he'd found salvation in the form of a lady and a lifestyle surrounding her.  Anything that didn't match up with the bubble was evacuated with force.  A year or so passed, I ended the affair with the lady and returned more or less to myself with a couple hundred healthy and/or bruising lessons from my little escapade: one lesson: nothing encourages forgiveness than a good strong tail between your legs in front of those you've wronged.  Apologies are empty vessels without admission of your failings and mistakes.  I made a healthy round of apologies and admissions and all is good, in fact, all is better than it ever was.  I learned a great deal about myself, and about friendship, from all of it.  Yes, I may have alienated some people for a time, but the real friendships have endured.  But I can guarantee no one would have forgiven me if I'd come up and said, "I'm confident I've made a mistake, I just can't come up with one on the spot."  That statement that Bush said (and please, pardon the digression to a personal tale... it's awfully selfish, but it is connected) basically makes plain that Bush is either ignorant and/or a pathological liar: there are at least a couple (dozen) statements and courses of action he and his Administration have bodied forth that have been proven erroneous--i.e., that the "Mission" was "Accomplished" as he swaggered on the battleship; that there are masses of WMD's all over Iraq--and another couple (dozen) awaiting proof of error.  He's never once atoned for his mistakes.  Owning up and atonement is an 'option' in your personal life; one can go without it, even if it's more than a trifle.  Taking Responsibility and Atonement should be a requirement for the leader of the most powerful nation in the world.  And the bottom line: a man who is so despised by at least half of the population should know better than to flaunt himself like a gesturing cowboy when his mistakes are all a-flutter, as they are right now.  Disclaimer: talking hot-headed smack about the President of the United States is a cliché at this point in the game, which is a telltale, sorrowful fact in itself.  I hope no one thinks that I think I'm solving some big problem by prescribing a better course of action for our President.  This hot-headed smack is part-and-parcel of the problem facing the Democratic party (and all liberals opposing the Bush regime), in that, well, criticizing and slandering the work of another man is a damn easy thing to do when you're not doing what the dude's doing yourself.  And hot-headed smack isn't convincing anyone who's getting his back.  So, anyway, pardon the hot head; i'd have tried a little more diplomacy, but, well, I haven't had a good example of good diplomacy in a while.  So there.
     


    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm delinquent, I know.  I should have started up with my boy, but I've had my head in the clouds.  The planet of communication (Mercury) has been in retrograde for a couple of weeks until today.  You know what that feels like.  All the voices in my head have been, until today, whispering sweet indecipherables into utterly clogged ears, and now, all of a sudden, today, like the Dolby Surround prompt in the previews, all the voices are speaking clearly and concisely.  So I've got my scribbling mojo back, you could say.  And that's my opening.  Take it or leave it.  What first inspired me to jump on this bandwagon today, actually, was a comment by my compatriot about OPEC and the war not being about oil.  Dude, you said, "Democrats, that's your cue."  Well, here I am:  The war in Iraq may very well not have been about oil.  We don't really have any proof of that.  But saying, definitively, that "the war is NOT about oil" is like saying that the Paris Hilton tape HURT her reputation, or as ludicrous as saying that the war was about homeland security, when all proof shows that nobody's any safer with that glass-eyed, unkempt (former ally to the US) Saddam Hussein out of his hole and out of Iraq and in custody.  Furthermore, gas prices going up is not necessarily a sign that our intention in Iraq was NOT their oil; it could also be, blatantly, yet another example of the failings of the economy and the relative JackShit the Administration has actually done to make it all better.  I can stand by the idea that the Administration's intentions were Iraqi oil because the whole engagement in Iraq has been, more or less, one big planning flaw after another.  No wonder we're not paying less for gas!  We haven't gotten control of theirs yet anyway!  There could be more clarity to that.  But I'm just a hot-headed Democrat today; I'm entitled; the Republican administration is leading us down a cold road.  Someone's gotta balance the warmth.  And HAPPY BIRTHDAY, belated, to my boy!
     


    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've seen  urlLink  Sweet November   a number of times now, and I grow more fond of it each time.  Not only is  urlLink Charlize Theron  criminally beautiful and the apex of my Hollywood adorations, the depth with which she plays her character is just extraordinary.  She plays a free-spirited, material-shunning woman that offers a cynical, jaded man (Keanu Reeves) one month to "help" him essentially discover himself.  Every moment is a moment of enjoyment, everything that she does is handled and seen as a child handle and sees all.  Ok, yes, to some degree I straddle the optimist and the cynic, probably heavier on the later, but their interaction and relationship is largely carried by the talents of Theron as an actress.  Perhaps no where is that more clearly demonstrated and realized than in her  urlLink Oscar winning role in  Monster  .  For a former model, she sure is one hell of an actress.  Perhaps this rant is a bit off the mark, considering I generally cover news and technology with a discernible gusto, but I think it's at least socially relevant.  The lifestyle we all lead is with a generally unnecessary celerity, losing the moment in stock tickers and reality television that generally makes me want to defenestrate myself.  This movie is a great reminder of this, and perhaps in Theron's character portrayal, I find salvation.  Perhaps it's a dated male ideal, in fact, it probably is, but then I guess you can call me old fashioned.  The idea of a woman dedicated to the idea of using her liberal life to exonerate a man's soul from the confines of a financially and aesthetically driven, shallow lifestyle is just... cool.  I don't know how most guys would react to that, but I think it would be an uncommon moment of acquiescence for me.  Ironically, however, I imagine that if that idea truly was substantiated, I would probably curl up into my usual emotional judiciousness, don my apathy suit, and jaunt on down the well cultivated path of detachment and wonder why I'm so melancholy, meanwhile reminiscing how I would've abjured my comportment with my 20-20 hindsight.  That can also be read as I'd mess it up and wonder why.    But hope is better than nothing.  I'm hoping that Charlize will read this and email me.  I'm hoping that I'll make enough money to never have to worry about it.  I'm hoping I'll be on a regular sleep schedule one day.  But Benjamin Franklin may have said it best when he orated, "He that lives upon hope will die fasting."  Hope is at least a decent snack between meals though.  Of course, I may just be a Douglas fir.  Full of sap. 
     


    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
         Cingular and ATT Wireless aren't waiting until their merger is complete to start  urlLink blending their networks .  Good news for subscribers to each... I hope.  I'm an ATTWS subscriber.   A friend of ours is in Kingdom Hospital ( urlLink pictured here, on the left ), which will start airing next week at 8pm on Thursdays, instead of its former 10pm Wednesday time.  A good move, perhaps, in that more people watch television on Thursdays, but they're putting it against CBS's  CSI: Crime Scene Investigation  and NBC's  The Apprentice .  Not a good move.  This was to be ABC'S ratings cash cow, having such a prosaic season.  It's a shame to move such a good miniseries into the ratings guillotine.   OPEC is trying to screw us again with a  urlLink 4% cut in crude oil production .  Good plan, we're already bleeding, why not open the wound.  Is this proof enough that the war  maybe  wasn't about oil?  Democrats, that's your cue.   The smoking ban in Connecticut begins today.  I was the last to smoke a cig in the bar last night, beaming with pride and internally weeping at another lost freedom.  Will it hold?  I'll watch the stats.   Get your drugs from Canada!  New Hampshire Governor  urlLink Craig Benson does .   3 1/2 to 7 years for sending out  urlLink 825 million bulk emails.   Connecticut law, which is the most severe when compared to Maine, Massachusetts, New Hampshire, Rhode Island, Vermont, and New York (most lenient), gives up to  urlLink seven years for possession of a narcotic (heroin, crack, cocaine) .  I'd be curious to see if a casual drug dealer makes more than a bulk emailer.   
     


    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Google is beta testing a new  urlLink free email webmail service .  They'll be offering 1 gigabyte of storage space, which is about 1,000 megabytes, searchable and all.  This is a  very  aggressive attack at Microsoft and Yahoo, no suprise.  But what once was once an affable business relationship with AOL now becomes a direct attack on their (AOL's) main cash cow.  Moo (boo hoo boo hoo).  Google has been my favorite search engine for years.  They used a very honest page ranking scheme and they don't have ten thousand splash pages/links on their home page.  Very straightforward.  However, lately I've been reading some information about  urlLink Google's cookie that expires in 2038.   The CIA had to stop using a comparatively innocent log-analysis cookie that expired in 10 years, and their document search site isn't even used by many people. Google handles 200 million searches per day, and their cookie expires in 2038. One of Google's leading software engineers, Matt Cutts, has a top-secret clearance and used to work for the National Security Agency. Google doesn't even feel the need to defend their cookie policy; they merely laugh off anyone who inquires about it.  I have my doubts about the validity of it all, but it is interesting.  The amount of data that they collect would be a data miner's dream.  If Google ever started to lose large profits, they could just sell all this information for a ridiculous amount of money.  You can find out how to thwart Google's cookie  urlLink here.  
     


    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have a lot of animosity towards spam.  It’s a basic nuisance that we all deal with, and wouldn’t be so bad if it didn’t take up a large part of your email box most of the time.  The horrible part is that spam continues to evolve.  There are spammers who offer free access to porn sites, and use the images that hotmail has for security as the signup key.  They then get the image code, enter it into the hotmail confirmation signup (automatically) and tada, another spam account is born, beating the new  urlLink MSN security practice .  But a new annoyance has begun.  I’m now getting spam as text messages on my cell phone.  I’m not talking like I get one a month; I’ve gotten 5 in the last two days.  Previously, I always got excited by text messages, because they were usually from some of the really cool people that I know, sending me a little tidbit about their day, or just saying hello.  Now, I’m getting messages like:  “learn the juicy details on anyone GO TO: www.theymonitoryou.com”  or  ”get all skeletons on your wife!”  or  ”check out the juicy details on inlaws”  or  get all the hot facts on your lover”  or  ”read all the hidden secrets on friends! GO TO: www.weapprove.net” .  It’s like they really know me!  Wait, I’m not married, nor do I care about all the rest.  Coincidentally, all of these text messages come from… you got it, MSN accounts.  Granted, this is all very aggravating, so I decided to call my carrier, ATT Wireless (a.k.a.   urlLink ATTWS  .  I was expecting some resistance and difficulty and a long time on the phone.  Miraculously, after dialing in all the info required, I got an operator in  one ring .  This is unheard of in the cell phone circle.  I was almost totally unprepared.  Usually, I have time to formulate what I’m going to say, how I’ll say it, wonder what tune is playing on the hold playlist, get mad that I’m waiting so long, wonder what I forgot to do today, and finally get a non-English speaking operator who tells me they have to transfer me to the correct department, and then the process repeats.  But surprisingly, my operator was prompt, offered me upfront a new package deal promotion (I declined), and asked me how he could help.  I told him I was getting spam and all the details, including the websites promoted and that all of the spam came from MSN accounts.  I asked if I was paying for these, and he told me that everything was ok, I’m only charged for text messages I send, not receive.  He then took my account (there are two numbers on it) and told me it may take up to twenty days, but that he sent it in for processing.  And that was it.  I was done.  Incredible.  Luckily, I’m not getting  urlLink porn spam  yet, but at this rate, I assume it’s not far away.  This website suggests adding your cell number to the do not call list, but I would advise against that.  I’ve heard rumors that illegal spam promoters actually peruse that info for prospective calls.  I have to give my thanks to ATTWS for being so pleasant.  Although I’ve heard otherwise, I’ve never really had any large complaints about them, and I get better service than most.  Thanks again, ATTWS, for being a provider I choose to stick with, although you’re probably going to be Cingular soon anyway.  And to the spammers: leave us alone on our phones.  Stick to your regular means of advertising.  I will further let it be known that I choose to boycott any text message websites that I receive as spam.  Although it doesn’t mean much, it’s my little fight against the shadows, and I’m still naïve enough to think it means something. 
     


    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I think of myself as a generally honest, straightforward person.  Sure, sometimes I slip down the slope of moral corruption momentarily, but so do most (that slope is slippery!).  I always find, however, that the greater part of my dishonest side always shows itself when I see a friend I haven’t seen in awhile.  It's not, however, purposeful, but rather more of a reflex.  It comes from the initialization of a conversation, and we all do it.  It’s funny that the question most people ask yet don’t ever want to hear the answer to is derived from one simple question:  “So how have you been?”  When was the last time anyone ever really thought about that?  Usually the first response is, “I’m good, how are you?” or “I’m freakin’ FAN-tastic!” or some other trivial, subversive retort that all mean the same thing.  Derivations.   In math, a simplistic definition of a derivation (I can’t believe I remember this) is a dynamic representation of the tangent at all points along a graph.  With this visual representation comes many rules: chain rule, quotient rule, inverse rule, etc.  It’s a whole semester of stuff that I’ve just cut down into a few sentences.  Anyway, conversation derivations are much the same.  They’re dynamic tangents based upon a single question or statement.  Basically, they don’t follow what the ACTUAL path is but the path that has one single point in common with the beginning question.  “So how have you been?”  “I’m good, how are you?”  “I’m good, thanks.”  Occasionally, I like to throw something different in the mix, just to see how people react.  The fastest way to lose their attention is to say, “Eh, I’m ok, but it’s kind of been a hard day…”     &lt;glaze&gt;   To check for friends: “I’ve had the worst day…”  Friends will say, “What happened?” while others will say offhandedly, “That sucks.”  It’s interesting to observe the reactions of others, and something that’s fun to try.  Give it a whirl; throw something different in the mix, because it’s at the very least entertaining, and sometimes enlightening.  I have one friend, a female, who sometimes, however, just won’t respond to questions.  It’s not that she isn’t bright (she is), or that she didn’t hear it (she does), but she just zones for awhile.  I can understand this, as I have a bit of ADHD myself, but the manner in which she does it is unique.  I can’t figure it out at all, and it’s rare that I get thrown off that profoundly.  “How are you doing?”  I’ll say.  “…”  It’s so weird, and maybe this whole post doesn’t make sense, but people who pause in odd places TOTALLY throw me off.  I've always felt (and maybe  The Celestine Proficy  has something to do with this) that conversations work by themselves, and if you pay close attention, a group will always subconsciously realize who should talk, so long as there aren't any power struggles within said group.  Has anybody else had this experience, or am I just totally crazy?  Sometimes silence is golden, and sometimes silence says more than any words ever could.  But when the natural flow of conversation doesn't just ebb, it actually dries up, it's a strange and disconcerning moment.  Or maybe I'm just annoying and she's ignoring me.  Who the hell knows?    Note:   I've been sick for a few days with a fever and stuff, so this may actually not make any sense to anyone but me, and me only at this moment.  Or maybe it's the hotest epiphany EVER.  I'll figure that out when my head clears up, or when the comment(s) rolls in.  Right now, I'll go with the egomaniacal delusion of grandeur, because I live in the land of make believe, and in my land, I write real goodly. 
     


    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Administration's Little Piggy house of cards, surely made of lesser stuff than even straw, has finally been blown completely over.  With the news today and yesterday that Ahmad Chalabi has  urlLink passed pivotal U.S. intelligence to Iran , the cancer infecting the infrastructure of this mesmerizingly flawed WarHawk policy has finally metastasized.  Let's take a look:  First, they pressed for war against much opposition (i.e., millions of people across the globe rallying together against the war).  They got the resolution to strike based on evidence that they possessed WMDs (so far, ...  urlLink one dirty bomb of sarin agent  more than a year after invading); that they were an imminent threat to Americans (well, no, but, yes, cuz (well done!) you put thousands of Americans in harm's way there!); and all this evidence (as it turns out now) was dished to them from the mouth of a self-interested turncoat who's now giving top secret US information (and why in hell is HE getting top secret information!?!?) to Iran.  ... Now they'll probably insist on invading Iran to get that information muzzled up again!  Second, some higher-up, perhaps even the  urlLink very highest up , authorized the use of  urlLink law-breaking procedures on prisoners of war.  [See some of my earlier posts for more information on that.]  Not to mention that they used those procedures on law-ABIDING, innocent civilians, in most cases.  Third, they fashioned a BUH-FUCKING-RILLIANT exit plan involving, well,  urlLink no planning whatsoever , or rather, planning with such extreme, faith-based, and downright delusional optimism that there was no inkling of damage control should certain variables NOT turn out absolutely positive in Iraq.  And, well, nothing has turned out positive at all.  In my humble opinion, this is just the last straw.  All the blood, the lives, the money, the credibility we've put into this war, and it was mainly based on information provided by an unreliable man who was once "convicted of fraud in absentia" and is now trading in US secrets, and all the while receiving $340,000 a month from the US government.  Talk about flaws in policy.  This Administration...OfFICially. Gets a vote of ABSOLUTELY NO FUCKING CONFIDENCE.
     


    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      There are certain rare occasions when my hometown NYC actually feels like a tight little community.  The cataclysm of 9/11 was one such event--the throngs united in grief and action.  Last year's rally against the war in Iraq and against the Bush Administration: hundreds of thousands taking to the Saturday streets to raise voice together: another such event.  Even the first day of this spring, when Central Park became home to hundreds of lunching folk in rolled-up trousers and Hanes as outerwear, all of us in awe at the budlings and warmth.  Yesterday, Sunday, I took part in another such event: the  urlLink AIDS walk .  The annual march meanders through Central Park before exiting onto the streets above the park, over to and then down Riverside Drive until veering back into the park to its finish line roughly six miles from the start.  I haven't seen reports yet of this year's turnout or fundraising, but last year's Walk grossed over $5 million for AIDS research, garnered from over 45,000 New Yorkers joining together with their networks of sponsors.  This year's, I'm sure, will have similar, if not better numbers.  At first, it feels like a cattle herd, trudging slowly and restricted by the sheer density of entities.  I tripped on others' heals and stepped on others' toes, even swung my arms into another's smiling face when I got excited about the glorious weather (No, I am not a quaking shaking Quaker!).  But as the route extends north, the pace quickens, and walkers are afforded a little more breathing room.  I was struck immediately by the diversity of the crowds (well, not immediately, but after shaking groggy eyes awake--the Walk requires a treacherous 7am alarm).  My team (called the Street Walkers--the organizers of our team live in the West Village near a reputed tranny/hooker hangout), comprised mainly of gay men, and me and my girlfriend, were flanked by men and women of so many different creeds, colors, tastes and tales, I couldn't possibly enumerate them all.  But the bottom line is that we were all there for one over-arching purpose: to raise awareness and aid for the ever-growing global crisis that is  urlLink AIDS .  In a city where it is so easy, by force of the sheer and variant multitudes of people, to simply put on blinders to others and live in one's own little bubble, thru one's own tunnel vision, it is a real inspiration when an event like this comes your way and enables, in fact, forces those blinders and that tunnel vision away from you.  And all we did was get together with friends and walk through New York on a beautiful Sunday morning!
     


    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I went out tonight to play some more pool, which only really lasted for a few moments.  I was told that my friend Alex had a blog, so I went to check it out, and I discovered another friend's (Matt's) blog, and that he had taken a few funny quizzes.  His results are  urlLink rather amusing .  So I figured I would take a crack at it as well.  Here's what I got:  Imagine this:   You have a dominant kiss- you take charge and make sure your partner can feel it! Done artfully, it can be very satisfactory if he/she is into you playing the dominant role MEORW!   urlLink   What kind of kiss are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      Better yet, check this out:   PASSIONATE LOVER. You love to love, always looking for a relationship. You cannot live without it.  Your lover must be passionate and you want that you and your partner melt into each other.  He/She should not try to take the domination.  You dont want a relationship without passion, and the sexuality plays a big part. The first moment you meet him/her is one of the most important. There has to be something between you, you cannot explain. From the first moment on everything must fix. But when this passion disappears you disappear to. For you it is better to leave than to see your love restrained.   urlLink   	~THE big LOVE TEST!! What do you need? With PICS! For girls and boys!~     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla     Wow, I just need to stop there I should say.   urlLink Alex's blog  has extensive movie reviews and literary commentary, which I will read so as to raise my IQ beyond that of a common primate.   urlLink Matt's blog  is just straight up funny.   Since I'm refering blogs tonite, I can't forget to mention TJ's place, especially this entry Kev wrote  urlLink about his neighbor's dog :   I find myself aiming a lot of anger at Patches, this ugly little dog whose name I wake to every morning. He is creepy and sickly and small (or, as my dad used to say, “I’ve laid turds bigger than that dog.”). He runs up to you and barks, but zips off if you try to pet him. He is a master of the piss and run, whereby the dog races up to some property of yours that you would rather not be peed on, lifts its leg and pees for one second, then races away.    Poor Kev, it must really be annoying, but damn does it make a great story and a good laugh.  Thanks again Kev.  Ok, that's it for now, I think that I ought to try to sleep more often, but it really is just a big waste of time.  Besides, I can always write totally useless blog entries which amuse me and prevent me from sleeping anyway.
     


    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      You might notice a little bit of difference in... ummm the entire site design.  This seems a lot more readable and a little more straightforward.  Considering how little you're allowed to modify things because of the template design, it's nice to have some rounded edges and things to work with.  A few little things to mention:  I copied the relevant comments except for ones that didn't have any text.  I also transfered the names.  However, we have a new commenting system that is limited to 1000 characters or less, so some of you wordy people (like Tracheotomy man) will have to split it like I did for him.  It also allows for others to trackback if they want to blog about a specific post and they're Haloscan members too.  It just serves as a better way of linking up and networking.  The design has a few little flaws right now, but I'm done trying to work it out.  Speak up and let us know what you think.  Remember, this is a forum for everyone, we're just the topic moderators.  Ok, so a little more than that, but your comments inspire us to write more, so be heard people.  Thanks!  
     


    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I’ve used aliases (bad ones) here for the sake of anonymity.  I got a phone call from a girl tonight (no, that’s not so unusual), and she wanted to see if I wanted to go to a bar with them (a few girls) that’s 25 minutes from my house.  Granted, that doesn’t sound so bad, except for a few little factors:    The bar is filled with people I don’t know, generally younger than I am, and they all look like they just decided to start their frat/sorority here   I like the bars that are actually 3-4 minutes from my house   My buddy wanted to play pool, and again, that was a lot closer   The girls tend to flirt with guys a plenty, and I wind up twiddling my thumbs   I’m not taking them home    I told Sasha I was tired (I was) and that I was going to play pool with a buddy.  All of a sudden, her friend Isabel gets on the phone, and asks me to come out.  Again, I repeat my story, and she says to me, “Sasha told me to tell you that she’s going to wear a really short skirt tonight, and that you should come out.”  Well, that’s dandy, except that I’ve definitely become the “nice guy” of their little group, and that’s not self-proclaimed, because I’ve been introduced that way.  For those of you who don’t know, a “nice guy” introduction is like a death sentence before a trial.  I’m like a practical car for someone in their mid-life crisis, or a eunuch in the  Bachelorette ; I’m there, but serve no purpose.  It’s neither good nor bad, it’s purgatory.  It’s a question without an answer.  It is, apparently, me.  This is all no big deal, because it’s important to have female friends to get objective perspectives, get a little womanly comfort, and to remind you that you’re not a leper.  I realized this awhile back, and they’re nice girls, so I don’t protest.    The funny thing was, they thought a short skirt would make me more likely to come out, but it is useless bait.  Even if I happened to be attracted to Sasha, going out because she had on a short skirt, realizing my identity to her, would be like banging my head into a brick wall to remember not to bang my head into the brick wall, and I need that like I need a hole in the head.  However, it is interesting that they thought it would sway me.  And maybe it shows that they don’t exactly hold the highest opinion of me yet, which is precisely the reason I went out to play pool, and why I’m not sitting here feeling bad for a hot second. 
     


    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My compadre has officially encouraged me not to watch the video of Nicholas Berg's beheading, as it's proven to have caused nightmarish hauntings upon his psyche.  I saw stills and my imagination filled in the rest--the moving image of his head being severed, the sound of his curdling scream--and that might be enough for me.  But it is not enough for me to sit and accept from the Department of Defense, or from the CIA, or from any institution, the conclusions that have been purported in many waves of media in the last couple of days.  I accept that Nick Berg was murdered, and may God have vengeance on the souls of those responsible for it; I accept that he was decapitated on video, and may some strong manner of human jurisprudence be smitten upon those who did it for the political statement it shouted out.  A number of articles have come out in the past day or two exploring some intense discrepancies, (perhaps mere) coincidences and overall very interesting tidbits that belie the seemingly black and white conclusions of guilt and meaning behind the murder.  First, there's some confusion about who Nicholas Berg was.  Yes, an American, a Philadelphian, a 26-year old male.  The interesting  urlLink hitch in the tale  begins when one considers how it is that "the FBI questioned Berg in 2002 after a computer password Berg used in college turned up in the possession of Zacarias Moussaoui, the al Qaeda operative arrested shortly before Sept. 11 for his suspicious activity at a flight school in Minnesota."  Nicholas Berg's father explained this striking coincidence by saying, first, that there was no wrongdoing on his son's behalf and that Nicholas had "met Moussaoui while riding the bus to classes, and had allowed the suspect to use his computer."   urlLink FoxNews  also highlights this merely "coincidental" link between Berg and Moussaoui.  This connection might explain why Nicholas Berg was detained in Iraq prior to being abducted by his killers.   The details of his detainment are in dispute right now, as the US Government claims that the Iraqi police picked him up first.  A  urlLink recent article , on the other hand, includes statements from the chief of Mosul police who blatantly counters that allegation: "The Iraqi police never arrested the slain American," he said. "Take it from me ... that such reports are baseless."  Nicholas Berg's father contends that the US Military and FBI had questioned Nicholas in Iraq, disclosing correspondences with all parties to that effect.  A  urlLink research dig  into Nicholas Berg's father brings us to another interesting crossroads in this murky situation.  This article details that "on 7th March, 2004, just three weeks before the first anniversary of the invasion of Iraq, an  urlLink 'enemies' list  of anti-war groups and individuals was posted on the Free Republic forum."  It seems that Nicholas Berg's father, Michael, was ardently against the war in Iraq and consistently suspicious of the current Administration.  His son Nicholas on the other hand was diametrically opposed to his father and vehemently supported President Bush and the war on terror and the war in Iraq.  That enemies list is on the internet; hell, it's posted right here.  You can rest assured that the "enemies list"--which includes predominatly a wide variety of law-abiding, utterly upstanding organizations that happen to fall on the progressive side of the spectrum--was also safely in the hands of the FBI and CIA.  This article suggests that the reason why, "during his detention, [Nicholas] Berg was questioned by FBI agents three times," is that the FBI were suspicious of Berg for his father's political views and that it was a simple case of mistaken identity.  And speaking of mistaken identity: the suspected murderer of Nicholas Berg is Abu Musab al-Zarqawi, a militant linked to al-Qaida.  A  urlLink recent NY Times article  indicates that the CIA believes with "high probability" that the killer on the videotape was indeed al-Zarqawi, despite a number of rather blatant discrepancies on the videotape: such as (a) al-Zarqawi is reported to have lost a leg in a bombing, yet the tape shows no limp from a prosthetic; (b) al-Zarqawi's appearance is widely recognized around the globe (with photos of him circulating on a WANTED ad in which the US government offers a $10 million reward) and is therefore not tending to mask himself in public appearances; (c) the murderer's accent is arguably NOT from the same region of Jordan as that from which al-Zarqawi hails.  Now, why should I be suspicious of the CIA's allegations against al-Zarqawi?  Why would the US come to that conclusion if it were faulty?  Consider the following: the reasoning for war in Iraq included (a) allegations of WMDs (which don't exist) and (b) Iraq's ties to al-Qaida (which, UNTIL NOW, don't exist).  Pinning this heinous crime on al-Zarqawi (an al-Qaida operative) and placing him in Iraq suggests for the first time that there is a link between al-Qaida and Iraq, and therefore justifies the War in Iraq, for the first time.  All of a sudden, then, it starts looking like a sunny day in Washington with al-Zarqawi's prints on this murder.  Now, from all this, where do I stand?  I'm officially unsure about who murdered Nicholas Berg and why, and why it was videotaped and sent out as a political statement as repercussion for American transgressions at Abu Ghraib.  I'm thoroughly unconvinced that it is as black-and-white as the CIA is purporting.  Furthermore, I'm leery of anything that inspires as much emotion and ire in the American psyche as an American being brutally beheaded on video; rash conclusions run rampant with such intense emotions.  I'm also suspicious to the Nth degree of any governmental institution offering stringent conclusions in the face of gaping shadows of doubt.  I'm also increasingly suspicious of the Administration.  I'm still looking for the truth behind it all, and it's safe to say I would not be surprised by any actual truths that may come out.  Add  urlLink this  to the mix: "Berg's body arrived Wednesday at Dover Air Force Base in Delaware. His parents had requested permission to be at the base when the coffin arrived, but that request was denied. Sen. Arlen Specter, R-Pennsylvania, said Thursday that refusal came from the Department of Defense."  Strange to deny parents their God-given right to see their son's body.
     


    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm generally someone who sleeps very little for a multitude of reasons, but I'm adding this tidbit because it's different this time.    I'm afraid to sleep.  The basic reason behind this is because of the video I watch today for my  urlLink Where Is Your Rage article .  Let me make something decidely clear:    DISCLAIMER: Do NOT watch the video!!!!    I'm sure I'll be fine for those that feel that's of interest, but let me tell you, I'm affected, and it's not something I will pass on to anybody I know.  I say to watch the video for the purpose of the argument, knowing that most of you will be intelligent enough not to proceed down that road.  Just trust that it's   not   something to see, and that I'm among many people (including most journalists) who recommend not watching it and wished they had never seen it.  And for me especially, had never heard it.  
     


    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The contrasting viewpoint on Grife's article,  urlLink The Horror...The Horror .  Remember the SAT?  Morals are to war as oil is to water.  We, as a country, walk on a very slippery slope at this point in time.  With the mistreatment of prisoners, according to the Geneva Convention delineated rules of war, the public cries out about how inhumane we are being.  Guess what?  I don’t blame anyone.  If I saw my friend’s head blown off right next to me, and managed to capture that guy and had a few minutes in a room with him, humiliation would probably be light treatment.  Typically, sleep deprivation is used by psy-ops in order to learn information from prisoners, and that’s considered within the bounds of the Geneva Convention.  I’ve had some friends that have gone to serve, and they’ve definitely changed.  Life over there is not easy, and the public outrage is beginning to bring up memories of Vietnam.  Remember what our public did to Vietnam vets?  They were spit upon, yelled at, and denounced, all by the country who raised them.  I don’t condone the actions of these troops, because what they did was depraved and a perverted, and probably unnecessary, despite claims of psy-ops orders coming down, but I don’t blame them either.  I’m not over there, wondering if I’ll see my family again, under constant anxiety of bombings, shootings, and various other attacks.  Under that much stress, people are prone to do things to relieve pressure, and they’re not always pretty.  In Vietnam, some soldiers were known to cut off an ear from each kill and put them on a necklace.  Depraved in regular society, sure, but when you’re out in the jungle, it doesn’t seem so strange.    What’s really the problem is the media hype, which led to a “retaliation” execution.  These 5 executioners are animals.  Pure, unadulterated animals.  It’s been hours now since I downloaded and watched this video, and I’m still nauseous.  Watch the video, you can get it from Kazaa, Limewire, or another p2p, but watch it only if you have the stomach.  It isn’t Hollywood, it isn’t photo editing, that’s a real person.  His name was Nick Berg.  He was 26 years old, a civilian, and lived in Philly.  And don’t think they just guillotine him either.  He’s beheaded, and slowly, with a machete.  They start on the side of his neck and don’t chop, but carve through, and the screams actually made me physically recoil…  I’ll leave it at that, because the description is grotesque and inappropriate.  I wish that I had never even seen it, because I don’t know if I can ever forget.  This is like concentration camps; it’s so bad you almost can’t believe it’s real… you don’t  want  to believe it’s real.  To the people who sit and criticize from their nice comfy leather chairs I reiterate: morals are to war as oil is to water.  How do you fight an enemy who lacks courage, dignity and morality?  A faction with no discernable trace, these people float like shadows and stab into backs.  We have to hit hard, and sometimes morals take a backseat to the goals.  It’s sad, it’s wrong, and it’s not something that should be publicized with tabloid-like zeal.  I used to think that the war against “evil” was a really lame line, but I’m a convert.  I believe we  are  fighting evil.  I never thought I could see a human be truly demonic… I was wrong.  I’m sorry Mr. Berg.  And to the leather chair types, I have but only one thing left to say:   Where is your rage?    Watch that video, and tell me how you truly feel.
     


    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's disturbing, to say the least, that the world is watching right now as  urlLink photos  and videos of our troops and commanders humiliating, sodomizing and torturing prisoners in captivity leak out.  The repercussions of this incredible travesty may very well echo out for untold lengths of time, as these indelible images (of "American inhumanity") burn into the psyche of detractors of American foreign policy around the globe.  Just yesterday, the boldest repercussion was made manifest, as a group claiming to have ties to al-Qaida beheaded a Philadelphian man on video and sent it up on a militant Islamic website.  The savage murderers attributed their actions explicitly to the abuses in Iraq now being publicized.  Disturbingly graphic stills from the video just appeared on an the Drudge Report  urlLink website  today.  What's disturbing even further today is that there are actually people in the American government who look at the many photos circulating now (proof of torture and humiliation by American troops against peoples we are told we are liberating) and don't see anything reprehensible about it.  United States Senator James Inhofe, a Republican from Oklahoma, is  urlLink "outraged by the outrage"  flying about in papers these days.  He claims that a great majority of these prisoners "have American blood on their hands" and so deserve no special care from their captors and questioners and, in fact, are being justifiably punished.  Rush Limbaugh even goes so far as to compare the abuses to  urlLink "fraternity hazing."   Well, firstly, it certainly violates the  urlLink Geneva Convention  to inflict harm of any inhumane nature (including, of course, torture) on any persons, even insurgents, who have been placed out of combat by detention or injury.  Yes, this means that it is illegal, by internationally recognized mandate, to do what these pictures show American troops doing. And secondly, strapping a college kid to a tree by wrapping him head-to-toe in  urlLink saran wrap , while humiliating, I'm sure, is kind of a whole load of fun while drunk, as compared with being stripped naked and having vicious barking dogs unleashed to your nether regions.  People line up for hazing rites like those saran wrap antics, not for having legs devoured by dogs.  There's also a  urlLink report  going around that 70 to 90 percent of Iraqi captives were erroneously arrested.  You do the math, folks.  That means that most of the men depicted in these pictures were, according to the Red Cross crew and their authoritative, authentic report, innocent Iraqis mistakenly arrested and held captive, for sometimes months, and subjected to untold lengths of depraved maltreatment.  The question now stands: what do we do now?  It seems to me that, if the latest  urlLink conclusions  are true--that the abuses were delegated from high-up commanders--then this is only further proof that the planning for this war was and still is just atrociously, reprehensibly faulty, and that the Secretary of Defense should get on  his  knees and beg for a wiser international coalition to come and save this situation before even greater repercussions bear their fruit.
     


    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
          Sun Microsystems is working on a 3D version of Linux called  urlLink Project Looking Glass  (you can see picture examples  urlLink here  if you’re too lazy to read).  I’ve been hoping for something like this for awhile.  Windows might finally have legitmate competition from Linux, and this might even persuade me to throw my copy of XP out the window (snare -> crash).      urlLink Update:   100 bar and restaurant owners gathered a week ago to pool the $10,000 retainer needed to hire an attorney to fight the  urlLink Connecticut smoking ban:    Bar owners claim they are losing as much as 60 percent of their business as smokers flock to establishments where they can light up.    urlLink Casinos and private establishments  are exempt, however.  Big Brother… but(t) out.  You know, there’s a VFW one town over and the casinos are about an hour away…. Perhaps it’s time for a change of venue.       urlLink $50 million in back royalties  are being paid back to artists in back royalties.     Some of the leading record and music companies have agreed to payout almost $50 million in unpaid royalties to thousands of musicians under a settlement agreement. The royalties were not paid because the record companies supposedly lost contact with the artist and were unable to disburse payments. Artists that were shortchanged include big names like Sean Combs, Gloria Estefan, Dolly Parton and David Bowie.    You have GOT to be kidding me.  This may be a rant in the making for another post.    Dentists, beware: You can use your own stem cells to  urlLink regrow your own teeth.   Healthier, and all natural instead of implants or dentures, they grow at a normal rate and are actual teeth.  Cool!  And guess what country has discovered this….    The chief executive of CVS called for the  urlLink legalization of imported prescription drugs.  It’s about time.  With competition from imports, the pharmaceutical industry will actually have to cut it’s exorbitant prices.   Google is going public, but they’re doing it a little different (of course).  With their clout, they can actually hold a  urlLink Dutch auction.   How this will pan out is really up in the air, but it definitely is an interesting idea.  Note, however, that are keeping control of the company by  urlLink having two tiers of stocks, retaining controlling interest.     
     


    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I remember this old joke, if that's one would call it, that brings an introverted chuckle out of me whenever it pops into my brain.    LOST: Dog with three legs, blind in right eye, half a tail, and recently castrated.  Answers to the name Lucky.  I often think of that in hard times, because it keeps me grounded.  That poor bastard, can't even find his way home and has everything against him, yet there are people out there that care enough to look and miss him.  It's one of those half heart-breaking, half funny jokes that you giggle about when they come up.  This is brought to mind because I just found out today that I'm a pall bearer at my Aunt Eve's ceremonies.  About a week and a half ago, I dislocated my left shoulder doing something stupid (not really sure how).  It wasn't horrible, since it's happened before and it's loose and it's used to being out, but it's weak and mildly uncomfortable until it pops itself in properly.  That happened about two days ago, and now I have full motion back without the pain.  It just won't hold much weight.  I keep asking everyone to put me on the right side of the casket.  I'll probably even ask the caterers who will look at me like the troglodyte that I am.  I just have this horrible image of being on the left and my shoulder totally poping out, the casket falling open....  Just bad imagery.    I booked my flight from Florida back to Connecticut for tomorrow.  A one way flight this close to departing time requires a donation of blood, an appendage, and a piece of your soul, but there's no way I'm going to miss paying my last respects.  I also figure that my family is going to need a shoulder to lean on (that was way to punny), especially my mom.  Years ago, before I left for college, I had a friend die.  The reason isn't really relevant, but he was a guy I became friends with as he started to clean up his life.  It just happened that he fell back one night, and it ended his life.  The horrible part is that I had been there to support him and his sister the year before when his father passed away.  In about a year, they lost a father and a brother, leaving behind the mother and daughter.  It was a cruel, cruel twist of fate.  I just did what I could to make his sister smile.  I didn't really have anything else to give her.  These tangential stories do coalesce, however.  I'm strangely unaffected by death.  The process of struggle makes me cringe a lot more than someone actually passing.  Perhaps that makes me look like a truly apathetic, sterile person, but that's not the case.  I'll miss the people in my life that I have lost, without a doubt, but I also know that the time I spent with them was great and the best I could manage.  I don't regret, because I tend to think that just having them in my life was a blessing, and that they choose (on some level) the proper time for them to go.  I'll always love my aunt, but perhaps she's in a better place now.  Many people think that my attitude is unnatural, and some have stated jealousy in my management of my emotions.  What they don't realize is that things tend to hit me later, after all of the comforting and consoling of others, the rush and the stress.  I sit down and then my mind has time to chew on it.  That's when it hits me, and I cope with it just like anyone else, in my own way.  I've matured enough over the years to know how I handle things, and how I need help.  With the things that have happened lately, I'm a lot less afraid to reach out a hand and acknowledge to everyone and myself that I can't always do it on my own.  Even if that means I have to pay $300 an hour to someone just to rant and talk as non-linearly as this post has proven to be.   
     


    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The whole idea (superstition) that bad things happen in threes is beginning to take on a whole new meaning as of late.   I don't mean to levy a whole bunch of melancholy on the masses, but for some reason, collecting my thoughts in front of the keyboard on daily basis is a wonderful form of catharsis for me lately. And because of the amount of stuff that is shifting its way upon my shoulders as of late, I need more release than a jog, a workout, and a few self-involved friends to lean upon.   Today, I decided to take some time to rest and workout because my shoulder slipped out yesterday and I needed to workout to keep the muscles strong. At one point when everything slows down, it might pay to see the doc and find out what's happening with my shoulder, but I don't envision that happening any time soon.   I woke up late (slept until 1 p.m.) to my cell ringing right next to my head. Rolling over to find who awoke my ridiculuous slumber, I found out it was my mother calling. She called back right away. Usually my mother's pretty relaxed about everything, so immediately I woke up thinking I had done something wrong and was about to get chewed out. Granted, it wasn't rational thinking, but when one is half asleep, rationality is pretty much last on the list of thought processes.   So I get up to have a cig in order to clear my mind and get myself on track for what I imagine to be a lecture. Mom calls again. Now this truly is odd, so I pick up to find out what's going on. She was definitely upset, and my stomach dropped. She then proceeds to tell me about my aunt, but first, let me give you a little backstory.   My aunt on my Mom's side, who we shall call Eve, was that really cool aunt who broke all the rules when I was a kid just to see me smile. Unfortunately, she suffered from some thyroid problems that caused her to have big emotional swings. Regardless, she always put me on a pedestal and treated me like gold, and as a kid, the swings were something I was aware of but never judged. She was dating a guy the whole family disliked, even I as a child, and somewhere along the line, she wound up "falling" out of a third story window onto concrete below, and became physically and mentally impaired. She couldn't really walk, and she regressed slightly, but she still had a lot of spirit, but was entered into a nursing home.   So Mom basically calls and says that my Aunt Linda choked on a piece of food, aspiriated, and had resperatory failure, and that she was going to the E.R. to find out what was happening.   Long story short, my aunt had no oxygen for 30 minutes, was totally unresponsive to anything, and had nothing left in her eyes. They signed a DNR, and she died at around 10 pm.   I'm sitting here, outside, under a tin roof garage in Florida, listening to the hypnotic syncopation of the raindrops and wondering what is coming next. My Grandmother being really sick, my aunt just passing, and my shoulder falling out don't equate as the three bad things. I'm hoping that I'm seriously downplaying my shoulder and that this is the end of the three. I also now realize that I will probably have to fly twice in a week, which you all can gather from  urlLink my previous flying article  is not something I look forward to, nor that I enjoy. I'm thinking of looking for someone who does hypnosis down here quickly so that I can be strong for the family members that will need it for the next couple of weeks.   The benefit of all this, if I can convince myself of that terminology, is that my viewpoints and fears are changing. I'm growing up in an environment that is unavoidably complex and enlightening. I've realized that many of my petty fears and insecurities are so mundane and trivial, and that they either need to or are changing.   I don't want to be totally alone.   I want to die peacefully and quickly, whenever the time arrises.   I want to make the most of my life.   I want to love and be loved.   I want people to smile whenever they think about me.   I want to live, and live well.   
     


    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The ignorance of people never ceases to amaze me.  I was at the hospital yesterday because my Grandmother is in ICU.  Security at this hospital is remarkably lax, to the point of absurdity.  I think I've actually seen a security guard maybe three times in the few days I've been there.  Anyway, so my father and I are sitting in the ICU waiting room, which, when others are in there, tends to be a little bit heavy and sometimes morbid.  People in there are usually nervous, melancholy, and generally reserved.  That was, up until yesterday.  A family walked in that had a member in ICU.  Keep in mind, I usually would welcome a little bit of life and smiles in this situation, but this came nowhere near that kind of warmth.  Literally, I think 12 people came in for one individual, and they varied from 60 to 6.  They were loud, obnoxious, inconsiderate, and their conduct was unbecoming for the decorum of the waiting room.  I heard a mother comment, REALLY loud about her daughter like she wasn't there, "God, she looks great.  She lost so much weight she almost isn't fat anymore."  The children are running around like rabid animals, screaming and yelling without any semblance of concern from the parents.  I think they were tazmanian devils dressed in the disguised of children.  I wondered if I could explain that to the police in a rational matter later if need be.  Two older women walk into the waiting room with heaviness on their shoulders.  There are easily enough seats in the waiting room as it was my father and I, and empty chair, and the family taking up the rest of the place.  Four kids were sitting in seats, and  not one of them was told or asked to move by their parents.   When I was younger, if I did that, I would've gotten my head chewed off by one of my parents.  These parents just didn't give a flying __________.  One lady sits in the empty seat, the other stands.  I'm finishing up a pizza because we had an opportunity to eat which is something I generally seize at a given moment.  Finally, my father and I got up so the other woman could sit.  We left, before I really lost my mind, and I suppose I should be thankful for that.  Time passes, and we return.  The status of the waiting room has not changed.  These people are not only obese and aggravating, they're  still being loud.   The craziest part is the fact that it was DURING ICU visiting hours, so they could easily have gone in to visit.  I was tired and borderline furious.  I was figuring I could take out at least three of the men in a fury while keeping the children at bay.  Such unchecked ignorance needs to be hammered down, and I was ready to split wigs.  If the parents couldn't teach respect, maybe the children would learn from the fall of the parent.  Instead, I chose to be diplomatic and tell the ICU receptionist about the situation in as friendly a voice as I could muster.  She seemed at a loss for words, but I figured she'd call security to quiet them down.    I never saw it happen.  I left in the nick of time.  The funiest part is, the hospital has signs all over that say, "Quiet please.  Healing in progress."  I love that sign.  I actually dreamt last night of walking into the room with that sign and saying, "Is anyone here literate enough to read what this says, and could you please read it aloud?"  Then I started to beat some heads in.  I guess it pays to be non-violent most of the time.  I figured at least if I were gonna lose my head and get into a fight, we'd both be in the perfect place to recouperate.  I mean, it is a hospital.  I also figured that if they were there to visit someone in ICU, I could just put them in a bed.  It's a good thing I dream.  I might be blogging from jail.   Note: I'm not typically violent.  I like flowers and bunnies and big smiles.  But sometimes I just need to vent. 
     


    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I was reading a post at  urlLink Leese's blog about airports  and the emotional reaction and her childhood redux:   To me, airports represent two kinds of emotions: joy and sadness. I get happy whenever I pick someone up from the airport. I get really sad whenever I have to drop someone off at the airport.   It's a really insightful and well thought explained story.  On my side of things, airports have never really had that much of a profound effect on me, but I have been affected. I used to fly relatively frequently to see my grandparents in Florida.  It was usually once a year or so, up until the end of high school and when my parents split up (these weren't completely concurrent).    A side note: this is why my posting has been later than usual for my three faithful readers.  I'm down here now because my grandmother is very sick and in the hospital.  Today was actually the first day she was able to speak for any period of time.  She's an 89 year old spit-fire and the most unbelievably "tough old broad" (her words exactly tonite).  In fact, she's probably one of the toughest people I know across the board.  I'm pretty proud to say I have a little bit of her blood in me.  Anyway, over time and a decent amount of bad flights, which are easily attributable to my mantra of Murphy's Law (is it sewn onto my forehead?), I began to develop a few misgivings about Bernouli's theorem.  Read that as I began to turn into the four-grade-girl-who-just-saw-a-mouse-but-doesn't-want-to-scream when I fly.  So as I white knuckle my way into the sky, forget what moisture feels like in my throat, and locate my nearest exits and lovely white vomit bags, I always wonder, why am I flying?  This time I had a good reason and solid motivation, but generally that isn't always the case.  I just wish it wasn't so bad for me, because I actually like going places, and I like coming home.  I just don't want to take 5 years off my life from ridiculous anxiety.  I mean, really, what am I going to do if something goes badly, fly the plane?  Flap my arms?  Use my massive powers of telekinesis to deliver a multi-ton plane and its passengers to the ground?    For those that don't understand and think I  am  that little girl, I envy you.  In the meantime, I'll make sure to either run up the airport bar tab, or see if my doc will allow me a few tranquilizers to see the world.  Either way, bottoms up!
     


    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Good Afternoon, folks.  My compadre started up a little list last week, and now I'm'a bring my own, of things that just make me a wee bit flabbergasted and awestruck.    1.  It's one thing to create a motorcycle with a solid reputation for craftsmanship and beauty.  It's a completely different thing to make  urlLink an impeccable paper-craft rendering  of the motorcycle.  Now, That's love!  2. We've all had hangovers before.  I had a hangover two weeks ago and actually wrote a brief, slightly curdled piece that was up here for a day or two before I stripped it, realizing that it was just plain dumb to highlight my own momentary stupidity and toxicity.  I'm hungover today.  In fact, I may bring that point into play in points 4, 7, 9 and 14 below, but you'll see for yourself on that count.  In the meantime, take a gander at  urlLink this summary of a hangover study , which basically gives yet another reason why women have the short end of the stick, ... so to speak.  3. Why something like the  urlLink State of the Commons organization  isn't getting more press is beyond me.  I mean, I normally hang to the left, as you probably know, but this website just seems like a mesh of universal truths that only a dolt could deny.  I mean, it says we're all richer than our wildest dreams!  4. I'm getting paid with full benefits to sit here and do JACK FUCKING SHIT!  I mean, I don't mind getting a check for warming this seat and browsing the internet, and sending a vague smell of last night's liquors out across cubicles here every couple of minutes, but I mean, REALLY.  When there's nothing going on at work, shouldn't they just send a mu'fucka home!! Can't he just go HOME and go to BED!  5. Here I am, still.  Doing the same thing.  Yes.  And I feel so full of self-pity, I even went to  urlLink this website  to make my queasy belly turn again.  6. In honor of having seen Stephen Wright perform last night in Stamford, CT.... Here's a website (named  urlLink The Dullest Web Site in the World ) I can imagine Mr. Wright reading this with unbearable depths of enthusiasm.  7. Why  urlLink this dude's stories about working at Barnes & Noble  isn't on prime fucking time TV is way way WAY beyond me.  It's absolutely brilliant.  It almost makes me wanna work there just so I can have the misery that inspires that genius.  But not really.  Enjoy this one.  8. And why'n't I have  urlLink an Uncle like this ?  With wise words like this?: "When it comes time to pick out that first tattoo, remember: it doesn’t matter how much you like that one comic book. There’s always a chance that eight years later someone will make a movie of it that stars Sylvester Stallone. And you’ll be fucked."  And this: "Burt Reynolds? Nope. Tom Selleck? Uh uh. Try Chile D. Molester. Shave that fucking mustache."  9. For more on  urlLink Stephen Wright's witty little quiplets ....  A couple of my personal favorites: (a) If "con" is the opposite of "pro," then what is the opposite of progress? (b) Why do you press harder on a remote-control when you know the battery's dead? (c) If a cow laughed, would milk come out her nose?
     


    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
         How is it that I’m single for quite a few years now, and I’m still giving out relationship advice that people heed and consider knowledgeable?  Wouldn’t it be more effective if, you know, I applied it to myself effectively?   How is it that I can actually look at my watch three times before I actually remember the time, and when somebody asks me what time it is, I have to look again? (Would the really George Carlin please stand up?)   How does an MP3 player have a 16 hour battery life while my laptop has a 3 ½ hour battery life?  MP3 players are probably 1/20th the size of a laptop… make a better battery.   Why does Connecticut  NOT  allow the sale of alcohol on Sundays?  Does it make a big difference?  Does one actually have to  plan ahead  for Superbowl Sunday in order to relax while Janet Jackson has a “wardrobe malfunction?"   Why do people forget to use turn signals on the highway?  Is it really hard to push down the little lever?   Why is it when you call for customer service, and press 1 for English, do you get someone who sounds like you pressed 5 for the pig Latin dialectic of Mandarin Chinese?   How is it that Japan has a high-speed cell phone network, yet I can’t get service in my living room?   Why is it that I can buy a product that will tightly seal food in a bag, but I can’t find a pair of shoes out of 50 that will fit?   Why do they still build shower heads at the five foot mark?  There is nothing more frustrating than trying to take a shower while practicing my limbo at the same time.  In the morning when I’m showering, the last thing I want or am really capable of is an exercise of stamina and strength.   And why do I always use that tiny little bit of the soap bar?  It’s impossible to use that effectively.  I might as well just use a quarter to try to wash.  And it’s always when you’re IN the shower that you realize you need to get another bar of soap.  Of course, why would I want to get out and use my nice dry towel or drip all over the floor to get a new bar?  It’s much better to spend triple the time to try to get clean…    
     


    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A fun little poll for some people.&nbsp; I had to exclude some just because I can't name everyone.&nbsp; Enjoy.   For the ladies:  Who would you kiss (romance), who would you sleep with (carnal), and who would you throw off a cliff (self explanatory)?              I'd do one about the girls, but I don't want to offend.  The guys will take it humorously, or I can remove you if you ask.  This should get me in a LOT of trouble.      
     


    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I got this email awhile back, but I decided it's totally post-worthy.&nbsp; I have no idea who authored it, but it sure wasn't me.     Police are warning all men who frequent clubs, parties and local pubs to be alert and stay cautious when offered a drink from any woman.   Many females use a date rape drug on the market called "Beer" to target unsuspecting men. The drug is generally found in liquid form and is now available almost anywhere. It comes in bottles, cans, from taps, and in large "kegs." Beer is used by female sexual predators at parties and bars to persuade their male victims to go home and have sex with them.   Typically, a woman needs only to persuade a guy to consume a few units of Beer and then simply ask him home for no strings attached sex. Men are rendered helpless against this approach. After several beers, men will often succumb to desires to perform sexual acts on horrific looking women to whom they would never normally be attracted.   After drinking Beer men often awaken with only hazy memories of exactly what happened to them the night before, often with just a vague feeling that: "something bad" occurred.   At other times these unfortunate men are swindled out of their life's savings, in a familiar scam known as "A Relationship." It has been reported that in extreme cases, the female may even be shrewd enough to entrap the unsuspecting male into a longer-term form of servitude and punishment referred to as "Marriage."   Apparently, men are much more susceptible to this scam after beer is administered and sex is offered by the predatory females.   Please forward this warning to every male you know. If you fall victim to this insidious Beer and the predatory women administering it, there are male support groups with venues in every town where you can discuss the details of your shocking encounter in an open and frank manner with similarly affected, like-minded guys. For the support group nearest you, just look up "Golf Courses" in the yellow pages.     
     


    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My buddy and his wife came over today, and they brought their little pup.&nbsp; Yellow lab, so small, she was playing with my two puppies and even took a dip in the pool.&nbsp; She's a gutsy one, that Sasha.   After awhile, she began shivering, so we wrapped her up in a towel, and my friend's wife was holding her.&nbsp; I asked if she minded if I did it for awhile, and she happily obliged.   There's nothing more precious than holding something young that you adore.&nbsp; I lounged in the sun for awhile, trying to console a shivering cold 5 lb. puppy.&nbsp; It was wonderful.&nbsp; I decided to re-wrap her in something dry, took her inside, lay down&nbsp;on the couch and watched a movie, with her wrapped up and on my chest.&nbsp; Body heat worked well, and she finally stopped shivering and slept deeply.&nbsp; I wish I had a picture, but couldn't find my camera.&nbsp; It felt so good.   It's funny how sometimes the things we all need most come in small packages, and are often the things we avoid with great tenacity.&nbsp; It was so nice to let something close that was fragile and precious.&nbsp; It reminds me of what is underneath all of the defenses and walls within.   What a great day.  
     


    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I went to Super Stop and Shop today to return copious amounts of cans.&nbsp; For those of you who aren't aware, in CT, you pay five cents per can as a deposit, and if you return them, you receive that money back.&nbsp; So I horde a whole bunch and bring my garbage bags in to return 'em at the big grocery store.   In there, I met an old man.&nbsp; He was wearing a Connecticut Post baseball hat (one of the local newspapers), a worn-down shirt, plaid shorts, tan sneakers and black socks.&nbsp; He looked like a guy who might've been homeless, but had too nice a watch on.   I offered him the machine for bottles because he only had a few and I had a lot.&nbsp; I figured I'd save the old man a long wait.&nbsp; He was surprised by my trivial attempt at chivalry, graciously accepted, and hurried his way through his bottles.&nbsp; I explained to him how the machine worked because it's a little temperamental, and I had a system down by now.   After he had finished with his bottles and I began my process, he says, "Excuse me sir, may I ask you a question?"   Well, if you're gonna call me sir, you sure can.   "Sure," I said, trying to size him up as I'm shoving bottles into a mechanical monster's mouth.&nbsp; He appeared a little off, something that isn't tangible, but noticeable if you're prone to notice those things.   "When you drink, do you get depressed?"   Here's where my mind began to go haywire.&nbsp; I'm processing if he is homeless, a reporter trying to get information without identifying a source, homosexual, etc.&nbsp; Finally, I decided to just give it straight and let him give me the answers.   "When I was your age, I could drink a lot and it wasn't anything.&nbsp; See, booze affects a part of your brain that has all of your energy.&nbsp; When you're young, you have lots to give up, but as you get older, it starts to affect you differently."   I nodded my head in a totally inexperienced, naive-appearing encouragement.&nbsp; Is this guy preaching to me in the bottle return store?   "See, I'm 60 now, and I even notice a difference from when I was 40.&nbsp; The other day, I had a few drinks, and all of a sudden I was thinking of all these ways to hurt myself.&nbsp; That had never happened to me before.&nbsp; That's what depression is, when you want to hurt yourself.&nbsp; It's funny."   Normally, I feed into these discussions.&nbsp; Weird people approach me all the time, looking for answers.&nbsp; It's not something I think about.&nbsp; When I'm in NYC, my friends always have to slow down because every homeless person is asking me about life, or some weird, abstract idea they have.&nbsp; Sometimes it's aggravating, but generally I make a point of trying to steer some of them somewhere better.&nbsp; You'd be surprised how fast I can understand someone on a level that's pretty high.&nbsp; I've had people talk nonsense to me, and yet I totally get where they're coming from.&nbsp; It's a curse.   This time, however, I didn't do anything.&nbsp; I just turned around and dumped science on a guy who may have been asking for help.   "Well, yeah, alcohol is a Central Nervous System depressant.&nbsp; As you age, your metabolic rate decreases and your ability to mentally and physically tolerate foreign substances decreases because your CNS isn't as strong" (yes, that's a quote).   "Oh, so I just explained something to you that you already knew," he says, and turns around and leaves.   All of sudden, I can feel something go click.&nbsp; It's not something I can really explain, but it's like a piece of my inner-self goes - click-&nbsp; and I know I did something wrong.&nbsp; For lack of a better explanation, it's a metaphysical cut where someone is seeking a tether that you cut off.&nbsp; It's like a sinking boat and a guy throws you a line that you just toss right back at him.&nbsp; It sucks.   I blew it off and went back to my car to drop off the boxes before I went in to get my money.&nbsp; He walks by me again in the parking lot and says, "Don't get depressed!"&nbsp; I laugh, and keep walking.&nbsp;   - click -&nbsp;   My mind is processing all of these things that I don't care to explain, but I realized that in my selfishness and as a defense mechanism, I just blew off a human being.&nbsp; Guilt rushes in and I have to shut off feeling for awhile.&nbsp; I go in, get my loot and a lottery scratch-off for giggles, and head back out.&nbsp; As I'm walking out the door, I see this 30 something year old guy yelling at one of the old ladies working there.   "But my wife  TOLD  me there was a sale," as his face was turning red.&nbsp; I laughed, and thought it was weird to see two people in a few minutes that were total opposites.&nbsp; One who threw out a line and was rejected, and one who holds so tight onto it, he won't let go.   This is the kind of stuff I feel bad about for days.   Oh, I made $26.40 which means that I returned 528 cans and bottles.&nbsp; Man, am I thirsty.  
     


    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have numerous friends in relationships nowadays.&nbsp; In fact, when I go out, I’m often the third or fifth wheel, which makes it necessary for me to be decently secure in the fact that I’m not a leper and don’t repel relationships.&nbsp; But being in this position causes some great annoyances sometimes, and I’ve outlined a plan, a proposal if you will, to deal with this minor dilemma.&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;  Relationships should be EXACTLY like signing up for a cell phone plan.&nbsp; Here’s why:  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  1)  Plans should have a minute limit.   &nbsp;  Unlimited nights and weekends are available, but the cost is so prohibitive that no one would or should sign up for it.&nbsp; You must schedule, in a given month, how many minutes you will use.&nbsp; If you pick too much, you’re wasting, and if you pick too few, you have to pay hefty overage charges.  &nbsp;   Translation:  Be relatively consistent about the time you spend with your significant other.&nbsp; If you’re not, you’ll cramp the other person and your friends will learn to hate you for being unreliable, inconsistent, and stupid.&nbsp; There are exceptions to this rule, but they are infrequent.&nbsp; Co-dependence does NOT count.  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  2)  Please have consideration for others when using your service in public.   &nbsp;  Everyone gets extremely aggravated when people are yelling into their cell phone when they’re commuting, in a restaurant, or other quiet place.&nbsp; Keep it down!  &nbsp;   Translation:  If you’re in a good relationship, that’s great.&nbsp; I don’t need to see you rubbing and tonguing each other with reckless abandon, however.&nbsp; Everyone is guilty of this at some juncture, but try to keep it to less than an absolutely disturbing and traumatizing event for those whose conversation you are interrupting.  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  3)  You may only sign up with one carrier.   &nbsp;  You cannot have one phone and multiple providers, though mergers like AT&amp;T and Cingular are changing that.  &nbsp;   Translation:  However, if you find yourself signing up with a plan that has two “carriers” for greater coverage, God bless you and please let me know how you pulled that off.  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  4)  Your service is a privilege and you should not abuse it.   &nbsp;  Remember to occasionally take breaks from using your cell phone so you can appreciate it when you want it or need it.&nbsp; You’ll be more satisfied in the balance and also less likely to run over your minutes.  &nbsp;   Translation:  If you’re reclusive in your relationship and it ends, or you wake up one day and realize that you don’t hang out with your friends anymore, don’t come crying to me about how you feel alone.&nbsp; You isolated yourself willingly, and now you have to work for abandoning the people that have stood by you for years.&nbsp; “But… but…” But nothing.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  5)  Helping friends find a provider will allot you extra minutes for that month and the next two as providers will overlap their service.   &nbsp;  As with many companies, bringing business their way is always beneficial and generally comes with some sort of reward package.  &nbsp;   Translation:  Hook a friend up with a friend!&nbsp; It pays, and creates situations for double dating, which is good for all and provides the ability for outlets and good times.&nbsp; It’s good business.&nbsp; It’s good networking.  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  6)  If you are having difficulties with your provider, please resolve the issue privately, quietly and with great discretion.   &nbsp;  Every customer services rep fears the screamer.  &nbsp;   Translation:  There are few things more uncomfortable than a couple fighting when you can’t say anything derogatory, funny, witty, helpful, or one-sided.&nbsp; Take a TV time out, socialize separately, and resolve your issues during your minute plan.&nbsp; Don’t waste my time and damage my eardrums.  &nbsp;  Also, don’t use this as an excuse to cling onto each other after resolving.&nbsp; You will too quickly lay down the foundation for the next argument.  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  7)  If you are planning to only have short term service, don’t pretend to sign up for long term service thinking you’ll get a better deal.   &nbsp;  There are services out there that are pay in advance.&nbsp; You don’t get all the fancy amenities, but it gives you the bottom line service.  &nbsp;   Translation: &nbsp; “Booty calls” are just that, then there are friends with benefits, and all of the steps prior to or in lieu of a relationship.&nbsp; Don’t be sneaky, just lay it out.&nbsp; It makes everything easier and everyone happier, and your reputation won’t get any worse than it already is.  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  8)  You may take a copy of this contract, but further insight will not be provided.   &nbsp;  Companies often like to make fools of their customers with small print, crafty language, and legal –speak.&nbsp; This document is easily more straightforward.  &nbsp;   Translation: &nbsp; If you’re an idiot and need this explained, please seek help elsewhere.&nbsp; You’re clearly still a developing Neanderthal and have yet to join the human race in language or in thought.&nbsp; If you don’t even know how to print this out, then perhaps you should consider donating yourself to science.&nbsp; You may be the missing link between chimpanzees and humans.  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  9)  Discretion about your provider’s technology and service is important.   &nbsp;  If you have great service, don’t brag too much because you’ll find that it will jinx your service or cause other customers to take away your bandwidth.  &nbsp;   Translation:  If you’re going to brag copiously about your significant other and they are female, I will either begin to rethink my current service or will miss having service at all and will start to actively pursue yours.&nbsp; Braggarts are like the dancing elderly idiot in the Great Adventure commercials: they either aggravate, scare, or entice a person, and sometimes a combination of the three.&nbsp; If you’re a female bragging about your man, you’re in even more serious trouble; think of sharks seeing blood in the water and you’ll get a Disney idea of what’s to come.  &nbsp;  10)  You cannot rely on other providers to cover areas that your provider does not.   &nbsp;  Each has it’s own technology, and there is no overlap.&nbsp; Also, each provider has its downfalls, so you must put some thought into picking which provider you choose to sign up with.&nbsp; You may find yourself unable to switch carriers down the line, or be charged a hefty cancellation fee.  &nbsp;   Translation:  If you’re dating someone, and yet you go to your friend of the opposite sex for consolation, advice, to bitch, etc., something is wrong.&nbsp; I’m not gay, you are not my hag, and I get absolutely no benefit from being your crutch so piss off and make your man deal with your shit.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  For guys, if you’re going to come to me and bitch for a really long time about how your relationship isn’t working, and yet you don’t take one step towards trying to mend or end it, I’m going to take that beer bottle I’m trying to enjoy at the bar and shove it down your throat.&nbsp; If you have the courtesy to buy me the beer, I’ll wait until the second bottle.    
     


    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Some of you may know that I love to debate on politics.&nbsp; Not argue, debate, but I was a little surprised about the answer to my  urlLink test results . Here we go:           According to your answers, your political philosophy is: libertarian    Libertarians support a great deal of liberty and freedom of choice in both personal and economic matters. They believe government's only purpose is to protect people from coercion and violence. They value individual responsibility, and they tolerate economic and social diversity.   &nbsp;
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
         >       Well, these are my girls.&nbsp; Raven is the black one on the left, and Shadow is the yellow one on the right.&nbsp; I took this today for everyone after the three of us had played frisbee for an hour or so.  &nbsp;  Fun little tidbit: The girls  love  to play frisbee/catch.&nbsp; Since Shadow is the older one, she tends to bully Raven a little when it comes to making catches or retrievals by land.&nbsp; However, I have a pool in the backyard, and Shadow has never gone in it.&nbsp; I got her from a pet store at 4 months, and I think that perhaps she had some trauma with a pool.&nbsp; She'll swim at the beach though.  &nbsp;  Raven, however, is a freak for the water.&nbsp; You would never guess it seeing her.&nbsp; She's very relaxed, and loves to cuddle up on the couch with me whenever she's allowed.&nbsp; But when something goes in the water, she  leaps  in after it.&nbsp; I'm talking she'll clear 10 feet of water before even hitting.&nbsp; It's amazing and really graceful.&nbsp; She then passes it to Shadow (whom I often call Shads) and Shadow brings it the rest of the way to me.&nbsp; One by land and one by sea.  &nbsp;  Recently, Raven suprised the hell out of me.&nbsp; I was teaching them both frisbee, which took all of 30 minutes, and started throwing it in the pool for Raven.&nbsp; Although this thing is made to float, it can sink a bit before it pops to the surface.&nbsp; I watched her pick her head up in the water, and dive down into the water.&nbsp; Her tail sticks out and actually goes under with her.&nbsp; She proceeds to  paddle down .&nbsp; Today she went under for a good 10 seconds before coming up with the thing.&nbsp; Didn't even choke.&nbsp; It boggles my mind.  &nbsp;  For those of you that don't know, dogs don't do this.&nbsp; They're pretty boyant, so it takes work to do that.&nbsp; But Raven is such a good swimmer I can hang onto her tail and she'll drag me from the deep end to the stairs, with no effort, and she's only a 80 lb. dog.  &nbsp;  Anyway, just thought I'd share.&nbsp; Sorry if I'm being a wee bit too proud, I can't help it. :)     
     


    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Sorry I've been negligent to all those out there that visit, I just had my three moment happen the other day, and all that's gone down has stepped in and made me very weary.&nbsp; A friend had a car wreck leaving my house, and I actually pulled her out of her car and rode in the ambulance.&nbsp; Doctors sent her home, only she had a tear in her small intestine that required surgery a few days later.&nbsp; Damn hospitals make too many mistakes.  &nbsp;   Anyway , in light of all of my heaviness I've been levying upon the masses lately, I figured I would share a fun little story that made me laugh the other day.&nbsp; A friend of mine, who actually lived at my crib for a month at one point, just got a Lab puppy.&nbsp; He's always wanted a dog, and after hanging with my two Labs over the years (I'll show a pic if anyone wants to see), who happen to be two of the coolest and greatest dogs  ever , he decided he was going to get one.  &nbsp;  A few days later I got a phone call from him, with the dawning realization that having a puppy is a bigger job than he had first anticipated.&nbsp; I laughed for about 10 minutes straight, trying to be nice initially, and then realizing that I was laughing harder because of it.&nbsp; I said to him, "When you first said you were getting a puppy, I just quietly said to myself ' He has no idea what he's getting into, no idea. ' "  &nbsp;  He got hysterical and began telling stories that only true dog lovers can appreciate.&nbsp; Throwing a ball across the room, and the dog running after it, tripping on her big puppy paws, and careening at a high velocity and using her head to stop herself on a table leg.&nbsp; Then he's on the phone, talking to Sasha (that's her name), asking her why she's digging so many holes in the yard and what that will accomplish.&nbsp; I said to him, "If you can actually rationalize and analyze a situation with your dog, you need to let me know right away."&nbsp; We laughed more on that too.&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;  Somebody once&nbsp;said that&nbsp;God made babies and puppies cute so you wouldn't kill them.&nbsp; I still remember when Raven,&nbsp;my younger&nbsp;one, was little and I&nbsp;took her to a friends house in my shirt&nbsp;pocket, with her little paws sticking out.&nbsp; She was really cute.&nbsp; Then I took her home and she peed all over my&nbsp;bed.&nbsp; Man, I love my dogs.  &nbsp;  Maybe this isn't the best post in the world, but I know a few people will have nostalgic smiles on their face reading this.&nbsp; There's nothing like raising a puppy, at least in my experience thus far.&nbsp; It may be a job, but the memories are incredible.  &nbsp;  Good times.&nbsp; 
     


    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Thanks for suggesting this  urlLink personality test , hoss.  Here are my results:  Wackiness: 68/100 Rationality: 44/100 Constructiveness: 74/100 Leadership: 68/100    You are a WECL--Wacky Emotional Constructive Leader. This makes you a people's advocate. You are passionate about your causes, with a good heart and good endeavors. Your personal fire is contagious, and others wish they could be as dedicated to their beliefs as you are.  Your dedication may cause you to miss the boat on life's more slight and trivial activities. You will feel no loss when skipping some inane mixer, but it can be frustrating to others to whom such things are important. While you find it difficult to see other points of view, it may be useful to act as if you do, and play along once in a while.  In any event, you have buckets of charisma and a natural skill for making people open up. Your greatest asset is an ability to make progress while keeping the peace. 
     


    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Seeing  urlLink Jay's post  about the results of his  urlLink personality test  led me to the same place to see how I panned out.  Interesting little quiz, and a good laugh.  Enjoy my results and let me know what you all got if you go there.    Wackiness: 46/100 Rationality: 40/100 Constructiveness: 46/100 Leadership: 64/100    You are an SEDL--Sober Emotional Destructive Leader. This makes you a dictator. You prefer to control situations, and lack of control makes you physically sick. You feel have responsibility for everyone's welfare, and that you will be blamed when things go wrong. Things do go wrong, and you take it harder than you should.  You rely on the validation and support of others, but you have a secret distrust for people and distaste for their habits and weaknesses that make you keep your distance from them. This makes you very difficult to be with romantically. Still, a level-headed peacemaker can keep you balanced.  Despite your fierce temper and general hot-bloodedness, you have a soft spot for animals and a surprising passion for the arts. Sometimes you would almost rather live by your wits in the wilderness somewhere, if you could bring your books and your sketchbook.  You also have a strange, undeniable sexiness to you. You may go insane.     LOL
     


    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, so I've made the girls list (in absolutely no particular order).  I had a whole set of criteria to make it democratic, and that generally held up, but I still had to make a choice or two.  If anyone wants off and another wants to be on in trade, then just post for removal and the next to comment after if they want in is in.  There were others I wish could've been included, but alas, I'm only allowed to give 9 choices.  I'm sorry I couldn't add those that aren't on there.  Other than that, let the chips fall where they may!  I'll call off the voting sometime next week and keep the results in hard print then.  Good luck ladies.                
     


    
</post>


</Blog>