<Blog>

<date>31,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This is the response I got from the grad studies coordinator from the McGill Political Science Dept. I held back until today to email them and ask when they'd make their decision for grad students. It took an incredible amount of will power on my part. I figured it was reasonable to wait until 2 months after the application deadline to start pestering the grad coordinator. Now it's taking everything in my will power to not email back and say "WHEN WERE THEY SENT????" Instead I sent back a short, perky and polite reply basically saying "Thank you for your quick response to my query." I've even threaten to starting coming into work at 7am so that I can leave by 2pm to be in time to get the mail.  Oh this is going to be a painful and highly distracted few days.... if it doesn't come by the weekend and I have to spend the entire weekend waiting then I think I might be forced to the bottle. 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So after that last post I went back and scanned the rest and all I do is bitch and whine. My life is not miserable. I could potentially be laying in a ditch somewhere after being thrown out the back of a half ton full of chicken or something. So here's my list of good things: - My apartment because it's a nice little sanctuary away from everything. - My family because they're hilarious...who knew I'd like going for beer with my mum and brother. - My friends because even though most of them are in the middle of crunch time with school they're still good enough to check in and see how things are going. - The fact that I'm reading a hilarious book and have another one on order. - The daffodils on my kitchen table that I bought on a whim because they were pretty. - Finally, that this post as allowed me to waste my last ten minutes or so of this interminable work day.  There are a ton more great things, but those are the few that came off the top of my head right now. I must admit I'm fairly uninspired at this particular moment and give that set back I didn't do badly. 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have no idea why people think Fridays are so fricking great anyway. You still have to work and you lack any motivation to do anything at work which then make the day go by a snail's pace. Yeah, it's the last day of the work week and yeah you can stay out late a kill a few more brain cells drinking, but most of the day is spent in utter torture because you know the end is in sight and it just won't come fast enough. Stupid Fridays.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Isn't it strange how things become an obsession? Seriously, I've been checking the online McGill application status constantly for weeks now. It never ever changes from "Ready for Review." I feel like phoning up the stupid admissions people and screaming at them "It's been ready for review for 2 whole fricking months!! Get your act together!" I think they do it just to torture us poor 'A type personalities' really - they sit there with all the applications, make their decision within a day and then go off and have a 2 month coffee break before they come back to tell the anxious applicants that they're simply sub-standard. I know there's nothing I can do about my application now, but I think that's what bugs me the most - the total lack of control that I have over the decision.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So lets add another nail in the coffin of my currently pathetic existence (notice the 'currently' - it's important because it means that I think that I can get back to being unpathetic). I'm literally falling apart at 23. Ever since I turned 23 a few weeks ago it's been one thing after another. Who the hell gets foot problems at 23?!?! Me apparently - I am in fact sitting here in my newly purchased granny shoes. Ok so maybe they aren't that bad - a little plain perhaps, but for someone who loves shoes, this is footwear death (but I must admit they are comfortable and definitely helping with the metatarsalgia - which is my new word this week by the way). So if it was just a case of a messed up foot then I would just brush it off, but no. I have battled 3 colds (took me awhile to figure out that it wasn't just one big cold because there were actually very brief periods of feeling better in between them). So yes, 3 colds and metatarsalgia - not bad. Now add the stupid ear infection in there and you've got my last three weeks. Last night was the straw that broke the proverbial camel's back though - 4 hours of coughing, despite the complete overdose of cough syrup, which eventually resulted in 2 hours of sleep.  So now I'm sitting here with my granny shoes, coughing, with a runny nose and squint tired eyes looking like the queen of the undead.... Oh it's gonna be a good one people! (p.s. eventually there'll be a happy post... eventually).
     

    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Welcome to post number one of my very first (and only!) blog. It kind of seems like I'm writing emails to myself - or rather to the rest of the world should the rest of the world care to read it.  I got in touch with someone with whom I sporadically touch base with last night. A vagabond of the finest variety who is always ready with witty repartee and an amusing tale of adventure. The latest one is his plan to hike the Pacific Crest Trail (http://www.pcta.org/) from start to finish. Now just ignoring the blisters, the potential loneliness, danger, and sheer hardship that 5 or 6 months of hiking would entail, it would seem like the adventure of a life time. Even just attempting it is admirable in my books.  I guess it just made me think of my mundane existence (current existence at least). I never wanted 9 to 5, but guess where I am? You got it - a 9 to 5 job (well 8:30 to 4:30, but who's keeping track anyway). It's like my brain is rotting in this semi-corporate concrete academic jungle and I've got to figure out an escape route before I settle into mediocrity.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Jesus, Mary and Joseph I think I'm in love with my accountant. Right now I'd bear his children if he asked me. Alan the accountant is a GOD. So I've never done my own taxes before and I thought that at 23 it's something that I should learn how to do. I decided to do a little trial run over the weekend to see if my accountant's number and my number matched. I came out with $1372.00 owing (It's a very long story as to how it got to that point) and I followed the instruction very carefully. Alan, bless his little bean counting soul, came out with $387.06. He then filed it for me.  I have decided that doing my taxes is one thing that I don't have to master. I am ALWAYS going to go to an accountant. 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I crawled out of bed this morning after being abruptly awoken by the newscaster informing me that a bomb had gone off in Riyadh this morning (I didn't realize that the CBC newscasters sounded so shrill at 6am). So I thought to myself "Self! Get your lazy ass out of bed!!" So being rather compliant that early in the morning, I did.  Made myself some breakfast and I still felt like crap. Sat in front of the morning news finishing my coffee and I felt like there were hundreds of munchkins not only having a party in my head, but in my stomach as well. This is when I started to think that since I had been to the gym twice this week that I could skip today - it wouldn't be a big issue. I could get into work early and make up time for the afternoon I'm going to miss on Friday to fly to lotusland. BUT, and I'm proud to say, GUILT PREVAILED!! Ok so I didn't do the full grueling 45 minutes of cardio (a combination of the bike and the punisher - commonly known as the cross-trainer). I only squeezed out 25 minutes on the bike, but that's not the point. The point is that despite not wanting to go and dealing with the partying munchkins, I still went and to be honest I feel very very well now. Pat on the back for me. Now to go and get an obscenely large coffee with copious amounts of sugar.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My family has the most bizarre approach to death. It generally involves drinking and laughing. No, we don't drink or laugh ourselves to death, although I have known a few relatives to do so, but we tend to think "well, they're gone and there's not too much you can do about it so you might as well have a drink, have a laugh, remember the good times and get on with your life." I personally think it's a healthy approach, but other's look at me strangely when I say things like "The family's going to the coast to plant the crispers. You can fit 6 to a plot!!! Cool hey?" (Translation: We're going to Saltspring Island to bury the cremated remains of my father, his mother (grandma taylor), nana (my mother's mother) and nana's husband (actually my step grandad, but I didn't know my real one so he's as good as they come)) We're even going to pour a bit of each one's favorite alcohol on the graves (dad=scotch, grandad=rum, grandma=gin and nana=sherry). No, my family is not full of alcoholics, we're English and Scottish - it's in our nature to drink. Ok now this part made me laugh pretty hard - my mother (a very cool British lady) suggested that since we were on Saltspring Island (the hippie capital of Canada) that we should smoke up at the burial too, that and she wants to shock her wet noodle brother (John) and his manipulative uptight wife (Brenda), who unfortunately are coming along with their slimy son Richard and his new girlfriend (entirely inappropriate to bring her).I nearly choked laughing. Not only that, but she suggested in front of my Auntie Sandi (not really my aunt, but I've known her forever), who also happens to be an ex-nun. Sandi laughed, mum grinned and I thought I had been transported to the twilight zone. So I'm flying down there Friday after work (yay - my sucker brother has to endure the 11 hour car ride) to do this thing. Taking a bit of a holiday while I'm at it (seriously can't wait for that). I never liked the idea of actually burying bodies, but this is ok with me. I can remember going to visit my great-grandparent's graves in England when I was 8 and should I decide to fornicate/breed/have children (your choice of word) then it would be kind of nice to take them to see their grandfather's and great grandparent's graves.  so yeah, my family looks at death in a very light hearted manner... 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yesterday - no make that Tuesday - I was sitting on the bus after having had dinner and drinks with   urlLink Sarah   and this guy I know from school, Chris Jones, came on the bus. Had a nice chat and he asked me if I had been accepted to McGill or not because I hadn't updated my blog for awhile. Kind of threw me for a loop. I didn't really think that anyone that I knew actually read this thing, but since Sarah had a link on her blog to mine I guess people actually followed it. Then I got curious and went to check on other blogs for other people I know and came across   urlLink Steve's   blog, who also referenced me (said I jumped on some sort of bandwagon or something... I didn't even know his existed until today). Maybe it shouldn't amuse me so much, but it does...  P.S. I haven't figured out how to make the bullet points go away - live with it.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It seems like life is moving too quickly this week. Well not too quickly for me - it's not moving fast enough, nor is it moving in the right direction. Earlier in the week an old friend from when I lived in France back in 1996/97 got in contact with me. I was incredibly happy because I hadn't heard from her in ages. She's now living in Paris with her fiance and her new baby girl Emelyne. Not that I want to be having children right now, but I'm entering that age where my friends are starting to get married and have kids. That started back in January when the first of my close friends got engaged. On a less monumental level I have a few friends who are in these 'adult relationships', making plans to eventually be engaged. So needless to say, given that I can't hold down a relationship with anyone for any extended period of time (not that I've been given much opportunity to do so recently), I would say that I'm not as 'advanced' in that department (at least by societal standards). However, that doesn't bother me much at all. Quite Negligible. On the other front though, I'm definitely more disturbed. The whole 'my life is going nowhere and I'm pathetic' self pity train came rolling into town yesterday. While sitting at my desk (which is only mine for the time being since I'm a lowly temp) folding pamphlets I had another friend explain how he was trying to get out of a business meeting taking place in Washington DC on Sunday so that he could drive up for Calgary and come to visit. Now, I started to justify it by saying to myself "Alex, you're the youngest of your friends. Quit fretting." BUT then I realized that this particular friend had already been in his high flying job for a number of months by the time he was my age. You add that to the crazy talent friends who are writing great historical novels, the friends bettering their minds (and lack of sleep tolerance) by furthering their education with a masters, among others who have their lives on track and what I'm doing seems rather mediocre. There is a silver lining. It's not that I'm sitting on my ass doing nothing about my life right now, it's that the decisions are out of my hands for the time being. Due mainly to the fact that I'm obsessive about planning (some might call it a control freak), this drives me nuts because there's not much I can do to further my goals. If I'm still in this state of limbo in a couple months I want someone to come an shoot me, but for the time being I think I can handle it.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So some of the torment is over. I got my  big fat rejection letter from McGill last week. I knew it was a rejection letter the minute I pulled it out of the mail box - it was far too light to be an acceptance. Apparently they had a staggering 500 applicants for the MA Political Science program and only took 30 students. That essentially means that I'm not in the top 6% ... not all that surprising really. Not surprising, but crushing nonetheless. So now I'm waiting to hear from the University of Western Ontario. I've already been told that I didn't make the first cut, but I am on their waiting list in case one of their first choices doesn't accept. I guess it's better than an all out rejection. Other than that my mood matches the weather: cold, dark, windy and wavering between rain and snow. I definitely should not be at work today and I most definitely should not be cold calling. That involves being perky and today is not the day for perky, especially with 3 hours of sleep.  The only thing I can tell myself is that it's bound to get better. I've been offered a job back at the University of Alberta, which unfortunately is at a lower pay than my current position. Now why wouldn't I just stay here? The experience at the new opportunity is better and this job is ending at the end of May. I'm also applying to various international internships, although, considering they shot me down last year I'm not holding my breath on those ones. The urge to go and sling beer in some exotic locale is incredibly strong today. Not quite as strong as crawling back into bed and just ignoring the world though. And both of those aren't as strong as the voice of reason telling me that if I don't work I don't get paid... if I don't get paid, I get evicted and then what will I do? So yes, I'm going to muddle through the last 4 1/2 hours of work and make a valiant effort to blast away the dark cloud hanging over me.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok so maybe it's not pundit valhalla, but still it's pretty cool. I sent an email to CBC Sunday after watching a segment on thier show this morning and they've asked me to come in and tape my response so that they can air it on the feedback section next Sunday.  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I can't stop following election coverage. I'm addicted. If there's no election coverage on TV, I switch to the net. I must admit that I'm thoroughly enjoying the rants of the boys over at  urlLink Points of Information , but I have to admit that I'm a little disappointed that no one has mentioned John Crosbie yet. I know he's all the way out on the Rock, but damn, if there was ever a colourful character in Canadian politics, he's it. He's been around for 28 years. I'm not even 28 years old. He's recently announced that he's seriously considering running in his riding of Avalon in Newfoundland and will be making a decision over the next few days. Now this is really something else considering how vehemently he opposed the merged conservative movement in Canada. I've just had a conversation with my mother about this in particular. Her company provided the interpretation services for the PC Conference held in Edmonton about 18 months ago and she recalls listening to Crosbie's comments regarding potentially running one conservative candidate in each riding across the country - this wasn't even a merger discussion and as my mother says "his comments were so blistering that the paint on the walls peeled." Apparently, he changed his mind a couple of months ago regarding Harper and his new party. He now finds Harper to be a rather moderate conservative. At any rate, his entry into the throng of things would make a contentious election that much more thrilling (yes, I just described elections as thrilling). Rex Murphy did a wonderful commentary on this development on tonight's The National, while it isn't posted yet,  urlLink here's  the website it will be on when it does get posted. At any rate some of the best Crosbie quotes are as follows:   It is better to be sincere in one language than to be a twit in two.  -(referring to his own monolingualism and Trudeau's biligualism), 1983   The problem with [fellow Newfoundland MLA Tom] Burgess was that his support could never be bought. At best, he could be rented, and perhaps only by the hour. -from  No Holds Barred: My Life in Politics , 1998   Just quiet down, baby. - Canadian justice minister John Crosbie to parliamentarian Sheila Copps in 1985.  At the time, Crosbie was responsible for laws respecting the equality of women. (now this one I don't necessarily 'approve' of, but heck it's funny and I'll be damned if Tequila Sheila can't hack it.)  There's plenty more of good ones...  No holds barred Mr.Crosbie, No holds barred.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      OK. Lesson number one for the boys at the gym early in the morning. DON'T ENCOURAGE THEM!!!! And by them I'm referring to the twinkies - think fluffy, cream-filled, nutritionally-handicapped desserts and then apply that to girls and you have twinkies. The girls who come to the gym in next to no clothes, a push-up bra, with an inch of make up on their face, play with the weight machines and giggle. Boys, if you encourage them by checking them out, or even worse, blatantly hitting on them, they will only come back. Don't reward bad behaviour. It's like if little Suzie or Bobby threw a demon-possessed temper tantrum in the grocery store and you said "oh that's ok sweetie, of course you can have the 4 lt tub of ice cream all to yourself." Now guys, I know what you're thinking - but I like eye candy at 7:30 in the morning! So here's a few reasons why it's not as good as it looks: 1. That inch of make-up is covering some hideous monster. I swear. If she's insecure enough to be wearing dark lipstick at the gym at 7am then trust me, what's underneath is not a pretty sight at all. Not to mention the fact that if she's that insecure it will only mean that she's lousy in bed - not exactly the uninhibited type. 2. She's wasting space. The reason why we're all in the gym at that time in the morning is because it's not busy then and we want to be able to use whatever machines we want when we want. When you have to wait for a machine because twinkie is sitting on it pretending to work out it only goes to piss you off. 3. Her body isn't that good and at the rate she's going it will never be that good. Now don't get me wrong. I don't actually think the boys in the gym are to blame for this phenomenon. I blame the twinkies. Get a fricking life!!! If you have to come to the gym in full make-up and no clothes to pick up men at the crack of dawn then you have some serious security issues. Go see a therapist or something, or, if you insist on showing up at the gym, at least come dressed appropriately. I'm not saying you have to look like a slob, but wearing a push up bra isn't acceptable (nor is it very good for support). So yeah, basically get yourself some self respect chiquita and boys, fight those urges, please...   
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Stupid internet. I was half way through a post and it crapped out. BLAH!!! Anyway, I'll re-write what I can. I'm rather sporadic about this blog and as such am going to cram multiple topics into this post.  Long Weekend  I spent much of the long weekend out at my mother's house in the country. We of course went for the mandatory Friday beers at the Faculty Club - drinking with old academics is actually quite amusing - but then we moved everything out to my mother's. On Saturday we had a barbeque. Ate too much, drank too much - the usual. The fun part is when we broke the music out, which oddly enough doesn't happen that much at my mum's shindigs, but Wendy, a friend of the family and yet another Brit, had a hankering for a little bit of Elgar and Pomp and Circumstance. That then turned into Holst's Jupiter and Mars from The Planets suite. It was rather amusing watching the old people get excited about it.  Then things went a totally different direction. On to some classic Canadiana. Now if any of you think that Stan Roger's  urlLink Northwest Passage  isn't anthem worthy you need your heads checked out because you're "smoking the dirty weed" as my Trinidadian Uncle Ruthvan would say (he's not really my uncle, I've just known him since I was an ankle biter) - just imagine that saying with a thick Caribbean accent. Anyway, it's an fantastic song - it actually gave me goosebumps. Now, since it's clear that we have no logic with regards to our music transitions and as long as you keep that in mind, you'll see that our move to Bob Dylan and then the Stones was totally natural. Bear in mind that we are getting progressively drunker as the evening goes on, so we end up dancing to Dylan and the Stones. Best part was when we'd ask Auntie Sandi if she knew the songs as we went along (I mean these are total classics like "The Times, They are a Changin'" and "Satisfaction") and after each one she would just grin and say "nope." She was actually in a convent for most of the 60s so any pop references from that time are totally lost on her - it's really quite sweet.  Anyway, after about another hour of that we ended with a final rendition of Northwest Passage and called it a night. Thoroughly drunk (minus the DDs) we respectively poured ourselves into our beds and cars.  Fantastic Saturday night if you ask me.   Elections Call  It's like Christmas. Seriously. I love elections. I'm not even sure why I love elections, I just do. Just ask a chocoholic why they love chocolate and they probably won't give you a very good answer, but they'll cry like a baby if you take it away from them. That's me with elections. Anyway, our current PM decided that June 28th will be the day when he strolled on over to the GG's house on Sunday morning to ask for parliament to be dissolved. Old news now I guess, but still exciting. Especially on Sunday. I spent much of the day recovering from Saturday night in front of the TV with copious amount of tea watching  urlLink Cross Country Checkup  with Rex Murphy since it was televised this particular Sunday (it's usually only on CBC Radio One). What cheesed me off is the fact that they didn't take a caller from Alberta until an hour and a half into the two hour program. And then they took a totally moronic idiot from Grande Cache that went on a homophobic rant about same sex marriage - way to dispel the stereotype about Albertans and Conservatives. I seriously cringe when I hear the socially conservative rants. Needless to say I started to dial frantically to make the point that we're not all like that, but it was too near the end of the show to actually get on.  At any rate, it's not so much the actual political parties that excite me. I love everything about elections - the debates, the controversies, the polling, but even more I love the actual elections machinery - voting days, polling stations, scrutineers. Everyone has their things - some like Russian literature, some collect insects, some pick their noses - I like elections.  So yes, that's enough rambling for now. For those that are interested I'm almost finished transcribing. I think it might actually be driving me insane. I have sudden urges to bash the transcribing machine, but have to refrain from doing so as I know (a) the replacement machine would come out of my paycheck and (b) it wouldn't change the fact that I still have to transcribe. I'm on the last focus group though - there is an light at the end of the transcribing hell tunnel.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So I'm sure some of you have heard this one before, but it's been expanded since having a discussion with  urlLink Colby .  To give you all a little bit of background, here's the letter that I wrote about this that was published in  urlLink the Edmonton Journal  back in mid to late December of 2003:   Dear Sirs,  The East need not fear. Western Alienation is alive and kicking. While watching the Global National report on the hiring practices of the federal government, whereby one must now be bilingual for the majority of federal jobs, the reality of Western Alienation hit close to home. According to the report, 71% of new hires in the federal government are Francophones. Taking this to its logical end, in order to work for the feds one must be bilingual and since the majority of bilingual people in the country are Francophones, it's normal that the vast majority of new hires are also Francophones. Unfortunately, this is not the case. As a 22 year old graduate from an honours political science program who wants to serve my country, one would assume that I would make an excellent civil service candidate if only I had bilingualism. But that's where the sadistic humour of it all comes into play. I am fully bilingual from having lived in France and studied in Quebec. It's not because most Westerners don't speak French, it's because we are from the West. Anyone who has used the Post Secondary Recruitment website or jobs.gc.ca, as I have been doing for the past 6 months, would know this. At least three quarters of the time when a job matches my profile on the website my hopes of even applying are crushed because in order to apply one must reside within particular postal codes, which are inevitably from Ontario or Quebec. So my advice to those of you new graduates out there who are qualified to the tee, bilingual and all, but live in the West: don't bother applying because you won't get far.  Cordially,   Alexandra Taylor.   *Please note that the nice people at the Journal edited it to take out all the grammatical blunders and superfluous use of language - this is the draft that I originally sent them.*  Now my argument in that regard hasn't changed very much, but Colby wrote an article that touched on bilingualism and another one of his readers wrote to him explaining that the costs of maintaining bilingualism in the federal government are astronomical, pointing out things like glass ceilings for unilingual managers and how computer virus alerts are delayed by several hours as they are translated into French before dissemination. Of course at this hour of the morning I didn't quite put two and two together - I just nodded and said that the man has a good point. Then Colby pointed out the following: "They're connected in the sense that, if the policy doesn't provide any meaningful incentives for the creation of a bilingual citizenry (which is your quarrel), it can't possibly be worth the costs (which is his). Was it meant merely to reward the already-bilingual and their descendants?" So yes, my distaste for my wasted French education grows daily. I'm not saying that bilingualism is a bad thing. I like that I live in a bilingual country and I really like speaking French, I just wish that it was actually of some use to me in terms of government.  
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      That or somebody help me out and shoot me for my own sake. I just can't handle garbled audio tapes of old people talking gibberish on a Monday morning. I'm so frustrated I'm about ready to throw this stupid transcribing machine out the window... if I had a window that is. So a rather uneventful weekend. I actually got highspeed internet at home. Yes, I know, I was living in the stone age. Well actually, I was getting dial-up for free by hooking up to the service my mother uses at work, so if I didn't have to pay for it and if it didn't bug me then why bother getting a cable connection? Shaw offered a two month trail period thingy with free installation and whatnot so I took it. It's not a bad thing really. I still instinctively go and check phone messages when I get off the net, but other than that it's pretty much the same, but faster. I actually made the effort to go to the gym on Saturday - usually I would only go weekday mornings, but I thought that I would make use of the car and go Saturday morning too since I had no big plans. My quads are still screaming in agony at me. They literally seized up while doing squats and I don't think that they've unseized. I keep trying the whole "work it off" method, hence the cardio at the gym this morning, but every time I get to the bottom of a staircase I seriously cringe. I look like I'm an octogenarian when I walk - it's pathetic. Apart from the quads though I had that wonderfully satisfying day after ache everywhere else which slowly dissipated. I also ended up renting a pathetic excuse for a French comedy on Saturday as well. I was feeling the need to see a French film and "Va Savoir", which had been highly acclaimed, had been staring at me from the foreign film section at Rogers for a number of months so I finally rented it. Bad move. Usually like French comedies. They're dry. They're witty. There's always a certain sense of bon vivant in most of them. This one was just weird and totally irritating. It got the hack 20 minutes into it. So add that up with a complete reorganization of my closet (perfectly colour coded and culled for spring - yes, I'm weird), my usual Sunday morning news shows, reading the paper, a massive grocery shop at Superstore (AKA the 3rd World Market), some cleaning, some cooking and picking my mum up at the airport last night and you have my totally uneventful weekend. And I liked it dammit. I've had too many eventful weekends in my adult life not to enjoy the mundane ones. 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey - so I've been fooling around on this thing again. I think that this template is much more appealing so yay me. If you made comments on previous posts, unfortunately they're gone :( I've opted to use the comment function on Blogger as opposed to an external one. Feel free to re-comment on anything!! (In fact, do it so I don't look like such a fricking loser). 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, so quite honestly I don't come from a white trash family - they're far too damn British to be white trash. Heck, I don't even think that they could be considered the British version of white trash despite the fact that my mother is from Manchester. But, I did grow up in small town Alberta, generally considered to be the epitome of white trash.  Now since starting university, no take that back to high school when I refuse to go to any of the schools out in the country and insisted on driving into the city, I have essentially been citified. I live in my little apartment with every convenience within blocks of me, coffee shops on every corner, bars within stumbling distance, etc.  Since I had the yuppie mobile last night I thought "self, make use of the damn thing." So while looking at my laundry hamper and determining that it was decidely ratty, I thought that I should go and buy a new one. Being the multitasker that I like to think that I am I also thought I'd get my mum's birthday present (a pedometer) at the same time. Now where on god's green earth can you get a laundry hamper and a pedometer in the same location? You got it - Wal-Mart. Usually I avoid this bastion of white trash at all costs. It tends to scare me. Well, no, not scare, but disturb me. I was feeling adventurous and perhaps a little kooky last night, so off I went. I walked through the doors and my senses were assaulted with white trashness - the harsh blue pinnies that the checkout people and greeters have to wear, the faint sound of country music in the background, the unusually large woman in spandex with a kid propped up on her hip shoving me out of the way and the unmistakable smell of McDonald's fries wafting from the heart attack special restaurant that is conveniently located in every Wal-Mart. Trudging along the aisle, focused on the task at hand I found myself humming along to Randy Travis' "Forever and Ever, Amen" and it stopped me dead in my tracks. I knew all the words to the damn song and I hadn't actually heard it in years. I was immediately transported back to grade 8 in the school gym two-stepping to that song with John Wasyluka because along with square dancing, line dancing and the polka, it was a mandatory part of the gym curriculum. For some reason that just made me grin. So I just carried on looking for the things I wanted, but now I wasn't nearly as uptight or antsy about being in white trash heaven. You can take the girl away from the white trash, but you can't take the white trash out of the girl. I think I'm the only one of my friends that I know who can ride a horse bareback, who learnt how to drive manual on a tractor (not in some cushy AMA car), who can toss bales like it's nobody's business, who didn't have cable TV until she was 21 and who has been known to shot-gun a few beers in her time.  So yeah, I like my life now. I like the comforts of living in the city. I like that I can get up at 8 and make it to work by 8:30 if I have to. I like that my workouts are in a gym and not a farmyard. But in the end it's nice to take a little trip down memory lane.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So I got a little distracted from listening to old dears talk about walking to school in 10 ft of snow, up hill both ways, shoeless and added a few things to my blog - first of all there's a few more blogs of note.  urlLink Steve Smith  updates his at least daily and quite often more with a variety of topics (a very nice time waster - no offence intended).  urlLink Duncan  is the newly elected VP Student Life of the U of A Students' Union - generally a rather amusing fellow.  urlLink Colby  is a columnist for the National Post who generally has an incredibly wide variety of rants on subjects ranging from the CBC to post-modern hockey trophies. Finally  urlLink Four Bad Men  is a new blog that I expect to be nothing but fricking hilarious from having seen the antics of a few members of their illustrious foursome. I recommend all of them if you're just dicking around at your computer trying to waste time
     

    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So the new job isn't too bad. And by that I mean the people are nice, the hours are flexible, I love that I can walk to work and for some odd reason my gym pass still works here at the university. And by that I don't mean that the subject matter is terribly interesting. I mean I'm sure gerontology is fascinating for some - they actually have real live students studying this stuff, but frankly I find it bores me. Yup, I'm appropriately bored stiff. I'm going to give it the benefit of the doubt though. I think I'm bored because right now I'm transcribing audio cassettes of focus groups, which is more frustrating than anything else because I wasn't there to observe the focus group, but I know I like researching, looking up articles, getting lost in the library, etc. so I think once I plug through the focus group tapes I'll be home free. Apparently the National Post has a whole segment on what's wrong with the CBC on a regular basis. This is what I learnt from my mother, ironically and avid CBC Radio listener and National Post reader, on the way to the airport over my lunch hour (she's jetting off to the west coast to visit friends for the weekend and that usually means I get the yuppie mobile, aka the subaru). She said that they pointed out that the CBC refers to groups such as Hezbollah and Hamas as "activists." Now, I recognize that these groups in particular aren't exactly your dope smoking peaceniks and that calling them merely activists is very misleading, but at the same time it's not as though the National Post is going to one day start labeling any of the IDF's actions as terrorist. It's all in perception and how critical you are when you hear/read the news. I'm not saying that everything that the IDF does is terrorist, nor am I saying that every single Palestinian who supports Hezbollah or Hamas is a terrorist; however actions of individuals and groups of individuals within those organizations are without a doubt terrorist in nature. But of course no one actually gets to that point of the argument. Of course I get shut down as soon as I make the point about the National Post and it would seem that there's very little I can do to avoid that no matter how hard I try. And trust me, I've tried. Five years in a poli sci degree in which three were spent studying exactly this particular issue doesn't make me an expert, but I would like to think that it makes me slightly more informed than the average person, no matter how intelligent they are (such as my mother). However, I must admit, most of the time I'm very grateful for coming from a rather pro-Israeli British family and having a number of pro-Israeli Jewish friends and having studied under a rather pro-Palestinian Pakistani - it makes it much easier to see both sides even if people are too quick to label you one or the other. If you've made it to the bottom of this disorienting and rambling post, my hat off to you my friend... 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Quitting smoking isn't nearly as painful as I thought it would be. It was pretty bad over the weekend (I started on Saturday morning), but all in all the work week has been just fine. I've been having about a nicorette a day as opposed to the wad I had shoved in my mouth over the weekend. Now I know it's not this easy for everyone, but I wasn't really a hardcore smoker when I decided to quit. On average (i.e. you take the weeks where I smoked 20 a day and the weeks where I smoked 1 a day) I probably consumed about 4-5 cigarettes a day over the course of about a year and a half. The main problem with quitting being this easy is that it makes me want to start again knowing that it is just that simple to quit - kind of warped and pathetic logic, but I tell ya, those after dinner cigarettes are to die for... 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So I got the research assistant job at the U of A. My new worksite for the next 4 months is in the Human Ecology Building at the ass-end of know where on campus working for the Reseach on Ageing Policies and Practices Project. It's ended up that I'm getting paid the same amount as I am currently doing accounting work, but this stuff is more up my alley (reading, researching, writing, etc.). I start that come Monday morning. My boss has been very very good about it all considering I've given her 3 days notice. On top of all of that she's organized a lunch for me on Friday - I've only been here 3.5 months and I'm honestly only a temp, so all things considered, that's very sweet. I have to admit, I won't miss the work here at all. It's fine if we're really busy and there's a million and one things to do, but for the past few weeks it's been slow and I can't stand being bored. I will miss the people though - they're all very funny and relaxed. It makes for a great work environment and I'll be sad to leave them.  However, I've always been one for new adventures and I've never even thought about doing research on old people, so bring on the geriatrics.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Usually when I open my mail box there's nothing but junk mail, bills and stuff from the bank that I never ever open (I actually have a big pile of bank stuff on my side table).  Today was different - there was a Canada Post Parcel Notice. I never ever get parcels. It also stated that I would have to pay $12 to get the parcel. With my curiosity piqued I wandered off to the post office trying to figure out what it possibly could be. Of course by the time I got there I was convinced that UWO was going to make me pay $12 to be rejected because that would be par for the course.  I asked to see the parcel before accepting it and it was from France... actually Paris to be specific. Unless UWO has relocated, my theory was shot. I paid the money, which incidentally was for customs, and tore into it. Inside I found a beautifully wrapped bottle of Guerlain perfume with a note saying "A surprise from Paris, thank you for all of your help - Michel." Now ask me if I know anyone, absolutely anyone, called Michel?? Nope. Spent the whole walk home wracking my brain. The two people I know that live in Paris are both girls and definitely don't have spare money to be buying perfume. Did I have some strange, out-of-body experience where I 'helped' some guy named Michel? Then the paranoid freak started kicking in - what if it's really poison that will seep into my skin and kill me slowly as a revenge for some wrong that I committed?  I figured it out in the end after phoning my mother. A month ago I did a charity translation for the French Funeral Association and they contacted my mother to get my address since the translation was through her agency. This was their way of saying thanks. Let me tell you, I definitely don't think that my translations are worth a bottle of expensive perfume, but I'll take it. Only in France would you send perfume for translating a funeral association website...  At least I'll smell prettier than the dead people. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So my vacation started out last Friday with a terribly sprained ankle. It was a fricking balloon by the time that I got on my flight at 5pm. Try lugging a suitcase and sports bag around with a messed up ankle, which incidentally took 6 or 7 days too heal. But, even a sprained ankle couldn't quash my good mood, so I kept on trucking from the airport to the ferry terminal and eventually back to our summer home on Saltspring Island, BC.  As I've previously mentioned, the whole purpose of the trip was to bury the dead relatives in a plot in a wonderfully overgrown country cemetery on the island conveniently situated behind the cinema/community hall/pentecostal church on Sunday mornings. Now, I wasn't dreading that at all - they're just ashes. It's not like it's actually the person itself (Although I must admit the undignified cardboard box that houses nana could have at least been coloured pretty). Nope, I was dreading my nutcase relatives to whom I have no spoken in 5 years. Needless to say they were as nutty as ever (by they I mean my Aunt and her youngest son - my Uncle isn't too bad). What do you say to your Aunt who's "channeling messages" from your dead father over dinner? I just drank some more wine and had another cigarette and grinned. It's truly amusing when you're half ripped. Anyway, we all survived the nutty relatives in the end. My kid brother (all 6'3" of him) had me convinced that the strange smell I kept smelling in the house was really grandad (who incidentally died 5 years earlier). I kept saying "it's impossible" and he pointed out that it's exactly like his cologne. So I just wandered around saying "I smell dead people" and giggling to myself until I crossed paths with the incense that our Buddhist neighbours left for us on the sideboard. Yup, I can be totally and incredibly naive at times. I had the best of intentions when I left for lotusland. I thought to myself that I could go to the gym daily considering that I had no definite plans. How many times did I actually make it to the gym? A big fat zero. And I swear I must have eaten my weight in barbecued products and wine. Not to mention that I discovered that I make a killer cesar. Needless to say, despite only getting 4 hours of sleep last night, I still dragged my lazy (and probably 5 lbs heavier) ass out of bed this morning at 5:30am and hit the damn gym. Hmmm what else can I tell you about BC other than there was a lot of eating, drinking and lounging around on the balcony tanning, reading and staring at the ocean? Oh I did end up in Vancouver for a day (I seem to do that insane trip at least once each time I down there - 3 hours by boat there and 3 hours back - for some reason I still love ferry trips). I meant to go and have a wonderfully liquid lunch with my good friend Christopher (possibly the most charismatic and enigmatic man I have ever met). He even offered to fake sick to take the afternoon off work. I wrote down his cell number the night before in a slightly wine soaked haze and I wrote it down wrong. I couldn't figure out his work number and despite the fact that his father was at home, no one was answering the phone at his house. So I went downtown to my favorite tea store to pick up some lavender earl grey tea and then made my way back to the ferry with my favorite wannabe rockstar, Nicola. Like ships in the night Chris and I crossed paths. I phoned him that evening only to find out that he had made his way downtown as well. So here I am back at work. Budgets aren't too bad when you get to take a break from them. Of course I'm just trying to console my starving intelligence... 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So as some of you might recall for the past few months I had been lamenting my mundane existence. Then last week I got an offer for a funded MA position at U of Western Ontario. That was exciting, of course. I finally had my course planned out. And then tonight I get home and find an email in my inbox telling me that I have been short listed for an internship with NATO in the Public Diplomacy Division and they would like to know as soon as possible if I still wished to be considered for the position. Who was I kidding when I thought it would be an easy ride from here on in in terms of what I was going to do? I know I shouldn't complain, but now I have to make a tough decision because I really want both. Suggestions are, of course, always welcome. 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So that's one logistical and financial nightmare done and over with. My mother has offered to do a road trip with me to London, ON at the end of the summer so I can move some stuff down in the yuppie mobile. I think it's going to totally rock. Yay Mum!
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's the home stretch people. A mere 70 1/2 hours until elections get underway. The fact that I know that makes me kind of pathetic, but honestly, who the hell am I trying to impress around here? I've decided that my poll station staff should be very, very afraid. No, not because I have perhaps a little bit of a reputation for being an evil bitch around elections, I'm surprisingly sweet tempered this time round despite all my whining on this blog. Rather, they should be afraid because I actually haven't been trained as a Central Poll Supervisor, nor have I read my manual. To be frank, I actually don't know what the hell I'm doing come stupid o'clock in the morning on Monday. Although really, I do have 70 1/2 hours to teach myself, so you should all be fine. If you're voting at the Knox Met Church on Monday, be nice to me. And be nice to the poll station staff. They have to put up with my particular brand of insanity all day. In other news, I have no idea what's up with Western. I mean yes, I'm still going, although I'm not making any definite plans until I get the Faculty of Grad Studies letter. Let me explain. The letter I received last Friday was a letter from the Political Science Department saying that they were recommending me to the Faculty of Graduate Studies for a Master's with full funding. To me that says nothing is final until I hear from the Faculty of Graduate Studies. Yes, I know it's a rubber stamp case, but I don't want to jinx it. So I've been checking out potential places to live in London, Ontario throughout the week and trying to figure out how to move without giving up my first born child as payment. Heck, U Haul, at $2105.00 just for the smallest moving truck without mileage or insurance, would take all potential children. Anyway, I think I've decided to just not take anything but my books and clothes. Who needs all the Ikea furniture. So if anyone is interested, I've got a futon, a small couch, a lounging chair thingy, a lovely small dining room table with the most adorbale chairs among other things.  My next concern is the fact that my brain has been going to mush in my soul-sucking meaningless day jobs. I have a plan to re-educate myself over the summer. I haven't read one stupid article on the Middle East since I finished my undergrad and apparently I'm supposed to be well-versed in it. The lovely  urlLink Sarah Kelly  and I have made a commitment to have study nights. She on her editing contracts and me on various articles to help me determine what exactly I would like to write a thesis on.  Anyway, that's the update on my life. The elections office is dead since no one can vote or change thier address 6 days before the actual polling day, but nonetheless the astmosphere is still exciting. My research job is doing fine, despite being stuck transcribing again. However, I think my sanity has taken a vacation. 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So I got my acceptance letter to the University of Western Ontario in London, Ontario this Friday. Unfortunately, due to the fact that I worked a crap load this weekend, I haven't had much time to think about it. So, yay me, going to grad school. 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yes, I know, I suck monkey balls. I should post more, but you try finding time to post with two jobs and no sleep you insensitive bastards!!! And I sure as hell don't want to hear from you folks that only need something like 4 hours of rest - you're not normal.  Ok now, I've gotten my defensive apology out of the way, lets update you on my goings on. Still working both jobs. I'm on day 12 of working every single day and I've got to admit, I can't wait to have some time alone.   As a research monkey I've finally been given something a little more challenging than "here, listen to they awful, garbled tapes and then type them out exactly." Well, I'm actually still doing that, but there's a light on the horizon. It looks like as the token political science student my multiple task masters seem to think that I have some level of expertise in policy research. I keep half jokingly mentioning that some how I don't think that researching federal policies on social capital and aging well is all that related to terrorism in the Middle East, but a door prize to anyone who can make the connection. At any rate, the research should me more interesting than my tasks up until now. I think I might have moved up a rung in the research monkey hierarchy.  Now on to elections. The sheer level of utter incompetence is flabbergasting. I can't stand it. There's one computer in the office and despite the fact that the returning officer and assistant RO hardly ever use it, apparently it's not really for the rest of the office to use. Now, while making phone calls that's not an issue, but when I want to effectively organize the information recorded from the phone calls I'm unable to. All I keep telling myself is that this complete lack of technology will be effective training for when I eventually get around to elections monitoring in developing democracies because at the rate we're going in our returning office, I think it's comparable. I'm still working with a 40 year old, chain smoking idiot savant as my day time counter part. I'm job sharing with her and the thought of her messing up what I've carefully organized during my time in the evenings and weekends makes my blood boil. I've actually left explicit notes asking her not to touch my precious poll station organizational chart that took me more than a few hours to master, but apparently my notes aren't quite firm enough. Perhaps some physical reinforcement for my dull coworker would be appropriate - something like electric shock therapy every time she goes within 2 feet of the chart.  At any rate, I have discovered that working as a minion is frustrating because you can't do anything to change the system despite making suggestions and trying to do it yourself. Doddering old fools who have been doing this since before dirt was invent apparently aren't all that open to new ideas, despite the fact that they won't be around for the next battle. Once again, I'm harking back to the youth involvement thing. Can anyone think of how to rectify this? It's a catch-22. Youth aren't involved. So when youth get involved and try to inject a little bit of 'innovation' into the process they're shot down, so therefore, why should youth get involved?   Finally, as much as it may surprise some of you, I actually have maintained some sort of semi-normal semblance of a social life throughout all of this. I manage to have lunch with the lovely Ms Kelly and Ms Alexis on occasion, I'm apparently attending a BBQ tonight and a hack reunion tomorrow. And I have the yuppie mobile again, which is going to make all of this all that much easier.  So there you have it folks. My update. I promise to start writing much more topical pieces once I get my brain back in order again. 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's hard to think of something new to name each post!! But if anyone of you can guess where the lyrics are from you get a special bonus prize. They happen to be on the two CDs currently playing in my car.  A.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      For the past couple of days Ive been a bit run off my feet as you can probably tell from my last post. Ive been working as a recruiting officer in the Edmonton-Strathcona riding office for two days now and Ive got to admit that I really love the energy of elections, but I do have a few observations.  (1)The system is designed to exclude youth. Now, Im speaking very specifically about what Ive experienced in terms of recruiting poll station staff. The system is geared towards seniors generally. All of the training sessions are held during the day with only a totally of 4 training sessions out of about 20 held on a Saturday. Now thats not too bad if you just want to be a poll clerk or a deputy returning officer (poll clerk checks the voter off the list and the DRO gives them the ballot and then counts at the end of the day); however, if you want to work in any of the other positions  Registration Officer, Information Officer, or the one that Im going to be working as, Central Poll Supervisor, you not only have to be able to arrange to take Monday June 28th off work in order to help run the elections machinery, but you also have to take off an additional morning or afternoon to be trained to do so. Im thinking if I bribe my boss with cookies that I might be able to swing that.  (2)Along the same lines as the first point, youth arent really seen as key in the organizational process. You would think that given the hype surrounding the youth participation rates and given that both the returning officer and assistant returning officer of my riding are senior citizens who likely wont be running the show next election, that having the few young people there that actually are interested in the machinations would be a great blessing. But no, we are minions and nothing more than that. Dont get me wrong, they dont mistreat the youth (I should start up a charity for mistreated elections youth), but they dont bother to really involve them, no matter what kind of external experience or enthusiasm they have.  (3)There are a lot more people who are excited about being poll clerks that I thought. I thought that as soon as I said Hi, my name is Alex and Im phoning from Elections Canada that I would get a great big sigh or something else to that effect. Instead people are saying things like Oh wonderful! or I was waiting for your call any day now! It makes my job that much easier. I have to admit that by the end of a 4 hour shift my cheeks and jaw are aching because Im smiling so much on the phone (much of that is due to the fact that when I put on the perky phone voice I tend to instinctively smile).  Anyway, those are just my preliminary observations, so as my friend Mr Jones says, take it with a 1 kg box of salt because honestly I could just be talking out of my ass given my steady progression towards sleep deprivation. 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Have I mentioned that I'm superwoman? Seriously. Actually I've decided to petition the powers that be to make the planet spin slower so that we can have a 30 hour day instead of a 24 hour day.  I started my elections work last night. I am a "Recruiting Officer." So you call can now refer to me as Recruiting Officer Taylor, or Chief or Commodore (Commodora?) will do just fine. Ok, so my position isn't that important. I'm in charge of recruiting 450 odd poll clerks and DROs for the 200 odd polling stations at 47 location in Edmonton-Strathcona. It's actually just fun working in the elections office. This of course means that I'm working 11 to 12 hours a day and weekends too. No rest for the wicked I guess. My credit rating is going to like me for this though. The interesting thing will be to see if I can keep up the daily workouts with this insane work schedule.  Anyway, if any of my wonderful readership (the few of you that there are) happens to live in Edmonton-Strathcona and wants to work a poll station, get in touch with me. The pay is actually decent. 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, despite the fact that I didn't get to play with the real pundits, I did get my letter up on the  urlLink CBC Sunday  website.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I hate it when weekends aren't restful. Even though nothing I did was of great importance, I still didn't manage to sleep much. I went to see Harry Potter on Saturday. Good times. It was a well done film and I like how they adjusted the story to be more film friendly. Given the sheer size of the 5th book, they're going to have to start doing that anyway. Sunday was spent attending the broadcast of  urlLink Cross Country Checkup  at Edmonton City Hall. Hello hack central. There were hacks of all stripes in attendance, although honestly I don't think that any of them were there for the conservatives. At any rate it was an interesting show. The topic was 'what issues are important to the west in this campaign?' and they used the candidates from my riding, Edmonton-Strathcona, as their panel. I even asked a question, which I'm sure pleased my mother more than anybody else in the world. Incidentally she turned on the radio in Halifax just as I was asking what each of the candidates would do to rectify the either real or perceived sentiments of western alienation. Needless to say there was a "proud momma" message on my answering machine when I got home. I know that doesn't seem like a full weekend, but there were other things mixed in. Maybe I've just gotten too used to being lazy on weekend. I read  urlLink Janet's Blog  this morning when I got into work (I'm avoiding the dreaded transcription) and she has a post questioning if confidence is sexy. You see, I think most men pay lip service to the whole "I want a confident woman" deal. All of them say it and very few follow through with it. At least not in their early to mid 20s I'm finding. They want a confident woman as long as it doesn't challenge their confidence, intelligence, ambition, etc. Yes, that's a generalization, but for the most part it's true. As such, I am a firm believer in the whole "opposites attract" deal. The trick is to find someone with different talents than your own so you can equally be confident/ambitious/intelligent in your own ways. My approach is to do what makes me the happiest. If a guy comes a long and happens to fit into my little paradigm then yay for me. And before I get comments about being uncompromising and whatnot, I am willing to shift, but not totally overhaul the paradigm. Anyway, anyone's interested Janet's tirade is insightful. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So I'm taking the stupid hit count thing off this damn website. Every time I check it (around once a day or so) the little children's song "Nobody loves me, everybody hates me, guess I'll go eat worms..." goes through my head. So yes, frankly, I couldn't give a flying fuck if no one reads this - it's mainly a good place to rant. BLAH I say, BLAH!  Ok on to something slightly more interesting. In pursuit of my elections passion, in addition to being glued to the TV, I contacted the returning officer for Edmonton-Strathcona to see if there were potential employment opportunities above and beyond the usual poll clerk positions. Perhaps my standards are too exacting, but if you have to ask if you've reached the Edmonton-Strathcona Riding Office when you call, it tells me something is wrong. It would appear, based on a brief phone conversation and not much else, that the returning officer for my riding is on death's doorstep. Apart from being rather confused he didn't really seem to have it altogether (i.e. on a Friday evening when the phones were ringing off the hook and he was the only one there and not able to offer any substantial information, his response to my query regarding employment during the actual campaign period was - "I guess I could use a bit of help.") I'm guessing it's not that desperate since he hasn't called me back. So in my hunt to get some more electoral administration experience I'm going to ambush him this afternoon and thrust my resume at him. OK so perhaps it won't be quite that aggressivee, but you get the gist.  This is all in the pursuit of eventually being "qualified" enough to volunteer with an NGO to do elections monitoring and implementation. I was told that I'm too young and underqualified to work for room and board basically being a gopher for the older, more experienced elections monitors/administrators in developing democracies. This honestly cheesed me off a little bit since CANADEM is a Canadian NGO. As a Canadian NGO you would think that they would understand that it's next to impossible to gain electoral experience in Canada outside of an election period and as such there are going to be  very   few active, enthusiastic youth who would be "qualified" to be a glorified gopher.   My ranting isn't making much sense, so I'm going to wrap this one up. Do any of my 6 readers have any interest in elections work or am I the only one with that particular hankering? 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So apparently the program has been pre-empted. I guess I can't begrudge the veterans.    Hi Alexandra,  We have just determined our show will be pre-empted this week due to D-Day programming.  Thank you for agreeing to come on camera for us but we will not be able to accomodate this week.  Thanks again,  Regards  Allison Brachman CBC News: Sunday Feedback   Ah well, there goes my 40 seconds of punditry in a legitimate setting.   
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So the whole participating in the feedback segment of CBC Sunday is a little more nerve wracking than I thought. They said that I didn't have to read my email verbatim and could comment as I please. After re-reading the email, I don't think it would translate too well into TV segment. In fact, it would translate terribly. So now on top of figuring out what to wear so that I don't look like the Goodyear Blimp, I also have to figure out a coherent statement.  Anyway, if anyone's interested, not that anyone actually reads this blog, it looks like I'll be on the Feedback Segment of CBC Sunday on Sunday morning. I know it airs on the local channels at some time, but I only ever catch it on Newsworld from 9 to 10am. 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        From Timbuktu to Tijuana, you know all about world culture and politics. You've seen it all, and what you haven't seen, you watched on one of the "smart people channels." Your friends tell you that you should run for governor.What people love: You've always got a great story to tell.What people hate: You make them feel like ignorant plebians. Sometimes you slip and CALL them plebians.   urlLink  What Kind of Elitist Are You?    brought to you by   
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I love talking to people so far removed from my normal life that what you talk about usually has nothing at all to do with your every day going ons.  I don't know if anyone remembers, and if you do you're officially a loser, but my very first post was about a friend that was all about the amazing adventures. At the time he was on his way to start hiking the Pacific Crest Trail all the way from San Diego up to Chilliwack. I was jealous. Not of the hiking in particular - I'm more of a day hike kind of girl - but of the adventure. Of the free spiritedness of it all. Of the saying 'fuck it' to the whole world and doing something just because it's a challenge and it's something that intrigues you. At the time I was sitting in a poorly lit office dealing with morons who didn't know how to use excel and expected me to magically make their budgets balance. And I was bitter.  Anyway, this friend never did make it up the entire PCT. In fact he lasted a week (which is impressive nonetheless), but that's not really the point. The point is that he saw something and he, at the very least, tried it. In fact, he ended up in Lithuania some how and seemed to fill his life with a few more foreign adventures.  This time around I'm not so jealous. I mean, of course,&nbsp;yes, I am because I would love to just pack everything up and say 'fuck it' to the rest of you SOBs and head off to Lithuania or Istanbul or Cairo or where ever, but that's not me entirely. I mean I love doing that and have been known to do it once or twice, but the adventure isn't necessarily in the location.&nbsp; It's in the things you choose to do and the people you meet and the experiences that you allow yourself to be open to. It's not so much a specific location that I crave (although really, I wouldn't turn down Istanbul), but change. I can't stand being static and that's why the moving to London for grad school is as good as any backpacking trip right now.  Anyway, to that particular friend, despite his incredible flakiness, I say thanks.     
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So apparently the Rotary talk is a go. This makes me nervous. I mean I know that I know quite a bit about the Palestinian-Israeli conflict, but I never seem to know enough. I had this problem when I wrote my undergrad thesis as well. I researched and researched and researched and left the writing to the very last minute because I NEVER once felt ready to write. I mean once I got going everything was fine, but it was tortuous to actually get going. I only have 20 minutes to talk. How the heck do I cover the Palestinian perspective in that time? How do I do it so that I'm balanced? I think it's the questions that I'm going to get that make me even more nervous. I've already banned my mother from asking me questions, but there's still dozens of others that could throw hard hitters at me. Part of me thinks that if I can't do this, then how do I expect to be able to write a master's thesis and then defend it in front of a panel of profs.   Do you know what else I hate? I hate hearing something, formulating a wicked counter argument and then falling asleep ten minutes later only to forget what I heard or what I thought. I've been wracking my brain all morning trying to remember what I heard in the 4th lecture of the Gifford Lecture Series that Michael Ignatieff did at Edinbourgh last year. I was laying in bed last night listening to his lecture on the dangers of nihilism in terrorism/armed resistance/counter terrorist forces and it came to a point about the Palestinian-Israeli conflict for which I had a totally wicked counter point - then I passed out. Dammit. I've convinced my mother that we should buy the lecture series on CD and listen to them on the trip to London. Maybe I'll catch it then or maybe my brilliance is only present between the land of consciousness and the land of nod.   Since none of you other buggers seems to be updating your blogs other than Heather and Janet and since my life is so dull that I'm stealing ideas from others, I think I'll comment on the whole making lists about the perfect guy thing. Part of me has a rather definite one in my brain and part of me doesn't even want to make one because then if you have one you risk becoming closed off to anyone who doesn't match that list. Then again, if you don't have one then you get into a relationship, it's quite easy to make your list match their qualities rather than your own fundamental likes and dislikes. So, to prevent that, I try to keep my intangible list basic and it's split between things they cannot and can be. Most of it's based on experience, but some of it seems rather unattainable.   1. There cannot be any cheating  2. If you patronize me you get the boot.  3. If they don't respect me then why the hell do they bother?  4. The must have: intelligence, wit,&nbsp;a sense of adventure/humour/curiosity, kindness/compassion, ambition/drive.  5. They've got to love to travel.  6. They have to think I'm fricking amazing and that includes things like respecting my intelligence (gee, someone thinks highly of herself), my drive/ambitions and my inherent faults.  7. They must have a mind of their own. I shouldn't be able to manipulate them easily though I might try (yes, that's evil, but it's also part of the female nature).  8. I'd much prefer if they were taller than me, well groomed&nbsp;and at least average looking. Other than that, physically I don't really care, or rather I can't think of specifics. I know what I like when I see it.   But in the end, this list is pointless because I have met men like this in my life and it's blown my mind, but if there's no chemistry, there's no point.   Wow, doesn't this feel like a cheap wanted ad.   So yes, this is a random post. Deal with it. Comments would be appreciated. Very few people comment on my blog. It makes me sad.      
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ha - Only because I'm bored and want to waste time and&nbsp; urlLink Janet  did it...  According to  urlLink www.okcupid.com &nbsp;I am a:   The  Wild Rose  (Random Brutal Lover Dreamer).&nbsp;Colorful, but unpicked. You are The Wild Rose.&nbsp;Prone to bouts of cynicism, sarcasm, and thorns, you excite a certain kind of man. Hoping to gather you up, he flirts and winks and asks you out, ultimately professing his love. Then you make him bleed. Why? Because you're the rare, independent, self-sufficient kind of woman who does want love, but not from a weakling. &nbsp; &nbsp; You don't seem to take yourself too seriously, and that's refreshing. You aren't uptight; you don't over-plan. Romance-wise, sex isn't a top priority--a true relationship would be preferable. For your age, you haven't had a lot of bonafide love experience, though, and this kind of gets to core of the issue. You're very selective  &nbsp; The problem is them, not you, right? You have lofty standards that few measure up to. You're out there all right, but not to be picked up by just anyone. "You're never truly single as long as you have yourself."  Your exact opposite:The Dirty Little Secret  ALWAYS AVOID: The Bachelor  CONSIDER: The Vapor Trail.      
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So Mr. Martin has chosen his new cabinet. Frankly, I think the man is a disingenous prick. This is for two reason. First is when he started his campaign to be our newest dictoator, and by that I mean back before Jean resigned, he was hell bent on engaging and involving more women in the upper echelons of politics. A mere 8 of the 38 cabinet ministers chosen are women. Now for this I can't really fault him. Admittedly there are only 34 female Liberal MPs and perhaps the other 26 simply didn't have enough experience, weren't qualified, didn't pour thier coffee correctly&nbsp;or didn't kiss enough ass.  While the West didn't get shut out with a total of&nbsp;6 cabinet positions out of the 38, it's still fairly paltry when you consider that 3 of the 6 are from Greater Vancouver, which, while important, isn't exactly representative of "the West." Ralph Goodale is the only Liberal in Saskatchewan and at least in part was kept on for that reason. The news coverage over the weekend with Martin at a Stampede Pancake Breakfast was selectively truthful at best. For all his comments about including the West, he couldn't be bothered to host a general pancake breakfast to get some support for his paltry minority government out here, but rather he held a pancake breakfast for 2000 glad handing Liberal party sycophants. I'm sure that's going to do wonders to endear him to Westeners. This all goes to reaffirm my thoughts on the nature of Canadian politics and the (excuse me if I put it bluntly and crassly) cock blocking of the West.&nbsp; urlLink Chris Jones  over at POI also touches on this subject in his most recent post if anyone is interested&nbsp;(on a side note, his incorrect, I haven't move to the dark side yet, but will be in 5 weeks or so). Anyway, those are my preliminary and superficial thoughts on that matter so far. It's not a surprising cabinet composition, but it's still irritating.   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yay for the sunshine. Except for the part where I gave myself sunstroke from doing hard physical labour in the 33C heat. Stupid Alex.  Anyway, the weekend went well. I took a jaunt out to the country to help my mother out with a dinner she was hosting. Each year her Rotary club has a charity auction and my mother puts up a dinner for 10 to 12 people hosted at her house with alcohol included. Each year the there's a new theme and the stakes get higher.&nbsp; We've had Mexican, Greek and a riesstaffel (I know I spelt that totally wrong, but it's some kind of Indonesian dinner thing). This year is was Indian. As some of you might have gathered, my mother is a wonderful cook and she does especially well with curries and other Indian delicacies. Unfortunately, cooking curry in that kind of heat is a little bit insane. She also hired entertainers this year. A couple of fantastic Indian musicians who played the tabla (the hand drums for those who don't know), the sitar and the Indian flute. Amazing music, but if you listened carefully and hadn't drank too much, you could notice that every once in awhile they'd throw in a Western tune. Hey Jude, The tally man song and one that I'm sure Mr Smith would have enjoyed - Bridge over Troubled Waters, which incidentally was quite hauntingly beautiful on the Indian flute with the tabla accompaniment, were some of the selections. Anyway, the night was a success. I was wrangled into being a guest speaker at their Rotary meeting. They had a Zionist Jew come in a give a talk about Israel and Palestine and now they want me to come in an give the opposing view. Should be interesting. All the old people kept on drinking while I packed it in by 10 pm because I had the most ferocious headache. They called me a light weight. I felt mildly pathetic, but didn't care because my bed was so inviting.  All in all, it was a lovely weekend.&nbsp; I got a great tan, drank and ate good food.  On a side note, I'm officially into UWO now as I confirmed my acceptance on Friday. Upon the advice of Alexis, it would be inappropriate to leave and not have some kind of going away shindig. I'll keep my miniscule readership posted.  &nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Just a quickie here. I emailed the NATO guy on Monday politely telling him what an honour it's been to even be shortlisted for the position, but due to a late acceptance offer that I simply couldn't turn down that I'd be going to grad school in the fall and that hopefully this will only make me an even better applicant when I apply again next year. That and the usually blah, blah, blah stuff. On Tuesday I got this response back:  "Hi Alexandra,  I am very pleased for you, but do consider re-applying next year. Indeed, I did my last interview on Monday and had planned to call you today to offer you the internship. So, my loss!  Best wishes and stay in touch,  (Name Blanked Out)"  So that was lovely news.  It turns out the laptop purchase has now become a "congrats on getting into grad school" gift from my mother. My mum rocks. 49 minutes left. That's all that's left before I go and do some retail therapy with Alexis - we both are in desperate need of the endorphines that shopping seems to produce for both of us.  Other than that, my life is painfully boring. When I come up with something interesting to say, I'll let the three of you know...  A.   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's Friday afternoon again. Seriously, it's the worst time for me to work. I'm drained from the week and I absolutely lack any motivation to concentrate on what I'm supposed to be doing, hence, this post. So the interview with NATO guy went really really well. One of my best ones ever. It's a shame I'll be turning it down, but the more I think about it, the more convinced I am that it's the right decision. Still burns though. My reason knows all that draws me to it is a romanticized ideal of working at NATO. In reality it's unfeasible due to cost. $12000 is going to get me nowhere in Brussels for 6 months when I have to pay for my flight, insurance, etc. with all that too. Anyway, it was a nice idea while it lasted. Masters' plans are progressing quite nicely. I've booked my flight down there for the August long weekend so I can find a place to live. Because no flights go to London on a Saturday I'm profiting of landing in Toronto by spending the evening with a friend who I haven't seen in awhile. I'm actually really excited about finding a new apartment. I love moving. Ok, that's a bit of a lie, I love all the planning and stuff, but the actual moving part usually isn't so much fun.  It looks like I'll be well funded for this degree too. I mean not perfectly funded so that I don't have to take out any loans, but my tuition and about 65% of my living expenses are covered. Luckily I'm debt free so I can get a loan out and not have to be worried about adding it to some astronomical pre-existing debt. And by debt free, I mean totally debt free. I paid of the last $600 on my credit card yesterday. It looks like all that election work was good for something after all. I'm also planning on buying a laptop. Sarah and I are going to go laptop perusing on Sunday. I think I already found a damn good deal with Dell. It's an 'Insipiron 1150.' Sounds like some cheesy machine from the Jetson's or something. Being a total and utter technopeasant when it comes to these kind of things I asked around and I also got the specs for "Laptop Recommendations" from the UWO site. Anyway, the 'Inspiron 1150' (say it in a booming voice and it's funny) fits all the requirements. So for $1451.00 I get the laptop and a free ink jet printer. And that price includes GST and shipping. BUT being such a large purchase I'm a little wary, so that explains the foray to Best Buy, Future Shop, Compu Smart, or whatever other store tickles our fancy to compare prices. Any suggestions are most welcome. I started reading Michael Ignatieff's new book  urlLink The Lesser Evil . I haven't gotten that far into it (a couple pages before I dozed off last night), but I always find his writing most enjoyable to read. If I could write like that about the topics he does, I would be totally set in both the journalistic world and academia. It's a wonderful re-introduction to non-fiction in substantial amounts. I'll keep you updated on what's said. Well, the blog saved me again. I now have a mere 15 minutes left and in that time I think I will plan my research attack for the weekend. How nerdy. Then again, I never denied that I am just that nerdy. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Sleep is a beautiful thing. For the first time in weeks I have caught up on my sleep and you have no idea how happy that makes me. So now that I'm mildly coherent I'm going to do a rather large disorienting post.  Election's Wrap Up  17 hours of hell. That's what it was. I LOVE people who happen to have their voter information cards. It says directly on the front of them "Keep this card. It will give you quicker access to your polling station," so don't start bitching at me when I make you get in line to figure out where the hell your voting. Cranky voters suck and from what I understand, given the volume at our station and given the amazing abilities of my information officer and poll staff, we had the most efficient location in Edmonton-Strathcona, so if you don't like it, bite me. There's my rant about voters done.  On to scrutineers. If I ask you to do something perfectly reasonable, like, oh, let's say - DON'T GO BEHIND THE VOTING BOOTH!?!? Then maybe, just maybe you shouldn't be back talking to me, especially considering that I can so easily punt your ass out of there. Other than that and a few other minor incidents, the scrutineers were well behaved and well trained. Kudos to the parties on that front. Finally, Elections Canada really fell down in two areas. Training for poll station staff and voter registration. Now as a caveat before I rant about this one, those of us in the riding offices did the best we could given the resources and time we had. The revising agents worked like madmen and I can tell you for a fact the recruitment and training session lost their minds. BUT seriously - why the fuck wouldn't the manual include a comprehensive section on closing the polling station and counting??? Did buddy who wrote it just give up at the end!? It was beyond pathetic and at the end of a VERY long day you don't want to piss off the poll station staff even more by not telling them what to do. On the voter registration front, given that they knew and election was coming, why the hell didn't they advertise the mobile stations better considering that returning office was in the middle of no where? It's beyond me. All in all it was a definite learning experience. I take back what I said about the returning officer. He is old, but if you can still pull of an election with relatively few hitches, especially compared to some ridings at 80 years old, you deserve appreciation just for that alone. Not sure if I would give it another go any time really soon, but for some reason I think I'm addicted to elections.  My Normal Life  So I'm interviewing with NATO at 06:30 on Monday. I have yet to receive a formal acceptance letter from the Faculty of Graduate Studies at Western. I know it's a rubber stamp situation because the Poli Sci Dept doesn't recommend people without knowing the funding is there, but still, what if something freakish happens and the FGS doesn't send that letter? I'm going to need a fall back position. Hello NATO. I can't even remember what I put in my application. I hate phone interviews - they're no where near as effective as face to face. At any rate the position is as an assistant in the Public Diplomacy Division in Brussels with the Canadian Liasion Officer and damn I want to do it, but I know grad school is the smarter long term decision. Other than that life is finally normal again. I've started looking for places to live on the net in London. As soon as I get the formal letter I'm booking a flight down there over the August long weekend to find a place. I've printed off the course load for the MA in Poli Sci program and while it's intense, I know I can handle it. I've also taken out a few books from the library on various Middle East topics because I desperately need to brush up. So apart from staying in my PJs all day, I'm going to clean my apartment and get some reading done. Just the kind of Saturday I was looking forward to. A.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So I bought the 'Love, Actually' soundtrack and I adore it. Hence the title. The song keeps swirling around in my head and in my head I'm totally rocking out to it, just like I was driving in from the airport this morning. I think it's going to make the work day that much more pleasant. Anyway, I'm back from my jaunt down east. Oh the tales to tell. Saturday was a little surreal. I was meant to be staying with my friend Mark, who promptly took me to a party as soon as I got into town. Being the total and utter scatter brain that he is, he mentioned that we were going to the apartment of the sister of one of his friends with whom I once had a brief crush on ending in a very short and awkward coffee date during finals where after 20 minutes he shot up from the table and simply said "I have to go." And left. Mark blames it on exams, I had other ideas. Anyway, Mark, being the wonderful scatter brain that he is, failed to mention that awkward coffee date boy was going to be there too. Thank god for being good at faking it. I actually pulled off a very friendly greeting whilst shooting daggers at Mark with my eyes. He could have warned me dammit!! So I was over reacting, as per usual, but luckily my over reactions were all kept internal. Anyway, I won't go into details, but the evening ended up with me being separated from Mark and his girlfriend, ending up in some British mod club with awkward coffee date boy, his sister and her two friends, who in my mind were perhaps the most affected 22 year olds I have ever met. After the club apparently the beach was in order (I just wanted my bed at that point, but wasn't too sure how to get back so I went along). After a rather long trek to the beach and some serene contemplation we all went for breakfast at a diner. After that and a long bus ride home, I ended up crashing on the sisters couch for a couple hours. Anyway, it was strange and not at all what I planned, although I have to admit that it wasn't at all awkward with awkward coffee date boy, so that was nice. Ended up at brunch with Mark, his girlfriend (who by the way is absolutely wonderful) and a couple they knew. I must admit, brunch and a wander through Kensington market on a Sunday morning is far more my speed than staying out all night partying. Caught the train to London sleep deprived and hung over on Sunday afternoon. London isn't what I expected. I mean there's nothing particularly wrong with the town, but it's not nearly as picturesque as I expected it to be. It's kind of sprawled. Anyway, the University of Western Ontario is a beautiful campus and that's definitely important. I found a place to live. My search started Monday morning when Leo and Angie came down from Guelph to help me look. First two places were near campus and total dives. I was waiting for the cockroaches to come up through the floor boards. I thought to myself, there is no way in hell I'm living here, so we started looking further away from campus, especially considering that I get a free transit pass as a grad student. I ended up in this converted bubble gun factory. Does anyone remember Thrills gum? You know the purple stuff in the yellow and white packets (I think) that tasted like soap? Yup. The factory that was converted to loft apartments used to be the Thrills factory. I got a ground floor suite and it's huge and I don't care that it's actually in the ghetto. You read that right, Alex is going to live in the ghetto and she's happy about it. Apparently I'm on the edge of the ghetto. It starts at Adelaide street and I'm right on Adelaide. And I'm pleased with my choice. No more pristine neighbourhoods with the same old tofu eating, tree hugging residents. All I have to say is thank god there's a police station kiddy corner to me. I think that's the only reassuring thing for my mother. There's also a small Hispanic district a block away with cool little dingy cafes and stores. Downtown is 5 blocks away and it's totally removed from academia. So yes, if anyone wants to experience the small city ghetto with me, the apartment is huge and I have a guest bed! 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>