<Blog>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Based on the recent response to Richard Clarke, and the reaction of people towards Bush with regards to Iraq and the war on terrorism. It is safe to say that future presidents will pass on this style of controversy. Let the world rot like Clinton did, and avoid the Bush Sr. / Jr style of political demise. After all who needs sound leadership?
     
    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I will attempt to import my blog from .mac to blogger, if not it can be read at this url. (click on title) 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I must be psychic.  Speaking about the management issues in oil and gas industry in the prior blog, it is clear that the related accounting issues are systemic throughout all industries, or just in Canada.  Stating their is a difference in the way the Canadians and Americans approach their business problems, this problem is likely Canadian only. The Enron's and WorldComs prove the American desire to start over is both constructive and healing. Whereas Canadians like to relive the same car crash over and over again.  Therefore based on that it might be wise to hone up on our methods of politely answering the phone. Houston will be calling.   
     
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Canadian oil and gas industry leaves the door open for a further extension of the branch plant management style that is becoming prevalent in the oil and gas industry. My concern is for the method of management that occured in Calgary up to 1983 was a branch plant management style where international companies owned and operated the industry. This mindset was eliminated by the dynamic and entreprenurial spirit that is prevelant in Calgary and I fear that the branch plant method may soon return.   Why? Its really quite simple, we have continued to prove that we are having significant difficulty in maintaining our deliverability and reserve base. The ability to drill wells on the prairies is constrained by a number of resource limits that impede the work that is required. When the work is completed the ability to estimate and deliver on the basis of what it will cost is poor and deteriorating quickly. This is particularly difficult in the oil sands where cost over runs are approaching 100% on multi-billion dollar projects.   A secondary issue and one that is the focus of my thesis is the reporting and accountability capability in the industry. My opinion regarding reporting is that it is desperately constrained. The ability to "report" to the various regulatory and statutory requirements is constrained by the systems in play. Other industries can use applications such as SAP to meet the revised Sarbanes Oxley and CICA requirements, however, SAP in oil and gas, in many instances, can not even report gross and net on operations and capital.   I have a couple of pointed questions regarding the attitudes of those international producers that have taken over Canadian independents in the past few years. Believing they had cherry picked the best of industry for themselves; did they subsequently regret their acquisitions on the basis that, with the key talent moving on, the remaining management was inadequate to run the company? Hence moving the management to other locations?   Those companies or assets that were of no interest have found a home in the royalty trusts where the objectives are limited to the further exploitation of the reserves and the explicit renunciation of any and all exploration.  This is not what the industry needs in the long term.   With only a few real independent left, the time for those remaining, should head the saying that we reap what we sow. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Since everyone is leaving Iraq based on the terrorist threats to their countries. (Spain). Now would be a good time for Paul Martin the fearless prime minister of Canada stand up and do what he said he would. A very novel and unique idea for a Canadian prime minister.  He said that he wanted to repair the damage made by his predecessor and patch relations with the United States, and specifically George Bush.   Well bigger opportunities don't come along that often Mr. Martin. Call up George and state that you would be very pleased to send the other 5 troops of Canadian military to Iraq to fight in the War on Terrorism.   Just a thought, however, I think that Mr. Martin will no doubt be creating his next crisis to divert Canadians waning attention span.   (No slight against the 10 outstanding Military personnel in Canada. They have done extremely well on a poor budget.) 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Its Formula Michael, Not Formula Juan.  Line up behind all those that were bumped in line before you. And stop criticizing the son of Max Mosely's nightmare.   You should know by now that you can not beat Michael. 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Google's IPO is scheduled soon. Why they wanted to do it was a mystery to me but I now find that the company had to complete the standard of public reporting anyways. This requirement was invoked due to the probable size of the market cap is in excess of some predetermined number of billions. Google has some proprietary data that they do not want in the public domain regarding their financial situation.  Nonetheless, parallels to the Netscape and .com IPO's has begun with the expectation that Google's value will exceed $25 billion on its IPO. Far greater, by a substantial margin, then any other valuation. The average investor will be wary of the market price of google, however, if microsoft can top out at $400 billion, I would suggest that Google may be worth at least that.   Given the lead start they have over their competition, evaluating their use of the technology, and their pipeline of products. The only concern Google has is the speed of acceptability of their application of technologies. (Gmail for instance.) This company is a thinker and an innovator, and that in addition to the billions in cash from the IPO, will be the reason that the internet and technology continue to morph into its potential.   It certainly is going to be an interesting ride, and start the countdown for the demise of Microsoft. (My Microsoft countdown started 15 years ago.)
     
    
</post>

<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I only wish.  Seems the powers that be at Ferrari are reading this blog. Recently Valentino Rossi was invited to test a Ferarri at Fiarino. Completing 20 laps he came within 3 seconds of the lap record. Not bad for a guy who doesn't drive a car.   On a related note, Max "the black shirt" Mosely has decided to propose major revisions to the Formula one rule book. Since Max created the monster that is known as the six time world champion Michael Schumacher. I wonder what monster Max will create with these new rules. It is pleasing to note that McLaren's Ron Dennis has given up responding in any form or fashion when Max speaks. Keep up the good work Mr. Dennis, Max is out of his mind which is nothing new.  Watching the races from ten years ago, specifically the Monaco Grand Prix, this being the first race of the calendar after the death of Ayrton Senna, shows the quality of the talent in 94 and 95. No wonder Michael won, no Nigel Mansell, No Alain Prost, and No Senna. Instead of coming in fourth at best, he just needed a road car to bring him home the win. No disrespect to De Cearsaris or Martin Brundle intended.   
     
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alan Greenspan looks like he may have been able to achieve what it is that he set out to achieve so long ago. The years of stable prices has created the opportunity for an extremely efficient market economy. An efficiency that is realized on a global basis. The ability of the market to respond is truly remarkable, and required. There are a number of challenges ahead, and it seems that Mr. Greenspan has prepared us well for this future.   On Tuesday in his testimony to the Senate, Mr. Greenspan noted the level of sophistication that the market was using to hedge their risks and leverage the assets under management. And when you think of the changes in the means and methods of financial instruments, the analytical tools and understanding, not at the higher academic levels, but contained with the common public understanding, its no wonder that the market looks very rosy to Mr. Greenspan. 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Apple announced a number of products and alliances that place their video production and editing in the High Definition era. But only 64 bit apps.  Of particular interest is the alliance with Panasonic. Seems like Apple has prepared a method to secure the intellectual property rights of the movie creator and ensured that the technology respects that any copying will only be done in an authorized manner. I'll bet Pixar would never be interested in that. Doing a deal with Panasonic is a first for both companies and proves that Apple can establish standards with any electronic manufacturer. Somebody should think about doing that with Music, wait Jobs did but he only implemented it several years ago.  Ho hum another day that Jobs locks up another major future business, while all the others run around trying to get into the music business.  Jobs needs to understand that talking big is more important than products, services and strategic positioning years in advance of the rest of the manufacturers.  On a related manner the announcement of Storage Area Network services will be available in the fall of 2004 shows a distinct lack of understanding that Apple is a PC company and not a super computer vendor. (Virginia must have been a fluke!) Besides Intel is only now planning commercial versions of 64 bit processors with Microsoft announcing their 64 bit offering in 2005. Why does jobs not understand that delivering 64 bit processors, operating systems and applications will never win over customers. Just announce the stuff is coming, thats all that the consumer wants!  I hope that the press continues with their field day in making Apple look like a bunch of idiots, the press needs the company. It certainly will be a long time before Jobs realizes that execution is more important then strategy, at least so the saying goes.  In an unrelated manner, keep serving lunch Jobs, the press and your competitors don't seem to get it. 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There was an emotional and deserved pause by the legend Valentino Rossi in Welcome South Africa this weekend.  Rare would we ever see such a display. Dominant in the Honda for the past 4 years, Rossi chose to leave to take up his bitter rivals drive of a Yamaha. Although a competitive offering, the budget and scope of Yamaha was sizeably smaller then Honda's effort. Rossi's rivals stated that if they had the Honda they would also win, so Rossi obliged them.  To take the pole was a surprise.  To win consecutive races on different machines has never been done.   To win consecutive championships on different machines has never been done, and only done on different machines in a career once before.  This is what a true champion thinks and does. The otherwise impossible.  Michael Schumacher is nowhere close to attaining any of the respect that he claims with Rossi now in the picture. Schumacher should have long ago swapped rides with either Mika Hakkinen or Jacques Villinueve, or even join them at the same team.   As the prior blog entry reflects, Rossi's championship makeup is established. It is time for Schumacher to begin to better manage his career before he becomes a brief anomaly in the history books. 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Valentino Rossi gets back on his bike (Yamaha) this weekend and starts to demonstrate his championship attitudes and capabilities. I hope that both Max Mosely and Bernie Ecclestone, past and current presidents of the Michael Schumacher fan club, note that Valentino is a champion and what they have been passing off as a "champion" in Michael Schumacher starts to fall apart.  I only hope that its not to late for Ferrari to recover from the inevitable decline of Michael 'mania' induced by Jean Todt. (Michaels sycophant boss)  To a spectacular season of demonstration of daring, skill, personality and the championship attitude of Mr. Rossi.  
     
    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Microsoft appears to have a use for the money that they have generated. And like all things Microsoft it is counterproductive. Recent speculation around the motivation in the Sun settlement and other settlements has revealed a possible new strategy.  This may also be considered innovative by Redmond however, the application is not.  The use of Patents to eliminate the use of open source code in the corporate environment appears to be the strategy they are laying out. Retroactively applying for patents on existing patents, the old embrace and extend with a legal twist, attempts to lock out any non-licensed software from interacting with any licensed Microsoft software operating in a client corporation.   Legal technicalities aside, the money used in a court of law in this fashion will only seek to "embrace and extend" the threat and effect of Microsoft "innovations" in the marketplace. The solution that Microsoft has suggested is that don't run any non-licensed software in the corporation. 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Was that not something that Jackie Gleason was asked?  The comedy routine continues with the Ralph in question, Schumacher, states that the Toyota team are in discussions with him for the next year.   Reading my prior blog, you'll notice that Ralph does not deserve a civilian license let alone a Williams.   It now appears that Ralph is out of the Williams for next year as their does not seem to be any major announcement of his signing.   Toyota would pay for the Schumacher name and that is Ralph's best interest. Williams have no signed drivers for 2004, and yet don't seem to be the least bit concerned about it.   As we start the 2004 season we can clearly see the pretenders and the contenders, and really only the current stable of champions of Jacque and Mika Hakkinen, but not Michael Schumacher and Juan Pablo Montoya and Kimi Raikonen are capable of securing a championship. Mclaren have their drivers, Ferarri have theirs and Williams is sitting back and cherry picking the real talent.   Lets hear it for Sir Frank for continuing to be the smartest guy on the grid. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This article marks the decline of the PC as we now know it.  Long live the Mac.  If 700 PC's can only muster 180 Gflops, and 1100 G5's in Virginia are the third fastest supercomputer in the world at 10.28 Tflops.  Then note the PC's death occurred on April 5, 2004. Just don't tell anyone who has a PC.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Now is the time to go on the record regarding this years F1 champion, and a few other rambling thoughts.   The champion will be either Kimi Raikonen, with the second alternative being Juan Pablo Montoya.  Constructors championship will go to McLaren.  I hope that Jenson Button recognizes the efforts of one Jacques Villienueve in his current success. I am certain that Dave Richards and Button will realize the former champion efforts by the end of this year. They will look back at the end of the year and wonder how they were so successful at the beginning and how did they tail off.  Time for Patrick Head and Sir Frank to seriously consider the replacement of Ralph. The man does not deserve a license, let alone a Williams. Time to get Jacque back and make some hay with the BMW boys early. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In my past blog I wrote about the strong analogy that could be drawn regarding the extinction of the Buffalo and the current situation in energy. (Click on the title to be taken to the old site)  I wanted to add that in Canada we have a historical site called "head smashed in Buffalo jump." The site documents the native method of herding the Buffalo over cliffs.  I was thinking that there may also be a strong analogy between the Buffalo (again) and the energy industry (again). The fact that the commodity prices have risen so substantially has created a new operating environment for oil and gas companies. However, it is also just as remarkable that the companies have not changed any of their thinking regarding the approach to oil and gas. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't recall where but I remember reading that the Chinese are having difficulty in developing pipelines to fuel their energy needs. The ability to meet the demand for energy within China will not be met by China. The need to import energy is well established when we consider that China is now the second largest importer.  The inability to secure the pipeline and deliverability for its domestic needs, the Chinese feel susceptible to an oil embargo from the Pacific Ocean. They are therefore developing their first, and certainly not last, aircraft carrier. Now that is a bold energy policy.   
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This week saw two important developments in the technology world.  Microsoft announced that a major component of longhorn's 2007 release will be a major initiative towards super computing. This would fully exploit the 64 bit technology of long horn and be the typical Microsoft type of wonder.  Secondly the denial that Apple orchestrated towards its users in allowing the concept of a virus attacking their system did not muster the appropriately deemed result.  That this is a theoretical possibility, and it is important to think what could happen if, that no one was attacked, and indeed no virus has been written, does not accelerate the concept to the full blown risk that the PC people have as a result of turning on their machines.   Anyway, Jobs just keeps delivering products that are fast, powerful and safe, which is proof he just doesn't get it, when all you have to do is promote garbage 4 years before the time you expect to deliver to really earn the care and attention of the user community. 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Michael Schumacher's car betrayed him by heading directly into the wall. Either that or Juan Pablo Montoya's "car" betrayed him by not attempting to avoid Michaels Ferarri.  Maybe next time the six time world champion will be able to muster the ability to overcome the special attributes of his car. 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Step two of my 2003 prediction is about to be undertaken.   Ralph Schumacher has reportedly signed with Toyota, and good riddance.  The road is now open for two seats to be filled at Williams in 2005.   With such limited talent available, Villenueve is the only proven talent remaining.   The machinations of Patrick Head are only to reinforce the prior blog entry, that the M. Schumacher sycophants Eccelstone and Mosely pay for the Canadians substantial $35 million annual salary. 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It should be clear at that time that the "technology revolution" started on May 10, 2004, and a major re-configuration of the development market will occur.   The event that I am speaking of is the Apple Worldwide Developer Conference and Steve Jobs will be using this forum to make some major announcements. The first is the announcement of "Tiger" there next version of the operating system.   As I like to do, I like to make predictions of the types of products will be made.   Further details of these, and why they are important will be posted to this blog before the 28th.     - Redevelopment of the entire IBM suite of development products on Apple's Platform. I previously predicted this and look forward to the day that it actually occurs. Requires IBM to port their tools to Apple's G5 processor, aka the IBM 970 processor. Apple's contribution to this will be the release of their API to Cocoa and WebObjects to IBM.     - This offers enterprise customers an impenetrable security model for any developments made on this homogenized platform.     - Updates to the Xserve to 4 - way processors. This will be the outer limit of the 1U server, and the beginning of volume production of these units.     - Updates to Xraid, and clusters, with the addition of a "blade" processor based on G4.  Further elaborations on these points, particularly the "security" model will be made prior to the 6/28 deadline, barring the silencing of this point by Apple or IBM.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The title will lead you to the glitch that caused the Terabyte.  There is always the future.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My Gmail states that my Gigabyte is now a Terabyte.  If only this were true. I noticed that some other services had bumped their disk space to 1 GB in response to gmail, however, a TB would be awful nice.  Not much I could not do with that.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Buzz is the real innovator and visionary in the Canadian economy.  By effectively killing Air Canada, he has effectively solved the energy demand issues, and increased the wear and tear on personal vehicles, sustaining the Canadian Auto Worker for another two generations.   All without any explicit government support. Who says you can't teach an old dog new tricks. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Some needed debate on the oil price situation.  This attempt is being run at this blog site and at the econolog as the encouragement to discuss this point was made. (Click the title to go to the econolog site.)  The facts are what is causing the Americans to believe there is a conspiracy in oil supplies.   Attempts to put across three important facts generates significant resistance, these facts are.   - There are no alternatives to the use of oil and natural gas.   - There are finite supplies.   - The American economy requires energy in its current form for the next 5 years to sustain its advanced economy.   These facts should also be augmented by the consideration that:  The world is a global economy where supply and demand are international on critical commodities.   The American has significant competitive weaknesses.    - Significant reliance on imported energy.    - High labor costs in comparison to China and India.  The use of imported oil by the Chinese is now second only to the U.S.    - The Chinese are building Aircraft carriers.    - India and China have communist governments.     - The Chinese economy is operated for the long term, the Americans need to meet the next quarter numbers.     - The Chinese economy is one tenth the size of the American economy, and the same size as the Canadian economy yet uses 3 times as much fuel to create the same GNP as the Canadians. (Values are approximate.)    - There is a new political alliance between the Russian, Chinese and Arab states on the supply and demand of oil.     - There are now beliefs that the new political alliance can develop their resource without American technology. The dependence on foreign technology hurts their economy.    - The Chinese strategic competitive advantage is their low labor costs and large population. (And a disproportionate number of men.)  The American mind set that Cheap oil fuels the ribbons of SUV's is the most ridiculous abuse of resources since their abuse of the Buffalo.  This tendency for short term thinking is coming home to roost in the new Global economy.  I would assert that the Chinese are purchasing five to ten times as much fuel as they need to "stock" their own strategic reserve to be used as a competitive weapon against the "west".   The United States needs to wake up and learn some really tough lessons. Its a competitive global marketplace.   
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      while at the Starbucks. An order for a half coffee and half cocoa? Was this a new kind of refreshment? I did not see the desire to drink that type of mix but to each their own.  After I thought about it, I began to think that maybe the individual had a significant trend identified. So I did some checking.  The high end developer is using Apple's PowerBook for its Unix underpinnings and Java integration. Key to the evangelist is the explicit and overt support for the hardware by Dr. James Gosling, the founder and key contributor to the Java Programming Language.  What Dr. Gosling uses the PowerBook for is also the "Mac" only development environment known as Cocoa. Cocoa is the product name that Apple provided for the development environment acquired when they bought Steve Jobs from Nexxt.  I also use Eclipse and Netbeans, but use Cocoa and purchased WebObjects from Apple. Cocoa is also used as the primary development environment by my kids. Yes it is that sophisticated and capable that Gosling and my kids are now using the same development environments. My oldest (13) uses Cocoa with a group of like minded kids in California and Kentucky through their iSight webcams.   The point is that I subscribe to Cocoa, WebObjects, Eclipse and Netbeans environment mailing lists. (Please review how I use Gmail in this blog.) The volume of WebObjects and Cocoa based mail is significant. In most cases almost 5 to 1 of the other environments. Is that good or a reflection of more problems. The analysis shows that Cocoa based questions and answered are being debated by academic and scientific based individuals. (Apple quietly announced a science based market drive that is reaping big rewards for the firm.) The doctors and scientists are solving and debating some severe technical issues. They are not debating minor points.   Although Eclipse and Netbeans are young and starting the troubles and difficulties of these environments don't compare to the robustness and maturity of the 10+ heritage of Cocoa and WebObjects, but they are still crawling. It will be interesting to see if anyone suggests that Jobs should take Apple out of the development and science based areas as well. I would expect they will catch on to this and make that recommendation in as little as two years from now.   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The limit of collaborations.  Collaboration is the future of how the economy and businesses operate in a fundamental manner.  I have always subscribed to the theory that I would put out all my ideas at once and let them develop as they should through the process. Feeling that their are no limits to what should be stated and just continue to push the thought forward.  I now define the limit as the point where the idea is too over the top, or just nuts.  So I apologize to all of my victims for the over the top methods of my collaborations. Lets see if this limit has any effect. 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Anyone interested in analyzing the ideal political model should review Formula One and the powers that be in that sport.   Bernie Ecclestones ability to influence and affect change through political manipulations are a case study on there own.  The natural foil for Ecclestones political desires is Max Mosely. Son of the "black shirts" Mosely and a political animal of his fathers and Ecclestones class.  The current problem is the sports declining appeal due to the dominance of Ferarri. What is required is a spark for the sport to draw the fans back and that is one Jacques Villeneuve, and although "Bernie" and "Max" fought the young Canadian at every turn, they now realize the value of his honest and direct nature.  Enter Sir Frank Williams who understands drivers best and the fact that Jacque was his last world champion and best opportunity for 2005. Jacques testing in France this week leaves one believing that the universe will align and the Canadian will drive for Williams soon.  Enter Patrick Head, partner in the Williams organization and technical genius. States the Canadian was in France not on the invitation of the team.  So Patrick was does this mean? I believe that the sport needs Jacque so badly, and the solution to Williams driver line-up is Jacque, that Sir Frank and Patrick feel they can poach Jacque and have the powers that be contract and pay the Canadian for his services in F1.  Bernie and Max have acquired Billion dollar fortunes through their alleged ownership of Formula One. Sir Frank and Patrick Head, who like other teams, do most of the real work in Formula One, is a modest man of maybe $100 million in net worth.  If Bernie and Max want Jacque in the sport they can pay for him, and the "league" will pay for his services. After all what is that saying "let the end user pay".   Watch out Bernie, your slipping, and by the way how come the Queen has not called yet to provide you with that much coveted knighthood? 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Not to steal a famous saying and denigrate in the context of a commercial point, but...  Every two years I drive across the Alberta Montana border (twice) to support the Arthur P. Cox Memorial Ryder Cup Team. (We still hold a perfect record.)  I was thinking ten years in advance and marveling at the size and number of Nuclear reactors that have been buit on the Montana side of the Alberta border.  It is the only practical means for North America to secure its long term energy supply. (The reactors fueling the process of heavy oil extraction.) 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Comments regarding the role and influence of Apple in the marketplace are making an interesting turn in their tone and substance.  As opposed to declaring that Apple is on a death march, they are encouraging the company to abandon the Macintosh to pursue the iPod and give up on enterprise computing.  In the world of rampant vested interests (which is today) Steve Jobs appears to me to be one of only a handful of strategic innovators.   Strategic innovation is the only method that can sustain a firm in this new market environment. Vested interests are the counter weight to the innovator.   Keep up the excellent work Mr. Jobs, they'll get it some day.  Oh, the comment about the enterprise will be certainly be those individuals with vested interests next biggest mistake. 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The beheading of an innocent American civilian should put this debate in the proper context. The Al Queda and Iraqi prisoners do not deserve our concern. They are criminals and abused their system for 25 years to advance their personal causes. These people are scum and nothing makes that more evident then the fact that they think today's actions are in response to the prison incidents.   Wake up, this is war and they are the enemy. 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      These url's and this blog are documentation of an issue that I discovered in my Master's thesis and is the risk associated with the use of IBM's Workplace toolset. This product has a very "dark" side and companies should be warned about the threat. Contact me for further discussion if you would like.   This issue is particularly of concern due to the fact that today, IBM announced the Workplace product and its intention to eliminate Microsoft Office.    urlLink Computerworld    urlLink Techworld    urlLink Financial Times    Technology has now stepped across the threshold of being either benign and inert, or positive. To that which is either positive or destructive to a corporation. My thesis documents how these technologies have the capability of causing significant damage to a corporations data integrity. That this threat is an unintended outcome as a result of IBM dealing with the eight-hundred pound Gorilla known as "Microsoft".   This toolset wants Microsoft out of the corporate marketplace, and I would think that the majority of the corporate world would agree. However the unintended consequences of technology today, whether IBM or otherwise, brings the context more in line with a game of snakes and ladders where the board game is played in the offices of technologies customers. 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Significant changes have occurred this week that will have an impact in the next few years.  The most prominent news was Intel's announcement to ditch the next generation P4 desktop and Xeon processor development. Sighting the heat problems they stated that to resolve the problem was too great compared to the potential results. The solution is the ability to run dual processors in one chip design. Now I may be wrong but the IBM 970 and Macintosh G5 both carry 215 separate instruction units, I am certain that they will warmly welcome the future Intel competition. Just as the Model T is not used in transportation today the Intel processor will cease to be a viable commercial solution.  Microsoft has noted difficulty with their secure computing environment and has stripped some of the functionality from the 2006 Longhorn release. This environment in response to the viral and associated security issues that Microsoft is experiencing. As I have stated before, building the worlds largest structure out of toothpicks will lead to problems. The toothpick analogy to the Microsoft technology I think is valid. Now I may be wrong but Microsoft was using this environment to manage the intellectual property rights of MP3 copyright holders.   Apple announced "Tiger" there next iteration of the Mac OS X. This following on the heals of their SAN, Xserve G5, iTunes, New Powerbook models, Final Cut Pro, Motion etc. It would be unfair for me to compare these two environments because the Mac is such a poor second cousin of the Wintel duopoly, and no true computer user would use a Mac. 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As an avid Apple user and proponent, I enjoy watching the fits of the Microsoft Intel world struggle with the viruses, security and performance related issues. Add the heat issues that Intel is stating are the primary reason for the next generation P4 demise, to the never ending deadline for Microsoft Longhorn, one begins to see and appreciate the reasons why the Macintosh platform should be avoided at all costs.  If after 8:15 in the morning your machine was running without a hitch, that would require that you do a full days work. Everyone knows it is much more enjoyable to chase down phantom security holes, fiddle with the "dip" switches and unexpected performance failures as your full time profession.   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Trust the googlers to come up with Gmail.  It is truly a dream of a system and is highly recommended. The concern about privacy is *%(#$. The ability to have the advertising of the vendors that you may be interested in, fed to you without any effort will only be interested in consumers that are looking for new and innovative quality products. Those interested in *$%&# will keep by the Microsoft product suite.  One of the ways I use email is to get the most current information about vendor's product by aggregating their various mailing lists. As time passes, the ability to search the recieved mailing lists provides the means of determining the answer to questions that are not generally known by anyone.   The ability to search provides a knowledge base that does not otherwise exist. As you add additional vendors, and add Google's search capability, you begin to have a technical knowledge base that begins to be amongst the best sources of technical information anywhere. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I seem to be out of step with the majority of thinking regarding the Iraq war in general, but particularly on this topic.  It would appear to me to be acceptable for the American soldiers to be treating the Iraqi's in the manner that they are.  Although I realize it is inconsistent with the Geneva convention regarding war criminals, it is better then what the American soldiers should have done to those people. (just shoot them next time, and skip the problems). And I am certain they are being treated far better then they were "dishing" it out over the past 25 years to their victims. Those being the innocent women and children that did not follow the rule of law under So Damned Insane.  These alleged humans, the Iraqi prisoners, are the primary reason that a dictator has the ability to keep power for their own purposes. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      An interesting dichotomy is being identified and discussed regarding the energy prices and the energy industries reaction to the shortfall.  Firstly review of the ISM manufacturing and non-manufacturing indexes for the month of April 2004 reflects that the American economy is under a massive increase in GDP. There are various pricing pressures that put the pricing index under a severe strain, registering 88 for the month. The review also reflects that although there are inflationary pressures, there appears to be a trend for increases in productivity to meet the constraints. That although the inflation pressures are impressive, the productivity is offsetting the trend and mitigating the impact.   The pricing situation discussed previously, has an odd anomaly in the long term energy prices are not accurately reflecting the shortages in the future. The energy industry uses these long term prices to determine and allocate their capital budgets to the greatest return. Costing exploration and development on the economics of $28 oil is fundamentally different then the current prices of $40. Not until the long term prices reflect the current prices will there be any reaction by the industry in allocating funds to riskier projects, or to increase their overall capital exposure.   Based on this dichotomy in energy pricing, the need to ask if a revision of the pricing model to better reflect the supply and demand in the long term is required?   I would also postulate the need for the higher energy prices is only beginning to be reflected in $40 oil. The future of cheap energy solutions is over and will never be seen by this generation again. With the increasing productivity of the U.S. economy, and the level of economic activity increasing the demand on energy, a further doubling and tripling of prices may yet occur. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Everybodys favorite topic these days is the cost of energy. People are surprised that the oil and gas companies are charging so much for what consumers have taken for granted, and abused, for so long. Consumers should grab a Starbucks latte and start thinking seriously about this topic.  One of the more critical areas that is a source of my frustration is the short term thinking that goes into the pricing of the commodities. My frustration was that commodity pricing was essentially based on the availability of product as reflected in the current inventory, general deliverability and storage. I felt that this has been short sighted and needs to be revised. The point I discovered is that the pricing assumption is not necessarily incorrect. The inventory numbers are supported through the assumption that all oil and gas reserves on a worldwide basis have been reported as increasing year over year. The oil and gas companies continued to find more then they produced, therefore the situation was constantly improving. This tacit understanding was not flawed but a reasonable assumption.  The issue today is the reserves of the oil and gas companies are beginning to be questioned as to their validity. Trained in management I always found reserve engineering to be somewhat of a black art as opposed to a science. These reserves, as Mr.Mattheww Simmons states, are known exactly what they are when they are gone, much in the same way an actuarial knows when the subject has died. Everything else is an educated guess.  Unfortunately the oil and gas companies needed to optimize their reserves in the past 15 years based on the stock market demands for performance, and the consumer markets demand for energy. Deliverability became the issue more then the reserves. Again, as Simmons states, there has been a limited amount of application of known technologies to prove the reserves were not there. This has created a situation where some producers are writing down the value of reserves. The situation is well documented at Shell and recently was noted in El Paso's reserve write down of 40%. It appears to me that the latter instance creating little or no market response.  Another issue that will amplify the scope of the write-downs is the fact that reserves are booked as financial assets on the oil and gas companys financial statements. The statements are valued on the prices realized; less capital required to access them and the operating cost to recover them.  The issue should be defined by the fact that the majority of the gas reserves recorded when there was an abundant gas reserve, but at the low gas prices of around $1.50. When the reserves are booked there is an implicit need to reflect the commercial value, and would have probably been valued at their net of around $0.25.  At the current gas prices of $5.95 the net should therefore be around +/- $2.50. It is inappropriate for a company to restate their reserves upwards to reflect their revised market value, but accounting rules require the strict recording of the lower of cost or market value. The question then should be asked by those that are drinking Starbucks coffee is:  	Why are Starbucks prices going up to cover the costs of milk? 	Why are gas reserves being written down on producers balance sheet?  I can assure those that are able to answer the second question will begin to understand the real value of energy very soon.  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Seems to be talking to one Canadian Jacques Villenueve.  Frank is either leveraging Jacques desire to drive a championship car, for little in salary, to make Ralph Schumacher cave on his ridiculous salary expectations, or legitimately negotiating with Jacque.  As mentioned before, Frank is the key poacher of high quality talent that is championship grade at low costs. Villeneuve is probably going to join the ranks of the other greats who signed on with Frank to be with a racer. The other greats all went on to championship status soon after signing with Frank. Nigel Mansell, Alain Prost and unfortunately Ayrton Senna were all grateful to be driving Franks cars. 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Seems that the powers that be at Apple are feeling the markets response to them is strong. Product announcements are coming fast and furious with the 28th of June being the ultimate crescendo.   
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have always subscribed to a theory that the value contained within the North American marketplace was subject to greater risks that the average consumer / investor could not comprehend. The ability to move from the consumer to the investment environment would create winners and losers and these would lead to significant opportunity or destruction of value.   This destruction, in my opinion, has commenced with the markets slow and insidious decline in value. There will be no overnight reconciliation, only death by a billion pin pricks over a number of years. Only when the average consumer can perceive the losses that have occurred in this environment, will the death be realized.  The value declines will come in a number of methods that were assumed to be the basic fundamental components of western living or lifestyles. They include personal values, securities, and pensions.   The home values and personal possessions are the premier concern of the Western consumer. These are attributed far greater value then they currently can and will realize, therefore the value associated to these has already diminished. The value of homes will be reconciled during these coming years and exacerbate the capital deflation in the western world.   Securities are scary. Particularly mutual funds. When money is managed through the explicit renunciation of accountability, problems occur. Consistently the accountability deficiencies provides greater opportunities to mitigate the accounting for these deficiencies. As time passes the deficiencies only become epidemic and are manifest in the "owners" losses.   Bonds and stocks are provided much of the liquidity and support through the consumers and not through the investment in capital goods. Therefore the decline in those will occur in this time frame as well. If the value of the U.S. dollar declines, then these problems will become difficult for many to overcome.   Pensions are a direct result of the health and viability of the marketplace and the companies that employ the majority of the employees. Here I ask if the large organization, with its inherent hierarchy and associated bureaucracy can survive the natural force of self forming teams. Based on my direct research in this area, the answer is an unequivocal no.  Death by a billion pin pricks provides real opportunities to those that are able to use this decline. The only requirement is the capacity to use the tools afforded all in the technologies, the very advanced education of each individual, and investments in capital goods. The analogy I would use would be to ensure that you have a producing asset stuffed in the mattress. 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Although the Sarbanes Oxeley legislation is based on a definitive need. And the political environment appears to have struck a measured and reasonable solution to the moral and ethical decline in corporate America. The scope of this corporate issue is significant, with its implications bringing into question many fundamental assumptions that the markets are based upon. Nonetheless this legislation is having some internal political dynamics that were unexpected and undefined when the legislation was passed.   The unintended consequences are that a distinct division in the accountability within the organization has formed. With the CEO's and CFO's having signed all of the financial data in terms of the responsibility and accountability of its accuracy, the individuals responsible have been identified and are limited, in my opinion, in there ability to defend their actions in the future. The consequences of a breach are probable jail time. The evidence necessary to trigger the conviction being the signature of the CEO and CFO on the document.  The remedial methods at the CEO and CFO's disposal is an increased role of the internal audit controls and the increased emphasis on the annual audit.  Where are the directors in this process? Are they provided a free pass? The organization certainly has attained a pass, in that they have now been stripped of the responsibility and accountability of the accuracy and integrity of the corporate data that they prepared. That does not suggest they are involved in some criminal conspiracy, however, their diligence in identifying and reporting any inappropriate actions may be diminished in the legislations focus on the key principles in the organization.   When this issue is added to the decline in loyalty of staff within organizations, the focus of employees becomes more personal with their pensions, benefits and income taking priority over any and all organizational issues. I would also extend this to include individuals who have budgetary control are affecting the long term perspective of the organizations development and operations.   This long term issue is manifest through the commitment of the organization in any long term improvement. These committments and objectives are and should be the premier concern of those with budgetary control at this time of globalization. These employees are not that interested in engaging in difficult or controversial organizational tasks, and undertaking any risks that could affect their compensation. Therefore organizations are undertaking limited, if any, long term strategic or operational changes.   The identification and solution to this issue has not appeared in the market at this time. What the ultimate resolution will be is undetermined and is of great concern. This concern stems from the probable amendments to the legislation being impossible due to the fact that any change would be sending the wrong message.   If the enforcement of Sarbanes Oxeley is a political issue, does that impute that enforcement is a direct accountability of the president of the United States? 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      With globalization, supply and demand becomes the method of allocating resources and establishing prices.  There appears to be an advanced market in all resources when the global market place is considered. Allocations of resources and pricing are completed in a rapid manner, and effect all areas of production and consumption.   Competitive threats and opportunities are global in there source and disposition as well. With the effects of innovation and abundancies of resources felt immediately.  Or are they. My concern is that the standard of living experienced in North America and other advanced societies appears to be disproportionately higher then the standard of living realized in other regions of the world. In this efficent market, the Chinese producer has a competitive advantage over their more advanced competition in that they can access lower labor costs more easily.  If the supply of labor in China and India are as they are, does this not affect the labor market on an international basis? Is the standard of living the measure of comparitive advantage of an individuals productivity in the global market?  It therefore should be asked, how will the North American standard of living be sustained with the incremental supply of populations from China and India. Is the supply of human resources in a global market, not realized by the global market?     
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Six time champion. Now that means something.  Another prediction based on the results of the opening prologue. Lance will easily win his sixth championship.   No one, even looks close to touching him. The build in time over the next few weeks may become significant.   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The speed at which many of the societal changes are happening are truly fascinating. The results of these changes may or may not be seen or realized by many before it is too late.   It would seem that many of these changes are affecting life in North America more then the rest of the world. With the rest of the world gaining at the determinant to the North American society.   An example is the Canadian election. The ability for the country to instill a government such as the liberals, headed by a criminal group of unaccountable and allegedly unknowing administration, boggles the mind. The head of this group, our now famous Prime Minister is a tax evader and drug smuggler. This so that an unproven honest guy doesn't muck it up.  Certainly interesting times, you reap what you sow.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>