<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey All!  My name is Jillian, and this is the Seaside Blog!  Members:   urlLink Jillian  Natalie  urlLink Phileda  Virginia  OK!  The Background 411:  Hi!  My name is Jillian and my family has owned a Beach house in the beautiful  urlLink Seaside, Florida  since I was four years old.  Since then, a yearly tradition has arisen when we take at least a 2-week-long vacation there in June, right after school gets out.  For a long time, it was only my family and Natalie's family, but after Nat and I went to camp and met the infamous  Phileda , we decided that she should come along as well!  And as for Virginia, she is a wonderful product of my move to Atlanta, GA, and of my Jr. High school Pace Academy.  She is my best friend from Hotlanta, and is a fantastic addition to our wonderful tradition!  All four of these fantastic girls have been granted access to this blog, and hopefully will be posting their own thoughts, ideas, and stories on this board, for all of y'all to enjoy!  That's all for now!  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If someone from the Seaside managerial committee is reading this, give these boys a raise! Bradley, Zachary, Robbie, and Torrence (?). These four young men gave us excellent assistance in the Bike Rental Shoppe and the Adult Pool. When we were new to Seaside these four young men welcomed us in and showed us that not all poolside workers are 50+ recovering alcoholics. Many of them are, in fact, attractive teenagers looking for summer jobs. Now, I'm not saying they don't have their... retarded sides, but they are generally fairly normal. We would like to thank them for not kicking us out of the adult pool and for not landing on top of us in the pool- feel sure that would have resulted in a couple of broken bones. So to these hotties I say hello, Philadelphia
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well hello all,  Sadly our time at Seaside has passed, ( I was sooooooo upset when I left), but we did have a pretty awesome time. I am sure that Seside needs a rest from us after all that we did. Sadly we never did get to that documentary that we wanted to do, o well. On the other hand we did do a pretty good job conjuring up fun. My new fav place in Seaside is the adult pool(hehehehehe), though I must admit that I went to the adult pool not only to enjoy the pool, there were a few other reasons (hehehe). O well, we also did very well finding guys, though I have now officaly been branded a boy-crazy girl, even though I am not one. We had a marvelous time with all of them, except one named Joey , and his sister Rachael (whose last names will not be given away for there personal protection, trust me, if you knew what they did you would turn red). I am afraid though that I owe an apology to a certain boy named Stephen, I am so sorry, please forgive me. And also to all the people who I meant to say goodbye to but never got a chance, well a hearty GOODBYE to all. Anyway got to run, going to see a movie.                                   Ciao,                                Natalia                                 (you know you love me)
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, what were we talking about anyways?  Neither Philly or I remember, so we'll just recount what has happened so far.  Ok, we went the beach the first day and all four of us were horrifically sunburned... we're peeling and blisterin all over the place. So... now we are all four here now, so we're gonna say some cool stuff...   Well, It's rained for the past 2 days, and we have not started said documentary yet... we have had several encounters with boys, but none of them seem to like me.  They always fall for Natalie (most of the time) or Phileda, and I am surprised to say that Virginia hasn't really had them falling all over her... she's so pretty i would expect them to.  Anyways, I don't think it's that important anyway because I mean, boys might seem important now, but in the long run, the only thing that matters is that we have a blast!  Which at the moment, I am succeeding fabulously!  So, I guess all is good on the Tantiginous Donut.    I am very tired because we have been getting up early to either go running or meet boys at 8:30 in the morning (throw's hairbrush at Phileda).  I plan on sleeping late tomorrow morning, ahem, no matter what.  Well, I'm sure my lovely girlies can think of ways to get me out of bed, but I'm so so sure that it would be incredibly incredibly hard to do... see? I'm rambling on like a crazy woman! This is a sign of tiredness...  So the sun finally came out today!  We went the the pool and further developed our sunburns... i mean... uh... TANS... we are... TAN i promise... well, its all good.  it will turn into tan, but im just scare of becoming one of those gross 50 year old ladies with really gross leathery/cancery looking skin... so i make sure to apply SPF 30 everyday, even though it has given me sun poisoning in the past andmy dermo in atlanta told me not to do it, but i really dont wanna get too much more badly burned... and im not breaking out it itchy red bumps so i dont have sun poisoning, so ive decided that my dermo was wrong... WHOA im going way off subject...  So seaside has rocked my socks off so far, and its so exciting that its so much fun!  we actually go up to talk to boys this year instead of just watching them and giggling... oh we were so silly!  well, I'll talk to all you cool people later... i have some serious dinner to eat!    You know I'm worth it!  -Jilly
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey all you cool people!  Jillian and Phileda here, we are currently at the house of my (Jillian) Grandmother, enjoying croissants (*ahem* crescent rolls) and the cool air conditioning... Now, we have decided to tell of our fantastic adventures so far on our wonderful (*ahem*) road trip to the beautiful Seaside.  Ok then, I guess I'll tell you later cuz its dinner time!  Chao (haha like, food, and goodbye, teehee im SO smart!!)  -Jillian and Phileda (mostly Jillian)  :-P
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi ya'll its me, Natalia!!! This is sooooooo cool that we have this blog. And well to the readers who have seen our wonderful bolg, I, Natalie( a.k.a the big N, or Natalia), part of the fabulous four, am for the first time since this blog has been published decided to grace everyone with my presence (Partly because up till now my computer has not worked well enough). Anyway back to Seaside and the wonderful girlys who share this wonderful place with me. The countdown has started and only a few days left ( thank goodness, I am desperate for a tan renewal). Two of the very fabulous four have already departed to this very special haven, where all of us girlys can depart from our very hectic schedules and enjoy the sun, fun, and whatever else we can conjure up for our pleasure. This year however I believe that we will be making yet another fabulous documentary,though what it is about has not yet fully been decided upon. Past documetaries include 1. The Pink House 2. Clothing discrimination 3. The Twenty dollar bill As you can see we have quite the imaginations, hehehe. Anyway I probably should wrap this up before I make everyone jealous. So I must run      Ciao,         Natalia         (you know you love me!!!)       
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      El llamo of this blog... Ah yes, very- interesante. Very- us. The title is (if you noticed in Jillian's blog and my blog) a combination of both of our titles. The Tantiginous Donut... Here's a defenicion:   Tantiginous donut - a donut that is able to change shape at any time it wishes.  Now, donut can mean any number of things. It can mean the course of which life continues, neverending. It can mean the circle of people we find ourselves in contact with through our everyday lives. It can mean the way our brain works, moving through things and then coming back to them hours later, in a complete circle. The Donut is our way of saying "our world", basically. Our world of living, our world of thinking, our world of partay-ing, our world of loving, our world of breaking, our world of sharing. It's everything.  La rosquilla es la vida.   Amo, Phileda
     

    
</post>


<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Today's Horoscope :  You're presented with a bunch of conflicting choices: Should you stick with what you know or take a chance on what's behind the glittering curtain? Don't worry too much about making the right decision -- you don't have to make up your mind right away.   Well, yes, I do get my own personal horoscope every day in my email. (Which is, by the way, horselover@karnesec.net should you want to email me) You can get one too, at  urlLink Astrology.com . It's free and I think they're really accurate.   "Accurate?", you say. "A horoscope?" Well, yes. I actually am facing an extremely difficult conflict right now so today's was accurate! You know you wanna know so let me tell you all about it.  I could take a chance right now, I could choose to leap off on a limb and just do what I want and live my life on the sweet but wild side, or I could wait. I could wait until I'm just a little older (like 6 months from now :P) and then fling myself over the edge. But I decided today, I'm not going to make up my mind. I'm just gonna let my life take it's course- I'm not going to plan for anything- Or make a decision- Or do anything. I'm just gonna let my life go with the flow and be determined by other people's actions. What do you guys think?        "These chics don't even know the name of my band. But they're all on me like they like they wanna hold hands, cuz once I flow they know that I'll be the man, All because I'm the lead singer of my band."  Fun, huh? I keep waiting for CHRIS TO BURN ME THAT CD! COME ON CRISPY!     OK, I wanna tell you guys the story of 4 girls "going out on the town".   Picture  urlLink four teenage girls with beautiful tans .  Jillian: Beautiful long brown hair. Multi-colored eyes. Wearing a turquoise lace-up shirt from GAP and her favorite jeans. Natalie: Beautiful long honey-caramel blonde hair. A striped one shoulder top and bright blue jeans. Virginia: Gorgeous medium length brown hair. "The Yellow Sweater" and a white halter top with, yet again, more blue jeans. Phileda: Lovely (if I do say so myself lol) multi-toned blonde hair. White peasant top and, ah ha, you guessed it, jeans.  Well, one beautiful summer night at  urlLink Seaside, Florida  us four went "out on the town". It was warm, but ever "fashion conscious" we decided to wear blue jeans and a nice shirt. OK, I'm lying, we didn't decide to wear blue jeans, it just happened that way. :)  Seeing as it was pretty hot, we decided to get  urlLink Pina Coladas from a sort of, roadside vendor? I swear all of them were spiked. Especially Virginia's! We were so spazzed out it was weird. They were really good though.... lol. Anyway, we got our PCs and just walked aimlessly around town.   We passed the "ice cream guy" that we would always see hanging around outside this shaved ice place. At point i would spill shaved ice on myself in order to be able to ask him to hand me some napkins. Good times... lol. I never really saw his face, he always had these huge glasses on lol. SUNglasses. I think he was slightly gothic- he was sitting on this stage with these gothic looking people (or at least punk.... at the very least) and playing the guitar. Hotness, people. lol. What is it with me and nearly gothic people?! I have a weakness I guess.  Anyway, then we went and sat on a bench. Yes, sad, we know. But anywayz. And these guys with really big bikes were sort of following us around. Their bikes had at least.... 4 foot span handlebars. Anyhow, we sat down and these guys were driving past and asked me/us "Do you like my bike?" Talk about dorks. Oh well.  So anyway, we got bored then, so we went back to Mellow Yellow and we were out on Jillian's porch singing "Ain't No Mountain High Enough" (you know you can all see me doing that) when these guys in the next door house yelled at us to "Shut Up! Yal are awful!"  Don't you guys think that was harsh?  Love you all 2 Bitz N Piecez,                                         Toxic :P
     

    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well... I bet I'll regret this once I start not having time for it, but what the heck. Aight peeplz. If you're here you better know who the heck I am. I am Phileda. And yes, a seven nation army can't hold me back. I can't forget. Don't want to hear about it. Every single ones got a story to tell. From the queen of England to the hounds of hell. And that ain't what you want to hear but that's what I'll do. You know I'm having fun...  Well, let's see. Something interesting to talk about for today.  Here's a typical Phileda day!   6:00 - Wake up. Take a shower using 'John Freida Beach Blonde' :).  7:00 - Run out of time but still don't know what to wear. Close eyes and pick something.  7:20 - Leave for band.  7:35 - Why did I bother getting to band so early? The warmup was played by like... 5 people? lol. It wuz fun.  English - I just realised, like now, at 7:30PM lol that I don't have my English homework. Oh well.  World Geography - What are factions? Who the h*** knows what a faction of Cyprus is?   Spanish - I really don't want to know how I did on that test. It can't have been all too hot.  Lunch - It was cold.   IPC - My favorite class!   Geometry - God. Could we do more work, possibly? I guess we could, yah.  Health - My favorite teacher lol.   Well, after that I had tennis practice. That was fun. I was hitting really well, I think. Although this was the let down part: Coach Warlick: "Phileda how could you hit shots like that and not even win a point at the tournament?" Phileda: "I don't know!!!!" CW: "I was counting on you." Phileda: "I don't know!!!!"  I know what you're thinking. Sad, huh. Yah it burned.   OK, I know that was kind of boring. lol.  Here's the "highlights" of the day.  1) Courtney, where WERE you? 2) I can't believe I dropped that note in the hallway and Mark picked it up, READ it! AHHHHHH. 3) I still didn't get my gym bag back from wherever I lost it. lol.  I am going to come up with topics to write about in future so it's more interesting. Any ideas?  LOVE YOU ALL, no matter who you are! 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You know, humans make life so complicated. I wish I was a dog or something. No I take that back, dogs aren't as beautiful as humans lol. I can't remember the last time I wrote in this blog. Like 2 days ago? Something like that. I have a lot to say. First on the agenda is someone I see every day who I feel sorry for. This person: 'x' is a guy. He's a freshman, and that's all I'm saying about him. I see him on buses and in the auditorium and he's always by himself. And when we were marching for band today: he was standing there all alone watching us. I feel sorry for him. Maybe he's going through a depression? I don't know. Second, we took the TAKS today. Yah- woopdeedoo lol. That look's funny typed out. :)  Yah I had an argument with my BF today and I think we sorted it out... It's very stressful for me though. This weekend, let's see. Car wash tomorrow, working on science music video afterwards. On Saturday, parade, then Travis B's house? I dunno. Oh yah, and Steffy is staying over from Saturday to Sunday. My life is so confusing. Love, the Confused One
     

    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Steffy:  we have to go with Coach Huff I will Say *&&(&** this and wont go because he might want us to sit by him or something. I mean it he might make us do that or something that would be so sick. what he is a sick old man who still lives with his parents and has no hair  very interesting........... lol  And today in Geometry we had another interesting experience. Poor Austin. When Mrs. Rives was talking about two congruent triangles. Austin: What's congruent? Is that like where the angles all equal 180*?   Poor guy. 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes, I met today with Andrew, Travis and Courtney and we almost completely finished Courtney's SMV (Science Music Video) song, Complicated, by Avril Lavigne. I am doing Hero, by Enrique Iglesias (thus the title of the post). Travis is doing "The Middle", by Jimmy Eat World (I don't know WHY they picked that name). and Andrew is doing something by Nickleback- we can never remember the name! I think it's When I'm Gone. OK, If yal get a chance, go  urlLink here . This is a movie called "Badger" and it's so hilarious. If you watch it, after a while you'll just be laughing, besides yourself or what you think you won't be doing.  Luv u Guyz 4-Ever. If you have anything interesting to say, gimme a call or email me or something. You know I love to talk! Philadelphia
     

    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Went to the STAR horse show today in Beeville. Did pretty good! Won the Open 3'3 Jumper, Hunter O/F Open 3', and the Other Breeds 2'6 Hunter. Got disqualified from the first class I did- I went off course. lol. You know it had to be me. Well, I'm busy studying for "The Huffster" lol.  L8az, PT 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OK, if you read back a way (in the archives) you'll notice that my mom locked herself out of our trailblazer on the first day we got it. Well, today, my dad was driving a truck (I don't know why we have it, we just do)- a BIG diesel truck. And we took it down, hooked it up to teh horse trailer, and just as we were leaving to go back to the house, my dad locked himself out of it. Thus, confirming the suspicion that my mom, my dad, my sister, and myself are blondes at heart, if not in the head. For the following reasons: My mom: Locks herself out of car on first day. Puts anti-itch cream in dishwasher. Can't find keychain on her car keys. My dad: Locks himself out of car on first day. My sister: Asks if we let dead people out of prison. Myself: I'm only blonde in the head, not at heart.  Love From the Best 1/4th, Phileda
     

    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OK, I have certain people's "gay indian names", "pimp names" and "hit man names". In that order!  Travis Q- licking worm, Stinky Stewey, Big Pauly Jenna- stealing cat, Mikey Money Sign, Prickley Pair Courtney- stealing dog, Snugglez, Garbage Pete Ann- jerking hawk, Booker Da' Ball Buster, Hairy Henry Garrett- spitting gold fish, Street Law Shawnte, Da' Loot Phileda- sobbing fox, Poodle Man Jack, The Arm Breaker Jillian- falling turtle, Bizzle da Nizzle, Joe Bananas Natalie- running lion, Wild Joe Snaggletooth, Ruphas the Terrible Virginia- sleeping slug, Tony da' Beef, Twitch Travis B- laughing wolf, King Kong Throb, Rude Ruby Matthew R- kissing cheetah, Backhand Bobby, El Loco Andrew- scratching cat, Flash Funky Flex, Bloody Benny  OK, If you want to see something that will make you laugh your fricking ass off really hard for a long time, go here:  urlLink Badger Badger Badger.com  There is only one word for that website: hilarious. TURN UP YOUR SOUND if you go there. I think that should be our cheerleader's new cheer. LOL! Just go there people, you'll know exactly what I mean.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OK, Remember Elise's quote about the electric chair? And about whether they let the criminals go after they've been put in the electric chair? Well this one's even more hilarious. OK, my sister and her friend were trying to be all politically correct for some homework where they have to design their own law. So Elise goes, "Why don't we make a law banning gay people?" And Allie and Elise are both like, "No, that wouldn't make people happy." LOL! That's so hilarious if you think about it seriously. Anyway, Ah yes, one of my friends just said to me:  X: and just always remember that even if no one else in the world wanted be ur friend i would. PHILEDA: wow is this like a warning? X: i hope not PHILEDA: am i about to commit some heinous crime of society and be convicted a criminal and no one but you will believe that i didn't mean to do it? X: i hope not PHILEDA: i hope so too  OK, there's a certain person that's a really really good friend of mine. It's a fairly recent thing, like this school year. And he's really very smart, he just doesn't care. He doesn't bother to try. Or he doesn't realise he should try. And just so you know, this "he" doesn't apply to just one person. This applies to many people, but I'm refering to them as "he". I just know that this person could be striving to his full potential if he could see beyond the end of his nose. And this probably won't make a shit of difference to whoever reads this, but I feel like I have to put this out in the open. Why? Because I luv u all.   OMG! Speaking of freaky horoscopes, "X".   Libra :  Your two sides really stand out today, and people close to you pick up on the yin-yang thing. It's an excellent time to go out of your way to collect new experiences.  Dude think about the conversation we just had? Look at that horoscope. That freaks me out.  OK, Anyone wanna hear something insanely pathetic but true? I'm gonna stay up until 11:11 tonight to see if something special happens because I forwarded something. NOT! lol.   Well, Luv U All Till The Rain Falls Down Cuz I'm Coming Clean Luv U Ricky :), Phileda-the-way-you-love-me
     

    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here is an interesting conversation I had with a poor dude who messaged me completely unawares.   caotictheories: kiss my ass man BondGirl78118: where do you want it gay wad] caotictheories: hey! caotictheories: im not a wad of gayness BondGirl78118: so you're an ass of a man? BondGirl78118: ?!?!??!?!?!? well come on  caotictheories: asl BondGirl78118: 65/f/alaska caotictheories: you live in alaska? caotictheories: that reeks maam BondGirl78118: i tell you sumthine else that reeks..... caotictheories: no no no BondGirl78118: yes yes yes BondGirl78118: and it is.......................... your grandma's mashed potatoes caotictheories: my grandma doesnt have her own mash potatoe stand BondGirl78118: yah well you know what my grandma died 100 years ago so how would i know BondGirl78118: which actually is unrealistic if you consider the theory of relativity caotictheories: your grandma cannot possible be that old caotictheories: and i think you tell fantastical lies of your age BondGirl78118: ah ha! good work watson you've uncovered the missing link! you've solved the crime! you've detonated the enemy! caotictheories: naw give me my prize  caotictheories: your real age BondGirl78118: Ah, Caroline, I will be but one hundred and seventeen annules old when you are but thirty two. We can never be! I feel we are two ill-fated lovers destined to die in separate centuries. BondGirl78118: And what is your number of years spent on Earth, my little alien? caotictheories: hey!, i am a human beeeeeeeaaan BondGirl78118: Ah, do not try to fool me, I know you belong to one of the animal kingdoms, but you could not possibly be a vegetable, vegetables having no phalanges, carpals, or metacarpals, therefore incapable of typing a keyboard connecting to any kind of computer electronic. caotictheories: send me a piocture and i will tell you all caotictheories: or i will eat you BondGirl78118: From what side of planet Earth do you  hale? Or is the word hail?  caotictheories: im not sure caotictheories: from where i hale BondGirl78118: Neither am I, at this point. caotictheories: but i learned to tel time second period BondGirl78118: Congratulations. You would be in the...... 12th grade? caotictheories: i am BondGirl78118: Education is the key to our society, as you know. caotictheories: education is free caotictheories: thats the only reason i do it BondGirl78118: Did you know that one out of every one hundred people that do not continue education after high school will fall victim to a rhinoceri charge? caotictheories: what in the name of vegitable oil is that?! BondGirl78118: Well, in the unlikely event that you find a project called "vegitable oil" i will tell you. BondGirl78118: Mightn't I ask you a personal question? Previous message was not received by caotictheories because of error: User caotictheories is not available.   Ah yes.... the simple joys of life. Let me tell you something: That was fun.  Crazy Bastards 4-eva, BUt Not me, god willing, Phileda   P ositronic  H ydraulic  I ndividual  L imited to  E xploration and  D angerous  A ssassination http://www.cyborgname.com/
     

    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, after hearing an interesting story about a baseball player I feel compelled to share it with you.  my friend on my baseball team is a good hitter but he's been in a slump lately. and in our game last night he got out again his first at-bat. so he tried like playin w/ his nipples and used that as a good luck charm i guess. my other friend told him it would give him more confidence if he did it. so he was messin around and it actually worked. he got  3 hits in a row after that.  How thrilling? lol.   "My Random Poem By Phileda" by Phileda There was a girl. Her name was Earl. She had a bad day. Because someone said she was gay. Why is this bad? Because it makes her hate her dad. And now you ask why? Because her name should belong to a guy.  Kiss my ass all you writers and literature people. 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I Don't know whats up with that. I feel like a wound up clock. Here's a quote of mine:  Phileda: well then tell him to get off his fucking pedestal over the rest of the world and be your boyfriend! you shouldn't have to hang on to him while he's scared you're gonna leave.   OK, I was at the Pleasanton Wal-Mart today and I was looking at the CDs and this dude comes up and asks me if I need anything. I was like, "No I'm fine." So then I was browsing and he comes up besides me and starts putting CDs away. He stayed there for a while, and I was like, Oh wait!!!!! He likes me lol. So I asked him if Wal-Mart had a karaoke section. He goes, "Oh yah, a big one. In fact we need to get rid of some of the CDs." So I go over there, and he asks me if I am looking for something in particular. So I said that I was looking for a CD to sing to for a school assignment. He said, "Oh, high school or college?" (OK: he thought I might have been in COLLEGE? lol) I was like, high school. And then, he goes: "Oh." And walks away. and then he says "You didn't look like you were in high school." I was like, Oooo my frickin god, I'm a freshman in high school, you're some Coastal Bend affiliate who reminds me of a bisexual person but you're still hot lol, and my mom is coming over here to get me. So yah, that was interesting don't you think?   Anywayz. Tomorrow we're marching in band. *sigh* HEy, I can play the fight song, finally! lol  Love you all!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! Kiss my ass you haters (lol i'm sorry i don't know where that came from) Love Me As I Hate you! lol. Hey I luv u all,  Philly Dilly Willy Silly Phileda. God that was gay.  -Phileda
     

    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, at this point, Phileda is working on her essay, "The Effect of Las Vegas Prostitution on World Geography Teachers". To be published sometime before the end of school, time permiting. I think I'm coming down with a cold. OK, my sister is singing karaoke, and it's starting to get to me. She's probably the only person I know who's worse at singing than me. Besides my mom. lol. I can't wait until our SMV (science music video for those of you who don't know). So much fun. I want to see Michael and Austin's. I really want to see how they're going to get Austin wrapped up in tinfoil. I also want to enjoy laughing at a certain someone's playing of the drums. (TM lol)   Libra :  Today you're the glue holding everyone together. It might not be easy and it might not be fun, but if you relax and let yourself go into it deeply, you'll end up having a good time.   Haha. So untrue. These things are usually true for me but not that one. Right now I'm more like, being held together than holding people together.   August 26, 2003  A Berkeley High School teacher arrested in a prostitution sting says that her sex life should have nothing to do with her teaching career.  Lol. Oh well, reminds me of coach huff. I'll ttyl! Luv, Philly
     

    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      AMY: A friend is someone that will bail you out of jail. A true friend is the one sitting next to you in the cell saying "Let's do it again!"  Aww!!! I Love it! That's hilarious.  OK, Advice: Don't see Hellboy. It sucked lol. I thought the people were gonna keep coming back to life again and again. Oh yes, and if you get the chance, don't chew gum in Coach Huff's class. He'll make you write. Fat old bastard. Good Bye World. Phileda.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Eve had her FOAL, people?!?!?!?!??!?!?! That's like, so cool. It's a filly, and she's adorable, her head comes up to my chest. She's like a black/grey with a star. She's BEAUTIFUL. I will be sending you guys the address to some pictures once I've uploaded them on the computer. Today's horoscope:  Libra :  So things aren't perfect. Are they really that bad? If your big-picture outlook seems bleak, pay attention to the small stuff -- you've got a lot going for you, but you may not be giving yourself enough credit.   So true!!! My life is so complicated right now. But I guess I should be looking to the small stuff... Like, umm, my hair! It's so beautifully blonde from the sun. And, the fact that I have great friends, but that's hardly a small thing.  Luv u all, Phillidilly
     

    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, after being TRICKED into thinking I told someone's girlfriend something I shouldn't have said, ahem ahem, I worried about everything all day until I was told it WASN'T someone's girlfriend, but the "someone" himself lol. I can't tell you how unfair that was. My best friend thinks I should give this person another chance. However, I would like to point out that he has another chance, and he know's it. If he wants it, he'll take it.  Here's todays horoscope:  Libra :  You're really clicking with other people right now, and not just on a superficial level. The secret? You really listen, something many people just aren't willing to do.   Sure! Uh huh, my ass. I'm just confused right now. There's nothing else too it. I have to many people I'm thinking about. I can't wait till school ends. 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      He doesn't know this, I don't think, but I have a quote from Matthew R.  MATTHEW: Sex is good, sex is fine, either doggy style or 69. Just for fun or getting paid, everyone loves getting laid.  I don't know where he got that from but it's hilarious. So, I had an interesting weekend. Saturday: Went riding for..... ever lol. Sunburned, and HOT out there. And it was only 80*! What will I do when it's 100* and still as humid? Sunday: Went to the Russell's house for an Easter party. Why did I have to sit at the KID table AGAIN? lol. That always happens to me lol.  Monday: Well today I went to the movies with my mom and sister and we saw The Prince & Me.... Yah, it was, umm, thrilling.  Luv lotz n lotz, Philly Willy 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lol, I'm having a spaz. I bet my little sister $1 that it wouldn't rain today. I just lost a dollar... yah It's lightnening over my head. Haha, I think one just hit ground... Lol, can't I like, blow the electricity out of my house if lightening hits the computer? muhaha. Well, today we went riding for like 4 hours. It was HOT TODAY and just think, it was only 80F. Wait till it's 100. Won't that be shit loads of fun? Well I just took a "Who's your boyfriend?" test that really had nothing to do with that but, lol, I found out i am mysterious, loving, romantic, and athletic and that if I didn't send the retarded thing to 15 people in 5 minutes and 51 seconds Courtney would get into a fight with me. lol. Bring it on. muhaha. Yesterday I hid eggs for Mrs.Ridley's kids Sam and Katherine. They are so sweet! And guess what? They gave me a little model of a PT Cruiser. How sweet? Lol. Sucking up? Just kidding. They're so sweet. I'm trying to find random people to talk too. This is so fun. :P Luv u all, Philly PS: Always believe in a thing called love. :o)
     

    
</post>

<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today: Early Out! oh yah. So then I went to Kinky's house with Travis to take apart our RG. We've been putting that off for like 5 weeks, and it took us around 5 minutes to do. So then we killed about 4 hours at Andrew's house. We drove around, walked around, I tried to ride his bike in a skirt (haha), played poker (or tried), played spit (and lost to Travis), and then we played BS (btw, Andrew isn't very good jk lol). So after watching Andrew blow up 2 peanut cans with a gun we went to the movies.  Well, none of us are 17, I'm the oldest, I'm 15 lol. We wanted to see Dawn of the Dead. So I tried to pretend I was 17. Unfortunately, that didn't work. So then we got tickets to see Walking Tall. We got there, and I really didn't want to see it so then Andrew asked the front desk if we could switch to Scooby Doo 2.... (sad... we know) So we went to Scooby Doo 2, and we were the only ones laughing. I swear we enjoyed it more than these little kids lol. Of course, if we'd been smart at the beginning we would have bought tickets to Hellboy, which was right next to DotD and then gone into that one. But no... We just couldn't think that fast.  Oh well, Luv u all lotz n lotz, ~*Phileda*~
     

    
</post>

<date>07,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh yah. I got to school at 5:30 this morning. I got home from school at about 11:30 this evening. Why? We had Band in the morning. IF you don't know we got a 2-2-1 in concert and straight ones in sightreading. Fun-ness, I know *sarcasm lol no anywayz*. So then I went straight to tennis. Unfortunately, I lost the set 5-7. Made me so mad. I was like 4-1 then it just went downhill. I had so many match points. GAG ME! I also learned some extremely stupid jokes on the way home, especially the one about the chain saw, lol.  Lataz, ~*EPT*~
     

    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OK, COOL SITE:  urlLink Color Genics . It has all these fun personality tests. Here's some of my results. Bare in mind, they're pretty funny if you step back and think of me in their place lol.   MY TRUE NATIONALITY: French  You have high standards when it comes to cuisine, which should always be fresh, of the highest-quality ingredients and prepared beautifully. You are more inclined to use the rules of etiquette and social interaction as your guide to living life. Like many French, you have a developed sense of sophistication in love and social rules. You have impeccable taste and style and have perfected the search for quality of life, pleasure, well being and pleasant sensations.   WHAT KIND OF GOD I WOULD MAKE: Mystic Buddha  You would make an excellent New-Age god, the sort of entity that becomes ever more difficult to understand the more you learn about it. You are attuned to the cosmos in such a way that the mystical and religious are one in the same. The universe is God, and you are the universe.    You are a healthy skeptic who enjoys finding and laughing at the ridiculous aspects of life, other people and even yourself.  You have a good sense of humor that allows you to see through ploys and scams. You enjoy hearing about people's beliefs, superstitions and paranoia, if only to laugh inwardly at the follies of human nature. Ever the ironic, kitsch-seeking reveler in human absurdities, you will humor someone who wants to tell you about their latest brush with the supernatural … if only for the funny stories you'll be able to tell your friends later.   Funness, lol.  Luvz, ~*Phileda*~
     

    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OK. Here's my list of "Why the F**K did this happen to me?" for today.  1) Why the F**K did I get an 82 on my IPC test??? I thought I was doing good!  2) Why the F**K did I not get to see Eli as well? I Hate you ann. lol. jk. 3) Why the F**K did I have to sit through career day? I guess it was better than class, but still. 4) Why the F**K do I have to get up at like, 5:00am tomorrow morning?  You know, I hope I don't have any of my relatives reading this lol.  Well, I'll see you the F**K tomorrow ~*F**King Phileda*~ Lol. I'm in a bad mood.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes, I should be at school right now. :) As I'm writing this, on MOnday morning, yal are in Ms. Gonzales' class. I am about to leave the house to go to 3 or 2 (one of them might have to be cancelled) doctors' appointments. Fun-ness, right? Well it's better than school. God I have a lot of work to do. Study for English, study for IPC, Geometry, my mousetrap car. I hope there isn't anything else, I don't think I can take it, lol. The only thing that keeps my going is... my seven nation army... lol. I'm having a spaz now.  Well I luv u all, got to go. ~*Philadelphia Cream Cheese*~
     

    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well then. I have an excellent example of how blonde's get a bad name: my sister. At dinner we started talking about electricity when the lightning was going (lol).  DAD: They used to use electricity to get rid of bank robbers. They called it "Old Smokey". PHILEDA: That's kind of sad, imagine saying 'She died by old smokey'. MOM: Well... DAD: The electric chair isn't used any more, probably for that reason. ELISE: Do they let them go after they get electrocuted?  Sadness....... lol. Yup, we were like, "Uhh, yah, they let them go."  So anyway, what do you do when you can't figure out what you want, if you want the person you think you want, and what they want is completely unknown to you? God I'm so confused right now.   Libra     Lazing around the living room with your feet kicked up may sound like as much fun as hanging out with a crowd today. Don't feel guilty if you spend the whole day doing nothing at all.    No problem. lol. Today I woke up late, like at 12:00. I had a headache, ahem. I had stayed up until like 2:00 thinking though. Very confused but I think I have a sort of decision. I think everyone will like it. Lol, read posts below were I say I'm not going to make any decisions. Ah ha. Like that lasted very long. That shows what my will power is. About NOTHING.  Well I luv All u guys,  ~*Phileda*~
     

    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm sunburned. Bad. Like a sunglass burn lol. Here's things I look like:  A Tomato with sunglasses A red raccoon Red Flash with coconut bits in it Red Lipstick with Sparkles Strawberry ice cream with whipped cream A red apple with holes cut in it   Well that was interesting lol. U know u love me all the same.  ~*Philly Cheese Steak*~ 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      IF you don't know, my mom got a  urlLink Trailblazer LS . It is white. lol.  Anyhow, we had just gotten the car and I wanted to go play tennis with Courtney. So my mom, sister, me, and Courtney went to go play tennis on the high school tennis courts. We got out, played for a little while, and then decided it was too windy so we went to get back in the car, and found out: it was Locked!!!!! Yes, we locked ourselves out of our brand new car. So, when we realised that our cell phones, purses, and Courtney's homework were in my mom's car, we started wondering what we were going to do. We decided we would walk back to Courtney's house and use her phone to call Randy Witte, who's dealership we bought the car from.  Then we walked all the way back to the tennis courts. Words can't describe how funny we probably looked: Walking through Karnes City with a tennis racket and four people. Well... So we got back to the courts and sat around our car. Finally Randy shows up with this police officer (that Courtney knew, by the way). The police officer spends about 1/2 an hour sticking a long metal stick into my mom's car- but he couldn't get it. Yah, he wasn't all that great. Courtney, Elise, and I got cold so we decided to go sit in Randy's car (that he brought us). Let me tell you about this car.... lol. It was a big black, suburban. And it was old. I think it was an '80s or '70s model. It was.... hilarious. There were all these metal poles on the inside that we think came off of the outside of the car. It was a hooptie or however u spell it lol (i'm laughing my ass off right now) Anyhow, we finally have to call the wrecker service, and yes, the policeman is still trying (it's been, an hour? lol). The wrecker man comes, and does it in 5 minutes. Poor cop. His face was so red. So then, wow, we had our car back. We spent about 15 minutes trying to figure out how we'd locked ourselves out- we still don't really know. I think it's because we had set off the burglar alarm like 1/2 an hour before.... I dunno. We still don't know, like I said. So then we decided to go to Dairy Queen to eat. We went tothe one in Kenedy, for some reason, but we got inside and found out- they didn't take checks! As we were about to leave Dairy Queen this old man stopped my mom and asked us if we came from Kansas.... My mom told us she didn't want us near him so she told us to go to Pizza Hut while she like plowed it out of there lol. So we ran across the parking lot and we got to a ditch, where Courtney tripped. OF course, according to our luck, there were TABLES of hot baseball players staring at us as we ran and tripped from inside Pizza Hut. So we finally get to Pizza Hut, and start eating, lol. If you don't know, Courtney and I have a thing for Britney Spears (her MUSIC lol, yah her boobs are fake so we're not jealous lol jk ppl). So we tried to make the jukebox play Oops... I Did It Again. It wasn't loud at all, so we went up to the front desk and requested that they turn it up. Very embarrassing, but I swear they spiked the pizza, lol. So they turned it up all the way, and we put in a couple of dollars. And told the jukebox to replay the same song (Oops... I Did It Again) over and over again lol. We hit the button and it started out really loud, u know how it sounds, with the bass? lol. So we acted like idiots and ran back to our chair really fast. We looked pretty stupid I guess.  So we were sitting there eating while people were laughing at the choice of song and looking at us saying "Look at the blondes who picked BRitney Spears." IT was even more hilarious when the song kept repeating and people were like, "OMG, here we go again." But the BEST part was when we saw this guy who had been playing baseball sitting at a table with all his team mates- DANCING. lol. It was SO FUNNY, he was getting all into it, dancing while he was sitting there. We were dying of laughter. So, as we left I gave Courtney a penny and she went over to this guy at his table and goes "I like your dance moves", puts the penny down, and we left. His whole table was laughing their asses off, including the coaches, and the poor guy was all red. Let's just say- we know how to have fun. But it is kinda sad that we locked ourselves out of our car on the first day...  Luv u all 4 Eva, ~*Philly*~
     

    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "I believe in a thing loooove. Just listen to the rythem of the heart." Courtney has me hooked into this song. I swear this "person" has to be a he-she! What is with  urlLink his voice ? Anyway. I played tennis for like 2 hours with my dad. We took a break, and then went back and played more. FUN NESS. lol. We just messed around for the first two hours, then we went to the Tote and I had Sprite lol. Then we came back and played one set. And I w-o-n 6-4. Oh yah. That was so much fun. However, it was hard to concentrate with the track meet going on around us lol.  Well I'll TTYL, I'm so bored. l8az ~*EPT*~
     

    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       My Horoscope (Libra):  You may not feel like a wise old sage (and you sure don't look like one), but today, you'll get to play that role. Fortunately , what you say doesn't matter as much as whether you listen.   Hmm..... I wonder what could have happened today that would apply. Who said something that I replied too, but it didn't matter what I said, I should just try to read into what they said. lol.  That's creepy. Any ideas from ANYONE? lol. EMail me ppl. It's freaking me out.  I'm trying to design a workout program lol. I'm sick of running. I'm gonna work on it this evening. I want to think of something FUN to do, any ideas?  LOL, I feel the urge for underwear shopping. I know this is weird but i get the urge sometime, and we just got a VS catalog in the mail.   I'm reading YM right now, here's another one of my horoscopes.   LIBRA:  The boy you're into sends you crazy mixed signals. You wonder if you're in the twilight zone: Did you imagine those long talks on the phone? In the end--gues what?--you'll find he's not worth the trouble.  Hmm... I wonder what that means? That's kind of disturbing too. I hope it's not true lol. Makes me not want to put too much belief in these tings. God I hope thats not true.   I'm disturbed. I'll see you all later. Good Bye. Emma  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As all of you may know, I have many very special friend who live in Karnes City. One of them, I will soon have to part with. I will miss you SO much Courtney. For those of you who don't know, Courtney will be moving to Freer for the next 2 school years, then coming back her senior year.  Words cannot express how much I have connected with Courtney and she knows it.  I want to share some of our stories with you. :)   The Bathroom Story  Courtney and I were getting ready for tennis in the bathroom of the English hallway. We went in, and noticed that it, well, STANK. lol. It was bad, but I needed to change. So we went in and we were all like, "Oh man, I can't stand this anymore." and "God, somebody has a bad stomache." Finally, Courtney said "I can't take this anymore!" and left. I hurried to finish, and I was picking up my stuff from the corner of the bathroom, when a TEACHER walks out of the "stink-origin-stall". I just stood there, with my mouth open, grabbed my stuff and ran outside with Courtney. I told her, "Oh my god, it's a teacher!" and we were standing there making stupid faces (especially me lol, I had a suck face look on lol) and laughing when the teacher walks out, and says "How yal doing?"   Hmm... let's see. What's another good one... Well, there's the time Andrew was throwing dead mice at us when we were working on our Rube Goldberg? lol.   Oh, there's also the time when I ducked to miss Steffy's tennis ball (which she missed, and was coming right at me) and turned around and ran smack into Courtney's tennis racket- my eye was watering for a while.  Courtney has also had moments by herself- like the time when she was just walking across the room in Spanish, and wiped out- on her ass- flat out- for no reason.   We share many things- our favorite color: pink, some of our favorite songs: Say I Yi Yi, and some of our favorite artists: Britney? lol. :)  We also share some opposites- country music.  I know theres more great stories to share, so as I think of them (I'm gonna call her right now and find out!) I'll let you guys know.  TTYL, L8az,     ~*Phileda*~
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yah, I haven't posted for a while, have i... It's just been so busy! (the end of school- always busy, summer planning, special people :P, friends, piano, horses) I'm going to try to get back into this. I would like to call your attention to a coming blog- the Seaside Blog (of course, it will eventually have a better name). This year the fabulous four: Virginia, Natalie, Jillian, and Phileda will be blogging their experiences together in Seaside, Florida. This blog is open to all four of us. Please visit it! There's a link on the side of this page. Well, what can I say... Don't buy the D-12 World CD... It's not really worth it... There are a few songs- of course they're all insanely Eminem-typical (depressing, I'm-to-thug-ass-for-my-pants-so-fuck-me, yah u know how he is). I'll Be Damned has a pretty good hook. Of course, My Band is the best music on the whole CD. "How Come" is a pretty good song- catchy music.  I love Britney, as you all know, but her CD In the Zone, yah I've had it for a while know and I'm just really listening to it now, but there are only a few songs that are really good on there. They would be: I Got That Boom Boom featuring the Ying Yang Twins, Toxic, and Everytime.  Joey told me about "Anthem of Our Dying Day", a song by Story of the Year. That's a really good song people! It goes from a sort of light/punk rock to a heavy-metal rock for like 15 seconds, then back to the light-rock.  Yah, I don't know why I felt as if I had to do that- I am just into different kinds of music right now. Like this morning, I pushed the "find a station" button on my stereo and I just listened to whatever it came up with- just not Spanish, lol- What's the point in listening to it- I can't understand it! True- I listen to Spanish when I'm trying to do homework, but this is summer- there IS NO HOMEWORK! HELL YAH!!!!!!!!!!!!!! So anyway... OMG could it get ANY HOTTER?! It's 100*F with 100% humidity! This is awful.. If this is May, what are July and August going to be like?! Icky. Well I'm selling ads right now for debate. Very very annoying.  I thought of a name for the new foal: Lady Madonna. I think it suits her because she's a little know-it-all and she's very independent and playful. It's a Beatles song. Here's the lyrics:      Lady Madonna, children at your feet.  Wonder how you manage to make ends meet.  Who finds the money? When you pay the rent?  Did you think that money was heaven sent?  Friday night arrives without a suitcase.  Sunday morning creep in like a nun.  Monday's child has learned to tie his bootlace.  See how they run.  Lady Madonna, baby at your breast.  Wonder how you manage to feed the rest.  See how they run.  Lady Madonna, lying on the bed,  Listen to the music playing in your head.  Tuesday afternoon is never ending.  Wednesday morning papers didn't come.  Thursday night you stockings needed mending.  See how they run.  Lady Madonna, children at your feet.  Wonder how you manage to make ends meet.     So anyway, I'll have something new to write about tomorrow. L8erz!  Ur friend/enemy/ally/servant/master/competitor/team-mate/lover/chaperone/person/thing/it,  Phileda
     

    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Þh†LÊDå... says: h ok, did u know that theres supposed 2 b an asteroid headed for earth thats the size of a city? on september 29 actually. which is 6 days after my birthday and theres a 63% chance Travis says: or realls? Þh†LÊDå... says: ah Travis says: damn Travis says: when something like taht hits doesnt it like cause a lot of holes or whatever?  Sorry Travis- the blonde in all of us shines through at many times. Luv u all, Philly
     

    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Good news: I can EAT AGAIN! No pain! Well not as much, anyway. I can eat normal stuff and drink normal stuff again except sometimes I get heartburn just a little bit. I LOVE YOU PREVACID!  So yah, I love it.  Bad news: I typed it all out but then decided I didn't want to say anything so eat your heart out you nosy little bastards. :P Love you all!!!!!!!!!!!!!! Call me! Phileda
     

    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Phileda: No hablas, idioto. Tu es no divertido. Andrew: pinche hoto mofo fukor  L-A-U-G-H- M-Y- A-S-S- O-F-F!!!!!!!!!!!!!! lol.. That's great. We love you Andrew. Ahh, nothing like a few good laughs from an innocent friend. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Garrett: Don't drink and drive: you might hit a bump and spill your beer.  Classic.... lol. I love it. No, you really shouldn't drink and drive ppl. I have a cousin that died from that.  Love you all, Drink but don't drive :)  Phileda
     

    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OK, Yes I know it's Tuesday, but I want to talk about before today.  Yes, well, here we go, going through. :P  On Friday was the band car wash. Very interesting, lol. We made less money than last time. Even though we had more fun: it wasn't raining! OMG! lol. So it was fun, except I am sunburned, even my feet. But I am also tanned. The high point: drying this car and talking to this hot dude that had egg splattered on his car. Courtney was jealous- muhaha courtney, lol. The low point: Getting a soapy sponge put in my bathing suit, thanks Clayton.  On Saturday we were supposed to have to march in the sesquicentennial parade for Karnes City. "The Mighty Badger Band from Karnes City Land" gag me. Yah, well, we woke up, it was pouring with rain and lightnening (is that a word?). I called Mr.Campbell, and guess what, we still had the parade on! So we drive into Karnes City (pick up Jenna on the way) and we get to the bandhall and Phileda gets her hair fro-ed out running around in her poncho-that-looks-like-a-trashbag. So then we go inside and Mr.Campbell says we have to wait until 9:00 to see if it has been cancelled or not. And then, at 9:00 we learn it's been cancelled. So Steffy, me, Elise, my mom, and Jenna decide to go see Mean Girls. And surprise, surprise, as we leave Karnes City, it stops raining and the sun comes out! Haha, but the parade was left cancelled. The first showing of Mean Girls was at 1:00 so we had some major time to kill (it was like, 10:00). So my mom dropped us off at Bealls while she went to H-E-B. At Bealls we decided to pick out an outfit for each of us, and try it on. In about 15 minutes, the entire populous of salespeople were gathered outside the dressing rooms all wondering whether or not to kick us out. So, I started talking loudly about "Do you think this would look like to much for the after party?" Yah, so we got out of there pretty fast.  Then we went to Pizza Hut for an early lunch. We ordered a pizza, and it got there (FINALLY) and Steffy decided to grab the first slice. Steffy grabs the slicer, picks up a piece of pizza and aims for her plate... and misses- slapping the pizza against her shirt instead. Her white shirt... Haha, we love you Steffy. OK, if you haven't seen Mean Girls go see it! That is such a good movie. Even guys would like that movie. After the movie we remembered that Travis Q had lost his cell phone. So we asked the front desk, who told us to ask the janitor, who told us to come back on Monday, but we had our sad looks on, so he looked for us, and we FOUND his cell phone! We were so happy. So naturally, we just had to return it to Travis ASAP so my mom drove us to his house. We then faced a dilemma: we couldn't choose between 2 houses. lol. So we went up to the first one and knocked on the door (we picked this house on my analysis that there was a dog outside the other one and Travis doesn't have a dog). Well, it was the wrong door. So then we went to the other house (by the way, it was a dog statue, nice job Phileda) and knocked on the door- BINGO! It was the right house lol Yah so we returned the phone and all. Then, on the way home, a bird tried to commit suicide by flying into our windsheild, lol. Steffy and Jenna spent the night (Steffy snores, lol, jk). Then we got up early to take them to church. I then went to Wal-Mart to find Mr.Cline sitting in the band trailer with about 1,000 Krispy-Kream doughnuts, so we got our 2 boxes and went home! Then the heart burn whatever shit started and as of right now, I haven't actually eaten very much... lol.  Yah, wow that was long.  Believe In Love You Haterz Cuz That's Why You're Reading This- Cause I Love You Enough To Give You the Website Address! -Phileda
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Odd title, isn't it? No, I wouldn't call it odd. I'd call it ironic. Today, our society is built like a pyramid. Everything we WANT to know, everything we THINK of, everything we DO know is in this pyramid. Every once in a while a brick chips. It must be mended or it will continue to chip, then the one above it will be exposed, then it will begin to chip. And who do you think mends it? The godly people in this world... The people who believe that it is their duty to be as one person (do they even call him a person? I don't know) wishes them to be. They are the followers. They are the brick menders. These brick menders- what do they mend their bricks with? Well, they mend it with a universal tool: religion. Religion is available, it's cheap (until the church starts pressing you for money, you lucky ducks), and it's there for those who have nothing else. I'm not saying this is a bad thing- maybe our world is better off built with this mortar of religion. But, what will happen in the following scenarios:  1) Our world gets so heavy, with all the mortar, and all the bricks and mending, that we can no longer evolve. We cease to create new ideas because the mortar of religion covers up all our new pathways to new growth. IF you didn't know, the chips in the bricks allow for new things to be added. 2) The mortar no longer works- the bricks become immune to the mortar because of the weather (the passing of time, aka). What if all of a sudden we find religion is not the answer, then we can't change that because we've always depended on it. 3) The mortar cracks up and falls off... We are left completely unsupported: We are left defenseless and confused because we've spent our whole life depending on religion to tell us what is right, and what we should do...  Just some food for the mind.  Phileda 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm  an irredeemably eejitous, liberal, tight as fuck, seizure-inducingly boring spod!   urlLink See  how compatible you are with me!  Brought to you by Rum and Monkey   Yes, I just took that test. Go take it and then we can both find out how compatible we are with each other!!!!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was really tiring. I got out of bed because I could not sleep. I feel unusual because my antidepressants are making me hairy. I'm so sad. My kitten got run over this afternoon. I found him when I was coming home from school. His head was all squished. I took some photos. I'll miss him. Poor kitty. Last night I had to go and pay Joshua's bail. He's such a jerk. He got arrested for punching the Walmart clerk in the face for refusing to sell him beer. He's only 16! I want to tell the world that I love you all! You're all so special to me! I am updating this journal for the first time in ages, because I've been in prison. Today, I got a digital camera! Yes! But I don't know how to work it. Can you help me? I want to say thanks to the world for absolutely fucking nothing! You all suck. I feel so alone, no one ever reads this journal, or even comments to let me know that I'm not suffering alone. It's cold here, and I want to die, but I cannot figure out how many of you to take with me when I go. I went to the doctor yesterday, and he said I have bipolar disorder, and should stop smoking drugs. You should all do this quiz! It's amazingly accurate. You just put in your name and birthday, and it will tell you what your favourite sexual position is. This is so cool! This is like, a random journal entry generator... BTW, Travis Q thinks I shold make a new MSN sign in name: cityskank24_7... Ahem! How rude! LOL, jk Travis. How cute! That's enough for now. But I'll leave you with this thought - sharing your life with strangers on the internet is the cheapest form of therapy available. Leave a comment and tell me I'm beautiful.  Created with the  urlLink Gregor's Semi-Automatic LiveJournal Updater&trade; . Update your journal today! Powered by  urlLink Rum and Monkey   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>