<Blog>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      My 1st post for this blog....... alot has happened this couple of months... a marriage is going into the drain soon.... felt so terrible, specially for my precious daughter.... ended up in a broken family..  Have this song in my mind.... wan to let Yan know how i feel now... and thanks for the happy memories..  忘 我没有很努力要自己去遗忘  那些和日记一起收藏的过往  孤单在思绪之中变得很漫长   想 我没有很刻意让自己不去想  那些和照片静止的模样 我学着坚强  坚强到不用学着不想学着遗忘   还是害怕夜深人静时总想起你  还是害怕的不经意听见你的消息  然而当爱已经沉淀得太清晰  当拥有已经是失去就勇敢的放弃   还是害怕一个人时就很难忘记  还是害怕突然宁愿当初没有决定  然而当爱最后的出口是分离  我会这么相信 走下去  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Arrghh... pissed off.... Damm.......... today jus attend to a meeting regarding the extended working hrs~~  Shit man! Working on sunday consider as a normal working day~! no OT rate at all??!! Working on holiday only 1 off in lieu??? most pissed off is we are the only dept working this kind of shit hrs~~!!?? then those other depts? witout support we stay so late for wat?  i knew it at the 1st place that i entered the wrong place, the wrong job... but i have to live wit my choice..... wat to do.... sigh...  Yesterday movie, "Dawn of the dead" still floats around my mind...~ guess this show is rather disturbing to me....... feel like walking out of the cinema halfway man...~! 1st time i even felt this way~  The feelings for "her" is getting stronger... actually her name is Anna... i dunno whether this is love.... the anxiety to see her again, the anticipation of waiting her online~ Every morn, her face will like surface onto my mind~ Her smile, the way she laugh.....~ really make my day feel alot better....~   But..... i dunno whether can i love her not...? Should i get into a r/s again so fast? I'm not sure my papers is gonna sign on Nov... all up to Shane.... and i felt that if i dun express all these bottom up feelings.... i really going to burst from the inside~~!!!  Falling in love for some1 has never been so miserable........~~ 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today went out wit mummy and pa and shermaine out for lunch and shopping at Great world~ it's being quite a while since we go out as 1 family~ althou the places they go is not i really feel like going, but i no longer the Danny who will pull a long face and bey song about it~~ i jus walk and shop and see~ Guess i've grown alot...  Went out wit darling jie 2nite~ went to borders and see alot of wanted books i wanna get but .....no money~~ hate tis~ want something but can't get...~ have to earn for it then......  We talk alot~ glad to know tis jie also~~ we shared our experiences, guess tat's how humans grow.... to learn from one another mistakes? Well~~ hope tis jie can find wat she's looking for in life...... Bless her~
     
    
</post>

<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      2am in the mid of nite, jus finish icqed wit darling jie....~ been talking about serene tat meeting......tat fateful lunch wit her.... i really dun mind to harm her... i didn't hurt her i guess.... i jus wan us to be friends tat all.....Th epast jus treat it as a sweet memories.......~  came to know tis gal recently..... she's fun-loving, caring, nice~ well tat's only the surface........... but since knowing her till now, i can't help but seem like i'm attracted to her~ maybe she's got the factor? i really dunno..... Ever since wat happen to me and Shane, i dun really dare to step into a relationship, i told myslf.... but the initial feeling of love is there.....the feeling u get when u feel u love tis some1~ yet i'm shutting myslf cos after wat i've been thru.... but i can't wait for her to be attacted~~ i really dunno.... Very confused..... Sigh...... who can teach me wat to be? out there........
     
    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It's going to be a late nite work again 2day~~ standby sometimes can be relax, sometimes so busy until wanna kill someone~!! haha~~! Been out wit darling jie, koi-mei, lao ge, and lyn-sis las nite~ too bad the tix for sat nite fever was sold out..... so we went to marche~ Very long time since i step into marche.... tat was 4, 5 years ago...?? ya.....~~ Lao ge beam to me alot of new ringtones for my precious sony~ so i had a great time exploring me phone~~ It was a great nite...~ Darling jie was so funny, we started saying ghost stories and i noticed she getting pale~!!! hahahha~~! re-assure to see if she's ok~ after all she's going back alone quite dangerous~  Shermaine~~ daddy can't see u tonite again....~~ 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today is another common day... work, gym-ing, and go look at Shermaine....~ Jus tat in work there some setbacks...argghh....used to it liao.... was so excited about 2moro's Sat nite Fever when darling jie said $15 seats are all sold out... quite disappointed... after all, i'm some1 who like all these muscials, films......... sometimes i wonder... did i choose the correct career not? Why can't i make music? Guess situations dun allow us to do so here.... Sigh...  It's late in the nite now... mind started to wanders.... Jie quickly ask me to listen to some music... i chose the spa music she gave me that time..~ some tracks remains me of stuffs again....damm.... eyes sored again...  After all i've done, pick up gym-ing, pick up my rusty guitar skills again...~ There's still a part in me not wanting to let Shane go.... I remem las sunday, i walk past tis exact bench we once sat on...... She's pregnant, tired... wan a place to sit.. i let her lean on me, i hugged her securely, and she jus dozed off.... with Shermaine in her tummy....   Can't help but weep again....... Shermaine, daddy miss mummy alot.......~
     
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Went to meet up daddy today~ He still look as strong as ever....~ even at the age of 60+~ sad to say we only meet up once a month........ he's getting older day by day.... and he keep remind me : "Dan, keep contact wit ur bro and sis, even after when i'm not around..." Hate when he say tat.... dun wish anything to happen to him~  Got Darling Jie sms on way home~ she's meeting her blind date setup my her colleague~~ hahaha~~ wish her luck!!  Happened to saw Darling jie on msn again~ recieved a shocking news from her~ Apple jie and archie papa's twins are gone.......can't believe it and went to read it myslf in the forum.... can't help but drop tear... Suddenly i missed Shermaine alot..... i haven seen her for 2 days.... i can't wait to see her 2moro..........
     
    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It's another monday again..... work, and gym-ing wit parthi~ as usual, we discover the beginning of the week we always can't lift much~~ cou be due to the resting period on the weekend......~  went to see Shermaine as usual~ Maine grows alot, guess it's time to teach her wat's right and wrong oredi~ She does listen, if u tell her nicely~ Actually discipline a kid is not easy.....  Itchy hand i selected Tanya's songs in my mp3....... her songs always reminds me of "her"......~ all the happy moments we have, but everthing have to jus end.....  Stranger陌生人    词:姚谦 曲:蔡健雅   一朵云能载多少思念的寄讬 在忽然相遇的街头 当我们擦身而过 那短短一秒钟 都明白 什么都变了 一转身谁能把感慨抛在脑后 在事过境迁以后 这感情就算曾经 刻骨且铭心过 过去了 又改变什么 地球它又 公转几周了(浓情爱恋 都已陌生了) 我不难过了 甚至真心希望你能幸福 当我了解你只活在记忆里头 我不恨你了 甚至原谅你的残忍理由 当我了解不爱了 连回意 都是负荷 我不难过了 甚至真心希望你能幸福 当我了解你只活在记忆里头 我不恨你了 甚至感谢这样不期而遇 当我从你眼中发现我已是 陌生人 我已是 陌生人了   After bath, i jus casually switch on the tv and it set to channel U... (cos las nite i off it on Ch U)... Saw this taiwan show, xue di li de xin xin..... the actress looks jus like Serene...... Speaking of serene, ever since she's back on Dec las year, she's been asking me out~ but i always said i'm busy....... i dun mean to avoid her but i have alot of problems wit me now..... i dun wish to entangle wit her.... knew her characteristic, i believe she still haven give it up.... i still do have feeling also, but...... i'm not wat i used to be.... i can't... sigh.... 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Eariler this afternoon, totally turned off by this toopid field tech, Mah. Tested line at cab ok then go ahead to Dp loh~~!! not the 1st time testing line is he?? told me signal strenght is weak, noise is only 17.... good wat nothing wrong wat!! Like bey kam wan (not willing) like tat~ Called back and say Dp signal very bad..... then change pair lah!!! duh!!! cannot change main lah!!! everything have to spoon feed izzit? shouted at me somemore, say ask him to run up run down, lunch time oredi still cannot eat, blah blah~~~ other techs can finish and go lunch why can't he?? Why is he always the slowest?? Ask himself lah!! Complain union go ahead loh~~! As if they will care... Bastard~!  Jus meet up wit this guy, Melvin. Had bid wit him a T630 in the forum. A very nice phone but i still cannot play wit it!! cos new phones have to charge 6 to 8 hrs.....~~~ Such a pity he can't use it cos he's enlisted soon and camera phone are not allowed in camp~ Very nice guy tho~~ felt sorry to keep pester him for the reciept~ have to cos to safekeep myslf.... His dad's details are inside so it's rather inconvienent~~ but he manage to fold the receipt and copy witout the details~ appreciated his effort man~~! Cool i have a new gadget to play again~~ Opps..... guess i spend rather alot recently....Nomad Zen and now T630.... time to save up~~ Cou be going to KL this june or july i hope~ wanna relax and visit kang ming kor and yan ling, yan li jie..... so fast we all have our kids oredi...~ ;)
     
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Damm busy monday 2day.....~ Stupid helpdesk kicked over 100 over problems over the weekends~~ I wonder wat are they calling helpdesk for, to help users or jus simply to redirect all problems to us????~~!!! Damm idoits~!  Enuff of work, even today's gym's session seem to be cock up~! Both me and parthi dun have the right mood today man........~~ but i manage to get some intensive biceps workout...... wat a blue monday~~ sheshz.....~  Practicing on my axe now, as far as good.... have to bring it up slowly... still new from the song "sunshine of your love"... never mind~~ jus hit on it more often i believe i will able to master or add some of my own pluckings in~~ hehe~~!  Let's rock and roll!!!!!!!!!!~~
     
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Sigh another sunday gone..... 2moro is another working day again...~~ Feel really shitty why can't i jus have a job tat i'll be very happy on every morning to go working on it~~~..... guess nothing is perfect huh....  today went out wit darling jie again~~~!! haha~~ said robin is asking her out but she dun dare to single outing wit him, cos of wat has happen.... so ok loh, my obligation to protect this darling jie of mine~~ and anyway i wanna have my dinner..... went over to join them for dinner~  We talking alot about kids..... robin's niece and my Shermaine... guess kids are so wonderful...~ i really felt a sudden loneiness, thinking wat if i dun get Maine's custody.... sigh...   On the way to the MRT, the silly darling jie of mine keep pestering me to do the Jackie's "secretly loving u" song.... in the public somemore~~! damm embaressing~~! no choice loh do a small piece but she wants more.... give her a virtual kick and send her off hahaha~~! but glad lah she can be so happy, good for her~~ maybe tat's my soft side.... to see pple happy i'll be happy also~~.... oh well.... Good nite Shermaine.......
     
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Damm busy today in the office..... keep getting those big problems calls~ change circuits change until i numb liao~~ sian..... sat jus like tat burn liao~ but lucky can go for a ktv session to relieve stress~ finally saw sbg, as expected, quite tall..... and Travis is a very nice boy. Sbg sure have a way to educate her kids.. remained me of Shermaine, she seems to be so misguided by the in-laws...sigh..... still full from the dinner, the porriage sure is big bowl~ when to boat quay for a walk...... feel quite lost... and maybe i'm used to share Yan wit my problems... now like no 1 can share my problems wit me.... hao lost ah... 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Finally got the hair dye and type polish for mum and dad. Hmmm... the type polish look rather big bottle... quite wu hua for 10 bucks~ Damm pissed in the afternoon, called my in-law, not around~~ Shermaine?? Not around~ I go over she didn't say anything about bring SHermaine seeing the doc~ When i came back home, then mum said Shermaine afternoon went to see the doc!!! Wat am i?? I'm the dad please~~!!! Can info me not??? Hello???~~!!!  Idoit....  2moro work again....super pissed!!!! ARRgggghhh!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      2day i purposely skip my gym session, and went to Amway to collect mum's and her colleagues products..... Ended up the counter lady told me tat every 1st day of the month is stock taking day and i can only collect my goods on 2nd onwards~~ so asking me wanna do payment 1st not..... Arrgghh! Toopid Desmond and Francis didn't told me about this!!! Or maybe they dun even know about it... oh well.... jus a small matter.... Went over to see Shermaine as usual, noticed she's abit of heaty.... In-law said that she's like having a slight fever~ but she can sweat leh~~!! how can be fever?? Will call her up 2moro afternoon see how's Shermaine~..... Such a naughty gal~! very demanding~~! and short-tempered.... jus like her toopid mother...~! give her a smack jus now and she ignore me the whole nite... Sheehzz.....  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      nothing much happens today~ the usual work, usual gym~ but wait! today tried out this new weight gainer 3000~~ taste fantastic man!!! choco favour~~ most people thinks that supplement are very disgusting but no really~~  went to the gym with parthi~ see the usual gym people...the lady who dress very pro and figure, fantastic... hmmm the uncle with specs is not around~ He look professional thou.....  after all tat, went to see shermaine~ she's getting more and more smart every day~... hug me when i reach, give me a kiss when i going off.... but very temperemental gal.... have to see to tat...~ Oh well.... Good bye Wed~..
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Rite now, sitting in the office doing nothing... absolutely nothing! and now typing this boring message...  totally sucks~~!!!! the sunday duty is a total piece of crap! wasting my life away man! Wat the hell.... can't stand the boredom~! *bang wall~~~ *bang even harder~~! *wall collaspe~ :p  this is wat u get when a guy is totally bored~! *forehead bleeding.....
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Been a couple of night standby, actually working late isn't tat bad afterall~! seeing the night view of orchard. Maybe too used to be a loner, i actually enjoy it~! no1 to push u while u walking (cos orchard can be very crowded), no1 walking slowly infront of u~ 1 whole street or sometimes 1 whole cabin of the MRT to urslf~! Woo Hoo~!!  Maybe when it's quiet and late at nite, it's the best time to ponder stuffs. Alot of things happened this year... Be it good or bad, happy or sad. Really been thru and see thru alot. Life can just be so interesting to some pple. I guess i've experienced stuffs no1 can even imagine it will happen in real life~ Seems like a TV drama hahahaha~~!  Well Life is just a show we put up to entertain the mighty 1? hehe~~!
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      2day is my 1st nite in the office until 11pm. Well, maybe it's not tat bad after all. Nothing much to do also... Things seem to slow down on 9pm.. eventually nothing much oredi...  Maybe it's too long never had a chance to sit down doing nothing.. mind's full of lemon.. she really made a great impact on me. Glad we took tis rather well.. We still hang out, talk like friends. No any affects after my tat "confession" thingy~.. Well, i'm glad she took it well also.. After all, like X-bro said, we are both adults. We should know how to handle ourselves...~  Maine, when daddy go and visit u, u are still asleep. Be a good gal ok? Daddy loves u.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hmmmm........ sounds like things are coming my way~~ dun be cocky, danny~~! *knock head*    how you feel about yourself now (Wheel Of Fortune)    Perhaps you feel due for a bit of good luck or indeed are experiencing some at the moment. The Wheel of Fortune is a card of destiny. What is happening now we could call fate, so if positive things are happening with your love life, career or finances this is no coincidence. If no such things are happening, expect a sudden change in fortune.      what you most want at this moment (The Hermit)    The cards suggest Cal, that what you most want at this time is to know what to do, as well as companionship or a lover as you feel somewhat lonely or isolated at the moment. Perhaps you are feeling exhausted and in need of a rest - if you have been ill this is a time for rest and recuperation.     your fears (The Chariot)    The word failure isn’t in your vocabulary. You are worried things are more of a struggle than you expected, with more delays and frustrations. Things aren’t going to plan at all, just chill out, calm that mind of yours and you’ll find the strength to battle on until you succeed. This is a period of movement and change and conflicts ending in victory.      what is going for you (Strength)    Brave heart! Your self-confidence and courageous spirit is unstoppable at the moment. Be patient and compassionate, self-disciplined and strong and you will reap great rewards for your courage.      what is going against you (Judgement)    If you allow fear to stop you from taking a chance or a new possibility then you will lose out. Do not ignore the new opportunities being presented to you - a decision, new job or relationship could change your life for the better. Do not refuse change when change at this time is vital - feel the fear and do it anyway. Outcomes may well be delayed, however this is a time for positive action and not passiveness.      outcome (The Emperor)    Expect success and achievement of your goals, this is a time for fulfillment of your ambitions. If you have placed your trust in your father, husband/partner or a man of significance in your life, they will come up trumps for you. If you have been the victim of ill-will don’t worry, you will win in the end.    
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Went for a job interview in Potong Pasir today. It's a post for an assistant software engineer. the interviewer obviously is a chinaman~ Mr Chen Sen...~ Same name as the singer/songwriter...~ He's quite friendly, basically telling me alot about the job scope, found out it's more to the mobile communication area~ which is sort of wat i'm looking for..... he's also kind enuff to raise a few areas of concerns to me, paticularly the working hrs, which can be at times, from 8.30 to 9 at nite~ and the travelling distance from my home to the work place~ and also travelling overseas for couple of months to rectify customers problems~ Sounds very interesting, but those concerns i really need to ponder and consider about it..~ and Mr Chen sounds very confidence that i'm the right candidate..... Well, let continue my job search and see how things goes...~
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yesterday maomao's bday party was quite fun, i've never laughed so hard for dunno how many donkey ages oredi...~~ And also haven been to jack's place for quite some time liao~ their "rare" steak cooking skills are still fantastic~!  On the way home, koi-mei actually asked me this question.. Is Anna=Diana? Lemon jus asked me this question recently... and i guess i'm no longer able to hold on to the secret... Yes, Anna is Diana, is also lemonade, is also darling jie~ Sorry koi-mei, i made up a fake story...and lemon, if u see this, sorry i can't hide it any longer... dun get shocked okie?  I guess i'm not ready to tell anyone yet.. that's why i hide it to myslf until now~ the bottled up feelings are jus too great for me to handle...~ I felt myslf going to explode anytime!   What Koi-mei said yesterday is rite... if i really have feelings for lemon, keep to myslf... cos Koi sensed that she's not ready for another relationship yet..~ and i myslf is also not divorced yet... so better dun cause any troubles to each other...  Sigh.... i guess i've said tis b4, like some1 has never been so miserable.... 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well here's my readings..... dun look pleasing...~~  how you feel about yourself now (The Hanged Man)  You feel a little confused and perhaps fearful because you sense or know that there is someone or something you need to give up to be able to move on. This self-sacrifice isn’t always clear - you may not even know quite what or whom you should give up. This is a time of passage from one phase of your life to another and The Hanged Man can signify a time of spiritual development too. Perhaps you need to try and look at things from a different prospective.   what you most want at this moment (The Magician)  What you most want is a new love in your life, and when The Magician appears, a new love affair or perhaps a rekindled affair is at hand. All things new are possible, the result is up to you - its all dependent on just how much you want it.  your fears (The Hermit)  You are frightened of being on your own and loneliness, and you simply don’t know quite what to do. Take time to relax and in time you will have the answers. The Hermit signals a warning not to make hasty decisions, so try not to get too stressed, and if you have been unwell this is a time for rest and recuperation.   what is going for you (The Moon)  Despite the fear and bewilderment you feel, and the seeming difficulty of the path you have chosen, keep going - all will eventually turn out fine. The Moon is a good omen if you are in a clandestine affair; it also shows us how to be open to new and unexpected possibilities.   what is going against you (The Devil)  It's like you’re in a drug-induced haze - it feels great and always leaves you wanting more. This is addiction pure and simple, whether it's an obsessive sexual relationship, money deals that are too good to be true, materialism at any cost or recreational drugs. Take care - it won’t lead to a happy ending.   outcome (Strength)  Courage and self-belief is what you need to succeed. You may already feel overflowing with this, and if so there’s no doubt you will achieve what you want with your career, finances and love life. If you are feeling negative, look inward for that strength and courage, you know you are capable of having self-belief and you’ll reap great rewards.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      2day is a very tiring day..... struggling to stay awake and work at the same time~~ yesterday nite din sleep at all.... seems to having sleepless nites again... wonder why...~ the twisting and turing is unbearable man~~!!  went to robinsons and try to get mama a gift for the coming mothers' day~ too much things to select, and now then i realised, wat's mama's taste?? dun know wat kind of pattern she likes, colour she likes.... "Hao chan kui orr..." well.... might as well pass her the cash and ask her to buy herslf, ya sound very insincere but at least she knows wat she wans~ ;)  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Finally able to have a break after tons and tons of phone calls~ Jus now got the news about the starting of the extended hrs... 17th of May, wat the hell~! It's 2 weeks from now~~!!?? The union meeting no 1 bother to attend also, cos it would not change anything also.... jus check on my yahoo mail and fwah~! 2 online applications kenna spotted and they wan me to send them my resume~!! Guess maybe it's starting to turn good...~~ maybe the pai pai does help~ Thanks to darling jie.... Hmm... speaking of her, Serena said that i have a liking for her~~ and she freak out asking me is Anna=her?? sheehzz...~~~ Hahaha~! silly jie~ But witout her and the rest, koi, lao-ge, lyn and birdman....~ dun think i'll be picking up tat soon~  Thanks alot my friends.........!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      nothing much happens today thou....~ play with shermaine, went out to meet the usual gang~~ as i was alighting from the clake quay mrt...~ my feet jus keep me from walking the correct direction...lucky... The whole darn mind is all about finding a new job and anna.... her mental projection in me was like getting stronger and stronger everyday...~ i tried shaking the images away but...arrgghhh it's like haunted by them.... give me a break.... i dun wan another r/s pls...~  walking halfway luckily i snap out of it and i reached the traffic lights...(so fast??) About to cross the road, saw darling jie opposite, she going off for a dinner thou~ hmmm nice dress~  the guys and gal are playing~ noticed lao ge short hair~ hmmm he look more clean tat way~ stay tat way~ hahaha!! after dinner, went for the arcade a while and do some shopping in cold storage...~~ nothing much to buy thou...hmmm~~  boring but yet a day passed...... monday again... sheehz...~ oh well~ 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hmm.... not the 1st time staying up so late...~ jus went clubbing wit darling jie~ it's been a longgg~ time since i last club~ 4 years ago? ya sort of... get to know 2 of darling jie's colleagues, harry...? hope i get her name correct, and serena~ the place was ok at 1st.... started to cramp up soon after~~ and we got no chance but to stand beside the bar counter and dance~~ not much space for me to flare my moves thou~ hahaha!! i guess over a day's work~~ part of me is drain out~ or maybe age is catching up...~~ was getting kind of tired after all the squeezing, pushing, dancing~ darling jie and serena was knocked upon by the crowd several times~ i wonder why can't the pple jus stay at 1 spot??  omg....~ it's 6am... (touchs hair)... hmm quite dry up~ guess time to hit dreamland.... Hope anna can give me a break~~ stop letting me thinking of u~!! and shermaine~ hope u had a great time wit mama~~ daddy going to pai pai for u 2moro~~ good nite~
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Doing late nite this week again. Seems like the office is a nice place to think/ponder about stuffs also, minus off the noises, rushes.... Been thinking about wat parthi said in the phone jus now....~~   (flashback) Had a call from parthi the man~ Asking me whether i've called him jus now when he's at the gym. I guess i forgot to lock my phone again. Dial mistakingly to him maybe~ Well anyway, we were talking about the bonus that we're going to recieve tomoro. He told me this shocking news.. The girls mostly are being promoted and none of the guys recieved anything. Not even our ever hardworking supervisor - Chew. He's been around for like 5 years i heard? Along with Francis, Patrick and Ryan. Not 1 of them got any promos or increments... Parthi maybe right, it's high time we hit for greener patches... No point staying at this place, we are not being appreciated.   Parthi's lucky enuff. He landed himself in this Philips Securities and going over nxt year's jan. I was about to ask him whether that place needs any1 cos he said they are expanding. He mentioned some issues which are rather considering also... He asked: Their training will be overseas and it will take a couple of years, am i ready for tat...? i suddenly felt a moment of loss... it seems tat i have things here that i'm can't or bear to let go... Sigh..  Time to ponder....   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yesterday nite was so happening, until i fall sick today...~ Me and parthi went for the Linkin Park concert yesterday. The 1st 1hr of the concert sucks!! They played tracks from CDs (i guess) one after another until 8+~~ Then.. this korean band made an opening for the show.... They sucks man big time! The whole crowd was like dead~? They simply have no originality! Their songs  were merely imitations from pearl jam, nivrana, lim biskit... Sheeei~!  Then after the unbearable K band, there's another rows of played songs~ Urrgghh! The actual concert actually starts at 9.40 man! Damm! But all that unhappiness were quickly swopped away by Linkin's power packed performance~~ The crowd was crazy man! Still can't believe that i'm actually listening to them live! not on a player or anything~! Cool! Unforgetable man!  Today i was practically home-bound the whole day.... Had a severe flu and sore throat.. I guess cou be due to all the screamings and shoutings las nite while singing along with the band~ after seeing the doc, i was practically immobilise, in my bed.. The med was strong! after lunch i just simply knock out~~ As i was in my sub-conscious mode, my radio was playing 林芝 her 音乐日记...~~ She mentioned something which really meaningful... "如果是你的，你放她走她最终也会回到你身边。如果不是你的，紧紧抓住也没用。" Easy said then done.. Oh well...  It was until 4 i woke up, had a bath and pay a visit to shermaine~ Poor gal, i haven't seen her the past 2 days.. She's very happy to see me thou~ Such a joy, to see her grown up day by day...~ 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yesterday went out with a bunch of friends. They start blasting questions like why i don't wanna go venturing or did i planned anything for my gal yet?  Actually i'm a very practical person. I'll not tell anyone my plans until i'm 80-90% sure i'm into it. I can say i'm a perfectionist. If i wanna start, i make sure it's going to work. If it's not, i rather dun waste my time and efforts. Life is unpredictable. You'll never know whether it's going to be workable or not, but at least you yourself must be clear, and sure. All i can say is, rite now i felt, in terms of experiences and skills i lack alot in my field. I wanna build myslf up, increase my values and social circles b4 starting to venture. I make sure i have all my resourses ready then i start.   As for my daughter, i have done all the necessary financial planning for her. Be it education or medical. At the meantime, all i wanna concentrate is the divorce case and her custody.   After the conversation, i guess i was a bit agitated. I dun really like pple to teach me wat to do in life. I have my own ways.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yesterday went for this ISO briefing. Parthi got a nice name for this "ISO" thingy. "I asshole"~ muahaha~~!!! As usual, Mr "golem" conduct the meeting, the way he present his stuffs~ arrghh! *slap head... Talk halfway, "errmm" "ehh" "wait let me check"...  Pls~~~~~~!!!!! Is that the way people conducts meetings? WTF!!   And saying July we're going for ISO 9000. Fuck off man~!! Jus look at the so called "extended hrs". Got so pissed off by Mr Liaw's email. "Pls do not tell other dept about our 3pm-11pm shift. It's still under trial"  Fuck U~!  Hope they burn in hell.....
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Sunday is a day i love and hate~~ It's a day for resting the mind and soul~ but it's also the day after tat....work!!!  mind's full of "her"..... think i'm gettin mad... images runnin wild~ guess i have to control myslf... :p 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Parthi's back from US~! He bought quite alot of stuffs back with him. Got a San Frans paper weight from him. He also bought D some candles. How nice of him. Keep pestering him about the Gibson Guitar he promised to buy for me in california, hahahhaa~~!  Well, another good news is, he has submit his resignation letter. Tis month, he, together with Desmond and SJ had tendered their resignation. Things are getting out of hand i can say. We just can't stand the rubbish the managnment had implemented on us. I suddenly felt the urge to&nbsp;leave the shit place as soon as i can. But i can't let my emotions rules over me. Have to look for a really good place, career, then i move out. Or else who knows it's another shithole again??~  Ady was looking rather sad about Par's departure and my interviews, guess after all, we go thru thick and thin together, the 3 Musketeers. All i can say is, i told him this place is sinking. If we dun get out of it fast, we might just sink with it? Think about it, he has a family, a cute son. The last thing i wish to see is he being drag along with the managements.   Called up Igames today, was told that the managing director is overseas and has to wait for his return before the 2nd interview can commends..... I'm getting a strong feeling that this 2nd interview is not gonna be a smooth sailing 1... I guess i just have to be myslf. If i'm not the 1 they are looking for, i guess so be it.   &nbsp;    
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It's been hell in office since monday. 1stly, manpower was like down to 4 persons, out of 10 over pple. 2ndly, the stupid "Ghost" (the nick we give to Mr Woo, our manager, cos he always sneak behind pple back) keeps ignoring us with all the popouts and emails, stating statistics were very low blah blah blah..... Can he open his eyes big and see? How many of us are there and how to handle? I wonder if his head is filled with grass~ no brain!!   today the same thing happens, thou patrick and ryan were around, so things gets alittle in control. Yet~~! The toopid Mr Liew, my sup, walks around with his eyes "closed" practically, shouting "answer call, answer call" Shit him. Can't he see tat we're busy?  Wat the hell.   
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i had an interview at this Igames Asia for the post of network/system engineer. Really had a tough time looking for the place. Walking from street to street at serangoon.... Asking those mama shop uncle but they are like so goon doo~ either tat or they refused to help~ Oh well, i managed to find it on time also~ Lucky!  The company appears to be those olden days shophouse. Althou the place is not tat impressive, who cares~? It's the post i'm interesting of. As usual, was handed an application form. Hate filling these forms, haven't my resume explained everything? Oh well, guess it's a routine for every job interview..  Shortly i've finished, i'm being invited~ yes invited~! (see how friendly they are) into the interview room. 2 guys 1 lady.. Lucky 1 guy went out to answer his phone so i ended up facing 2 persons~ Pheww... less pressure then~ Went on quite smoothly, i intro myslf, they asking me some questions.... all the while i keep telling myslf to keep my cool...maybe the anticipation to get this job, giving myslf alot of pressure....but~ doing quite well eh~   Will know the results by monday... hate waiting, but no choice... Pray hard~~~!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today was a rather busy day, until i forgot to be blue~ hahaha~!! Time was fast when u're busy. After work, i had a meeting wit Choon Boon, my agent. Speaking of Choon Boon, he's a rather interesting person. Instead of talking about insurance, everytime we meet up, we'll sure chat non-stop~ like father and son~! haha~! Well.. he's old enuff to be my dad afterall~ From him, i sort of learn something from his past experiences... Like today, i told him about the interview on wed, he told me quite alot of stuffs about interview. Asking myslf wat i wan from the job. And a rather interesting question one of his client encounter when he went for interview....   "Crossing a rushing river wit u, ur wife and ur mother. U only have 2 life vests. Who do u giv it to? Why?"   This is to test one's integrity. My answer? hahahaha~~~  After reaching home, i decided to try out the fitness corner downstairs since the gym has been closed.. Not wat i expected. It's worse than i expected~!! It's so freaking small corner... Sheeh... i decided to do a jog to the fitness corner near to the central, treat it as a warm-up. The distance is jus nice for a short sprint and a good warmup. Ahh~ At least the fitness corner is still not too bad compared to the one i seen earlier...  Good workout i can say, feel more refresh~! Shiok! :)
     
    
</post>


</Blog>