<Blog>


<date>31,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today is the last day of January the rest of the year. Let's have a party.  I stumbled upon a blog from Fwak! Animation  today. Some acquaintances of mine, Eddie Mort and Lili Chin are Fwak! and they created a successful series called Mucha Lucha. Anyway, in their blog they mentioned the Armory Gallery in Pasadena and an exhibit called Sensacional! So, we checked out that and the rest of Old Town Pasadena. I highly recommend the exhibit (it's free) and I plan on getting the book that accompanies the whole thing. So, thanks Eddie and Lili for the tip.  The Version 2.4 of billingstudio.com  is done. Well, as done as it ever gets, anyway. It's possible that I'll connect this blog from the site, but I still have reservations about that. I wonder if my clients (or potential clients) have a need to read this shtuff. They could like my work and want to buy it and then they find out I like spinach or something, and...kablooey. The little man that lives inside my head tells me that it doesn't matter what they think, and I have to agree - but then I could sit naked under the freeway with my principles and that will buy my veggie burgers and Guinness Stout?  What a weird world.  I've decided to go ahead producing "Road Trip," my picture book, by myself. I've been reading recently about the Children's writer's and illustrator's market, and they advise against self-publishing and how you should study the market to know what to write. This time I think I will have to ignore what I think is usually wise marketing strategy and do it anyway. Sometimes art is to market and sell and make a bagful of money, and sometimes art is just to satisfy something inside that comes out of your head and lands on the world and that's enough. Are you following me here? I already have enough money, so I think I need more art.  Looking out my window, I can see Century City and the Hollywood Hills. It's extremely clear today, the sun is going to set soon, and it's very beautiful. I had one of the busiest, craziest episodes of work this past week, along with finishing my website and working on my book illustrations. So I'm sitting here now with my latte and my ibook and my ipod and my floor-to-ceiling view of Los Angeles, and I feel like I've earned all of it.  If you haven't seen  The Triplets of Belleville  yet, you are missing out on one of the best pieces of animation in several years. I loved it.  It's quirky, weird story with hardly any dialogue, and the animation is just amazing. It's the best use of 2D/3D combination I've seen since  Iron Giant.  
    
    
</post>

<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This is a photo of my grandmother and I in 1982. I was 12. It was taken in front of the John Wayne statue at Long Beach Airport (John Wayne Airport), on my first trip to California ever. At the time, we lived in Phoenix, having been recently transplanted from Chicago.     It was a simple family vacation; we did the touristy stuff like Disneyland, Knott's Berry Farm, the Queen Mary/Spruce Goose, and Huntington Beach. I remember it as a good trip for those things, but mostly I remember it as the first time I was ever in love with a place. Standing at baggage claim, I looked at the differently-dressed people, I felt the moist air and saw the colors of California. I was hooked. I loved Southern California on sight as much as I had hated Phoenix two years earlier. I can still run the images through my brain like a movie reel. There's a clip looking out our rental car window from the 405 freeway, getting lost. A shot out of the porthole in our stateroom on the Queen Mary. Sorting through postcards on the bed in Dana Point. Standing on the beach, looking out at endless blue water. All the cars, tons of cars everywhere. At some point, I made up my mind that I would live in that place someday. Since then I've lived in lots of places, and some of them have felt like home. My first glimpse of Germany felt that way, and so does Chicago still. But no place gave me the feeling that I belonged somewhere like Southern California did. I had never really belonged anywhere up to the time of that trip. I just read another article that blasts California and takes the usual potshots at the traffic, the hodegpodge architecture, and the vast spread of Los Angeles County. I can't deny that traffic gives me a headache just like anyone else, and 2nd Street between Figueroa and Larchmont isn't exactly a string of Parisian Boulangeries. But something connects me to this place and makes me feel as if I was meant to come here. The beach in Malibu, the trendy cafes in Los Feliz and the galleries in Laguna Nigel definitely outweigh the potholes in Historic Philipinotown. Looking at myself in the mirror, I still see the kid who got stuck on a place and never forgot to come back. Then I look at this photo and I see the kid who had no idea what his life would be, only that he wanted some part of it spent where he was standing right at that moment. Yeah, it's weird to look at a photo and know what you were thinking at the time. But I do. It's hard to see behind the goofy glasses and the hair, but the kid in the knit tie is having a religious experience. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Will the blog-switching ever cease?  I've been having *issues* with iblog. Sometimes it publishes, sometimes it doesn't. I'm certainly not going to pay for the full license now, so it's back to the free blogger service.  I'll try to load up my previous blogs here. Wish me luck. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Things I'm Looking Forward To:  *  'Tis the Season - Dodgers! (vs. Rockies on April 10 - guess who's gonna be there?) *   
    
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Last Saturday, we went hiking in Eaton Canyon, just north of Pasadena. It was about 1 1/2 mile hike to a 50-foot waterfall, where we ate lunch and snacks and just chilled out. We even saw a "frogman" repel down the waterfall in a wetsuit. That was weird.  It was a fairly easy hike for the kids, except where in a few spots we had to cross a small stream. They wore water shoes, but I was worried they would slip on a rock. They were fine, of course.  Check it out:  urlLink http://www.ecnca.org  
    
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Watching The Detectives     Listening to: The Best of Elvis Costello    Sitting at work today. I have to finish a project that spilled over into the weekend. Details, details. It's a good thing I live across the street. It sucks that I'm missing a park day with Jenni and the kids.   Things I'm excited about right now:   * The fact that I can feel air pumping out of my little harmon/kardon desktop speakers. Playing:  Pump It Up . Nice.  * Dodger tickets for next Saturday  * I'm finally getting into the storyboards for  "Toothless,"  my new animated film   Working on the weekend reminds me of when I was a kid and we used to go with my mom to the Wheaton Rec Center while she taught a dance class. We could play in the basement with the pool tables (no balls or cues, but they were perfect for landing X-wing fighters), or hide in various cabinets.  I like being in buildings when they're empty. Cool places I've been when they were empty:  Wheaton High School Auditorium  A C-5 Aircraft  Metrocenter Mall (Phoenix)  Paramount Plaza, 4th Floor (New York)  Times Square, 2 AM (okay, it's never  completely  empty)  O'Hare, Minneapolis/St. Paul, LaGuardia, Sky Harbor, Miami Int'l, San Jose Int'l airports  There's a feeling of peace and at the same time, a feeling of intense excitement, as if anything could happen at any time. I also like being up and about before anyone else is, which is why I get up at 5:30 AM to work out. Sometimes I'm disappointed when I see a lot of cars driving around, which is weird, I know.  It's time now to finish up this project and get out of here.  
    
    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Update from last post:   urlLink Dodger game  was mucho cool. Everyone loved it. we left in the 7th inning because the little Ewok children were tired, but we finished the game at home on Fox. We won! It was a good game, good seats, really expensive beer and lots of bathroom trips. Just what every sporting event should be.   About two months ago, I decided to get back in shape. Now, I'm not overweight by any standards, but I just felt like my health was juuuuuust starting to creep away from me. I was always a really skinny kid - even teased in grade school for looking wimpy (the glasses and microscope didn't help that image). I decided that to be big was to be cool, so I started looking for ways to "get huge." Around my junior year in high school I started lifting weights and taking supplements. Okay. I say supplements. What I mean is beef hearts, kidneys, whey, and soy protein in powder form, mixed into milk. No, it didn't taste good, and yes, it probably clogged my arteries. The caviat to drinking this vile mass-producing beverage is that if you stop working out and keep drinking it, you will get mucho fat. Guess what? After a couple of years of this criminal activity I weighed 187 lbs. and looked like the pillsbury doughboy - not the heavy man of muscle I wanted to be.  *note: I only use weight as a point of reference here. I don't usually weigh myself, and I know that even as I get thinner, my weight could go up due to increased muscle mass/density. The weight isn't the important thing.   I didn't even notice how I *really* looked until I got out of Air Force basic training (at 165 lbs.) and saw a photo of myself on my first day. Yikes. Ironically, after my dream of putting on lots of weight, I had to resort to strong measures to get rid of it. The American Way. Over the years I continued to work out and run on a sporadic basis, and I felt pretty good. After I became vegetarian, it was even easier to keep my weight down, even without exercise. I hovered around 172 until 2002, when I became vegan (no animal products whatsoever). I dropped about 15 lbs. quickly and felt great.  In 2003, I started to creep slowly back up to my old weight (I'm an artist and spend hours every day...sitting). Even my 34-inch waisted Levi's were feeling kind of snug and uncomfortable. After a long business trip to San Francisco, I decided that 2004 would be the year I got back to my body's natural state - athletic and thin - before I found myself buying new pants. I started out slow, just walking every morning at 6 AM and doing simple calisthenics - back to 3rd grade. Nothing fancy, just push-ups, sit-ups, and hatha yoga stretches I learned in New York. It worked, and I maintained for a couple of weeks. In the second month of that, I noticed a slight decline in my waist, but nothing spectacular. I decided to get serious.  I read a couple of books by  urlLink Jake "Body by Jake" Steinfeld  , and I got (excuse the phrase, please) pumped up. I started pushing myself more. Even though I eat extremely healthy, I do tend to eat *alot*. So, I started to limit my portions and my snacks. Beer only on weekends, that sort fo thing. It was working better, but I decided to take it a step further and join a gym. I researched a few downtown, but I wasn't thrilled with them or their high membership rates. I didn't need the whole gym, just a few areas. This led me to the decision to buy a   Body by Jake Total Body Trainer  . It's one of those things that does about 15 exercises using rubber bands for resistance. It had a 30-day money back guarantee, so I dove in and tried it.  The results have been fantabulous. After about a week I was several steps ahead of where I would have been before I started using it. After two weeks, Jenni started commenting on my new (old) shape. After three weeks, my 32-inch waist Levi's (that I bought long ago but didn't wear because of my former fatness) were falling off me. Awesome.  Now I'm more determined than ever to keep going and keep it up consistently. I can't describe what it's like to feel like this again. I've had a small belly bulge since 1989 (beer, drugs, and pizza will do that to even the thinnest person), and even that is vanishing into flatness. I looked at pictures of me from that time and it's very cool to think that I look better at 33 than I did at 19. Nice. I feel better, too - more energetic (cliche, but true) and ready to go hiking, skateboarding, and ocean swimming.  That's all I have to say 'bout that. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today was really great. I got out of bed.  I feel a bit strange because we've just moved to Idaho and there's a weird smell in the house.  I'm so hardcore. Me and Buzz went to the mall today, and I stole a whole heap of stuff. I got a Good Charlotte CD, a couple of DVDs and some new boots. Buzz got caught, but he fought his way out, and then we stole some lady's car and smashed it into a phone booth.  Last night I had to shave my entire body. Apparently, the lice that I caught from Amanda's friend are really hard to get rid of. I look quite strange with no hair and eyebrows. I'd post pictures, but my webcam is broken.  I want to tell the world that my girlfriend Jenni is the bomb! She made pizza last night, and even though I burnt my lips on the cheese, it was awesome!!!  (This one is oddly TRUE-DB)   I am updating this journal for the first time in ages, because I've been in prison.  Today, I got a digital camera! Yes! Here's ten thousand photographs of my cat.  I want to say thanks to my dad for giving me my own computer and digital camera. Here's a photo of my room. The weather in Ontario is cold. I have nothing more to say.  I went to the doctor yesterday, and he said I have bipolar disorder, which makes me different enough to be interesting, but the same as all the other cool people with bipolar disorder.  You should all do this quiz! It's amazingly accurate. You just put in your name and birthday, and it will tell you who you're sexually compatible with.  That's enough for now. But I'll leave you with this poem I wrote. It's about my friend Robert, who has bipolar disorder. Just like me. And Heidi.   Created with the  urlLink Gregor's Semi-Automatic LiveJournal Updater&trade; . Update your journal today! Powered by  urlLink Rum and Monkey    
    
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       An on-call weekend for me. I carry a pager with me everywhere, like a thoracic surgeon. Only I'm not a thoracic surgeon, I'm an art director and production manager. Comparing open heart surgery and graphic design really puts the word "emergency" in the right perspective, doesn't it?  Nevertheless, I answer pages faithfully and call in to get voice mails of the latest "emergencies." Somewhere there's a bar chart without a point. A time line of events needs a central theme,  stat!  Whenever I sit back an analyze what I do for a living, it always leaves me with a profound new perspective on what's important in the world. Oddly enough, it doesn't make me hate my job, it makes it easier for me to do.  Everyone in my home jumps at the beeping pager and instantly sighs, "Ohhhhh...mmmaaaannnn." It doesn't always mean I have to go anywhere even, but the reaction is the same every time. I'm glad, actually, because it means they care that I might not be here.  I picked up  When Character Was King,  by Peggy Noonan today. It's a bio of Ronald Reagan, and it looks really interesting. I don't identify myself as a Republican, Democrat, conservative, liberal, or otherwise. I side with logic and common sense - that's how I vote, and that's how I choose who I admire. I admired Reagan as a kid, but it's interesting to read about him now as an adult - understanding more about politics and the effects of his presidency.  I won an imac in an ebay auction. It gets here Wednesday and I can't wait. I'm turning my ibook over to Jenni and going for a little more speed and compatibility. I ordered an airport card for it and now we'll have two wireless macs in our apartment. Maybe I'll start selling access on my network? 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Oy. Vot a dilemma.  Okay, not really a dilemma. A decision. Harder than picking a president this year, but easier than choosing Cherry Wheat over Boston Lager.  Just when I think things are getting dull, things get un-dull.  Am I being ambiguous and enigmatic? Yup - on purpose, too. You never know who might be reading.   I have been presented with an opportunity that comes along every 2 years or so (because the last two were about that far apart). It means humongous changes for all 4 of us. It's a good thing, but still requires a lot of thought.  Stay tuned. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So it's 99% official - we're moving back to NYC this summer. The 1% is me trying to figure out if there's a deal-killer in there somewhere. Probably not.  So this Nick Berg thing is eating at me. Not because the act in itself horrifies me (although it's pretty bad), but because of the reaction of the media and our government.  The fact that we are shocked at the extreme actions of Al Queda and the Iraqis demonstrates that we don't understand our enemy, and we are not really prepared to do whatever we can to win this war. Obviously, they are prepared to do anything to win and communicate that to us every time they blow themselves up or kill a hostage.  What's the answer?  Win. That's the answer! I did not agree with going into Iraq or Afghanistan in the first place, but I think that now that we've committed to being there, we need to win the war. Otherwise, what are all these soldiers dying for? That's the real tragedy.  This is similar to George Washington crossing the Delaware on Christmas eve, except this time we are playing the part of the British. We are too far into the war in Iraq to be gentlemanly and we are going to lose.  Al Queda is in it to win, and we should be, too. All of this apology for tearing up the country and political correctness is not getting us anywhere.  That's my two cents. 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I think   Stayin' Alive   is probably one of the greatest songs ever written. Am I serious? You'll never know.   Whether you're a mother or whether you're a brother, you're stayin' alive.  Meditate on that a bit. It'll come to you.  I'm trying to get into New York City mode again. I thought the theme to  Saturday Night Fever  would do it. Oh, wait...I think I can see..yes! I can see a falafel stand...it's..in...Bed Stuy...How Deep is My Love... for falafel?  We went to Malibu this morning and hung out at the beach. Ahhh, California. 76 degrees, 4-5 foot surf, our dolphins were there. I'm really gonna miss all this. Fer sure, really. It's going to be hard not to be able to drive to the beach whenever we feel like it. I guess we'll have to find an apartment close to Central Park. I have about as many good memories of that park as I do of Malibu and Santa Monica Pier. Jenni and I are trying to cram some California into our eye sockets before we leave. There's definitely a trip to  urlLink Pea Soup Andersen's  and Solvang in there somewhere. No one will never know my affinity for Pea Soup Andersen's. If that place ever closes it will be the end of an era. Maybe by that time I will be able to buy it - and I would. What a cool business to be in, and a great location. A germ of an idea, and you are here to witness it. Breathe in the scent of capitalism. It smells like Pea Soup and crackers.  My trip to New York was really good. I did some walking around and even ran into some old Nickelodeon friends. They were so great and happy (surprised) to see me, I felt like I never left (thanks Mason and Amy!). That sold the move a little more, I have to admit. Gotta plan a housewarming party right around August. I stayed at the  urlLink Alex Hotel , one of those boutique hotels that are so popular now. It reeked of taste, but it wasn't very practical. It looked really cool, but it took some adjusting to. The best hotel I ever stayed in was the  urlLink Fairmont  in San Jose. Best service  ever . The Park Hyatt in San Francisco was pretty good, too. I have a thing about hotels, okay? Leave me alone.  I promised Gwendolyn we could have an Eloise slumber party at the Plaza when we get to NYC. I'm sure I'll have a review of that one, too. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I sent this to my friend  urlLink Lauren Antler  to qualify for her Friend of the Week. Who knows if she'll even get my e-mail? I better post this here just in case.  So I'm running in downtown LA (which is where I currently live). It's about 5:30 AM and the streets are still mostly deserted (which isn't altogether different from 5:30 PM in downtown). I get to 9th/Hope St. and across the way I see an old lady in a wheelchair. This 110-year old Civil War relic is pushing herself backwards through the crosswalk with her tiny slippered feet, which barely touch the ground.   Nifty wheelchair, though. Much too cool for her.  When she gets to the middle, she sort of stops and spins around, just kind of doing little donuts in the middle of the street. Looks like fun, but the oncoming light turns green. A debate begins in my little oxygen-deprived brain. Do I run into the middle of the intersection and find out what the deal is (and possibly risk exposure to one of those hidden-camera shows where the lady is actually Jamie Kennedy)? Do I watch the tragic events unfold before me and risk disqualifying myself as Friend of the Week?  Sickeningly Good-Citizen-Boy Scout that I am, I run into the street and grab her wheelchair, pushing her to the other side just as traffic (what the fuck, people???!!) crosses the intersection. I resist the urge to ask, "What the dealie, Pop-a-Wheelie?" and instead ask her if she is okay. The whole incident didn't seem to phase her a bit and she asks me to push her over to the other side of the street, which of course I do. What this Titanic Survivor is doing scuttling along the streets of LA at 5:30AM I will never know. Mostly because I didn't ask. I didn't want to know, to tell you the truth, because I was afraid she would end up over at our apartment for bagels and coffee at 6:15.  In those life-changing (hers, not mine) moments before the rescue, I can't believe I actually struggled with whether or not I continue my run or slow down my precious heart rate to save some old lady's ass? I mean, it's not like there weren't THREE OTHER PEOPLE watching this all go down. Am I a yuppie cad because I even toyed with the idea of ignoring her plight? No.  I'm a yuppie Boy Scout because this even bothers me at all and I can't just get on with my friggin' life.  But thank Allah I have a reason to qualify for Friend of the Week. I gotta do this again! 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
           Feel free to post your thoughts about our 40th President - good or bad. It would be interesting to have a cornucopia of remembrances of Ronald Reagan. Click on the "comments" tag and type your little fingers down to the first knuckle. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Check it out. A new comic idea. I'm thinking of doing this as a series.   urlLink So New York #1   It's very random. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
           urlLink   
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Non-dads probably won't understand the significance of this. As a former non-dad, I wouldn't have. I can barely grasp it now.  We rented a car at the Hertz downtown Marriott for Saturday's trip. It's right across the street from our building. NedFred Pastamobile® has seen his last days of VW Jetta GL reliability, so we rent for long trips. Poor NedFred, we offer a moment of silence for your increasing mileage and declining performance.    When I became a dad, I was prepared for lots of things. Diapers, filling juice cups, frequent bathroom visits, reading the same story 4 times in a row. What no one could possibly have prepared me for is shuttling between two toy stores for an afternoon, agonizing over the purchase of a Beanie Baby giraffe vs. a tiny blue plastic animal that cost 5 cents. In retrospect, I should really be prepared for  anything , by virtue of having tortured my own parents in the same ways. Their insanity becomes infuriatingly more understandable year by year.   So we're in Solvang, the World's Most Adorable Little Dutch Town in the middle of Dude-ifornia, populated mostly by knife-coveting redneck military masses of flesh in flabby tank tops (when I was in the service, we had standards, man). Okay, so it's not the center of coastal culture, but it has a kind of Euroclean, wine-swishing flair to it, and we're inside a sweaty toy store sifting through misshapen plastic animals. I'm cranky because I had visions of Jenni and I lounging in a shaded beer garden while the little imps play in the grass, and she's thinking  I can't believe you didn't expect this.  I'll never learn.  So this morning I have to return the rental, and like the Good Boy I am, I clean it out first. It must be the result of conditioning from working in the service industry as a youth, but I can't help but pull out the half-eaten pretzel sticks, cracker crumbs and papers from the back seat. Yeah, yeah, I know they have vacuums at Hertz. I'm the same Thoughtful Guy who stacks the plates at restaurants so the busperson doesn't have to work too hard after we leave. Some things just stick with you. In my thorough cleaning, I toss coffee cups, paper menus and a little paper bag (you can see this coming, can't you?) into the Marriott valet trash can. What a good boy I am.  >>>$2.35/gallon for gas? Jesus Christ! Don't we have oil in North America?  Three hours later, there's a search going on in our apartment. Where's the blue guy? Isn't there a paper bag around here? Did you see a paper bag? Did we leave it in the car? Of course not, I threw everything in the...  ...car...  ...away.  Oh darn.  One more trip to the Marriott.  The lady at the counter at the Marriott treated my little emergency like it was the most important thing that could have happened to her that morning. Either she was really bored, or my plate-stacking (and old-lady-wheelchair-saving) karma account was paying dividends. She radioed the maid, who handed me a plastic bag of coffee cups, cigarettes, half-eaten muffins, something greenish, and - will wonders never cease - a wrinkled, clothespinned paper bag with the tiniest five-cent blue creature I've ever searched for.  I grumbled my way back across the street, bitching into my cellphone about our priorities and stupid, useless five cent little blue guys - even though it was my fault I was on that mission anyway. The elevator ride made me think about it a little more, but I didn't  really  understand the importance of little five cent blue guys until I got the biggest hug in the world before I even got all the way through the door. You'd think I'd been back from the Titanic with the Hope diamond.  These are the kinds of things that not too long ago I would let go and not figure too importantly into the scheme of things. A blip on the radar screen of my life. It wasn't really that important to  me. Aren't there more little blue guys in the world? Oh, I still don't take this all too seriously. Will Gwendolyn remember little five cent blue guy when she's 15-going-on-29? Probably not, unless this blog is still around. Little five cent blue guy will be at the bottom of a landfill, releasing his greenhouse gasses and looking just as cute as he did in the store.  Maybe by that time, this story will actually be relevant to the non-dad.    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm on the other coast now (I still refer to California as "my" coast, so this would be "the other one"). I haven't been this busy in a long time. Oh. Wait. The last time I was in New York. Something about this city and the absence of anyone to come home to prompts people (okay, me) to work late hours. If I were single it would be really scary.  I haven't even had time to save anyone's life or stop violent crime. Not that I've ignored the fine citizens of Gotham, I just haven't seen any. My spider sense hasn't tingled all week.   Laundry List  Laundry Food shopping Post photo of name badge on blog      Laundry List  Laundry Food shopping 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Some people I talk to think New York City is a great place to be - unless you have children, love nature, or enjoy the more subtle, quiet pleasures of life. After all, it's a dirty place. Grimy. Unromantic. Noisy. Not at all like  The Heartland,  or  The Suburbs , where I understand it's heavenly paradise all the time. I mean, when you've got a WalMart, Pier 1, and Olive Garden, what else is there, really?   So this morning I went on a reconnaissance mission to see if I could capture this soulless pit of hell on pixels. I started in the dangerous black hole of Central Park. Here's my first pictorial report of what I found and my conclusions:  This is no place for children. They will be eaten immediately:    Even if they make it past the monsters, they will have to climb on this:    For adults as well, it's just one big concrete jungle:    To see great works of art, you have to go to a museum and pay high admission prices:      Sometimes I could not see  anything,  because there was too much debris in my way:    I noticed many people leaving in small groups, even if they had to row their way out:    This poor man had to use a special breathing apparatus just to stay alive:    Look at all that dirt! Disgusting!    Rickety, shapeless wooden structures were strewn about on the unsightly brick pathways:    The whole place was infested with horrible, vicious creatures:    Like this sickly, dying willow, I weep for the city:    That's all for today's report. I can't go on. It's too horrible. 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       What a celebration of color! Music! The People! Not to mention the glorious fireworks display over the majestic tower of Our Lady Liberty. I was thrilled, I was humbled, I was...  ...in Peekskill.  Yes, while New York City rocked in our country's 228th year, I was upstate visiting Tootie, Blair and Mrs. Garrett. Actually, it was my good friends Scott and Michelle, who hosted a combination 4th of July/birthday party (Michelle's) at their home in Peekskill. It was nice to get out of the city for a day, and I hadn't seen my friends for years (since our  Blue's Clues  days). I met another friend, Dayna, at Grand Central and rode the train up to suburbia. We hung out, drank beer and mojitos, ate veggie bratwurst and talked (mostly) about George. No, not the father of our country - the other one - the mentally retarded benificiary of the presidency. Many attempts were made to steer the conversation into happier waters ("Hey, is that new siding?" "The mojitos are great!"), but somehow it always came around to W. Ahhh, democracy.  I was glad to get away for awhile, but the only thing missing from the day was Jenni, Jacob and Gwendolyn. They should be here soon, and until then I will get by with cell phones and e-mail. I can't wait for the kids to see NYC again. I love Los Angeles, but New York is more stimulating - there's always something to see, just walking around the block. I want them to get the idea that there are many different people and ways to live, not just the middle-class suburban model.  The plan for the day is to take the DV cam and find something interesting to capture. My cash flow is on the low side at the moment (a result of living in two cities at once), so I will have to find cheap entertainment for the day.       Party favor and peach that is now inside my belly  
    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Morning: Rolled around, stretched, gave a leisurely yawn. Turned over, looked at alarm clock.     7:17 AM     Oh darn.    Whore's bath, throw toothbrush in bag, grab phone, out the door.    Welcome to Friday. Hopefully I'll sign my lease today and all will be right with the world.     
    
    
</post>


</Blog>