<Blog>


<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Lets see I just woke up to the sound of my stove clicking its not stopping. >_   Im suppose to go with my dad(Peter)for breakfast at the Ranch. I need to ask him for $42 so that I can get two weeks worth of unlimited metro. >_   You know whats sad... There was a time that I really looked up to my dad. BUt I was little then. That was before I knew or realized what kind of person he is. Sad I guess. =/    Oh well... Guess Ill update with you later... Im not sure what else to write at this point... Well maybe Ill give you guys a poem.     Good-bye Daddy  Once upon a time in a land far away.  A poor old man died one day.  He was alone with no family or friends.  No one to cry when he reached his end.  He was so lonely through out his life.  He had not money, no home, no wife.  Through out his youth, he was a cruel boy.  He played with women like they were his toys.  He grew real thin, and lost his looks.  He hung around with drugies and crooks.  He one day had a daughter.  But she left him just like her mother.  He was a mean old man. All alone.  He never even called her on the phone.  So when he went. No one cried.  Not even me. For the my dad that died.       -Joy   ----------------------------------------------------------------   Lets see, later on that day... went with dad for breakfast. bought Ms. Sonias Gift. bought metro for the week... went from 200 bucks to 240... ^^  Began cleaning My room at some point... It was a real mess... It was worst than Jasons was... YEA YOU GUESSED IT  
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Well  Lets start with last night, My grandma got drunk, my parents fought, my mom and I fought, my dad got mad. The house went into chaos. The music was blasted. Someone slapped somebody. Somethign broke... Everyone was yelling.... That was about 2am. This is was I woke up to the sound to. Isnt it great *sarcasm*   Today was long... and tiring... I went to therapy, Jason went with me... Which was sweet of him. He didnt really say anything... I guess he was bored. I liked him being there, but I found myself, trying not to say something that would make me cry or something, because truth is, I feel weak when I cry in front of him. I feel like a cry baby. *sigh* But what can I do? Im a sensitive person, despite the way I present myself. Pam told me that Im strong or something along those lines. Im so tired of that. I am not strong. Se was right about one thing though, I do want/need to be taken care of. Jason takes care of me, Thats one of the reasons I love him so much. He takes care of me.      Anyway, afterwards we went in cab to chase and my payroll card was not letting me take out money... That pissed me off. I got so angry... I think me getting so frustrated annoyed Jason. I look at it now, and am like "why the hell did you get so mad" I feel like I made a complete idiot out of myself for getting so upset about money. But anyway.... after a few hours of going from bank to bank and atm machine to atm machine, we find out that I never fixed my pin number or what not. I felt so stupid... but was excited cuz I could now get my money... I wanted to go right to Pioneers ATM machine, but Jason said for us to go to Chase. I getI was acting to hyper, because it annoyed him, but then he explained that he was getting a rash in his inner thighs, then I remembered having the same thing. I guess I felt a bit bad, because I guess I feel like even thought he has strong immunities and doesnt get sick often, his physical fitness is unhealthy... I worry about him.   It all turned out alright, Jason seemed very affectionate today which was nice... finally he went no the bus to go home, and I went upstairs. Mom and Carlos went to the movies, so I was left babysitting Emily. My stove went crazy with the clicking and gas and stuff... I began to Panic, I called my mom, she was no help. Eventually it stopped but then I got mad paranoid that I was going to die today.    Then Jason started talking about his chest was hurting, so I began to worry about him. If he had a heart attack, or wound up in the hospital I dont know what I would do. He is all Ive got. The mere thought of something happening to him makes me want to cry. I dont like that he''s constantly in pain. I wish I could take all that into me. Poor Puppy...     Heh, Puppy...I love calling him that. He called me snuggles before.... it was sweet. For soem reasons I love little pet names like that, I think its sweet. Jason doesnt call me snuggles n e more... I kinda wish he did... I liked it. I call him puppy all the time... He really is my puppy. I love taking care of him, I guess thats why I wanted money so bad, so that if he needs it, I have it for him.  Bleh sad I know   
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          I just woke up, and I feel real yucky. I dont even want to go to work today. But I have to so that my pay check comes in decent...well atleast today is the last day. Im going to ask Sharim about tomorrow's Boxing match. I wanted to invite my dad and monstro. But Im not even sure if my mom is going to let me attend. Bleh. What else is new?  I cant wait till Im 18 Any way yea. Last night I wrote a letter for Jason, telling him how I feel. But I doubt Im going to even deliver it. Maybe Diane is right, maybe we should spend some time apart... bleh. But what else worries me, is I have a funny feeling that this "Online crush" she has is in fact Jason. And I think Jason encourages it. But I dont know, That could just be me assuming things. I find her really annoying. And Jason says he does too... so maybe not. Im just so tired of all of this. I want to ask Pam, my shrink if she can give me some anti depressents or something. I wouldnt mind seeing the world in rose colored glasses right about now. You know what else is bothering me, is that I used to be suicidal, and depressed all the time, and didnt care about anything, my body went entirely numb. That feeling is comming back. I barely feel human contact anymore. All I feel now is tormented love for Jason, btu its more like Im feeling teh pains of love more than enjoying it. I can be laughing and smilng, and then a second goes by and I begin to think. Why do I bother laughing, no one even notices my smile. Bleh. 
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Lets see, What happened today? At first today I was suppose to go to the zoo with my job. I was goign to take Giselle along, but the trip got cancelled due to rain... I didnt really want to to go to work after that, I went to Jason's house being he wasnt going to school. I spent the day with him. You know I realize, Im a very depressed person. I look at him and he seems so distant to me. I love him with all my heart and yearn to be loved in the same way. But that will never happen. Hes not even in love with me. Which is messed up because Id do anything for him, and he knows it. Instead he loves two other girls who he's not even with.      Did they give him the love he deserves? Did they change their entire lives around to make him happy? Did they put their family and friends aside to be with him? Did they do his essay for school for him because he was having trouble? Did they sit him down to work on a report that he kept putting off? Do they worry about him the way I do? Do they wish they can take all his bad memories, fears, pain and put it into themselves so that he wont have to feel it? Do they make sure that everything in his life is going okay before they even think about themselves. Do they cry at the mere thought of him being in harms way? I do. WOuld they take a bullet for him? I would.       And all I really want in return is to be loved by him, for me to be the only one in his heart. For him to think abotu me throughout the course of his day. For him to not even feel the need to look at otehr women because he knows he has me. For him to respect me as a person.        It hurts being with him. But I guess theres nothing I can do, I  am a slave to my love and to all of my emotions. There is nothing I can do to change that.         People I feel threatened by in my relationship     1. Kristie  2. Vanessa  3. Karen aka Toby Wan  4. Thin and beautiful young ladies that I know he'd be attracted to.      People ask me why? And Ill say it.  I am ugly.  I am fat.  I have messed up hair.  I am depressed.  I am dumb.  I am not feminine.  I complain.  I am often sad.  I am spiteful.       All things that make me unattractive and unwanted.       I wonder if he'll ever love me the way I love him.       You know what hurts most, is the fact that I am not important in anyones life. I mean nothing to everyone. And then the one person who is my everything, and I beg that he feel the same, will never love me the way I wish he did.       I feel used sometimes... and it hurts. I dont know what Im suppose to do anymore...        If I die, would n e one cry?     What if I commit suicide right now, how long would it take people to realize Im dead. What is I fell into a coma, when I wake up, who would be by my side. A worst thought is, Jason, the person I would love to waken up my eyes to seeing, if I had been asleep for too long, he would probably assume its okay for him to date others. And would have moved on by the time I woke up.        I hate sex. It makes me sad.  I hate liquor. It makes me mad.  I hate drugs. It makes ppl bad.  I hate myself. And the life I have.   
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We got to the pool... when I went into the locker room, the girls from YMPJ were still getting ready, I changed quickly then went to rinse myself in the shower... IT WAS FREEZING!!!!!!! But that was alright... I let my hair down and we all went out to the pool. We saw the guys all in the indoor pool already, btu the girls were cold so wanted to go to the out door pool. Michelle and I dipped into the outside pool, then decided to join the guys... THAT WHEN ALL THE FUN STARTED. PEOPLE NOTICED ME. THEY WERE HAPPY I CAME. Everyone was dunking everyone else... I got dunked so many times. But I dunked people too... IT WAS SOOOOOOOOO GREAT. And it wasnt even like Jason ignored em, every so often he pull me off to the side and we'djust sort of hold each other... ;-) and touch eachother. It was so great. The water was so much fun.... Jason was having fun, I was acting crazy... I actually rememebr how to swim... But I can only swim beneath the water... Divad taught me how to make my sef sink to the bottom of the pool and hold myself there...  I dont think I could have had a more perfect day. Eventually it was time to leave, but being were in there and had so much fun no one complained... besides I WAS STARVING... lol... we went to mcdonalds, and everyone acted crazy there too... It was so much fun... We went to the train,Which for some odd reason was equally fun. Then got t the block.   I was a bit paranoid that my mike was going to see me then tell shara I skipped work to go to the pool. >_  But who cares. I had soooo much fun.  Everyone decided to play baseball... so Jason and I went to watch, but oddly enough, we wound up in the playground area, and sort of layes on the slide...  We had a weird debate about circumsision... which ended pretty Blah.   But I didn't dwell on it... the day turned out too beautifully.  I got home... mom and dad were on the computer ¬ ¬  Stupid people... Cant wait till Im 18 to get out of here...  Mom told me I could go out friday (which is today) Because Ihad to babysit... I got pissed, because I wanted to go to Jasons house... I barely go over there anymore... bleh....  She could have told me ahead of time you know, and I wouldnt have cared so much.   Im going to bake lauros cake today... I hope it comes out alright.   I might make Jasons while Im at it... If I make Jasons, his will probably be marble cake, and I might make lauros french vanilla....  Im not sure yet.     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay well one things that should be said is that I did get to go to the pool. I played hookie from work and went to pick up Jason. While I was sitting at what i like to call a cement sttop sort of thing, my hand felt something crawl on it. Me being scared of bugs jumped up, and looked around. but then I saw this furry little worm like creaturre with about a billion legs. It has a head, which looked more like an eye ball. I think it might have been a catepillar, being Ive never seen one before, but it still kind of worried me. So I just aort of watched it, it was so weird. I think it was an alien worm, here to spy on the human race... but being I was nice to my friend Alien bug, when the aliens take over, they will be nice to me for nothurting there pet. ^^  Anyway, Jason came out, and from the moment I saw him I knew the day was going to be full of smiles, I showed him my alien bug friend, who had just been hurt, and I felt bad. See what happened was he was trying to climb a statue but was really struglling. But after like 20 minutes he made it all the way to atleast the middle... lol... but then he fell. I jumped because he fell on his back, and wasnt moviing... Poor Alien bug... he was my friend I hope he's alright. Jason said it was a centepide with a bunch of fur... I dont hink he was.   
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          I dont feel well. My throat is sore, my head doesnt seem screwed on straight, My stomach hurts, I feel disgusting. I dont even want to go to work... Imma leave a little early I think. I dont really want to be there all day. Im getting tired of that environment. Maybe I wont hate it as much when they get the new place. Or maybe once fall comes it'll be alright, cuz then there would be less young women. But then again, they're going to be on intervale... And I really dont want to be traveling back and forth, Im beginning to hate public transportation entirely.   Its so freakin' weird the way my head works. I can be completely happy one minute, and entirely miserable the next. You know what I think it is, I have yet to find my passion... My erason for being... if all else fails what would I do. What would I work on... I like to write, but it doesnt comfort me anymore. I like to draw, but I gte bored of it. I liek to take pictures, but I dont feel it anymore. What is my passion. Its funny how everyone has something they love and enjoy doing, and can share it with people. Some people have this passion to do arts or sing, or dance. And it comforts them. Some people love the sound of music.  Some swim   Some people have friends to talk to.   Tell me world. What do I have. I dont feel like I have anything anymore. I dont even remember who I am.   I used to be a writer. I used to be an artist. I used to be a photographer. I used to be a thinker.  I used to be an activist. I used to be so many things.  What am I now? Who am now?   I feel so alone in all of this... no one seems to understand the way I feel. I want someone to understand. I want someone who can relate to how I feel. I want a friend. A stranger. Someone to talk to.   Im not even sure what it is that I lost, the was so precious to me anyway, that all these things in my head occured. Where did I change. I wasnt always like this. Im almost sure of it.  Damn this is turning out to be the most depressing summer of my life.   T.T  Oh I forgot   15 Days until my birthday...  Yippie    YOU KNOW WHATS FUNNY.   I wanted to ask Jason "Can I go to the pool too?" But then I remembered, you know he pobalbly wouldnt want me there anyway, and secondly I doubt anyone from YMPJ wants me there... So I didnt even ask. I hope he has fun though, he's been pretty down lately, he will definetly enjoy going. He loves the water.       
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          You know what... I was waiting for Jason to get on so I can talk to him... and stuff. Then I realize, its wednesday. He's gone with Che to film at that club... bleh.... He gets home so late wednesdays. I hope he has enough energy for school tomorrow... Id hate for him to miss another day.... but if he does... I think Id like to go to his house, just so that I may lay with him... and fall asleep in his arms... but then again... I really do not want him to miss school again... he missed today, and thats bad enough.... But I love spending as much time with him as possible... Damn I am head over heals in love with this guys. I see him everyday, and he still never bores me...  I want to marry him... spend the rest of my life with him. Bleh... imma shut up now  
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          New Roc was so much fun... I mean EXTREMELY. We played lazer tag, went on the double shot ride, ate pizza, played this war game for about 3-4 hours... IT WAS SO GREAT. I DIDNT THINK ABOUT ANYTHING BUT HAVING FUN THE ENTIRE TIME THERE. I loved it. I mean really truly loved it.  After wards we went to "Casa" which is this really spiritual organization on brook avenue, where they had a workshop, filled with spoken word and deep spirituality. It was so nice... I hope to meet activist like that when I am older. It is so nice. Minus the fact that We were let out at 6.40-50 Which pissed me off a bit... But hey it was all good. When I got to the block I saw Jay talking to Lea and stuff, so I just sorta of sat there with them.  I told them about my exciting day and stuff... It was wonderful... Then Divad came the subject changed to YMPJ going to the pooltomorrow, and Lea invited Jason. He must be happy, I know how he feels about pools. Heck, I havent been to a pool since florida, I sure do miss it. I really do. But I never get invited to go to that sort of thing. Especially by like n e one from the block, yet alone Lea. But Jason, he's so popular in a way. People love having him around. They invite him anywhere. Its nice. I guess I look up to him in a way. Im never the center of attraction.   Can I be honest here? Yea of course, you dont know me, you dont care. Well... It makes me feel bad when Jason gets invited to all these fun things, and has all these friends... I wish I was a part of all that. I mean I would love to go to the pool. But no, no one invites Tiffany... she doesnt do that. No one notices me. Im invisble.... I dont get invited anywhere. bleh. It sucks.   Like Jason said "No one even remembers [me], enless [I'm] right in front of them"   No truer words have ever been said to me. And you know what they say truth hurts...  You know whats worst, even when I am in front of them, they dont see me.   I like to think I have a secret admirer though, someone in the world thinks about me everyday, and wants to be my friend. And wants to invite me places. Some where in the world, tehre is a circle waiting for me.  They'd invite me to the pool Im sure of it...  I hope he goes though. He'd really enjoy it. =/
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Today we are suppose to go to New Roc City today... Im paying for Shanae so Im not really going to have any money to spend on aside from whats included in the group payment, but thats fine. I trust her. She'll ay me back... anyway yea... I think I lost five bucks. Which isnt cool. but oh well...its just money right? Even though Im slowly runnin broke... >_ 
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Okay, got to work. Checked my planner... Discussed plans with Leslie...  Now... Lunch time... All the girls took their lunch break, and went out, so Leslie, Sharim, Julissa and myself began to have a conversation on bisexual/homosexuality. Which was interesting. I dont care who knows that Im gay these days... Im proud of myself and who I am.  Anyway we were waiting for Myra to come back so that Leslie and I can go buy food at Taco Bell.   Leslie seems so interested with the whole bisexuality thing... I think shes bi curious but wont admit it... or hasnt reached that level yet.   Anyway, we came back from taco bell, and were having a workshop in which we were going to go outside... April and Crystal got into a fight, almost knocking Myra to the ground while hold Maricruz' son. They also knocked over a chair while Shanae was stil in it... I couldnt take all the drama, so my chest got tight. Crystal got fired. April didnt. Shanae was just upset... but they didnt blame her at all. Maricruz was happy to see her son safe, and laughing.    After all the drama was done we had cake and celebrated Jadines ending of an abusive relationship, and Leslies Birthday. I wonder if Id get a cake or card for my birthday which is in 17 wonderful days. ^^   Jason picked me up. With a bag of chocolate covered cherries.. ^^ I LOVE THEM SO MUCH, IM EATING ONE NOW!!! YUMMY!!!!! But yea, we made it back to the block and pretty much chilled with everyone... Josephine was so happy seeing me and Jason together and lovey dovey.. which was annoying after a while, chilli hated it... I dont know it over all, was an okay day... Im quite content at the moment.   I think Im alot happier then Ive been in a while... Jason made me very happy today, just because I felt very close to him today... We didnt do n e thing extraordinary or different but it was nice anyway. Just being with him made me so happy, I really felt strong love comming from him today. It was such a wonderful feeling. 
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Well. I feel kind of bad at this point. Yesterday, I went to work, we didnt really do much, I dont care... Im not looking for more things to do at this point. Nay way, we did not go to boxing. Because so many girls didnt really want to go, and others didnt hae on sweats and stuff. SO anyway, after work I went to the block as usual, and to my surprise, Jason cut his hair... I loved his hair long... But Im not gonna lie, He looks GOOD!!!!!! ^^' but Ill never admit that.... lol. Oh wait I kinda just did, huh? lol.  Well anyway, I took him to leptis to buy his mother a birthday gift, he picked out a teddy bear for her... Its very cute... but then when we went to get the card, I saw this beautiful lamp, that was in the shape of a teddy bear... I knew his mother would like it. But he seemed to get upset when I asked to buy it for her aswell as the teddy bear. So I tried to drop it, but didnt do very well...Eventually, he said for me to buy it, but he seemed saddened by it... I fet kind of bad, but for some reason I bought it anyway.  I didnt understaqnd why he was upset.  On our way back to the block I realized it though. I think he feels bad that I pay for things... I think it makes him feel like "damn I cant pay for anything" So I felt very bad, and felt I was insensitive earlier...  We stood outside for a while talking to Lea and Tim who were sitting in her car... We stood out there talking to her until like 7.40pm Which was okay I guess.  Got home... watched TV went to bed.  This morning, I checked my email and there was this invitation to join someone elses blog, I knew it was jason when it said "occupied emptiness" being thats what his website is called... So I read his blog... And it was sad... So now I feel like by paying for the movies, and his mothers gifts, Ive hurt him in some way.  He doesnt seem to undersatnd, going to college working for his associates, is enough of a life. Most of the people who talk about these fun lives, are either struggling in school or not in it. He doesnt seem to understand, so what if he doesnt have a job right now this second, as long as he finishes school, he'll have a better paying job and life than other people, who work at crappy little temp jobs.   I think thats another reason I like to buy him things. I feel like Im rewarding him for all his hard work... Im so proud of him. Not to mention I feel like I can lose him at any moment... So I guess in a way Im paying him so he doesnt leave me. I know he'd never leave me over money purposes, because if he had it his way he'd pay for everything. But being I know he cant... I enjoy paying for him.  Besides, I constantly have some problem, or am crying to hiom over something. He's always by my side when I   need   him. But Jason never  needs  me. In his eyes he doesnt NEED anyone... especially me... he could live without me no problem. I am nto a necessity in his life. So I feel, by buying him what he needs or wants, he has some use for me. And Im not just a walking bubble of stress for him.   I want to give him everything. Anything his heart desires... Does he desire the moon? Ill take it right from the heavens and bring it to him. Does he want to the sun, I'll cool it off so that not to burn him, and place it in his hands...Does he want the rain, Ill steal a rain cloud from the sky. Whether Id ever admit ti aloud or not, even if he wanted the girl across the street, Id do everything so that he can be with her. I want him happy always. But by the looks of it, the more I try to make him happy, and give him what he wants it depressens and upsets him even more.   I dont know what to do.    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           Girlfriends dont come in checks. (Dads dont come in checks part 2)   I look in the mirror and now I see. Theres someone else staring back at me. The face of my father, looking away. Oh I knew this would happen one day. My love came to me seeking nothing more then a smile. I took out my wallet, and we walked for miles. What I did not see, is he did not want gifts. Just my love and my sweet kiss. I realize who I was today. I am my fathers daughter, and can not change. I brought pain to the one I love, he who I almost lost. All because I did see love itself has no cost. but when all he desired was my smile, just me. I did not see, so instead I pulled out a twenty. I wanted him to smile. But I made him cry. And from then on, The happiness died. What am I to do? What have I done? 
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           Dads dont come in checks   There was this girl who had this dad, Who loved to spend every dime he had. He bought her gifts, he bought her clothes. But what she wanted no one knows. He was never there. He never did care. He was a sad fool. He could drink up a pool. He never said he loved her. He never said he cared. This was the burden she always bared. She did not want gifts. She didnt like what she had  all she wanted, was to have a real dad. She wanted to walk with him Have a talk from within. But he never had time for that sort of thing. So he pulled out his wallet that was not at all thin. And gave her a hundred, To play with and spend. She looked at the bill.  And tossed it on the floor. And looked at the dad, that was her dad no more 
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Okay. Guess I Should start with yesterday. I went to Jasons house. We went to the movies, adn saw I, Robot. That movie was Awesome! After wards, we were pretty hungry. So, Jason made me choose where to go to eat. I really hate choosing, it makes me feel very uncomfortable. Eventually, I decided fine, lets go to McDonalds. So we did. I wonder if I spoke top much during the movie... Damn... I try to be real quiet but I always have something to say. I wonder if Jason was annoyed with it.   Anyway. We eat, then decide to go over to brukner to look around. We went to Radio Shack to look for a video card for him but we didnt find any. I wanted to buy him something. I like buying him stuff but he didnt let me. Everytime I was like, okay lets buy it, he was like no. He doesnt like me spending money on him. But, I dont mind.   Though I do really want my contacts... but maybe I can get mom or someone to buy it, being my birthday is in 18 DAYS!!! ^^ Im excited, I mean 16 is a good number... Its the age of possibility... lol.   I really, really want a monthly cell phone...   But, I think I'd feel bad if I had one and Jason didnt... Because, I think he wants one more than I do. =/  There are only three things I really want, for my birthday...  A cell phone - maybe from like either Papi, or Dad. Vampire Fangs - From anyone with 100 bucks to spend on me Contacts - Maybe from. I mean, at first I wanted cat eyes, but now I like some other. :-/  Yea thats my list.  Oh yea, back to yesterday. So Jason and I walked around Kmart/Toys R Us and stuff... I wanted to pay for him to buy a gift for his mom. Her birthday is this tuesday. >_  Iono. Damn I like talking to Jason in the morning but by the looks of it I missed him. And I get in the shower at 8.30 to get ready for work and leave by 9.30 he wont be back on the PC by then... Oh well maybe Ill talk to him during my lunch break or somethin.   Today is monday. We have boxing, I wont get back to the block till atleast 7.30 >_  -----------------------------------------------------------------   I really do love Jason. I hope he knows that. He's the first person I think about when I wake up, and the last person I wonder about when I go to bed. No one seems to understand the extent of my love. Its just too great for words...But if love were power. Id be God herself. All because of my love for Jason. My sweet puppy. 
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Crap. Keep waking up to the sounds of that bloody stove clicking away. Its so irritating, I hate it.   Well anyway, I watched this cool movie this morning called "Womens Prison" its an old black and white movie, But its real good. Ita botu these women in jail. All for different reasons. One was a stip tease, but she wanted to be an impressionist, she was pretty good too. There's another women, who is said to be a psychopath but she's really kinda weak and sensitive. The Female Warden is a tyrant, and keeps putting her in isolation. Theres another woman whos husband is in the Males prison next door. Her husband finds away into the female prison to see his wife, and he impregnates her. When the male warden finds he orders the female warden to finsd out how he made to teh other side. She tries tio beat it out of his wife, but winds up hospitalizing her. When the otehr prison mates find this out, they mutiny. But she still dies. The only one one their side is the male doctor, who hates the female warden. And teh corrupt system. Its really good. I like it alot.  Well back to reality. Im suppose to go with Jason to see I Robot today. the movie is at 2.25pm so Im hoping he's dressed by the time I get to his house which should be like 1.30 or so. That way we can take the bus, to parkchester.(Grrr its raining >_<) Heh. That was funny of me, I said Im going with Jason to see I Robot, actually... Im taking him... I dont mind. I like paying for him. But I want to be paid for sometimes... It doesnt upset me or bother me too much though. I understand that money is tight in his house, and he dedicates his time to school. So he doesnt get a chance to find a job. Looking at it that way. Im very proud of him. Its hard to find a guy in the Bronx with a good head on his shoulders. Too bad he likes it here, and wouldnt mind living here forever. Which would probably be my main reason for ever leaving him. I need to get out of NYC. I dont mind working in the city but Id rather live upstate. NYC is a horiible place to live, especially the Bx.
    
</post>


<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         hello this is my first time doing anything similar to this and i guess this  is for me to be able to release the anger and confusion inside of me....Wow this is going to be lots of pages in that case. but i am just testing this for now need to see its limits ^_^     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       &nbsp&nbsp&nbsp&nbsp&nbsp Well today i had a blast obviously. I went to school and I found out that no one in class did their work, and being that i didnt even know that we had homework thats a good thing. Then I had my photoshop again -_-. Anyway; I finally told her the reason I didnt have her assignment. We got that straightened out. Then after that we just stood in the class doing work. Being that I had no work. It was a free period, so I chilled with Liz. She is a really nice person. I myself am suprised that I have gotten really close with her. I dont feel any attraction towards her. She's just cool to be with and shes the only female my age that I know. She has a boyfriend who she mentions like every 45 seconds. Which is good, cause we can be close friends with no one leading the other person on. &nbsp&nbsp&nbsp&nbsp&nbsp Anyway, after class was done I ran downstairs cause my girlfriend was waiting for me outside so we can go to the pool^_^. So we went. Origanlly I was supposed to go to meet up with some ppl. She wanted to go cause she hasnt beed to a pool in a long time and she also knows the ppl so she wanted to have fun aswell. I never minded the idea of her going. In fact I wanted her to go all along. Its just she had to work and i didnt wnat her to miss it. She missed anyway. &nbsp&nbsp&nbsp&nbsp&nbsp So we got there only to find the ppl getting in their suits . In other words we got there just in time. SO I changed and went out to the pool with my ppls. We got in the pool and waited for the females to come (which took forever). Then thats when the fun started. I was throwing everyone around chasing ppl swimming and just having a blast. I kept looking for my girlfriend to see if she was ok. I didnt want her to feel alone or bored. But when I saw her playing around thats when I figured she was doing just fine and was having equal amount of fun. &nbsp&nbsp&nbsp&nbsp&nbsp So I ran upto her every now and then to touch her and then went on playing around. After about 2 and a half hours that went by,which seemed really long. We all left to McDonalds. I took lots of pictures of all of us chit chatting. Then we got on the train, where we bugged out some more. And eventually got to the block. We sat for a bit then everyone decided to play baseball so I went to watch them play cause I was exhausted and all I wanted to do was rest. And then I ended up here.      &nbsp&nbsp&nbsp&nbsp&nbsp Yea I had lots of fun. For 1- I havent been to a pool in almost a yr, 2- Everyone was  glad I was there so it made me feel a bit special, and 3- I finally got to seem my girl all soaked and wet in a pool *drools* 
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Today there wasnt much done. I didnt go to school, thats a bad thing. I wanted to stay home and do my work. But i found myself falling asleep from exhaustion, and I didnt end up doing anything. I went to the block like usual and just stood there talking to ppl, found out they are going to go to the pool, so im going to meet them up tomorrow at the pool after school. I really miss swimming, it was the only thing that made me feel comfortable. I love water and how soothing it is. So I cant wait to go. Wow my day was really boring. I dont have anything to say. Oh well no ones reading this anyway. except maybe for.......  
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        &nbsp&nbsp&nbsp&nbsp Well.Today was a normal day. I went to school and did nothing. I went to my photoshop class which is boring as fuck. I hate the teacher let alone her assignment in which I have no clue in wat the hell she wants. On the birghtside i learned a few things today by a guy i met in class. After that i went home on that long train ride (its not really long, its just sleepiness makes everything seem long). I got home to find my mom there. Oh yea its her birthday. Anywho, I was tired so i went to  take a nap or atleast tried to. Then my gf calls me a bit out of breath and tensed over some fight that happened. If it were me I would have been all hyped about it. But oh well different strokes for different folks.  &nbsp&nbsp&nbsp&nbsp So anyway, I decided to do something different again. I went and bought chocalate covered cherries for my gf since she nearly cremes in her pants while eating them. Well obviously she liked them. It was really hot out there. And since I cut my hair the sweat drops down my face even more. But yea she came out and we walked to the bus stop. She started telling me about the fight that had happened in her job. I really dont mind that she is telling me this, thats ok. What I dont like is how she cant wait to tell me later on. Instead, she tells me this while the co-workers are like right next to me and they get quiet all of a sudden. I dont think she realizes it cause she is the one talking. But I dont want her to say something and then they go say she was talking shit. Cause then she gets all sad and shit.  &nbsp&nbsp&nbsp&nbsp Anyway. Went back to the block chilled there and then took her home then i went home to  find no one there. then later on my family came with pizza I ate stood online and went to sleep.   Yup like I said...... it was normal.  
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        well life sucks .. but what else is new. Jobless with no life. All i do is attend school for 4 hrs a day and come home and do nothing, go to my friends block and chill there till my gf gets home, take her home then go home to do some more nothing. Now thats a great ass life wouldnt you think?-_-. yea its great..........Well lets see... My gf got paid a few days ago and went through a massive breakdown cause she couldnt get it out of the bank... cuase she didnt realize that she didnt change the password rather than her account password so she kept putting the incorrect code. but eventually  i got that straightened out. Yay me!!!....I decide to go with her to the movies dreading every step i take knowing im not the one paying for it. Its like someone taking a small vein that runs into my heart and just pulling on it really hard everytime she pays for something. Then we went to eat. That i dont care about, I buy food every once in awhile.  So yea. I tried to be different this time and instead of going home i asked her if she wanted to go walk around and look inside the stores at the plaza cause i know how she likes walking and window shoppin and since she had money i thought maybe she would want to buy herself something. Instead everything i glanced at she wanted to buy. Why cant she understand how low and pathetic that makes me feel. I was always brought to depend on no one and never take unless its absolutely necessary. And to top it off its been very hot and what no one seems to understand is that my real only weakness is heat. I cant stand it. It hurts. I can walk for hours with agony and pain in my feet back shoulders anywhere if its cold. If its hot i wont make it too far barely 15 minutes.  But i tried to make her happy by doing that... although I dont think I succeeded.  The heat is the only thing that changes me entirely. And its hard not being able to control it. I try so hard not to yell or get mean to her. I dont know what it is either but lately I have been getting aggrevated with every little thing in everybody.  Whats wrong with me?Why am i so unhappy?I think i need help......  
    
</post>


</Blog>