<Blog>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      why do we try?  Call me negative or pessimistic, but seriously, why do we try?  If we want those around us to love us for who we are, why try?  Why put on the makeup the heels, the dresses, if this is just an attempt to lure those we want into our circle?  We want love so badly we sell ourselves out to Dolce and Gabbana for a solution.  But what happens when we cut it out.  When we say, enough, here I am take it or leave it....we really mean....take it or leave it, but please, go with the former, don't leave it, here....let me show you how valuable I am.....look, please.        Do we maintain any hope of love unconditionally or have we watched too many Meg Ryan shows to differentiate reality.  Here's the truth.  Love is easy the younger you are.  a.)  You have less past inherently in that you have actually been alive a shorter period.  b.)  You have less hangups, and may still have altruistic beliefs.  c.)  You have less wrinkles, and flab and GOD forbid proof of your lasting existence.  d.)  Less exes accumulated.  e.)  No bills, obligations, kids, jobs, i.e., grownup crap you don't like even when you have to deal with it.    Silly kids in college think their "serious" relationships are the end-all.  No honey, but yes, maybe the end.  Wait til you and your love-of-your-life have a mortgage, and bills, and one of you makes more than the other.  True love, if it exists can transend this.  Flaky "love" cannot inherently because it lacks the requisite endearment and frankly obligation.  My friends would have me tell you that love is not mortgages and bills, but a feeling.  Yeah, its the feeling that will keep your butts together when one gets laid off and the other has to work overtime.  Not the candles, or bubble baths, no sex can do that, its a form of, for lack of a better word, endeared obligation, you love the other enough to keep them afloat.  You throw them the liferaft first.  True love is perseverance, nothing less, the fact you don't quit, you have problems, yes, you have difficulties yes, but you don't want to wake up with anyone else.  You want to call that person first when you bomb a law school final.  You want that person to walk you to your door every night for hereafter, and nobody else.  You know if they screw up, you hope to GOD they call you first so you can try to help them.  You want them to know you love them.  Love is bigger than an ephemeral feeling, the fleeting tingly butterflies are lust or excitement.  Love is less exciting but more so, because it can be counted on.  You don't have to ask if its included, if they want to go, you know they will be there.  You know they will pull the covers over you the weekend before finals and not get pissed because you were running a fever and tossing and turning all night.  They put their arm around you and kiss your forehead the next day, asking if you want some water, if you are okay.               So thats it.  I think I am in love.  I am.  He doesn't know.  After turmoil and being stood up who knows how many times.  He is the one I want to pick me up for dates and wake up to in the morning.  When did this happen and why didn't anybody tell me.  My friends hate him,  because of standing me up, my dad wants a guy who will want me in a stronger less flaky way.  And here I am. In an un-relationship, with the person I want to share my pillow with, who was dating another before, and partially during my reign, and who I have ridiculous stupid quarrels with.  I love him.  I am actually not just saying that.  I really do, oh God what do I do, he doesn't want a relationship and I will be back in Spain on May 25th.  I cannot even imagine a date with another.  How in the fuck did I let it get this far?  I can't tell A. how I feel, not for fear of rejection but for the fact I am sure he will decline.  I took a final today, and I should be happy, right?!  Then at La Fogata, the girls and I hung out and ate and drank, etc., the subject came up about what we were doing tonight, I said I had plans, and another blurted out that I had plans with A.  She said, he begged forgiveness and promised not to be a punk boy.  Another girl at the table said, you know you are not the only one he begged forgiveness from, referring clearly to the girl he was dating before me.  I felt cold and alone and duped and stupid.  I wanted to jump in my margarita glass and drown in the tequila.  I was alone, I am alone, even though I am in love.  That is wrong.  I shouldn't feel this way, I need an out or a way to just get it out there and say it....but what to say...
     
    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It just gets more unpredictable.  A. just told me how he feels about me. He admitted he cared and missed me and didn't like life without me in it.  Hmm better late than never I guess.  After over a week of torture here we are and he is being sweet. The wonders never cease.  Also I made Vice Pres.of Family Law Assoc.  How did that happen?!  Well I guess I need to learn more about it now?!  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      okay, so these tests haven't given an accurate portryal of me, they are like a bad A&E biography.   Things I Like: Sleeping late [rarely happens, thanks to my newly acquired internal clock] Non-fat grande caramel machiattos Pink purses shoes My mini-dachshund Spike being quiet sometimes, talking can be unnecessary red wine and manchego cheese extra dirty martinis eggs benedict and tiramisu [separately of course] Criminal law, unless while being tested then remove to "things I very strongly dislike" list Spanish music, and salsa dancing Singing songs in the car with the stereo turned up Candles and dancing to sappy songs barefoot in the living room Compliments, although I tend to react to them less than cordially, I still like them...I am working on better compliment acceptance Being in College Station, Texas with my friends I miss terribly.  It hurts to think I am separated from them. Leather Yankee Candle Midsummer's Night Scent [yes it sort of smells like boys, but I like them too, coming to my next point...] Boys, men, guys, but one at a time, I can't manage multiple dating scenarios, too complicated Feeling wanted Getting A's [Few and far between, yes, but good when they occur] My law school friends...I think I might miss school this summer because of their absence Literature, even trashy romance junk  Things I very strongly dislike: cold-blooded creatures, i.e., snakes, lizards Spiders Roaches, and all bugs, I kill them heartlessly Sunburns, or in my case tanning bed burns Being ignored Feeling unimportant Being left-out Being forgotten or stood-up Feeling stupid break ups mud, dirt and sweat Thunderstorms, when you are alone My mom's Multiple Sclerosis Death and old age, my great grandmother had a large part in rasing me and she's 101. Suicide, my boyfriend in junior high killed himself, and many others close to me have followed suit Saying goodbye, and getting on planes LAW SCHOOL Reading really boring cases Garbage and dishes calluses hard of listening [not to be confused with hard of hearing which is not culpable by any stretch] warts [I don't have any but I'm just covering the base] The loss of my brother's interest in my life.  Aerospace engineering, Bill-Nye boy has pretty much cut me out of the equation. 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Haha newest test: personality type, maybe this one is a bit more accurate...haha..still, I sound like an asshole...not so accurate...Rachel, you're a Millionaire!   Your personality is actually determined by two personality sub-types - your primary, or dominant sub-type, and your secondary sub-type. You are a Millionaire which means you are a Success / Thinker Your primary sub-type is defined by "Success" characteristics and your secondary sub-type is defined by "Thinker" characteristics.   That means you're very ambitious and personable, and you've got a great sense of humor. Chances are you care a lot about how you look. You're bursting with self-confidence, and people admire you for your achievements and determination.  How do we know all this? How do we know that behind that bold exterior you sometimes worry that you're not good enough? Or that you can be so critical of your work that it verges on self-destructive? How could we have divined that you aim to succeed — and you'll quickly crush anyone who stands in your way? 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Took a test on who I was in high school...here's the results...very interesting...not so accurate..Rachel, you were a Popular Kid   Were you voted most popular, class president, homecoming king/queen? Was there a line just to sign your yearbook? Omigod! You were probably the envy of the entire student body! If they could only see you now...they'd probably still be totally jealous. 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When did I become so undesirable?  In high school, the girls were incredibly more mean than now, but the boys were suckers.  Life was sooo much easier.  I am 5'9", with a batchelors degree, working on a doctor of jurisprudence, green eyes, blonde hair, Lord knows I have lost alot of weight, now I'm a size 6, I have a great tan, and I am nice.  What do I lack?  I have ambition, motivation, goals [some philanthropic, others more self-oriented], and a european import for a car.  What do they want from me?  The recently ended relationship that wasn't a "relationship" called me tonight, but why?  What did he want me to say, you stood me up entirely too much?  I can't date someone who values everything more than me?  I'm not a side dish?  I want to be wanted and thats it, I want to have someone who wants to tell me special things first, or call me first when the world crashes in.  I want to be valued, not just another person, but special, important, valuable.  I didn't have that so I had to end it.  I cried tonight when he called.  He said I wasn't being nice when he saw me at school, I asked how he wanted me to react, what he wanted me to say.  I would say it, but I couldn't actually talk to him.  Its still too new, too burning, too sad and over.  I wish it wasn't, but then again, I cannot make myself be what I want to be in another's eyes, it will only happen or it won't.  When did pretty girls stop being courted by guys?
     
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The unexpected nature of life.  How did I get here?  This seems to be a recurring theme.  My friends in this catholic private law school, in conservative Texas, are pro-life.  I have always thought myself more the raging liberal.  But, upon questioning, I found myself the newest member of the recently created St. Mary's association for Law and Life.  This is  a pro-life group.  I told them I would only be able to join if I could still think that some abortions were permissible, i.e., rape victims, incest, mothers life in danger, etc.  Apparently this was okay, so my name is on the members list.  Wow.  I could never have foreseen this.  Yes, I suppose I am a fan of life, life is good, death bad, but I cannot adhere to any extremist view.  This group seems to run the gambit, myself representing more the liberal side, big surprise.  They had a table at school today and I helped and hung around a bit, got a buddy to sign up after assuring her that I am not an extremist and many others are not.  But, my friend from PILA [Public Interest Law Assoc.] let all hell break loose, feeling strongly that the proliferation of these ideas of a pro-life group were detrimental to society, that we might bring others to the dark side.  I don't understand how she can be shocked that a political organization exists on a law school campus?  Is this a surprise captain obvious?  I want to be involved in the upcoming service projects where we do diaper drives and the like for places like the unwed teenager mothers home.  Is this so bad?  Do I need to feel weird about that?  I am not an activist, but for those that in dire straits have chosen to have  a baby, should I try and help?  There decision is good a baby lives....it is sad when babies don't, and for indigent, mothers such a decision would be trying, should I feel crappy for being a part of this group.  Have I switched sides, or did I think this way all along?  Where would I draw the line?  I believe in gray areas, substantially, mainly, but for women who by their own volition get pregnant [yes, captian obvious if you have sex, babies may follow], and are financially set-able providers, why should they be allowed to have an abortion?  How could this end be the desirable one, shouldn't we say no, life is good, yes you will have to learn to get up at three a.m.and feed someone else, but don't most of society's evils stem from our apathy towards another?  Where did love your neighbor as yourself go?  or Treat others as you would like to be treated?  Faith, hope and love, but the greatest of these is love?  This is a catholic school, for God's sake, how in the world is a pro-life group's mere existence itself a shocker?  The wonders never cease.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My world just fell in on me.  Its over.  My heart hurts so badly I feel like going home and crying.  He stood me up saturday night after I got back from Eagle Pass having spent all day doing an immigration clinic for the poor.  He was supposed to see me, so excited yet, entirely exhausted I ditched my family to go home and shower and change and clean up.   I did my hair, put away clothes and spent the night on the couch waiting.  He never called.  After having said he wanted to spend Easter dinner with my family he said he was going to Austin the day before Easter while I was still in Eagle Pass.  I tried to overlook this and said, "Just get back early so I can see you on Easter."  Yeah, definitely.  Didn't happen.  I went to bed on Easter after trying to stay up for his call again.  The call came at 11 p.m. last night after I had given up and gone to sleep.  My easter was a disaster.  That Sat after I got back from doing the clinic I came to my house to find a  300 lbs. part of my oak tree obstructed half the street.  In the rain and hail, alone, I tied ropes around it and tried to move it in my skiing jacket sloshing through puddles.  I cried.  But no one seemed to care or stop or help.  I couldn't even make the damned branch budge.  I wanted to hear his voice to hear anyone's voice.  To have someone else there.  I'm alone.  I ran into him in the library.  "What's up?" he said chipper as ever.  Apparently his weekend had gone off without a hitch.  "You don't know whats wrong, come in here we need to talk."  I told him how he had stood me up.  He claimed to not know he had.  I hate holidays.  I hate being my only fan.  I hate having to hate, to feel so undesirable, so easily overlooked and forgotten.  I told him I was upset, I told him this on Sun night also.  I told himm my feelings were hurt.  He said I'll just let you go to bed you sound tired.  You know what, I think I am.  Maybe not in the exact way he thinks, but I am.  Today I said what I didn't want to ever say, what killed me and I felt my heart had stopped from saying.  "I can't do this, this isn't working."  He had no reaction, he just turned and walked away.  I am the only one hurting.  How do I sit through property, how do I get up tomorrow.  He was the only highlight of every day.  He was my reason for trudging through and sucking it up.  What is my reason now.  My heart is broken.  My chest feels sunken and I AM tired.  Tired of this.  Tired of not having something good happen.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ode to my Stomach  Oh, how I don't miss seeing you there Now I can once again fit in underwear My rolls are not bulging, flabby and loose I've said my farewells to my hard earned caboose I have full view of feet when I'm standing upright Watch out drag queens, I'm now queen of the night I don't miss all the carbs I've cut out If that means dates then I'm sell out I should focus on my soul is nonsense and such With this new figure I'll never more go dutch
     
    
</post>

<date>07,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Are all relationships ridiculous?  Do we psych ourselves out for just another TKO?  What do we expect, even when they seem promising, don't 50% of those end in divorce?  So, why do we date.  We get all gussied up, wear too much make-up, don't eat enough the day of because we are nervous, and then go out on this farce where you don't get to say what you really think about because that's "too heavy" and have to play this quid pro quo of silly shit like where you are from and what you did that day.  What I do during the day is not who I am, but what I do in order to be who I am.  Its the means to an end.  Is an atty's defining characteristic being an atty, or maybe more to the heart loving old books, overstuffed couches, small dogs, non-fat caramel machiattos and flying kites.  Does a person's job define them so unwaveringly, that the other more intimate qualities get overshadowed by the title.  Dr.______,  ______ atty at law.  Is this all we have turned out to be?  What about the fact we like to sing sappy songs in the car at full blast, with the windows up of course, or that one of our toes is a little longer than the others?  These are the hidden less obvious things, but the special ones that make us, that define us.  Problem is, people only meet the real you after a long time, somehow these are not the topics of first dates, but they are our best qualities.  Why can't people meet me sooner?  And especially now, why can't I tell him exactly how I feel?  I know why, because he would reject it.  But, at least then I would have said it.  I think he knows, but does he care?  How much time does it take for you to become special to another, and how do you know you are there?
     
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am wearing pink today.  I didn't realize, however, that this get-up was see through until it was too late.  Now the school has seen my hot-shorts.  Hmmm.  My unattached unboyfriend seems to be fading.  I hope not.  He didn't call yesterday, and I while waiting by the phone, hovering as it were, pulled a Bridget Jones and drank a little too much red wine in the process.  I think the theory intially was to stop when he called, but as he didn't I felt no need for cessation.  How did pink become a female color?  Why was blue the requisite color for boys?  Who decided this?  I think I will stick with my standard operating procedure black from now on.  I have been called psychadelic, techno, etc today.  Other girls that wear bright shit daily get no scoff.  But I am somehow the marked one.  I wear one bright dress and now I am an Austin Powers sidekick.  Negative Ghostrider, the pattern is full.  Am I the only person in the world who has not seen the third Lord of the Rings?  I hear its awfully long.  Why wasn't the Hobbit ever made into this epic series?  Sorry Bilbo.  Hmmm I wonder if the author was being funny calling him Bilbo, sounds an awful lot like dildo.  Haha.  Sorry, I digress.  
     
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Everyone needs to visit www.stupidshouldhurt.com.  Haha.  I am the idiot through the St. Mary's Break Party link that is wearing a navy suit and caught in the most atrocious states.  I start at pic 1.  Hmm hopefully if I run for office these pics will disappear.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sitting in the Westlaw lab at school.  Oh the joys of spring torrential rain.  The sun seems to be surfacing but from my seat in the center of the library I cannot confirm.  Torts looms next on my daily schedule.  How did I get only 16 speaker points on my 4th round of moot court.  The wonders never cease.  I was a debater in high school, now a law student, it seems my faculties have diminished.  Yes of course I get nervous in public speaking, but 16 points when most are around 22-25?  Hmmm. I question my capabilities.  I am woman hear me roar.  Or, in my case maybe stumble and stutter.  I guess this qualifies as one of my areas of weakness, but how to improve?  Karaoke?  Anything to defeat the fear of rejection from public performance.  My persistence in school seems to have gone as my patience did long ago.  What is in store for me next?  Public persecution from being called on in Torts.  Preferably not.  Does life progrssively suck more as you age?  Yes I have my first little wrinkles developing on my forehead.  I call them the "oh my goodness" wrinkles as the expression of shock makes them surface.  Note to self:  stop being so surprised.  Shouldn't I be more jaded at 23?  I generally feel my new liberalism after living in europe twice has left me affected, but not enough apparently to thwart the furthering of forehead creases.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      All About Me:  My name is Rachel, when I lived in Southern Spain my friends dubbed me Raquelita as I was the youngest of the group by far.  My mom is a kindergarten teacher, my dad is in insurance.  My younger brother is the idiot savant of the family, unless you are talking to him about quantum physics he has little to say.  He called my cell a couple weeks ago to ask how to mail a transcript, does it really need an address?  yes.  Its almost humorous, but he was serious.  No the mail carrier has esp.  My dog has cancer and my unboyfriend after dating since feb. has no desire for a relationship.  Maintaing the status quo.  My best friend in school, Tracy, is great.  I just never thought I would be best friends with the ultimate in sorority girls, with her new BMW SUV.  Lots of acronyms, eh?  My mom has M.S. and my goal in law school is to con her into early retirement.  So, I guess if thats the end, the means would more prudently be in law school that english lit.  But, am I sacrificing life to do so?  Yeah.  Sometimes I am.  I miss the freedom of undergrad, the "I think I'll change my major today [and thus the rest of my life]" the possibilities were tantamount to liberty. I am in a chain gang of sorts now.  I don't know what the cool music on the radio is.  How did I get to be buddies with the pretty girls.  The ones you hated in high school.  Am I THEM?  No.  Definitely not. [there's the rainman in me]  I miss romance and mystery and excitement.  Do we all?
     
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm a first year, an end of first year (1L) and I now realize I really wanted a Masters degree in Literature from Brown.  Oops.  My day- today- woke up hit snooze for a full hour.  Went to take the dog out only to realize I had given him intot he temporary custody of my parents, thanks to the lack of time.  I went to shower only to get out and feel like make-up wasn't  really  necessary.  I hate mondays, doesn't everybody.  Made it to school exactly 7 minutes before class, well there goes my "I'm gonna get there early and finish my brief before Constitutional law" theory.  He didn't pick it up.  Suddenly I felt let down, almost ssad he didn't pick it up and make me lose 4 points off my final grade for the lack thereof.  What's wrong with me?  I'm suddenly feeling sunken for not losing points?  Who am I?  I feel like I'm from the movei office space.  I hate law school, and my un-boyfriend won't label himself.  Maybe its not he brief that has me sunken.
     
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I played nicely today with stupid 1 and 2.  They want to go into Madrid with me today, if I let them, should i leave them?  Apparently Karen doesn´t really speak spanish, she said she can sort of understand it.  WHATEVER.  This could get interesting.  Anyway, now they wanna be my buds after totally treating me like crap.  Not gonna happen.  My roomate´s name is Fernanda, she is from Brazil.  I like her alot.  Did I mention classes started today?!  Yeah, uh I thought they were short, not really. I was up until 1am last night and didn´t even finish reading, although we didn´t get anywhere near through the reading, and I was just exhausted when I got up at daybreak.  Class starts at 9 am and they are 1 hr and 50 min long, back-to-back!!!! Every day of the week!!!  Dean Piatt is being really cool, everyone likes him and he is totally laid back.  I did some laundry last night but getting it to dry has been an ordeal.  I am going to go shopping this week, in the afternoon, in Madrid, I need more clothes on hand if washing has to be done in such a difficult manner.  Oh well, I have never complained about too many clothes.  My Sandra Day O´Connor materials were just fedexed to me thanks to the lovely dean.  Sweeeeet more books to carry. Will somebody please email me?  I feel like you all forgot about me?! DON´T.  
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay so, uh the Dean got here in one piece, uh apparently the girls did too, although I feel kind of like teaching them that Saturday comes before Sunday, the Dean asked the girls,  , their answer being,    But wait             Quite so, and I am too.  I am gonna have a very hard time dealing with them.  Anyway I still haven´t done my reading for tomorrow, wait....this si souding like the school year.  haha.  Orientation is tonight and school is tomorrow.  Apparently I forgot an alarm, so I had to go out and buy one.  But the little old man gave me a free battery, and even asked if I wanted him to wrap it,if it was a present, I told him no. I am going in search of laundry detergent, there are no laundry facilities anywhere.  You can have the hotel do it and the charge roughly 4€ per piece, it varies as to what exactly they are washing, these idiots are gonna ravage my clothes.  Sucks.  Glad I left my fav saggy Dolce cargos.  Or I can send the laundry out and they charge by weight, still it feels weird to have others touch my stuff.  thats icky.  Lots of love, pics will be posted on here soon.  TTYL 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay so I´m in San Lorenzo del Escorial. Of course the stupid girls I was supposed to pick up never showed. C´est la vie.  So I got up at 6 am after having 12 people from Singapore at Barbieri my hostel last night, who refused to follow the rules and chose to talk in rather loud abrasive voices around 4 am when everyone else is supposed to sleep.  Actually they talked all night long, repacking bags, turning on lights, apparently telling jokes from the raucous, incessant laughter.  I´ll give you one guess whose room they were in?!  Lots of fun, so after I got up at the crack of dawn to do the dean a favor, and while I was entirely exhausted I waited at the airport, at the right gate and everything after riding the metro and changing lines three times.  By 11:30 they hadn´t shown from their 9:25 arrival which was apparently on time.  I met a nice older taxi driver who waited with me and agreed to cut the rate.  At this point I was so worn down even I couldn´t have made it to the damn train station to get out here.  So I left, and paid 100 euros, horrifying I know to get here from Barajas Airport.  It was wretched.  The cab driver was nice, but the situation sucked for me.  I waited and did all I could and had signs and all.  I got here and they were like where are Amy and Karen?  I told them what happened and I had waited and nothing.  The people running the show from St. Thomas were nice and understood but the woman at the front desk was less than nice.  She said they had a cab driver for me when I arrived today the 29th of May.  I was like dude I got her days ago I never said I was going to arrive at the airport today from the US, you even have my itenerary.  The cab driver they ordered was all mad I still hadn´t slept but a couple hours, and I explained i was supposed to get the girls from the airport per request of Dean Piatt, but to no avail.  Nobody ever asked to hotel/program to order one.  So apparently they had assumed alot and after making assumptions even with knowledge to the contrary, they acted on idiotic proven wrong assumptions without telling us.  When they tell you, you have to find your own way to San Lorenzo, why would anyone in their right damned mind think a f&%$·ing cab was ordered for them.  I told them to yell at me tomorrow I was too tired today.  I think being nice is going to be a trait I seek to lose asap.  I am fed-up.  So genius me, I unload all my stuff and decide to take a walk and wander a bit.  Oh, wait, the best part is the stupid girls don´t arrive until tomorrow, their plane is for the 30th!!!!  Wow can´t believe I forgot to mention that before.  Anyway.  I am already just about at my wits end.  At least the cab driver was really nice.  I got to talk about my boyfriend alot, he was like a sweet little old daddy-kind of man.  And, he carried all my stuff inside for me and was particularly careful with my wheelie, he whispered that this bag had my laptop in it and so when we got inside he made me stand by it.  Anyway my room is pretty nice, I dunno if I would call it three stars, not really sure it deserves any stars, especially the front desk, but at least I had a nice walk although the rain started and idiot me forgot an umbrella again.  Oh well I just heard someone in this internet café say they were from St. Thomas, apparently all the people in here are from there, ahh the light at the end of the tunnel has shown itself, I was waiting. I miss you A.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OHMYGOD.  Murphy´s Law.  If it can it will, and as my first day, when it rains it pours.  I don´t know where to start.  My friend Emma is great.  Okay so I got up early yesterday, left the dumb umbrella in hope that doing so would encourage the sky to hold it in.  But don´t worry I wore dark colors just in case.  We played tourist first went to the royal palace saw the left over setup from the prince´s wedding last saturday.  Yeah, walked halfway around Madrid and met our buddy Patrick from the Hostel at street level of the Antón Martín metro stop.  He was late but no biggie we just sat and people watched.  He showed and we wandered until we found a pretty darned nice looking, but rock bottom cheap restaurant, the place even had a closed door and was full, a clear hit with the locals, and it had cheap paella for my buddies.  I had Gazpacho, and croquetas de pollo, yummy and we shared a bottle of vino tinto de mesa which was a wopping 2.25 €.  Highrollers, ha ha.  We loved to waiter the people, etc. My eyes were still bloody painful and red as a crayon so I was wearing sunglasses all day, but back to the subject at hand.  We were eating and seated against the wall near the rear of the restaurant.  Three at a table for four so the open chair we all piled our stuff in.  STUPID..STUPID..STUPID.  You all who have known me for awhile remember I have been robbed before in Spain.  So two guys come in and looked distinctly Morrocan or at least somewhere in N. Africa.  They sat at the newly vacated table next to us, the guy sitting next to the wall pretended to take off his sweater with one arm and with the other slid it under the sweater and snatched my purse, hiding it under his sweater.  He was watching me as he did it.  I saw the whole damned thing happen and decided I would fare best if everyone else knew what had just occurred too.  I called him a ladrón and told him to dame la bolsa, gilipollas,  which is incidentally the worst possible bad word in Spain, its roughly the equivalent of every single bad word in English in a package deal.  He claimed, obviously shocked the stupid american spoke spanish that it fell, three feet away in his hand clutchly tightly, under his sweater.  I´ve never seen anything fall three feet sideways myself.  Anyway, his story was ridiculous as I grabbed my bag from his theiving hands.  I said I was going to call the police as I got up and walked to the back now all eyes were on me, The assholes followed me to the back saying they were going to call the police for me, other male guests of the restaurant got involved telling me to tell the jefe, The asshole grabbed to only phone holding it off the hook and saying , now  yelling that I am a liar and that he was going to call the police I said fine I´ll pay, but he never moved to dial to pay the phone.  He obviously just wanted to have control so I wouldn´t occupy the phone with my call to the US embassy and the Muni police.  I told him I was going to call and he screamed and called me all kinds of damned american-isms, and hit me, no not hard, but all the waiters were male and jumped in between to pull the guy off.  It  also took the assistance of male guests to finally get the violent two out.  I kept telling them que ¡que te vayas!, ¡Ladrón!, ¡él ha tratado de robarme!, etc.  I was scared they would be outside waiting for me with knives afterward.  Then we walked to El Retiro I was still quite literally shaking, rather uncontrollably, really quite embarassing it probably looked like I was having a seizure.  My buds were trying to get me relaxed again and so we went to the café right in the middle of the walkway in front of the big pond and I got a massive beer.  Then I had to use the ladies room as naturally follows large quantities of beer.  But the ladies was out of order so Emma and I had to use the boys.  What I wasn´t told is that you can get locked in, and the doors are these big meat locker style steel doors.  Anyway, long story short I got locked in a tiny scary boys bathroom 20 minutes after a botched robbery.  After El Retiro we had been discussing how bad stuff happens in threes. I was like God please step in and don´t let a third thing happen I couldn´t take it.  So we went the grocery store on the way back to get food to prepare for dinner at the Hostel, and our favorite grocary meat man helped us, so starving and loaded down with ham and manchego and bread and water and paté of york ham we went back and started making sandwiches.  These scary pierced Swedes were in the kitchen I mean the fat one had rings stretching his earlobes, yes think national geographic, that could have been worn by me as bracelets and he had steel spike implants all over including in a row on his forehead.  Scary.  So they were asking where we were from etc., Emma said Australia, I said the US, they said what part I said Texas, and there was palpable disgust that arose in the room.  Noxious fumes must be put out by Texans because the whole f%$#ing room apparently had their stomachs turn in disgust.  I told them I was nice and I don´t really like Bush, and there are nice people in Texas.  They asked me what the population of Texas was and after giving them a rough estimate they proclaimed if I really was nice, then I was the only one in the state that was.  I found myself so threatened by that, after the crappiest few days ever that I was offering them all my paté and bread and everything else I could think of. So last night we went Salsa dancing, or at least tried and met some nice folks, but I found myself just getting more irritable.  I wanted to see A. after a day like that.  They even played my fav song Fruta Fresca, and any other day I would have gotten really excited.  But at least apparently Spanish dudes dig Australian girls, I was happy Emma got to learn to Salsa dance, the guys were all excited over her.  I think only middle aged, married, ugly scary drunk men hit on me, which is cool because I have somebody at home who I want to go back and see.  I´m not all about España right now.  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes, I am alive, very tired with scary red eyes but I´M IN MADRID.  Its lovely how my favorite places are all still open and I don´t have to carry a map around.  Mmmm.  Took the subway from Barajas, the evil airport from hell, and realized that to get to the damned metro I had to walk about a mile or more, in my daze I had no idea, and finally stairs and hallways later, there it was the entry to the subway.  Of course I didn´t know which line stopped there, but I found out at the next stop, then after changing three lines later I was finally on my way.  Chueca stop, home.  The hostel has been updated but fun as ever.  As I walked into the hostel, literally I met two friends, Emma from Adelaide, Australia, and some guy from Tijuana.  Rock.  I went to the Official Real Madrid store and not only FINALLy got my own real jersey, yes, its Beckham, and I also now own matching undies with the Real Madrid logo on them.  I´m hard core man.  Anyway, so even though I was awake at that point for 52 hrs. I had to keep going.  Remember how I said I wasn´t going to lug an umbrella there I would buy one on the street need be?  WELLLLLLL.....It had been raining here for over a week, lovely cold rainy crap weather, bloody miserable.  SOOOOOO...guess who was on the streey with a white short sleeved t-shirt and nooooo umbrella.   Yeah, very funny.  So Emma and I were far from our hostel after wandering around trying to not fall asleep until we had adjusted to their time, and we had to go into like every single store and finally I asked a scary policeman, ¿Donde puedo comprar paraguas?  I think he was taunting me cause he pointed to a little kids store across the street.  BUT, then....(drumroll)  I realized where we were.....Come on Emma there´s an El Corte Ingles at the end of this street.....So in my little black heels soaked white shirt, we ran, more teetered to the end of the block and into El Corte....Anyway I am now the proud owner of the ugliest umbrella I have ever seen....Oh, and I thought seeing a huge display of every color of Jelly Kellys in the front was a comforting sign.  We played with the Spanish fans and this elderly woman came over and helped us find a good pretty one for cheap.  She taught us what to look for in a fan and how to flip them open like the natives.  We are highly skilled professional fan-people now.  Be afraid.  Anyway so even today my jeans, yes the size 6 ones, are still hanging on my bunk drying out.  Yummy.  Emma has also learned of the miracle of café con leche.  Ahhh.  I miss A., yes mum I miss you too and daddy of course.  Speaking of Daddy, God help me that felt so painfully tragic to walk away from Daddy in the glass divided Houston airport.  Oh felt like my Heart was going to fall out.  He smiled and waved and waited watching until I disappeared.  Daddys are not easy to walk away from.  I was miserable waiting for the two stupid hours until I could board, alone, without my Dad to talk me down from ledges.  I just sat down and stared at the wall after I had walked into a news stand store to get a cosmo, etc. but I made a scene I was crying in public in while I looked at magazines like     , and I was standing there crying as I read them.  I must have looked kinda scary. I love you all, make my brother write me or tell him if he doesn´t I gotta a wedgie with his name on it for August. Te echo de menos.  Vaya con Dios.  etc.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Uh, isn't 125 a low IQ level?  Oh Einstein, Einstein wherefor art thou, Einstein....    Rachel, your Super IQ score is 125   Your overall intelligence quotient is the result of a scientifically-tested formula based on how many questions you answered correctly. But it's only part of what we learned about you from your answers on the test. We also determined the way you process information.  The way you think about things makes you a Creative Theorist. This means you are a highly intelligent, complex person. You are able to process information of nearly every kind with ease, using both creativity and analysis to make sense of the world. Compared to others you also have a very rich imagination.   How did we determine that your thinking style is that of a Creative Theorist? When we examined your test results further, we analyzed how you scored on 8 dimensions of intelligence: spatial, organizational, abstract reasoning, logical, mechanical, verbal, visual and numerical. The 3 dimensions you scored highest on combine to make you a Creative Theorist. Only 6 out of 1,000 people have this rare combination of abilities. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Fun links to really stupid stuff, REALLy stupid.  Makes my C in Contracts look good.  This one is a woman who called police officer to buy drugs...    urlLink    my fun link tool is not operating speaking of being stupid, so here is a manual link:       http://abclocal.go.com/wtvg/features/weirdnews/519_stupiddrugbuyer.html  "Kok" apparently not allowed to run for school office, pronouced "Coke" teachers assumed drug innuendo:  http://www.zwire.com/site/news.cfm?BRD=1675&dept_id=18171&newsid=11714407&PAG=461&rfi=9
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm about to leave, viva espana, but I'm not feeling so psyched.  My boyfriend, yes finally he is my boyfriend, left today to go home.  How is Spain a positive thing, it is separating us.  Hm.  On a happier note, looks like the BLE has approved me.  Nice.  They had been threatening rejection.  Oh, and crim law was an A-.  I knew it.  haha.  I guess that grade just shows I understand the criminal mind, haha, of course only in a purely educational way. Not in practice.  Yeah anyway.   I heard this country song, yes I realize that is the last thing I should listen to when I'm teary, but anyway the song is called "Love, Me"  Awwww I started bawling, Dad and I heard that song together once when it first came out and both of us got teary and I knew when it came on I should change the station, but no, no...   If you get there before I do Don't give up on me I'll meet you when my chores are through I don't know how long I'll be But I'm not going to let you down Darlin' wait and see And between now and then  until I see you again I'll be loving you           Love, Me  [to: A.]  
     
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Welcome to London.  So this trek started yesterday June 29th when I left l Escorial.  The night before I had to try to get a cab ordered for the next day to take me down to the train station at 6:15 am.  I should have figured out then that something was awry.  I asked the evil Russian front desk lady and she was like blah blah no, blah blah, I'll call, then in Spanish she asked if a cab could get me at 6:30 knowing full well the dude she called already had another booked at that time and that I had said 6:15 am.  Yeah bitchy huh.  Anyway so she was like go ask at the cab stand outside.  So I treked down with my buddies in tail and asked hte guy he was like no blah blah blah, and finally came to the conclusion to call his friend another cab driver and the guy he called could get me.  Then I found out the details.  At 6:15 I was to be waiting in the doorway ready to sprint to the car, which would be a gray, unmarked, personal vehicle of a short man wearing "low sunglasses" named Perfecto.  I know I shouldn't have, but before 6:15 I was waiting, or there was no way I would have made it.  So I get to the train 1 and train 2, and finally much later and exhausted get to Valladolid only to find out that sadly I was missing seeing Tordecillas, which was apparently near Valladolid where Juana la Loca was held.  SAD.  So the talkative cabbie went on and on, and took me to the airport.  I get there only to realize, retarded me the flight was for the next day, so I call the tourism office to ask about where to stay cheaply and they named all these expensive places, so I  went outside to the cab stand all my bags in tow, and find my cabbie and tell him my story and ask where to stay, so he puts me in a cab with a quiet dirver and I end up at Hostal Residencia Colon.  This was a surprisingly lovely and sweet little town so yesterday I had a day long vacation except I read for Sandra Day O'Connor;s class out of sheer fear.  I loved the city everyone wqas so nice to me and liked americans, and there were huge cafes and wide tree lined streets and I got to watch the news and relax , and all the local old people kept trying to buy me drinks.  Then today the same cabbie came back to pick me up and carried my stuff and talked, finally, and was so sweet, it left me with a renewed feeling about Spain.  Then I fought my way onto my ryanair flight and arrived early in London to find out that stansted is 45 minutes away on the high speed train, so 32 euros later I had bought my round trip train ticket.  Yuck.  Then I get to Liverpool station, after in a stroke of genius having checked my computer bag into left luggage for my stay in London, yeah one less thing.  So I try to go onto to Tube, only to find out they ARE ON STRIKE.  Bastards.  So I found this awful line to get onto a bus, and I realize every single person around me is better dressed than everyone I have ever seen in my life.  THEY ALL HAD ON SUITS.  So I finally, 2 hrs. later make it through strike-worthy traffic to Piccadilly, then ask everyone how to follow my supposedly clear directions and I realize british people are not especially nice, they sneer entirely to often, so I did it right back in my little burberry outfit and all.  So I wander with 50 lbs on my back for 45 minutes and accidentally run into my street.  I find my hostel, which is HUGE and see the people outside and almost run away, thinking they were too shady, but then I get inside and other americans talk me down off the ledge and my bunkmates seem really nice.  So then I drop my junk, make my bed, and wander more.  Accidentally I wandered onto the street off piccadilly circus with theaters, and in the distance what do I see..... "Do you hear the people sing.... Hint....."singing a song of angry men...."  YES LES MISERABLES IS PLAYING TWO BLOCKS FROM MY HOSTEL AT QUEENS THEATER, SO I RUN IN LINE AND BOUGHT MY TICKET FOR TOMORROW.  I guess london's not so bad, even though the people can be snotty.  
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Everybody count the number of sentences.  And I thought ya´ll were doing sooooo well.  Nope, daddy messed up.  The people at the condo group are going to take care of Mauruce, Hopefully he will be able to go back to work there now that he is no longer a care taker full time. It is almost tragic that you have to use a Blue Book and therefore write by hand! Enjoy your last hours in Spain as much as is possible and enjoy the trip to England. Love, Dad   Worthless, come on.  Anyway so off to London tomorrow I have to go to bed shortly, but I love you all and Have pics of Toledo today.  Besos
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I have written on both sides of five pages of the stupid blue book.  I have covered debtor-creditor, the bulk of the course, in depth and in tiny writing, but my best writing so doing it took over 9 hrs so far.  I am glad my visiting family has made it safely, but I am just sick they are there when I am not, AGAIN!!  This has now happened twice and next time the schedule a visit I BETTER BE THERE.  But on a different note, I just got word from Mimmy that  Maurice´s wife died.  I love him soooo much it just hit me like a bag of rocks, I know I am tired and a little worn down from finals, again, but this just sucks that I am not there.  He IS OUR FAMILY.  He took care of me all the time when I was sick and he has done as much, or more for my great grandmother than many of her blood relatives had.  What a tragedy.  I feel like a schmuck for not beign able to go to the funeral or help him or SOMETHING.  I´m crying right now, in the internet café from Spain, where I can do nothing.  Please extend yourselves to him, he has for us.       I leave for London on Tuesday.  I have figured out that the first train of the day leaves here at 5:47 am for Madrid, where I will get off at Chamartin and change trains (using my eurail pass for free, on the second leg) then go to Valladolid, Spain, arrive around 10:30 am, then make the trek to the airport, which is apparently far away, and I have to check in three hours early!!! Forty minutes before the flight they actually reject people from boarding!!! Then I will get into London after my flight leaves around 2:45 pm sometime around 5:30-ish I think.  I am still staying in Piccadilly, and Monsigneur Anderson will be in London also on the 3rd, so he asked if I would like to see Harry Potter with him in London!!!! Of course!!! So if anybody has more London sights I must see, please email them to me. I am getting nervous, and excited, but mainly just nervous about making my three million connections on time.        The older front desk lady here came up to me this morning early as I was writing my final and said she wouldn´t see me again since I leave tues, she gave me a hug and said she wanted to give me  "dos besitos"  she´s so sweet she has become my friend.  I almost got upset, so she said if I am ever back in el escorial I always have a place to stay with her.  Good things still happen I guess.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      here´s my horoscope, funny applicability again... You are tired of always being the one who bears the ultimate responsibility. There's a part of you that is wondering what would happen if you just let it all fall apart. But this won't happen, for your common sense grabs you from behind and shakes you, reminding you that you are responsible and that there are things you must do. So you buckle in and do what's expected of you. It's your nature. And then you can go to bed respecting yourself. Thank You rick levine from AOL
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Immigration is over over over, until August that is.  :(  I leave to London from the mysterious city of Valladolid on Tuesday, my only question is Where is Valladolid?  Yes Yes I have seen it on the map, BUT it is also the name of the province, sooooo is the airport in the city or the airport of the province.  HAHA Tuesday could get really interesting, REALLY interesting.  I have fallen into my I don´t want to do anything, A.D.D. state again.  I have only taken 1, yes only 1 final, and I am already feeling quite sorry for myself.  No, the final was not particularly bad, it was more like just another thing I didn´t FEEL like doing, I would have preferred reading Crime and Punishment by the pool, yes the book has been sorely neglected of late.  I also don´t FEEL like writing my take home exam.  The question:  "What did you learn in my class?"  is a guise for an actually trying and difficult question.  It, on its face, seems to be simple, but IT IS NOT.  The answer: "Nothing."  or "Not much."  I have already questioned Maloy about.  He said I should write more.  haha.  But they all keep saying, "there are no wrong answers."  Well, heck, I should get my Pass (vs. fail) from writing "Not a whole heck of a lot." Okay Okay I am not going to do that, you all know I have probably been freaking out as usual over just another stupid test.  Actually I have been compiling notes and trtying to boil down everything.  So I pose a counter question, how in the world do you boil down Bankruptcy chapters?  Uh there are lots of chapters for lots of types of Bankruptcy?  No, okay I´ll try again.  Um the chapters are all odd numbers, wait no, thats wrong too, ch. 12 is the only even numbered one.  Okay, oaky, you don´t call bankruptcy bankruptcy anymore, its not P.C.  Okay, but I was never actually told what to call it now, so I shouldn´t say that.  Um, Bankruptcy is bad don´t do it?!?  Uh you can liquidate, or reorganize, which although there seems to be a distinction in what takes place, are still both bad and should be avoided and stuff.  Okay.  Uh for debtor-creditor, uh we are all sometimes debtors and creditors, simple, ahh, but that sounds too simple like Playschool toys, primary colors, simple.  I dunno.  My notes have been compiled from outlines and notes into a notebook of boiled down junk I barely know.  But I have to fit my treatise on bankruptcy stuff into the confines of one bluebook.  How can this be done?  I am at a loss.  This is way more challenging than I thought it would be.  Unfortunately I am trying to get it written today.  SURE.  Other than that the Laundry put black spots on my white stuff, and so I brought it back and told themt o fix it and that they should then deliver it to my hotel as I would be entirely to busy with finals.  Well three days later after calling it arrived.  Ahhh, assertiveness is beautiful.  Speaking of, to my family, everybody needs to give Mim a big pat on the back for standing up for the people in Brighton Gardens and being assertive in pushing for change.  She said I would be proud, and yes I am.  It seems like my years of, "But I want both outfits."  has taught Mim to push for things she wants too.  Good progress, keep going, but enxt time threaten suit or to bring it to the attention of WOAI news and the changes might become permanent vs. temporal.  Good luck.  So has anybody seen my boyfriend?  Yeah, me neither. haha.  Hey A., if you get this Blog,  how are ya?  Alive I hope?  Doing well?  Had a birthday?  Yeah, well ya´ll keep your eyes posted for my MIA boyfriend.  Shucks, well I hope my parents house doesn´t flood AGAIN.  That would be a bad thing plus when it rains, Mom´s best friend Hank comes inside, since our dogs are wusses that cower from raindrops.  Good luck with that Mom.  My advice:  When in doubt, you have the key to my house, and I´m still renting my own room, so I can use it as I see fit since its mine, and I see that you might have a fit from everything, so just remember its there if ya need it.  Love you tons. -R-
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Still alive, no time to write.  In S.L. del Escorial.  Took immigration final, still kicking, sucked but not fatal.  All I get is a Pass/fail anyway.  Kisses to all.  Doing take home essay, but stalling horrendously.  April sent funniest email ever I cried laughing too hard.  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When it rains it pours.  Okay, so if any of ya´ll feel like jumping in and dealing with this B.S. for me, please feel free to.  Here´s a copy of a correspondence from Peter McLean and some other people including someone named Jenny, none of which I ever recieved.  And not included in this posting is the latest email from Peter McLean the housing company which says, " I don´t know where you are....I called your phone and the # is disconnected..blah blah.."  NO ITS NOT, MY STUPID CELL IS ON VACATION MODE FOR THREE MONTHS, I HEREBY MAKE THE DAMNED ANNOUNCEMENT THAT MY #S ARE ALL THE SAME AND SHALL REMAIN SO UNTIL FURTHER NOTICE.  If the idiots that did housing would just take 3 seconds and read all my damned forms, they all say in huge writing that I will be (Have been) in Europe since May and will not be able to be reached.  Plus, aol does not support their emails, it took much effort and help to be able to open this one and finally it had to be done in HTML.  FUN FUN FUN STUPID.  SO please feel free to get pissed at this woman.  I emailed VJ at school about the sudden increase in price and he is in turn contacting dittfurth and ariens to have them deal with it.  VJ said he had not been aware since the program started in 1986 of any student having to pay more because their roommate failed out.  Sure, time will tell eh?!  Anyway, so I have finals starting on Friday, its wednesday, and I leave for london on Tuesday.  I feel a bit of a time constraint.  here´s the email, which refers to me ingoring them/her/whomever...which is not, never has been, and will not be the case, are they so incredibly super-retarded they thought my embellished writings declaring my absence from the US were by some means a joke?   *****Please note that anything I put in Bold, I wanted to be emphasized for self-evident reasons.  Hi Jennifer, I have a single available in the hotel at $1,417.  Rachel has never respnonded to my e-mails or calls-she's in a half a twin and I don't even know what she wants to do. Please advise-I have only 1 single left. ----- Original Message -----  From: "Parks, Jennifer"   To: "heather"   Sent: Friday, June 18, 2004 4:35 PM Subject: RE: St. MAry's Law Innsbruck-Karwendel   > If there is still a single room available where Amanda Carroll and Sarah Thompson are staying, I would prefer to stay there.   I dont really know Rachel Rogers and I think it would be a little bit awkward, but if thats all that is available I will stay there too. > > Thank you, > Jenny > > I apologize for being difficult > > -----Original Message-----  > From: heather [mailto:heather@petermcleanltd.com] > Sent: Fri 6/18/2004 11:09 AM > To: Parks, Jennifer > Cc: > Subject: Re: St. MAry's Law Innsbruck-Karwendel > > > > > Rachel Rogers > > ----- Original Message ----- > From: "Parks, Jennifer"   > To: "heather"   > Sent: Friday, June 18, 2004 10:50 AM > Subject: RE: St. MAry's Law Innsbruck-Karwendel > > > > What is the girl's name?  I am going to look up her picture and if she > looks nice I will room with her.  ( LOOK SHE LOOKED ME UP AND WON´T LIVE WITH ME ) > > > > -----Original Message----- > > From: heather [mailto:heather@petermcleanltd.com] > > Sent: Fri 6/18/2004 10:45 AM > > To: Parks, Jennifer > > Cc: > > Subject: Re: St. MAry's Law Innsbruck-Karwendel > > > > > > > > I have an Mmex number on file for you.  I'll use that if you wish.  I will > > put you in a single in the hotel Karwendel at 1,417.00.  OR I also have > that > > girl that needs a roomate in a twin in the Studentenheim Karwendel-which > is > > where your guy friends are too.  The total for that is 1,082.00  Let me > > know. > > Heather > > ----- Original Message ----- > > From: "Parks, Jennifer"   > > To:   > > Sent: Friday, June 18, 2004 10:27 AM > > Subject: FW: St. MAry's Law Innsbruck-Karwendel > > > > > > > Hi Heather- > > > > > > Here is the email I was forwarding you.  I am sorry about panicking this > > morning, I was having breakfast with my mom and she does that to me.  I > > would prefer to stay where Brian Shahan, Rick Schreiber, Mandy Carrol and > > Sarah Thompson are staying.  If another girl needs a roommate and she will > > be staying in the same location, I can stay there.  Or if there is a > single > > available I dont mind paying the extra money.  If you need my American > > Express number or any additional information please let me know- otherwise > > you can charge the full amount to the number I faxed. > > > > > > I also just spoke with Sarah Thompson and she was under the impression > > that they had taken care of the final payment for Innsbruck. > > > > > > Thank you, > > > Jenny > > > > > > > > > > > > -----Original Message----- > > > From: heather [mailto:heather@petermcleanltd.com] > > > Sent: Fri 4/23/2004 3:52 PM > > > To: Parks, Jennifer > > > Cc: > > > Subject: Re: St. MAry's Law Innsbruck-Karwendel > > > > > > > > > > > > no problem-I'll put you in a single in the hotel and invoice you > > accordingly > > > next week. > > > Sincerely, > > > Heather > > > ----- Original Message ----- > > > From: "Parks, Jennifer"   > > > To: "heather"   > > > Sent: Friday, April 23, 2004 3:18 PM > > > Subject: RE: St. MAry's Law Innsbruck-Karwendel > > > > > > > > > > Hi, > > > > > > > > I was wondering if I could get one of the singles in the Karwendel. > > > > > > > > Thank you, > > > > > > > > Jennifer Parks > > > > > > > > -----Original Message----- > > > > From: heather [mailto:heather@petermcleanltd.com] > > > > Sent: Thu 4/22/2004 2:20 PM > > > > To: Deck, Tyler; Sheehan, Ty; Parks, Jennifer; Raymond E. Carr; > > > yoyifly@hotmail.com; Gonzales, Roland > > > > Cc: > > > > Subject: St. MAry's Law Innsbruck-Karwendel > > > > > > > > > > > > Hello all, Heather here, I am the person in charge of housing for the > > St. > > > Mary's Law Innsbruck.  I have your registrations forms and the Karwendel > > has > > > just informed me that they can offer me 6 more singles in the hotel > > (1,417) > > > and 3 twins in the hotel (1082 per person). > > > > > > > > Please let me know what you would like to do as soon as possible. I > have > > > to give away the unused rooms next week. > > > > Sincerely, > > > > Heather   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Leaving Barcelona, I look like hell, in the train station&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Bosc Bar crazy room, note the bar is right next to the wax museum&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Bosc Bar tree room&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Bosc Bar, note the fake trees, and I am blinking...NOT DRUNK &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Lost in Barcelona trying to find Bosc Bar, I had been to before, and leading a disgruntled pack&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Sarah and Pam at Ideal Restaurant&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Last Supper at the "Ideal Restaurant" on La Rambla&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Last Night on the Town&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Mediterranean Bikini Pic&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Next day on the way to the mediterranean on Barceloneta, thats my white butt&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Second Night in Tequila Disco&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Sarah dancing with random guy second night in tequila&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Me looking confused, very bad pic, night 2 at Maremagnum disco- Tequila&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Felice dancing with Random guy in Tequila- Maremagnum Night 2&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Dinner at Maremagnum&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      FYI:  Hank is my parent´s dog, the overly-active, Australian Sheep-herder, who nobody really likes unless he´s not around. Spike is my dog who thinks he´s human, and is perfect, although he has a bit of a barking problem, is overly-attentive, and tried to kill Tracy once.  But, really, he´s only a red,miniature dachshund   here´s a portion of a recent email from my mom : Hank understands, "Don't bite." He also understands, "Where's Spike?" Then Hank goes to look for Spike, and yes, bite him. When your dad says "brush" Hank stares at your dad adoringly and allows your dad to brush him. Spike understands,"Where's Rachel?"Then he looks around and seems confused, so I won't do that any more. Spike also understands "stay," and sometimes he will. Aren't they smart? Well they are smart, disobedient, willful, and have little impulse control.  Thanks Mom, that made me laugh!
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay so I still have stomach ebola, I´m still distressed about the hair mishap, and My stomach decided to wake me in the middle of the night and not let me actually sleep.  Hmmm, my immigration final is on friday and I  have my debtor creditor take home essay "What did you learn in my class?" due next tuesday. But on  brighter note, Happy B-Day A.  I miss you.  And congrats to Mindy, who went to the "Fund." in Toledo with me in 2002, SHE´S GETTING MARRIED.  Ah, I remember many wonderful bonding moments over Sangría hearing about her man Tim and now they are gettin´hitched.  CONGRATS!          This computer is actually a pentium two, so basically a dinosaur without a USB plug for my memory stick, which contains some good, some bad, some very bad, and some just downright crazy pics from Barcelona.  Hmm I guess ya´ll will have to wait.  And if anybody knows of a pimped out job, one of my friends is now looking, so please let me know.  Moving right along I skipped class today, wow, that is just amazing.  Proof of my illness and ill-fated hair.  Anyway, so I was out dealing with mail when everyone got back from class, and apparently started calling my room, my roomate was funny about it, kinda cool to know that people noticed I wasn´t there and missed me.  Anyway, I don´t think I am dying of Stomach Ebola, but maybe.  It is possible.  But, if so I wish I were dying in Roma instead, in Gucci.  HAHA- take care. I will now go on an internet café hunt for a USB equipped comp.           P.S. did anybody see the Spain game, that was some messed up stuff, huh?  
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, where to begin, you know when you have had so much happen that its tiring to even think about explaining?  Yeah, I´m there right now.  Okay so I am back in El Escorial from Barcelona.  Barcelona was okay, but um lets see, I had to stay in four star hotels, thats a long story I won´t go into now, I only prepaid 30 minutes at the internet cafe.  Um I went to the beach as planned friday and the sun was great and I could feel the tan coming, so I was like, well my buds are doing touristy things today, and we are all coming back tomorrow so I better call it a day early so I am ot fried tomorrow.  Yeah so I left we went out that night, yada yada yada, and then the next day we all met up etc. and went to the beach finally and the sun disappeared for the rest of the day about twenty minutes into it and the temp dropped to somewhere near 60 degrees, maybe less.  We toughed it out for about two hours then gave in and went to a Cuban joint I had been to last time off Barceloneta.  So that sucked I only have a baby tan thanks to quitting fake-baking before I left.  Then all was well until we were physically boarding the train, except Sarah lost her passport day one, but she fixed that within a day.  So anyway we are going through the detectors to board the train, and remember we had all five bought our train tix together, Felice went through 1st, then I did, so we were not far through, but yet on the other side, which these days is a significant distinction, when we heard drama behind us.  I put down my bag and turned to help with the spanish, because like all the train assholes I have had the joy of fighting with in the past they never speak english, even if they really do.  You know what I mean.  Anyway so I turn to see what I can do if anything and I sort of understand whats going on, eventually I realized when we got our tix the asshole in surprise surprise Atocha, fucking bastard, changed the month on the sweetest person ticket, Pam.  Pam is lovely and kind and sweet and quiet, so of course this B.S. happens to her and not someone like me who would probably deserve a little B.S. here and there.  They would not let her through and the train was physically departing in a couple minutes.  Before we could devise a game plan Pam had turned and dashed upstairs, alone, in Barcelona, without a spanish translator to deal with the most impolite assholes I have yet to encounter, shit even the gypsies that rob you are nicer, at least they take care to not disturb you, but here essentially the same had happened. Pam was robbed of her ticket, the right to employ its use was taken, and to be compensated they only returned half its value, a whopping less than 40€.  The deal with trains in Europe normally is that you pay some large price for one way, but the return if you get round trip in comparison to the first leg is minimal, i.e.  you may in some cases actually be paying around 80 € for the first part and maybe 1-5€ for the return, assinine plan, Yes, but thats the case normally.  But here they divided the trip by two and denied Pam a seat on a train they claimed full, which incidentaly wasn´t...rather half empty.  And I learned later when she went upstairs they told her all were full she eventually went back and forth from station to station crying and calling her mom collect, and she was alone, and I feel like a fucking asshole who should go to hell for being such a crappy friend, I could do nothing, I told off the interventor the man who denied her entry.  It wasn´t the denial that pissed me off, it was his reasoning and his blasted timing, what in all hell could she do with the train leaving immediately and the wait upstairs for tickets to the "sold out" (said with sarcasm) train taking more than 30 minutes to wait for in line upstairs.  So there she was.  The interventor is the newly created spanish position for the overseer of situations surrounding the boarding of passengers of trains at the security/inspection point.  He has the power to let people on the train should a mistake happen and the fault is the part of RENFE the spanish train comp.  He chose not to and his discretion was based more on a flexing of muscles and a clear enjoyment of creation of potentially erupting situations than anything else.  Felice, from houston and myself did everything said everything and since Tim was in first class he was let back through to run around and look for her, but she was not anywhere to be found, she was apparently waitng to be seen by an equivalent of customer service and equally sloth-like wait to be heard.  The asshole interventor only said when we said we bought the tix together, we bought them from the same place for the same place at the same time for the same time and since the month was incorrectly written on hers, that meant he made the mistake thus the mistake was renfe´s not hers and she should nto be punished for that which was essentially the fault of him, also the interventor.  He only said "demuestramelo"  "demuestramelo"  to everything we said.  We showed him our tix were the same from the same time and place, etc, that why would she get a ticket back for July when she leaves in a couple days for the US?  How could she stay in Barcelona, when she has class in El Escorial?  Also on the humanitarian side that she had never been to barcelona before, had class she had to be in tomorrow and did not speak spanish in order to communicate with those in a position to help her.  His answer:  "demustramelo."  He is a masochist.  EVIL.  Heartless, adn exactly what I have  encountered so many fucking times in damned train stations.  Pam went back and forth all day spending her 40€ on cab fare alone, and then finally later go to the airport and fought with a cab driver who was pissed at her for not being able to tell him what terminal, she kept sayin gany terminal.  She walked into the first airline she came across and said she needed the first flight to madrid.  We all got back and agreed to go together to tell professor Maloy, but everyone disappeared but Sarah who stood there as I grabbed the phone to break the news to the director.  He was nice about it, and not condemning of our futility, but kept me as the touch person in case of any change in situation.  We hadn´t eaten all day and sarah and I were teary on the Train after F. and I harassed the interventor every chance we had on the train, including, but not limited to a dramatic and embellished writing down of his name, etc. so everyone could see.  So after Maloy, we went for dinner, and we were sitting there and I was like she´s gonna be psised, what can we do?  We should send her flowers.  Then Pam walked around the corner and told us the story.  She had made it back.       Now on to my fun today.  My alarm did not go off, so I got up roughly 20 minutes before class.  GREAT.  Then I went to my hair appt. today and to gloss over the tragedy that has just befallen me-they fucked up royally.  They did exactly what I said not to do, and instead of fixing it they actually died it a second time the exact color I had said not to and four different adults, some middle-aged, and all professional hairdressers were actually yelling at me, truly and completely letting into me. I swear they wanted to see me cry, and god dammit it worked I cried, and they called me a stupid american among other things, and clearly the other clients didn´t like stupid blonde-haired, green eyed fucking americans, who asked to not have orange hair.  I was so polite, if not gentle and accepting, because I knew in the end the most important thing was me walking out of there with a haircolor I could stand to look at while I brushed my teeth.  This was intentional.  I´m serious, because they all had me crying and finally I was like no, this is screwed up. My week has sucked enough already and its only Monday.  I argued and told them what i wanted and reiterated that i said the same initially, and they are professionals, who I am sure are more than capable of fixing any color problem, and I wanted them to.  What did they do after screaming at me and telling me the color was not orange?, when oh hell yes it was!, I could have had a sunkist stamp on my head and passed myself off as the fruit.  And they all circled around  me and the hairbrushing bitch was truly, violently brushing me hair clearly ripping it out and watching the goddamned strands fall to the ground with a smirk, and there I was wide-eyed not sure what to do.  I could not believe it, I mean I have had some uncool things happen to me in Spain, but really this was too far fetched, too unbelieveable to even myself, as I sat in the chair watching, almost like I was a fly on the wall watching from a distance, and all I could remember was the Hoja de Reclamacion I had written on the train after what happened to Pam, "El tratamiento de viajeros estadounidenses" and I realized I was truly unhappy, not just depressed about the shittiness of what was happening, but that all this was wrong, it was wrong, and it was intentional and mean and fucking cruel and there I was in the chair with no one on my side. I felt alone.  Not homesick alone, but secluded from a society that while once was more, if not totally accepting, which now no longer even seemed to fake the guise of acceptance.  I am not Bush, I am not responsible, I did not vote for him, and my hair color is almost comical.  I mean it may actually be comical to everyone but me.  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The things I hate ...especially when I´m on the other side of the pond... short emails.  The "I´m-fine, its-hot, not-doin-much, this-weekend-I´ll-see-a-movie, went-to-the-grocery store, have-to-put-the-groceries-away.." that style of email  sucks , think harder, you are wasting precious space on the internet.  Make something up, I don´t care, tell a story, an anecdote, no "nothings new, blah blah blah."  IRRITATING.  Yes I know we all generally lead mundane, sometimes redundant lives, so tell me how you feel, what is important, do something different.  You don´t have to be in a foreign country to have something to talk to me about.  Most, but not all emails I am getting are actually verbatim (I mean every other email I open has exactly the same lines in it, are you all sharing a preconcieved email and just signing them individually?) but from different people, so I am setting a new requirement, I will return  all emails composed of five lines or less .  Sorry, but it seems like nobody really wants to talk to me, so I shall be forced to seek revenge by making you feel exactly as I do.  ESP. those closest to me, you know who you are I have bitched about this for awhile.  A good idea for a filler, is asking questions of the other person, think of them as prompts.  My idea for a prompt to you all is:  Do you prefer Gucci or Prada, and why?  okay so thats kinda assinine, but you get the point. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Thanks you for the last post that was courtesy of.. http://www.expage.com/5790StupidC
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      More stupidity from the internet to make me feel invincible... Investigating a purse snatching, Brunswick, Georgia, detectives picked up a man who fit the thief's description and drove him back to the scene. He was told to exit the car and face the victim for an I.D. The suspect dutifully eyed the victim, and blurted, "Yeah, that's the woman I robbed."   Elsewhere... In Nashville, they tell of Fred "Bubba" Johnson, the burglar who fell asleep on the sofa of the home he was robbing, only to be awakened by police.   Meanwhile... In Thibodaux, Louisiana, a robber with a thick Cajun accent couldn't get restaurant patrons to understand his demand for money. Frustrated, he whipped out his gun, but it wouldn't fire. Grabbing the cash register, he ran -- but got only three feet before falling down. The register was still plugged into the wall... Unplugging it, he tried again, but a regular diner decked him and called police.   And... In Rhode Island, cops were sure they had the right guy when the suspect in a string of coin-machine thefts proceeded to pay his $400 bail... entirely in quarters.   Stranger yet.... Texas authorities, responding to a store robbery, seized a man who was fleeing naked. When asked about his choice of attire, he said he'd stripped after the job because he figured his clothes would make him identifiable.   In the Heartland... Lawrence, Kansas - Officers tracked a midnight thief who prided himself on his running speed by following the red lights on his high-tech tennis shoes.   And Finally. . . In Virginia, a janitor went to great lengths to avoid I.D. in a 7-11 robbery, using a ski mask and rental car for the occasion. But he also wore his work uniform, which said "Cedar Woods Apartments" and had his name, Dwayne, stitched across the front. 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Stupid law of the day thanks to stupid laws.com    Stop that Black Beauty! Country: USA   In Marshalltown, Iowa, horses are forbidden to eat fire hydrants.    
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here´s my mantra for the day:  from horoscope.com: "Our greatest glory is not in never falling, but in rising every time we fall. " 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here´s my horoscope for tomorrow, sounds incredibly familiar....the person who I am talking about, knows who they are... "Something is going on that you don't know about -- but you can sense it. You know it. It's hard to tell if there is actually someone out there who is working to undermine what you say, or if this is more of a psychological issue where you are your own enemy and cannot see this at all. Take a hard look at how you are moralistic, for others may be rebelling to that, rather than to the relevance of your ideas. Reevaluate how you make your points, but not the essence of your individual ideas." also by Rick Levine, AOL  
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You feel good today with the Moon creating a supporting trine to Chiron, the Healer. Even if you have been experiencing difficulties, now you can transform your own hurts as you help others. You have the capability to be methodical in how you express yourself, yet simultaneously you can appear more lighthearted by what you say. No matter as easygoing you seem, the real you will come through -- and your passion will fuel whatever changes are taking place.  This is my AOL horoscope for today, by Rick Levine.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Rachel and Roomate Fernanda, before Roma, in front of entrance to El Escorial &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Tomb of Raphael, verified by Pope in 1838 when it was opened, located in Pantheon since shortly after his death, notice doves kissing in the center&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Day 3- Pantheon, black tomb in wall in ctr. is Victor Emmanuel&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    St. Peter´s Basilica day 3&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Pope giving blessing June 13th 2003 look for red velvet hanging from window&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Frederick I Barbarossa, 1123-1190, bottom, Frederick II King of Siciliy on top rt.  1194-1250, Henry IV top left&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Seal of Otto IV King of Romans, 1174-1218&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Pieta closest view day 2 Vatican City, St. Peter�s Basilica&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Closeup of Christ Sistine Chapel day 2&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Last Judgment Wall Sistine Chapel Roma&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Close-up Sistine chapel day 2&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Michelangelo-Sistine Chapel&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      More pics will be posted pronto.  Um arivaderchi, buon giorno, grazie, prego.  
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh and spaghetti.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here is what my dear friend Vern had to say about my Stilletto Stupidity: "1) Stop trying to be Audry Hepburn in Roman Holiday, it's not worth it.  That's why God invented tennies. " Thanks for the tip, smarty.  ;)  Anyway, Viva Italia, why am I in Spain?  Oh and I am going to see the Spanish Supreme Court tomorrow.  yo.  I hope I can find a way around NOT WEARING HEELS.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Tomb of Scipio Barbaratus&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    More famous Sculptures, it gets a little overwhelming after the three thousandth one&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    More Vatican Ceilings&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Somewhere in Vatican&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Hall of Sculptures, Maybe?-Vatican&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Some Famous sculpture...Vatican&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Part of line to get into Vatican Day2&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Dark pic of Pantheon Night 1&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Dark Pic of Trevi at Night&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Me and Trevi Noche 1&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Trevi closeup&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Trevi Fountain night 1&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Night 1, me somewhere in Rome, yes we were lost&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Where´s Waldo view from colliseum- look 4 Bride and Groom&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Spanish Steps day 1- military band playing&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Girls and Constantine´s Arch-Dark color pic&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Constantine�s Arch Roma&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Another view of constantine�s arch&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The girls and Constantine´s Arch&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Distant view of Forum&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Forum from Colliseum&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Me in the dark at Coliseo&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Inside Coliseo day 1&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Coliseo buds day 1&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Me and buds with audio guides at Coliseo&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Me and coliseo day 1&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Statue in Vatican day 2&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      okay so I am back now and pretty much in one piece but lemme tell ya, Rome is NOT THE CITY TO CRAM INTO A WEEKEND.  Or to wear stillettos in.  So.....my story....haha "that would suck if the only store open was Gucci and I bought designer flip flops, that would be exactly like the story of my Cousin Carrie who bought like a gucci umbrella because she didn´t have one and it was raining."  I´ll give ya one guess what area we were in that first night after walking half of Rome, by that time, I was willing to trade a kidney for flip flops...VIA CONDOTI.  Yes, the Spanish steps the shops, my MECCA.  The place I shall retire to one day and take Imelda Marcos´collection by storm.  My idea of heaven is what Gucci apparently looks like from the inside, the original, not the Saks Fifth Avenue San Antonio/last-stop-on-the-saks-delivery-route-reject-Gucci, but the good stuff.  I think I have a problem, an addiction of sorts, I had to leave cold turkey.  Anyway, so we get there, and I am suddenly skipping swollen feet, stone bruises and all, down the street, only to realize....they were closed.  My pace quickened....my heart stopped, oh no! they have all just closed!, but no a light in the distance....Look, one is open!....MaxMara.....the door doesn´t have the gates locked over it.  We went in looking for flat shoes....and then hahahaha....oh my god designer flip flops...truly and really  I own plastic flippies from MaxMara .  The best 23 euro I have ever spent.  So I continued the night in flippies and my super-stylin outfit that now looked strange with the beach shoes.   Night one, was long, day two began early and we waited in the line for the vatican museum/ sistine chapel since the crack of dawn, and literally, keeping in mind vatican city is large, the entrance was on one side of the walled circular city, the end of the line was directly on the opposite side next to the St Peter´s entrance.  FUN.  The lines make Disneyworld seem like nothin.  But I got in, and soon you´ll see the pics.  Then we got lunch and walked more (big surprise) and by the end of the trip we had seen just about everything in Rome short of the forum, however, we did see it opposite the colliseum, so really the trip was a raging success so long as my ability to walk (and not hobble) is regained.  This weekend I will be in Barcelona, yeah Eurail pass!  BUT, I am absolutely, positively not doing the melee, kamikaze, tourist frenzy.  I am plain tuckered out, and my feet may go awol if I don´t give them a day off.  So, if you need me over the weekend, tough, I will be on the beach getting burned and reading crime and punishment.  Beautiful.  Viva Roma.  
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When in Rome...eat lots of food, especially if you have to go back and eat more Spanish jamon.  Yuck...  The wine costs more here, but the food is damned better and costs the same.  I went everywhere, with mucho pics which will be posted as soon as I get back to San lorenzo.  I went shopping today, no Mom I didnt go crazy on the Via Condoti, BUT i could have!!!  EASILY.  My feet hurt.  Day one I decided, I had be play Roman and wear my little heels and cute outfit to tour in.  When in Rome... But no that is stupid I tackled the coliseum in stilettos, so anyone who still claims Fred Astaire is the better dancer is wrong, Ginger Rogers (good name by the way) did it backwards and in heels.  I feel tough now, but my feet are killing me.  So after hours of trampling Italy I gave in and said the next pair of flip flops  I see I am buying..... haha, then I said, wouldnt it be funny if we went into Gucci and I bought designer flops for lack of another store open.  Yeah, sure funny-   So we were walking and keeping our eyes open for shoe stores, and I was teetering around in stilettos,  but I found one store open......to be continued. arivaderchi
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I didn´t fail out of school, I got my con law grade back, its okay.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, good news, I am ahead in my reading for immigration law.  yeehaw.  I am not in Debtor-Creditor, surprise surprise.  I can´t wait for Rome all the Jamón here is getting icky,  I need pasta or pizza or something yummy.  We are going to get back Sunday night around midnight, sweet.  I am glad Duane from St. Thomas is coming so it won´t just be the three girls staying in the center of old Rome, now we have an escort.  Its funny, people keep saying, oh, well you might get robbed in Rome, wouldn´t that be scary, I started laughing, ¨Yes, it is.¨  Karen and I had a beer last night over dinner and it put both of us out of commission for the rest of the night.  I went to bed super early.  Oh and remember the class I had to fake a case recitation in, well Prof Maloy, knows my name now and when he´s calling role says my name then says, yes she´s here.  Oh and at breakfast he says ¨Hello Rachel¨ which is a little unnerving and not what you want to hear at 8am from your prof who gives the most reading.  I can´t tell if he likes me or if he suspects I had no idea what I was saying.  He said I did a good job, though at lunch yesterday, and that means all the other suckers in class will be called on before I will.  Haha.  Triumph.  Well, its not 104 here, hope you all develop innovative ways to not get scorched.  I am stalling I still have reading to do, hey mom, ¨Love you most¨ and someone tell my heathen brother to email me or I´ll have to make good on my initial threat.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      School as usual, I emailed Prof Burney about my grade to see where I clearly must have gone wrong, she said she would be happy to look up my exam notes she made and tell me where I can improve.  I am worried about S. it sounds like Innsbruck might not be happening for her.  Plus here apt flooded over memorial day while she was out of town and she came back to find water, about an inch in her house.  There must be something to the ickiness that is happening.  Penance for prior wrongs or forced appreciation of the good things.  I read immigration today and next chapter is refugee and asylee law.  Sweet. I leave for Rome on Friday.  On another note, I think the St. Thomas people are beginning to dislike the ¨St. Mary´s Girls¨ we have apparently developed a reputation for always doing the reading, and there are even rumors circulating that we´ve already finished the reading in both books.  Not so.  Wishful thinking.  I hope Rome provides a much needed release.  But of course, the books are coming too.  If any family members feel inclined to donate to the Rachel in Rome fund, please feel free to.  Oh, did I mention, I hate law school? 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tired of course, but surviving.  Today is almost midnight saturday night.  I just got dinner again with Karen Amy and Dean Piatt.  We have become a group of buddies.  I sometimes forget he´s the dean of my law school.  He apparently likes the band outkast and sang a song by Little Jon, the rapper and bobbed his head and everything getting into it.  The wonders never cease.  He also gave us a summary of Rocky and why it is actually a love story, haha.  Very funny man.  Very funny.  Anyway I am still feeling discouraged, this summer just isn´t how it should be.  I got my property grade back and I am less than thrilled.  I can´t explain how the class I worked the hardest on brought back the least desirable results.  As I said the wonders never cease.  I think my roomie is having a makeshift party in our room tonight, watching some movie called Red Dawn.  I wanna see Harry Potter really really badly, but I dunno of anyone who will see it with me, plus I would have to see it in Madrid where the closest decently sized theater is.  We went to Madrid today, we meant to see all the Museums, but we only made it through almost all of the Prado then we walked around forever and made our way back across the city to Plaza Mayor for sodas and water then walked up Calle mayor to the puerta del sol, I was the acting tour guide, we then went shopping in el corte inglés oh and before all that went all the way out to the Plaza de Toros of Madrid.  We had a very long but good, if not tiring day.  I got my laundry back yesterday from the take it and pay-by-the-pound place and it was still pretty wet, so my room looks roughly the way it did when I did all my clothes in the room with my roomie.  Tornado style.  Anyway.  Take care, I wanna go to mass tomorrow, but I can´t take communion so I feel kind of like its not the same.  By the way, Monsigneur Anderson from St. thomas, Dean Piatt, Amy, Karen and I went to dinner at a little place called Il Duetto, an Italian place and the dean payed again.  We even had Tiramisu.  I hope my incoming grades do not make me feel threatened enough to feel the need to discuss them further with the dean.  
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow I feel wounded.  My feelings were hurt by an innapropriate letter from someone I care about deeply.  What do you do, when you are trying to explain why someone was out of line and the other person is so intent on not being at fault for an obvious lapse in judgment, that they refuse to listen and lash out verbally.  I can´t concentrate since it happened and someone is just not listening.  There is such a marked difference from listening and hearing, its the difference between apathy and empathy.  I am in a weird situation now, I´m going to Rome on the 11th with two people I now feel awkward around.  What do I do?  Life actually really sucks for me anyway and its not getting any brighter.  I was studying last night with Karen late, after having dinner with the St. Mary´s crowd and Dean Piatt.  I went outside had a couple of café con leches to keep me going and after studying there awhile went up to the mezzanine to study, but the young woman who works at the front desk said she had to turn the lights off at 12 am, as per request of manager.  So all 10 of us were kicked out.  This was the first time i wasn´t abudantly prepared and all this took place while I feel crushed inside.  So I told Dean Piatt at breakfast today and he asked our debtor creditor prof to have mercy that we had tried but couldn´t finish because we had gotten the boot.  But, to no avail, Prof Maloy barrelled throug the reading and since so many had skipped he would call names from the cards of the students in class.  I will give you one guess who had tried to finish, but was cut off by the front desk lady, and was the last case to be called on to recite.  Nobody had gotten that far, but I was too afraid to say I hadn´t gotten that far.  So, I winged it.  I made sure my voice was steady and spoke loudly slowly and clearly and I actually did a good job.  That was my first time of winging it.  I told Dean Piatt after class in case I got docked for doing a shoddy job, but Maloy came up to me and said I had done an excellent job.  I B.S.ed my way through, but he doesn´t know, thank GOD.  Dean Piatt said congrats, now I am ready for court.  He laughed, obviously amused by my residual terror over a case.  I am just sad right now, I don´t like the things I need to be stable amidst this turmoil to run afoul.  F%$& the weekend, it feels like monday.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Emma and Rachel on Calle Barbieri: jet lag is bad&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    My room, the eight bunk room, look at the bed that is made with back pack on it at the back, thats mine&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    In the kitchen at Barbieri Hostel&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    My daddy at Houston Airport before my flight&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The night before I left Madrid for San Lorenzo inside Barbieri&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    In Barbieri Hostel, Madrid, with Buddy from Fundaci�n Jos� Ortega y Gasset, back from Toledo&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    El retiro&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay okay they are not really stupid one and stupid two.  I gave up being mean and vengeful, it just took way too much energy.  My classes are almost two hrs. long and back to back, it takes all day and breakfast is bright and early and lunch is only served if you get there on time, or you have to wait for the next course.  I have had to stay up late and study every night after exhausting days.  This is not an easy way to do it.  It is taking so much more effort than even school at home.  I was supposed to have read 75 pgs last night for just Debtor Creditor alone, then I had Immigration too.  I don´t have time to do anything and I am so worn by midday that I have to resist naps by not allowing myself in the physical bldg of the hotel, or then I nap and don´t sleep at night.  I actually haven´t slept for two nights now, except about 4 hrs last night, which for me is not enough.  I am sorry I can´t  email you all individually, I was under the very mistaken belief that this program would be a bit less strenuous, they say that it is, but they lie, it like the reading assignments that never end.  I look like hell, don´t have time for makeup and have let my hair go curly.  I am so damn tired.  Yesterday 15 girls and I decided to mastermind a jaunt into Madrid, very stupid choice on my part, it took into the wee hours of the morning to make up for time lost in Madrid.  This is also hard.  Apparently St. Mary´s is stupid and wrong, this isn´t a Bankruptcy course, this opens with Debtor-Creditor relations (a course I hadn´t heard of at St. MU), then we move onto Bankruptcy, then Secured Transactions, then wrap-up with Spanish/civil law.  To all the non law-junkies, thats a three hour course, followed by a three hour course, topped off with a three hour course, and a full other round of law school in the civil tradition.  WHAT AM I DOING?  I am buying sleeping pills today.  Mom can you fill my prescription ones and have daddy fedex them to me?  I need to sleep.  I have to dink café con leche constantly and still can´t function.  This sucks.  I hate law school.  Oh and the kicker is that the Dean keeps asking me to climb this literal mountain behind us, a 5 mile climb, how can I say no?  He is really excited and thinks I want to go, I want to get my reading done and figure out what Bankruptcy is?  I have to figure out how community property in Texa sfigured into a case where the Husband owed IRS taxes and wife didn´t get to claim her vested interest in her half of his money, something about the govt having priority, but even though the case said she wasn´t liable, only her husband was, that they could still get at half of her money through community property  because of his vested interest in her property.  Seems like a double edged sword, she has a half interest in  his income and is not at fault, but can´t protect her share, while he is the wrongdoer and his the only one liable, gets to pay off his debt by also accessing part of her half vested interest in his income.  What in the hell did I just say?  Did I mention I didn´t like property law?
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I am leaving Austria tonight to Munich then onto Prague.&nbsp; Its way cheaper and my Innsbruck&nbsp; fun meter has expired.&nbsp; So I am going back to the northern part of the former czechoslovakia to Czech Republic for some more chill time.&nbsp; I am getting homesick and need to refill with my friends.&nbsp;  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Wow, I feel empowered.&nbsp; I told the-ex-from-feb about how out of line he was over the UNO card game&nbsp;last night.&nbsp; I told him that he needs to close his doors, since he is constantly sitting in his room, through the thin walls and blasting his "I'm the Original Gangster music", while the rest of us actually have stuff to do, plus it echoes to our end of the hall.&nbsp; Its the music that never ends.&nbsp; He was apparently under the misconception that he had title to decibel rights.&nbsp; Not so.&nbsp; And I told him that the exact reason i dumped him in feb still obviously existed.&nbsp; He doesn't think about how he affects others.&nbsp; Plus his little solo last night while we were all talking....he sang Regulators....in his booming voice, above the roar of the crowd so (once again) all had to listen to him.&nbsp; He sang the whole song.&nbsp; I was like Okay, come on, everyone's trying to talk I can't hear the other side of the table.&nbsp; His answer, "I don't give a *%$#, you shut-up."&nbsp; No thanks jerko.&nbsp; I can't believe he went to Rice.&nbsp; He crashed my friends little pow-wow and then had to act like an ass.&nbsp; I think I will just become a nun and never date again.  
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Well, I am at least excited about Clinic in the fall...even if everything else topples, I have that.&nbsp; Hey, here's the link:  urlLink http://www.stmarytx.edu/law/index.php?group=program&amp;page=immigrationRights.php &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Pretty cool stuff.&nbsp; I am preparing my presentation on a law review article for tomorrow morning in Art Law.&nbsp; C. and I were going to make a second attempt at the pool, but considering Innsbruck missed the memo that its pushing August, and I had my fleece zipped up today, I don't think we'll be working on our tans in this London-ish weather.  
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Thats it! I am a genius for dumping ex-from-Feb. way back when.&nbsp; He is a pig.&nbsp; Pig Pig Pig Pig.&nbsp; Totally.&nbsp; I think its just remarkable the innordinate share of them I have had.&nbsp; Am I compensating for all the lucky girls who only date nice guys?&nbsp; Apparently.&nbsp; He decided to crash my buds Uno card game downstairs.&nbsp; He decided the whole time was appropriate to add little tacky, about-our-now-extinct-relationship comments in front of everyone.&nbsp; One move I made I was like, "Its all part of my game plan."&nbsp; He was like ,"Yeah like everything else you do.&nbsp; I was scared to touch anything in your house with a post it note on it."&nbsp; I said, "No you weren't."&nbsp; The stupid ass would eat my meals I had made for school the next day or my tubs of pre-made central market food so I could make it through the hectic week without cooking.&nbsp; Then he was like, "Yeah, you're right."&nbsp; Oh and the postits were because not only did I have a boyfriend then who would appear at my house to eat for free, DAILY, but my roomate's brother was living there eating everything too.&nbsp; It got ridiculous, I was paying but never got the benefit of what I bought.&nbsp;&nbsp; This is becoming a common theme around him.&nbsp; What a pig. Totally.&nbsp; And just last night he was like, "You could always date me again."&nbsp; No thanks, really, I don't have any kids and for the moment don't need any.    
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Argh.&nbsp; Soooo irritating.&nbsp; Well the ex thats&nbsp;here struck again today.&nbsp; I have this huge sign on my door that says "RACHEL IS RECUPERATING" so nobody would bug me for a little while, hey maybe I might have even gotten a much needed nap in?!&nbsp; Worthless.&nbsp; Well, I put my trash outside the door, also so the maids wouldn't come in and I made a pile of books next to my bed and decided to get a quick nap in.&nbsp; No.&nbsp; Not happening.&nbsp; Oh course the ex here, arrived home from school, being really loud, but hey thats cool I can be loud too.&nbsp; Then after everyone else in the whole building including the maids who don't even speak english, got the hint, he didn't.&nbsp; He called my room, wtf?!&nbsp; I normally refer to this phone as a blaring nasty ring, because its also my alarm clock.&nbsp; I answered and the first thing he says is "I saw your sign."&nbsp; Thanks dummy but obviously you didn't.&nbsp; He said he was calling to see if i needed anything.&nbsp; Yeah, genius, to be left alone.&nbsp; This is a totally typical example of his having convinced himself that he is the most thoughtful person in the world.&nbsp; This is half the reason I dumped him in the first place.&nbsp; He's not, he doesn't EVER stop to think about what the other person really wants or needs or feels, i.e., he has yet to actually go through actual the motions of thoughtfulness, i.e., putting thought into something.&nbsp; He will see what a societally accepted thing to do is, and go into auto pilot, without thinking of what the other person needs.&nbsp; I told him in the beginning I had to break up with him because he had yet to think past the end of his nose.&nbsp; He could have ordered his own pizza last night, or he could have left be a bit more since it was mine and I was starving.&nbsp; Worthless.  
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Haha, okay so this is me posing with a shot of Absinthe, NO it was not mine, especially after watching people drink the stuff and puke their little guts up.  &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Haha I was looking through some of my non-posted pics of the camping adventure in Croatia, and it occurred to me that something seemed a little outta place in the shed we stayed in....&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Yes, I realize that it is now 8 am and I am on the computer.&nbsp; No, I am not in class, this was an intentional move.&nbsp; I am taking what can interchangeably be called a "reading" day, a personal day, a "sick" day.&nbsp; If anyone tries to scold me for this, well a pox on you.&nbsp;&nbsp; I just don't care.&nbsp; I think I am displaying signs of burn-out syndrome, mainly the apathy.&nbsp; I have been acting like Peter from Office Space, post-hypnosis.&nbsp;    &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; So last night I decided, lets all watch a movie in Rachel's Room.&nbsp; I opted to see  Reservoir Dogs  a classic,&nbsp; but lets just discuss some things.&nbsp;&nbsp; Yes, I remember why I broke up with guest #1 in Feb.&nbsp; Yes, so he came over first and we were hanging out, and then he was like "I'm getting hungry, are you?"&nbsp; and I said "No I just ate," pointing toward my half eaten Kebab which I was saving for later.&nbsp; Well, he gets up walks across the room, grabs it and starts unwrapping it.&nbsp; It didn't really occur to me what was happening until the thing was almost in his mouth, so I said, "Uh, sure you can have it."&nbsp; Why didn't I say, uh, drop it dude, step away from the Kebab.&nbsp; Later he decided to sit entirely too close to me, I said something to try to kindly get the don't-bust-a-move idea across.&nbsp; Can he not take hints?&nbsp;  He only sat closer .&nbsp; What is wrong with men?&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; So, later on, I was hungry, OBVIOUSLY, since I never got to eat my whole Kebab.&nbsp; Hellloooo.&nbsp; So I said, I am ordering pizza from Nemati's.&nbsp; I ordered Caprichosa, my fav.&nbsp; The pizza gets here and I pay, but he digs in , without asking, then after eating 2/3 of the damn thing said, "I was gonna pay for part of it."&nbsp; Really, were ya now, funny because I thought I was going to  eat  part of it.&nbsp; I offered pieces to my two buddies sitting there, cuz I felt bad the whole food thing had erupted into a communal eating endeavor without them getting any.&nbsp; So I offered.&nbsp; In the end I was still hungry.&nbsp; Oh, and doesn't it seem a little, I dunno uncouth to just waltz in to your ex-girlfriend's room, and rather than chill on a chair or grab a seat on the rug, to plop right down on her bed to watch a movie.&nbsp; He didn't ask, and frankly thats my bed, thats just ewww, I dunno not right.&nbsp; So, there we all were, the Brady Bunch, watching Reservoir Dogs...Ex and I sitting on the bed,&nbsp;one friend&nbsp;chillin' in a chair, and&nbsp;one on the rug.&nbsp;   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Lovely, well I have read like 259,000 pgs today so I guess this is not really a day off.&nbsp; Yes, I know I took the weekend off, but really I spent entirely too much of it reading for school.&nbsp; Crime and Punishment has been neglected because of&nbsp;the Olympic-sized&nbsp;reading assignments for class.&nbsp; Lemme tell ya, In re: Sealed Case, is not a fun read.&nbsp; Figuring out the magnitude of the Patriot Act&nbsp;amendments effect on FISA is an ugly topic involving civ pro, con law, crim law, and all kinds of criminal theory I know nothing about.&nbsp; I think&nbsp;my brain is going to explode.&nbsp;  
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Dear everyone, I was scrolling through my emails and I remembered prior to my infamous breakup, my best friend since I was 5 yrs old and my all-time greatest supporter no matter what stupid things I am doing, had an opinion on the matter...here's part of the email...   &nbsp;&nbsp;  Hey kiddo- so I'm taking in all your logged transmissions little pieces at a time, can't over do it, then I will have nothing to look forward to for tomorrow, can I tell you how excited I was that you called, thrilled, anyway, think I already told you that.... Hows life??? I forgot to ask hows Cabana Boy???? hahaha... I thought that was entertaining myself. I mean don't let me discourage you, even if he is a loathsome bottom feeder who attaches and then sucks every last happy memory out of your body and replaces it with his own dissatisfaction, and self-hate, as well as hate for anything else that moves..... Ok ok I guess I'll quit, I still don't like him. Ok you know what I'll give him a chance but only if you want me to. He's going to have to pass a couple of tests however..... Test number 1: &nbsp;Crawling on hands and knees across the surface of a recently erupted volcano, while complementing your amazing sense of style, your humor, grace, wit, poise, and brilliance......Test number> 2: He must go with me to my bar and spend an entire night not watching girls make out with each other but instead tell me how much he misses your company, and how he wishes he was cuddling with you watching girlie flicks all night long, and if his eyes wander for even a second, I'm stabbing them out with a rusty spoon.and the last test, Test number 3: He must learn Latin, then recite William Shakespeare's entire collected works from memory while strumming a lute and dancing around in some very restrictive tights, while smiling...... Anyway, I thought it was funny...OK Love you lots, and I miss you a million bottles of peach propel   
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here's one of my favorite explanations links:&nbsp; not sure if its right, but its entertaining...  urlLink http://www.fiftiesweb.com/amerpie-1.htm   The words of American Pie, by Don McLean 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Okay, so in an effort to not have my family kill me for airing this...I will not disclose certain things.&nbsp; I have a relative, who is younger than myself, who is marrying this guy that I went out with in 8th or 9th grade.&nbsp; eww.&nbsp; he's nothing special thus that fact he made the "ex-list" but really he's more like, no I won't say the truth, in this case the truth might really hurt.&nbsp;&nbsp; They just sort of last minute told the family although all of his family has flown in town, and they are....drumroll....doing it at the courthouse.&nbsp; Okay so i gotta say it, he reminds me of the type who would comment during a Jerry Springer show, from the live studio audience.&nbsp; No college, no career, no ambition, just generally nothing.&nbsp;    &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Great and here I am still single, but as proven here, I guess there are slim pickin's.  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    More Innsbruck at dusk. Lovely, eh?&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Innsbruck at dusk, ahhhh&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Another awful pic of me, minus makeup, please remember it was raining, heavily, except right when this was taken.  And yes I wanted to pull a Liesel and go bench leaping around the interior, but apparently a few years ago an older woman was doing just that and broke her hip so they have it locked now. tragic....oh and the hip was tragic too.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Me [yes w/out makeup] and my surrogate Kuwaiti mother&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       To start with,&nbsp;  Where are all the frogs? &nbsp; You hear of Rainforest frogs, Lord knows there are San Antonio frogs, but where are the Austrian frogs?&nbsp; I am keenly aware of the little (or sometimes mammoth suckers) as a I have an aversion to cold blooded creatures in general.&nbsp; I think this dates back to the Frog Prince story and the childhood horror induced from 5 yr old thoughts of having to kiss one.&nbsp; As such, when I see one to this day I feel a sudden&nbsp; need to jump the closest fence, bus stop, street lamp, etc.&nbsp; Well, its been rainy and there is a river nearby and everything is green, but there are no frogs?&nbsp; Or there is a conspiracy to wait and jump me in mass when I'm struttin' 4 inch heels.&nbsp;&nbsp;    &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Moving&nbsp;right along.&nbsp;&nbsp; Went to Salzburg today.&nbsp; Rained.&nbsp; Big surprise.&nbsp; Did the&nbsp;Sound of&nbsp;Music Tour and felt at ease and happy.&nbsp; It was sooooo great.&nbsp; They expect you to be cheesy and even&nbsp;encourage it.&nbsp; However, they&nbsp;gave us the real story of the Von&nbsp;Trapps and smashed my&nbsp;happy little fairytale bubble.&nbsp; But they compensated by playing the&nbsp;music the whole&nbsp;time on the bus.&nbsp; Beautiful.&nbsp; We stopped for a tobogan ride and I declined as my fear of heights is second only to my fear&nbsp;of&nbsp;cold blooded, reptilian icky things.&nbsp; I watched from the bottom and made&nbsp;friends with a couple from Kuwait.&nbsp; I&nbsp;told the wife that my&nbsp;mother would kill me if she saw me shoot down luge going a gazillion miles an hour with no&nbsp;seatbelt.&nbsp; She hugged me, squeezed my hand, and said "I'll be your mother on the tour."&nbsp; They even asked for&nbsp;pictures with me, so in keeping&nbsp;with the general congeniality with my new-found-surrogate parents, I asked for pics with them too.&nbsp; I was glad I made&nbsp;friends with them.&nbsp; When we had first&nbsp;gotten on the bus, the tour guide [typical] asked where I am from, I told him the U.S., that wasn't enough for him, so I said Texas.&nbsp; I realized from the initial look on their faces that&nbsp;they didn't dislike Texans, but they well somehow unsure of sharing a bus row with me.&nbsp; So I started mission improbable to prove&nbsp;I was affable.&nbsp; Apparently I was a success, they walked me to the train station when it was all over.&nbsp; cool.&nbsp; So, the other adopted&nbsp;friends I&nbsp;made were a group of Aussies, amiable type of&nbsp;people as usual, and it was funny cuz leaving the tour we all said goodbye.&nbsp; I went up to my platform to wait a good thirty minutes and I&nbsp;thought I was hallucinating,&nbsp; I could hear&nbsp;their&nbsp;voices.&nbsp; Anyway they were on my train.&nbsp; But in the scramble to get aboard, we were separated again and I thought I would suffer the ride alone.&nbsp; So&nbsp;I sat and was busting out my MP3 player when whose voice boomed over the dull roar, but the Aussies.&nbsp; So anyway we talked all the way to Worgl when they got off, but when they did they did a very touching and&nbsp;not typical thing for a non-Euro....they&nbsp;both leaned down to hug and gimme a kiss on the cheek.&nbsp; Then they&nbsp;kept turning around and waving goodbye from the exit of the train and after they got off, until their heads disappeared descending the stairs.&nbsp; I dunno why, maybe from hunger exhaustion and cold rain, but it was touching.&nbsp; The whole day turned out to be sweet.&nbsp;    &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Then I got back into Innsbruck and waited&nbsp;for the stupid bus, which skid and almost took out another bus, thats&nbsp;one hell of a way to board a bus, immediately post-almost-accident.&nbsp; Then the Austrian comfort&nbsp;food I sought in my exhaustion was closed, and I realized I would be doomed to order pizza.&nbsp; Apparently somebody forgot to give Innsbruck the memo that its Saturday!!&nbsp; So I descended the bus a stop early in hopes of find some yummy filling Austrian food, which functions like&nbsp;London pub&nbsp;food in cold rain.&nbsp; And one light was on...Gasthaus Prugger...but I remembered I looked bedraggled, no make-up, I'd been rained on since early that morning.&nbsp; I went in even though its also a very nice restaurant, at this point I would have bought anything I was so starved for&nbsp;food I was getting dizzy, thanks to tour-rambo-Rachel's melee approach to visiting Salzburg.&nbsp; It was so good.&nbsp; Sleepy now.&nbsp; So long, farewell...      
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Okay, so I am going to Salzburg now.&nbsp; Well actually I am stalling, its sprinkling and ugly, oh well, I'm going anyway. bye  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Fun times, just found a pic of me in college, guess which one I am...  urlLink http://wchorus.tamu.edu/  
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       This is the epitome of politically incorrect:    &nbsp;  urlLink http://politicalhumor.about.com/library/images/blbushundercover2.htm    urlLink http://politicalhumor.about.com/library/images/blbushlordrings.htm    urlLink http://politicalhumor.about.com/library/images/blbushcomedian.htm   Okay so I'll be fair....   urlLink http://politicalhumor.about.com/library/images/blpic-kerryedwardslove.htm    urlLink http://politicalhumor.about.com/library/images/blpic-kerryforeignleaders.htm    urlLink http://politicalhumor.about.com/library/images/blpic-kerryband.htm   Wow I feel so guilty having done that...haha...but very amused  
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just got an evite to a birthday party in Miami for one of my buds from St. Thomas Univ School of Law.&nbsp; If I were&nbsp;in Los Estados Unidos I would be there in a heart beat!!&nbsp; I hope ya'll have&nbsp;fun, I am soooo jealous!&nbsp;  
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       George Bernard Shaw time:     &nbsp;   "All great truths begin as blasphemies."    "Youth is a wonderful thing.&nbsp; What a crime to waste it on children."    "The worst sin towards our fellow creatures is not to hate them, but to be indifferent to them; that's the essence of inhumanity."    "The reasonable man adapts himself to the world; the unreasonable one persists in trying to adapt the world to himself. Therefore all progress depends on the unreasonable man."    "Men are wise in proportion, not to their experience, but to their capacity for experience."    "Americans adore me and will go on adoring me until I say something nice about them."    "If history repeats itself, and the unexpected always happens, how incapable must Man be of learning from experience."    "We don't bother much about dress and manners in England, because as a nation we don't dress well and we've no manners."    "When a stupid man is doing something he is ashamed of, he always declares that it is his duty."    "There is only one religion, though there are a hundred versions of it."     Here's my Fav John Donne:    No man is an Island, entire of itself; every man is a piece of the Continent, a part of the main; if a clod be washed away by the sea, Europe is the less, as well as if a promontory were, as well as if a manor of thy friends or of thine own were; any man's death diminishes me, because I am involved in Mankind; And therefore never send to know for whom the bell tolls; It tolls for thee.  John Donne, Meditation XVI     &nbsp;    
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       So I slept in today, on my first day of the weekend I-don't-have-to-do-anything.&nbsp; Beautiful things, not having my jeering wake-up call at the crack of dawn.&nbsp; I woke up in the middle of the night though, and walked across the room to the phone because I realized I hadn't punched in the code for a wake-up call.&nbsp; Then I realized, haha, I don't need one!!!&nbsp;    &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Unfortunately, however, my plans of being stupid this weekend may be foiled.&nbsp; Its raining.&nbsp; So I guess I will hold my breath and wait for tomorrow.&nbsp; In the meantime, on of my good friends gave me some sound advice on the zoo here.&nbsp; In all honesty I have a weakness for&nbsp;zoos- and Missions games too- but that'll have to wait a bit.&nbsp; But, C. and I are getting seats for the season together next year, haha.&nbsp; I digress.&nbsp; Anyway, so after my friend recommended the Alpen Zoo, and to look at otters...minus discovery channel...I don't think I have seen an otter for real before?&nbsp; Do they have otters?&nbsp; Or am I going on the quest for the holy grail, Monty Python style?   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    The Pool Story .&nbsp; So, yesterday before her overnight train to Roma, C. and I decided we were going to kick back and chill a little; this week has put&nbsp;everyone in such a tizzy that we needed some R&R.&nbsp; Sooooo, we remembered hearing about this outdoor pool on the bus route, no we didn't ask "Which bus route?"&nbsp; because we are retarded.&nbsp; So, after hours of stalling we finally get on our swimsuits&nbsp;and grab our little mats to lay out on and head for the door.&nbsp; We got downstairs to the bus stop and sat down realizing where do we get off?, where are we going?, and other stuff imperative to know.&nbsp;&nbsp; So we were sitting there looking stupid as the bus neared and I remembered the tanning salon two doors down the street.&nbsp; "What about the tanning salon?"&nbsp; hehehehe.&nbsp; Anyway we went to the tanning salon.&nbsp;&nbsp; We got back later on and everyone was asking, "Hey, how was the pool?"&nbsp; "Was it far?"&nbsp; C. was like, oh it was good, which only made me laugh, cuz we didn't everyone to know we went tanning in Austria.&nbsp; I think my incessant laughter was what gave it away.&nbsp; Finally we were like, uh, we didn't make it to the pool....we went to a tanning salon.&nbsp; Okay so maybe this story is still only funny to me, but thats okay I entertain myself.  
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Besides the fact I am not in Turkey, let me focus on what I was trying to say to the people I was angry with.&nbsp; I was not angry with you in a silly way.&nbsp; There were things I did callously when I was in high school, that I am pretty darn sure messed up my little bro.&nbsp; As such any reference to me having a problem, where no problem exists, when said to my brother, runs the risk of him reliving things that I will die before I allow.&nbsp; Ch. is my only sibling and as much as he probably would prefer otherwise, I think of him as my best friend.&nbsp; To do anything or say anything, that could bring back the symptoms of distress Ch. used to display, will ONLY be answered by unbridled anger on my part, and to a point I hope you would almost expect that of the eldest.&nbsp; I am defensive, because once upon a time I brought things upon him, no 12 yr old should deal with.&nbsp; Therefore anything alluding to my actions then, with reference to my actions now, will recieve anger because they are wholly untrue.&nbsp; Please do not come to me, as a recent email said, and claim that such statements were made off-the-cuff or jokingly.&nbsp; This is not something that can or should be joked about and I fail to see why anyone would think they would be received, especially in light of the circumstances as funny.&nbsp; I am not laughing.&nbsp; I actually refused to talk to my mother for two days over this.&nbsp; That indicates in my mind that something is awry rather than humorous. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        The hills are alive, with the Sound of Music ... I'll give ya one guess where I am going tomorrow...Yes!!! After months of travelling, everyone else is going far far away and I have a chance to be stupid and run around Salzburg singing my fav Sound of Music tunes.&nbsp; C. was in my room looking for her memory card for her camera, while R. was uploading her pics onto my comp.&nbsp; Then K. walked in and it took me a minute to register what her shirt said:&nbsp; it had three pics on it showing a few of my favorite things and at the bottom is said Salzburg.&nbsp; That was all it took I was sold!&nbsp;    &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Oh and my Int'l Crim Law reading was ridiculous.&nbsp; RI-DI-CU-LOUS.&nbsp; Everyone else went to the Hofgarten or the casino last night, but NOOOO, RACHEL didn't.&nbsp; I ran around Karwendel reloading on diet cokes, in my yoga pants, trying the wade through the 80 odd pgs for Int'l Crim Law.&nbsp;Hello we have other classes to read for too!&nbsp;She must really resent this being a 1 hr class.&nbsp; So, I managed with much effort to get through it.&nbsp; In class today, half were gone, apparently there had been a mass hiatus after the announcement of readings day 1.&nbsp; She seemed surprised nobody was there.&nbsp; Then she asked about the readings, I almost snickered aloud, those that had shown&nbsp;to class were at the Hofgarten until some time shortly before the beginning of class and were not in good shape.&nbsp; Its Thursday dude, whaddya expect?  
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink http://www.moviewavs.com/cgi-bin/spark.cgi?Episode_217_Gnomes=217_phase2.wav   more stupid stuff 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I have tackled most of the reading, but really Int'l Crim law is unrealistic.&nbsp; She seems to begrudge the fact this is only a one credit course and retaliates by assigning mucho material.&nbsp; After reading pgs 23-73 and 178-183 and 1-6 and whatever else, I got to begin Art Law reading,&nbsp; I got through pgs 1-6 and then looked at the assignment in the big book, the first chapter, and wondered again why I am in law school?&nbsp; I think these questions surface more frequently on school nights after 10 pm.&nbsp;    &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Alot of people are going to Rome, including C.&nbsp;&nbsp; I was invited, but hey I had been there in June, so no I am not going.&nbsp; What might you ask am I going to do?&nbsp; Well, besides read for Int'l Crim law, I don't really know.&nbsp; Schools out for the weekend as of tomorrow and I am without plans.&nbsp; If I stay in innsbruck I am convinced I'll be the only one left behind, so that would suck, but what should I do other than that?&nbsp; I want to go to Prague really, really badly, but another horrendous train ride just sounds very unappealing.&nbsp; 22 more pgs to read, wait no, 21.5 more.&nbsp;   
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Whether or not I am mad at relatives, looks like I have to be in S.A. before Aug 12th.&nbsp; One of my best friends,V., &nbsp;is undergoing drastic surgery,&nbsp; I disagree with the choice, but this is her call and she's made it.&nbsp; I will be&nbsp;keeping vigil&nbsp;in her hospital room until the nurses try to drag me out afterward.&nbsp;&nbsp; V.&nbsp;I hope you are absolutely sure about this, you can change your mind.&nbsp; Of course you did this while I am too far away to sit you down and attempt to talk you out of this, but at least you are waiting until I get back.&nbsp;   
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Took Cochran's final, not much fun.&nbsp; In fact it was pretty darn tough, esp in the time constraints.&nbsp; I really worked myself up beforehand and was sitting in the rare sunlight, when who should walk by.....drumroll.....Tullos.&nbsp; Yes the one and only leader of the hellish Legal Writing class.&nbsp; This did not improve my mood, rather it brought back haunting memories of my brief.&nbsp; She tried to give me a pep talk, and told me to go sit by the river and absorb the negatice ions.&nbsp; I almost laughed,but luckily stifled it into a cough in the nick of time.&nbsp; I asked what negative ions were, feigning interest, and wondering how I could desire anything else with the word "negative" in it.&nbsp; Not very convincing.&nbsp; I passed on the negative ions and opted to chug some machine dispensed nasty coffee and my requisite Diet Coke.&nbsp; I paced beforehand and he only gave us an hour for a total of six essays...yes it was open book, no that did not make it easier, quite the opposite.&nbsp; The questions required you to know EVERYTHING and be able to flip to it and hopefully cite it in TMinus 5 seconds.&nbsp; My long essay, the last one, worth the most, ended up looking like chicken scratch, but hey not my fault...you wanna read..lemme type, you wanna squint look at my writing.&nbsp; I have another final due by 9:15 am for promoting-the-rule-of-unrelated-stuff, its a page long fact pattern that is crazy far-fetched.&nbsp; My answer will be in keeping I assume.&nbsp; Anyway, must start.&nbsp; Plus, I have somewhere near 8 million pgs to read for the two new classes beginning tomorrow.&nbsp; Something tells me they'll get read over the weekend instead.  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Finals today.&nbsp; Very Bad.&nbsp; How do I link Jurisdiction, Choice of Law and Recognition of Judgments in the International realm together, preferably with some coherence with only 25 minutes for the big essay [yeah, right, we'll see how big anything is in only 25 minutes], and 35 minutes for the 5 short answers that he is concerned we'll spend too much time on.&nbsp; Well, yes, Cochran, I would have to agree that's a valid point&nbsp;for concern especially since I am verbose, long-winded, etc.&nbsp; See, I can't even describe the lengthiness of my phrasing without using 2&nbsp; terms to describe it.&nbsp; Lovely.&nbsp; Also, I think my short term memory bank is on back-order right now, maybe in a couple weeks it will have caught up with the increase in demand, more likely, It'll flatline and I will come back talking in tongues, twitching, with a mad case of terets.&nbsp; Okay, maybe not.&nbsp; It also occurred to me that I don't really know what he is going to test on specifically.&nbsp; Great, I am now also walking in blindfolded, better tread lightly .&nbsp;&nbsp;     &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I am in&nbsp;between classes right now.&nbsp; In the next class I'll get my nasty take-home final on the class that would have better been named  Promoting the Rule of Art and Bankruptcy law with Sandra Day O'Connor speaking in the middle classes .&nbsp;&nbsp; Definite lack of coherence there.&nbsp; How exactly does studying stolen art cases and bankruptcy code sections have to do directly with promoting the rule of law.&nbsp;&nbsp;Yes, I am sure there is some lovely B.S. way to explain that, but really, gimme a break promoting the rule of&nbsp;a teacher whose husband likes to play stradivari violains, owns one, and there&nbsp;is case law involving strads, so she talks about&nbsp;it.&nbsp; Whatever, how do I prepare to explain this....what if she asks:&nbsp; What did you learn from my class? as occured during Session&nbsp;1 in Espana.&nbsp;&nbsp; my answer:     &nbsp;   1.)&nbsp; You like to talk too much and when we answer your questions, you doubtless will say we are wrong and then tell us the right answer is exactly what we just said.    2.)&nbsp; Your thought processes are muddled....you are as difficult to follow as Hegel, but Hegelian writings have the benefit of logic.    3.)&nbsp; You husband owns and plays a Strad and Guarneri.&nbsp; We're very happy for you.    4.)&nbsp; You chose cases that involve Strads and Guarneris, coincidence, I think not.    5.)&nbsp; Your husband came with you to Austria.&nbsp; I am seeing some connections finally.    6.)&nbsp; Your husband played in class and for Sandra Day O'Connor--aha you needed to justify his being here through your choice of classroom materials.    7.)&nbsp; I already took bankruptcy and answered all your questions in class.&nbsp;  &nbsp;   
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       My  c  o  l  o  r   options seem to have reappeared, no complaints here.&nbsp; I did my laundry today, not a small feat, as this seemed to be the day everyone has chosen to tidy up.&nbsp; My theory is that since we are all law students and have at least two finals in the next two days, we start our afternoon before by finding something we "have" to do in order to stall.&nbsp; Plus, there are only four little machines here and two dryers, and the people in line get pretty ugly.&nbsp; I beat them to it since I had an 8 o'clock for my first class and not promoting the rule of law, but I still had to wait two hours for a stupid machine.&nbsp; You might think that during this time where everyone is waiting for a machine, that we all must have brought our books to study...no...there were trashy romance novels cracked open, one dork studying [he's not really a dork, I don't thinnkhe has read for class at all yet], and myself who likes the stare at the wall for awhile routine.&nbsp; I find a few moments a day filled with absolutely nothing are quite refreshing.&nbsp; But, whats really funny is the state of my room now.&nbsp; I have clothes hung up everywhere, and the room just seems to smell wet.&nbsp;     &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  I talked to mom today.&nbsp; I hadn't really felt homesick until then.&nbsp; Yuck.&nbsp; I also hadn't called her since Spain, and with Cochran's final looming over my head, I wanted to hear her voice.&nbsp; So, I made the trek into town and finally found a good phone card.&nbsp; Then I tried to find a free pay phone it would work on, I called her finally and didn't want to get off the phone.&nbsp; Some other students were walking by the booth and I felt my face scrunching up to cry and I thought I would lose it and everyone would see.&nbsp; With all that has gone on, my friends getting academically excluded, and/or not being allowed to come to Innsbruck, losing a relationship I thought meant something, and realizing I was going to have to brush myself off for the start of a new school year soon without the benefit of those I had grown so close to, it just sucked.&nbsp; There are times when I pride myself on being so head strong and independent and times where its nice not to have to.&nbsp; God, I wanted my mom so bad, I felt like a little kid.&nbsp; So, stupid, but I am just not very happy right now and more than that I feel some extreme dissatisfaction with the endings of late.&nbsp; Nothing feels safe or predictable, like my volvo with all six airbags, its all so rocky and full of upheaval.&nbsp; Hearing how my mom has taught my dog to respond to new words, and how he's doing things I bent over backwards trying to teach him, but he wouldn't do, damn, it sounds like my life is going on without me in it.&nbsp; It feels like my friends are dropping out of the picture, my boyfriend [excuse me "ex"] is no longer a consideration, and I'm treading water watching it all get sucked into the tide.&nbsp; I really am upset, and I have t-minus&nbsp;24 hrs. and counting&nbsp;before Cochran's test.&nbsp; I'm venting, sorry.   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    More Croatian beach fun.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Rachel prior to being burned the color of a lobster.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    This is the "beach" we laid out on.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    More Adriatic pics from Croatia&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The beach 17/7/04 croatia&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The "wooden cottage" or "bungalow" in Croatia&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    C. demonstrating the lack of space in our "bungalow" really just a storage shed with a little paint in Pula, Croatia.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Croatia, Adriatic Sea, 16/7/04&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Venice 16/7/04&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Rachel in Venice&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Venice 15/7/04&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      More favorite stupid stuff: &nbsp;  urlLink http://www.jahozafat.com/MP3S/TV_Shows/South_Park/Episode_217_Gnomes/217_gnomesong.mp3  
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Warning, viewer discretion advised, that means you mom.   Fat-Kins Squirrel.    urlLink http://www.illwillpress.com/fatkins.html  &nbsp; beautiful. urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Darn I changed to pink, yes I like pink so I thought it appropriate.  Now I no longer have my fun color text...oh well.  So I got back from Croatia today, not a small feat.  By train it involves lugging junk to the train station in Innsbruck, hoping you make your train, and for the record, C. and I have at the most had 4 minutes to board on this trip.  Then getting into Verona, Italy changing trains at least once in Italy, getting to Venice, where we spent night 1, then getting up getting the train to Trieste, Italy, getting the next bus, which doubtless involves another wait, and we, being the special folk we are, got off in the wrong city in Croatia thinking we were in Pula, but actually we were in Rovinj. Bad.  Then we waited for the next bus and  got into Pula, and had to con a cabbie into taking us to our beachside getaway.   Okay so the train from Innsburck is about 5 hrs. plus wait time, then 3 more to Trieste and 3 more to Pula, unless you are stupid and get off early in Rovinj.  Today we took the Ferry back to Venice, which cut 6 plus hrs into 2.5, but actually into 3 thanks to the Venetian parade overtaking the waterways/streets.  I am so burned. I look like a lobster. What ever happened to my incredible tan I maintained through semester 2 of 1st yr, but lost in Europe?  Well it'll be back after this.  I am exhausted.  The "Wooden Cottage" or "Bungalow" on the beach was really a painted shed with no A/C and a shared community bathroom with the rest of the campsite.  Live and learn.  The beach itself was amazing and the campsite had its own restarants, and newsstands and a live band on Sat night.  Although the place itself, minus being as close to roughing it as I will hopefully come for awhile, was nice (a stretch of the word admittecly, but under the circumstances) the food was great and cheap and the water was gorgeous.  You know the crayola color cerulean, it used to be my fav when I was all of 7, well thats the exact color of the water.  The beach is rock, but not scary or uncomfortable, part of it is in big slabs where you can stretch your towel out on and set up shop.  C. and I did that all Sat.  Well, my body shows it, I am more of a purple red than a red red.  We didn't really sleep last night because we had to coordinate our ferries, and trains so we could get back. I went to sleep hearing the "band" at the campsite sing "When a Man Loves A Woman"  but obviously neither the male or female could really speak English, so most of the words were sort of fibbed.   i.e., When a man loves a woman, he'l giiiie er eryting e ccccn"  interesting yet very distracting when you are trying to sleep , but keep laughing over the made up words.  Anyway, I still need a shower, today was super hot.  Take care, glad to know my family has reappeared.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Oops, forgot this bad boy earlier, here's a group shot of TheLastIceCream...&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    What is Giev doing?  Oh, wait thats when we made all the guys wait while we went into the 18 millionth shoe store after the Corte Supremo de Espana.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Group Shot at Starbucks after Supreme Court&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Madrid Starbucks on Gran Via, yes we look goofy&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    After visit to the Supreme Court of Spain, on Gran Via, Madrid&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Before the ice cream incident, at our last family dinner at Restaurante Diann, tele kebab.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Laughing over Mickey Mouse Club song.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Don't Make fun of Mickey.  Yes, on the last night I ate a Mickey Mouse kiddie popsicle, so they all sang the Mickey Mouse Club Song to me, I think I am telling them to shut up here.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Jason on Gran Via in Madrid, eating his beloved Burger King.  Good, huh?&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Fun New Tools appeared on my create a post screen.&nbsp;  I just got an email linking me to some fun Spain pics I didn't have.&nbsp; Thanks Giev!&nbsp;  Oh and Croatia was fun.&nbsp; yeah more later.      &nbsp; 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Extreme close up!!!! Rachel in Innsbruck&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Justice Sandra Day O'Connor lecturing in Innsbruck, Austria 15 Jul 2004, view from my front row seat&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Getting tired.  Need sleep.  Maybe its the weather, maybe its the passing drama.  I feel a little down.  I'm okay but its one of those getting up in the morning and nothing you try on looks quite right.  It must be the Austrian weather induced sun deprivation, on top of SARS [bronchitis].  Or maybe its because I woke up entirely too late...7:12 and had to run through a shower, etc. and nearly fly downstairs to eat all of one little beany weeny sausage link and chug a miny glass of apple juice before running to the bus stop.  Did I mention I left my umbrella in my room again.  I walked outside looked at brother Todd and said, "Oh well, my hair's wet anyway."  Cochran's class was supposed to end early, but in typical Cochran style he said, "I'll give you back the couple minutes I owe you, by ending early."  No such luck, he carried us over and didn't even get around to handing out evaluations.  Got a cup of coffee afterward, i.e. espresso in a over-sized mug with lots of milk and sugar, two substances I wouldn't deign to taint my black coffee with in los estados unidos.  Well, maybe I will stay awake in class today.  She was reading basically yesterday, which apparently is hard to listen to even a Supreme Court justice do for an hour and 10 minutes.  I just hope she doesn't make eye contact again.  My face turns bright red, then pale white in all of 2 seconds, and I feel my eyes bulge in fear, probably like how a deer feels in its last seconds.  I am convinced I am sustaining heart damage from the skipping of beats that occurs during her eye contact, I also now have my reaction perfectly timed so when she looks at me, a quick smile comes across my face although I am really contemplating crawling under the desk and below people's feet to the end of the aisle and making a full sprint toward the door.  Okay, maybe I am being dramatic.  I think I just need some sun.  The dreariness and intensity of Sandy are a killer combo.  But then again she signed my classbook, pretty cool, huh?
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm going to Croatia tomorrow, by way of Venice.  C. and I are staying in a bungalow on the beach in Pula, Croatia for a whopping....17 euro per night, including breakfast.  Yeehaw.  heres the croatia site:  http://www.puntizela.hr    [sorry my link html stuff failed again.] pimpin aint easy
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Austrian beer is killer.  WAAAAY to strong.  Yes, so the party for Justice O'Connor last night was in typical St.MU fashion, i.e., no lack of booze.  I got my pic taken with her, although they made us do it in groups of 6-8 and everyone was vying for a place on her side.  I could care less where I was, I was still within a couple feet of Sandra, and plus I had red wine, so I was occupied.  Then a group from section B, none of whom I really knew invited us to go to Chilini's- aka the single "Mexican" food restaurant in Austria, rather pricey, which as a San Antonio native I found amusing.  So we ordered Margaritas, and I still didn't have an appetite thanks to my case of SARS (bronchitis really), so I had my frozen margarita and drank it fairly quickly.  So everyone was commenting on how strong the marg on the rocks was, so I ordered one....can you see where my night was heading?  Yes, so it was tequila, with a splash of sweet and sour for color.  I am still not sure how I drank it, maybe I had more wine at Sandy's party than I thought?!  I hate tequila, but anyway, then we decided lets go the the Hofgarten [keep in mind I had Cochran the next morning at 8am to discuss transnational litigation].  C. had never been, and I have an admitted weakness for it, and well I haven't gone out in Austria since week one, sooooo....famous last words.  Needless to say about 90% of the class during Sandra's lecture today was hurting.  Anyway my case of SARS [bronchitis] has resurfaced full force thanks to Rachel's stupidity in staying up all night long, in a little dress, stiletos, and this flimsy wrap.  It was downright cold last night with wind and rain.  Fun.  Anyway.  Sleep good.  By the way, if anyone knows my parents, why did everyone in my whole family, extended family included decide to go to New Mexico?  How long?  Why?  enigmatic.  
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just realized I am retarded and will never date again, let alone the craziness that happened tonight.  I walked into my room tonight and the guy who was flirting with me was standing in the center kissing another girl....in MY BEDROOM....we normally leave it open around this time so we can go to and from our respective rooms and hang out or watch CNN in the rooms where there are coveted tvs.  But no, this was messed up.  Then he acted like nothing was wrong, and I was like hello, go now, and apaprently he is the guy-who-has-never-been-rejected...there's first for everything, huh? No more dating -R-
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      April just emailed me, here's an excerpt...  Day 2: Can I tell you how much alcohol slows down the little hamster in my head, man, he gets slower and slower each time, and now I think hes figured out how to just sit by the wheel and spin it in his little hamster hand, so he doesn't have to get up and run...HUNGOVER...Ridiculous, I was all about some propel and Tylenol...[continues on about her craziness at the beach, concluding with]...So today we had the car ride from hell which you already know about and thats pretty much it, there was a whole bunch of stuff I wanted to tell you but I think the hamster ran away  Thanks April I needed a laugh
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My favorite quotes:  " If I fail out of law school... ...I'm gonna start my life over as a matador in Mexico ." -Thank you Taylor.  "I'm a law student [discussing grade policy]...I take a f#%&in' and keep on truckin'." -More words of wisdom from Taylor (go section A)  "Its like the Good News Bible (in re: my "Let's Go" Europe travel guide), but without the Bible part." -Claire  My Let's Go guide is now referred to as "good news" and Claire is "Good News Claire."
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Bratislava Castle burned 1811, bombed WWII, communist restoration&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Danube with Novy Most (communist built) bridge&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Baby wanted to play with the horse&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Playing chess on pedestrian walk in Old Bratislava&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    What is this sign for?&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Slovak National Theater circa 1886&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Bratislavan Philharmonic&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Rachel and Napoleon&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Polka and Napoleon-Bratislava&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Spray paint on a wall in Bratislava&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Hekyll and Jekyll's Polka DDOT Jammies in Bratislava day one&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    DDOT falling in pavement crack in Bratislava&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    oops, yes, the timer does work&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Bratislava day one- the homies&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Claire and Rach in Vienna&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Hekyll and Jekyll's Polka DDOT Jammies plus Gerardo&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Gerardo and DDOT in Vienna&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Hekyll and DDOT on dining car&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    DDOT laughing on dining car, we spent WAAAYYYY too much time on trains, very BORING, so we had to drink beer&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Hekyll and Jekyll on dining car en route to Vienna (night before Bratislava), no make-up so don't expect much...(nicknames: Hekyll  and Jekyll are the two crows from Dumbo that spun off into their own cartoon)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The UT buddies&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Polka Jekyll and DDOT at the Hofgarten&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Beer at Hofgarten&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Beer stickers from the Hofgarten&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    DDOT @ Hofgarten in Innsbruck week one&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    haha I know thats not what its supposed to mean, but "Gute Fahrt"....&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    DDOT and our UT buddy @ Hofgarten&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    After dinner at the Hofgarten, yes we like it there....&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    View from my window in Innsbruck, funny thing is the clouds cover the top of the mountains, yes those things keep going up&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    C. on left, followed by back of Cochran's head...we are checking out the peacocks at the opening party at Schloss Ambras, but haha look in the background at a snuggling couple, oops caught on film...&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ahhh a sigh of relief....with the occasional hacking cough thanks to bronchitis.  I actually (drumroll.....) skipped class this morning.  I decided I was dying and didn't want to speed up the process unnecessarily by trekking through Innsbruck to school.  Okay, Okay I don't really trek either, I more like stroll to the bus stop, wait and ride to school.  Beautiful.  Anyway, so in an effort to make up for my uncontrollable ranting yesterday, here are some pics, I'll start with good 'ol Innsbruck and then to Bratislava, the place I hope to one day own a summer home in...  And yes I am okay, I think, no, yes, I am okay!
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       WARNING:  FURY ABOUNDS.   ALL PARENTS, ADULTS, GRANDMOTHERS, AND GENERALLY SENSITIVE PEOPLE SHOULD TURN BACK NOW.  CEASE AND DESIST.  RACHEL IS PISSED OFF.   This is the only song going through my head now, I lovingly refer to is as the "Fuck you song."   Thank you Eamon for making a song angry enough to relate to.   See, I don't know why I liked you so much I gave you all of my trust I told you I loved you Now thats all down the drain You put me through pain  I wanna let you know (how) I feel..  Fuck what I said it don't mean shit now Fuck the presents might as well throw 'em out Fuck all those kisses they didn't mean jack Fuck you, you ho I don't want you back  You thought you could keep this shit from me You burnt bitch I heard the stories..    I broke up with A .,  hmmm...I wonder if he'll check his email first or this blog....if this is A.- read YOUR EMAIL.   Bratislava was cool, but an incident almost, damned near demolished my weekend.  On top of that, I have a raging case of Bronchitis and had to ride on the damned train for 7 hrs.  More on Bratislava shall come later.  For now, I need to lick some wounds and recover what shamble of pride I might find in the dark hidden recesses of myself.  A fucking waste, thats all my now ex-relationship was.  A waste of my time, and an apparent benefit to him, he had a puppet's emotions to manipulate.  No more.  My reasoning:   I am finished with his willful misrepresentations and outright flagrant lies, which he had deviously masked from me.  I know A.  You weren't "asleep" when you stood me up that first time, you were with her.  You were also with her, or at least trying to be with her outside the second time.  You didn't "forget" or "forget the time".  fuck that.  I can't believe that in an effort to dispel quarrels I actually said "I'm sorry" or "I'm sorry, too."  WHY.  WHAT THE FUCK DID I HAVE TO BE SORRY ABOUT EXCEPT I WAS A CUCKOLD TO A WANDERING EYE, AND I TURNED MY BACK.  I could also be called pitifully permissive and easily deceived. YES I AM SORRY THIS TOOK SO DAMNED LONG TO END.  IT SHOULD HAVE BEEN THE FIRST TIME YOUR SORRY ASS MADE ME WAIT ALL FUCKING NIGHT LONG, ALL DRESSED UP ON MY DAMNED COUCH.  I was actually worried, is he in an accident, is he alright.....YEAH YOU WERE FUCKING ALRIGHT, YOU WERE WITH ______.(name omitted to protect the innocent.)      I bought your pussy explanations, and even though instinctively something said, NO!!!, I acquiesced.  I said I was sorry too, for getting mad at you, no, no no no, Thats mistake number one= being mad was the correct state of mind, saying "I'm" sorry, was ass-backwards.  There is also the issue of two morally based topics thats were discussed between myself and ______(she whose name shall not be dragged into this shit).  1.  The non-disclosure of topic "a" to me, his girlfriend, but he rattled that shit off to _______, and is something that damned sure should have been brought up.  lets move on to topic "b"  this is great, I thought I was having the most appropriate relationship ever at 23, you know the old saying, "don't do something you wouldn't do in front of your mother."  well.....that would have applicability here.  But, no, there seem to be differences between the manner of relationships in his harem.   Three things, that one should not overlook.  I went to the vatican to get a rosary blessed for him.  Well I guess he'll need it.  Three big things, two so big they are not posted explicitly on here, for fear an unprepared person might read this.  BURN BRIDGE BURN.   
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For your knowledge I have entered the modern internet world and have enabled comments, just look at the bottom of postings, but as always if you prefer, you are still welcome to email me privately.  Lets talk about things I hate, fun subject, eh?  Yes, so birds, I hate birds.  If it were up to me I would take out every last one of their incessantly chirping lives and send them to a place where forgiveness is historically more prevalent and free-flowing than from myself.  Austria in my officially unofficial opinion is overwrought, if I had an A.K. I would really be doing them quite a large favor.  In fact if the rest of the world suddenly went into bird-extinction, Austria could compensate.  Okay, so I would not really go Rambo on the birdies, but Yes I am thinking about it.  Have you ever noticed that birds only chirp, or squawk (depending on your personal outlook towards birds), during times when you are trying to read Bankruptcy (and are thus readily distractable) or when you would really like a bit of sleep.  Plus they are like WWII bombers, you can never really feel safe unless you are inside.    Okay I'm playing with my dad's camera now...picture time
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I feel ADD I don't think I can take much more bankruptcy reading, after the last class, now this....ugh, Maybe I will procrastinate...yeah...looks like its I'm-gonna-be-a-tourist-time!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Last Night in London...Rachel, Monsignor Anderson, and Tim in Odeon theater on Leicester Square just before the start of Harry Potter III movie.  The theater seated 1,000 on both levels.  WOW.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The Sutton Hoo Ship Burial Treasure&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Costumes used in film, TROY, on display in British Museum&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Close-up of King and Queen of Lewis Chessmen&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Thank you Rowdy, wish you were here, I need someone to tell me to shut up and quit bitching sometimes.  Yeah, you are right, I'll be fine, but most  importantly I'll be so drugged up I won't care. haha.  Thats a joke, sort of, not really.         On to the point of this entry.  Rachel likes to take cheap shots at people sometimes, most recently being the-ex-from-feb, but I must say he can still be my friend, he is not worthless or a pig, I just like to call people names sometimes, okay, alot of the time, okay anytime they piss me off.  Yeah so he was kind of a punk, but probably didn't deserve being drawn and quartered, then burned at the stake by me.  Actually he has been a prominent member of the group that has checked on me and asked if I was okay.  He brought me a compensatory dmgs pizza today.         Okay now that I have partially retracted earlier statements, I thought I would let ya'll know that I'll be staying at the regent park hotel at the Munich airport tomorrow, as its a good 20 km outside the city and my plane leaves before the sun is even awake.  When did it get to be after 6 pm?  Back to my book, C. got me onto Marian Keyes.  
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Will somebody please tell me why the gods are shitting on me?  Okay so if last Sunday weren't the worst day of my life, it seems this Sunday shall follow in suit or take the lead.  My flight leaves out of Munich and into (drumroll) HEATHROW, one of the Al-Qaeda (however you spell it) targets.  Beautiful.  You see, last time Heathrow was under such an alert they shut down the flights to the states, and drumroll my flight from HEATHROW has a layover in CHICAGO, why may you ask is Chicago bad, besides helluva outta the way, because CHICAGO is another target.  This is great and I thought I had suffered heart damage having to maintain eye contact while smiling with Justice O'Connor.  All I gotta say is I hope the massive amount of self-drugging I am about to do on Sunday, doesn't kick in until I am actually on the plane.   Am I some mean bitch with bad karma or did I just draw the short stick this week?   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Okay me and all my friends are stupid, I mean s-t-o-o-p-i-d.  I really think law students by nature find ways to distract themselves the most during times where they need to study.  For example, when I am in the US I grocery shop waaaaay too much during finals or deadlines or other fun times.  Here the laundry room is suddenly overwrought with people using machines to wash a pair of socks.  Last night however was the worst, one of my friends got bad news about her friend having a heart attack, everyone was still engaged in heart to hearts with me and all I wanted was some red wine.  I was just following orders?!  The professors keep telling me to goof off and take it easy so....it all started by me just doing what they said.  Then we were watching CNN and all arguing about Darfor, however you spell it, and whose fault it was, blah blah blah and suddenly the new bottle of wine was finished.  Anyway, these things can unwittingly escalate from where you meant to have a glass and after hours of sitting on the penthouse hallway's floor with an ever changing group realize that its nice you were sitting just outside your room, you are not in any condition to walk.    So instead of walk I decided to IM half the world and probably sound really stupid and tell people about my blog address when that was the last thing I should have told esp 1 of them.  Genius.  Genius. Genius.  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Lady Justice on the Powder Tower in Prague&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Some random dude from the UK wouldn't leave us girls alone, so here's the pic he took courtesy of my camera&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    We liked the poster on the wall at the Mexican American food restaurant in Prague&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Prague by night day 1&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Prague&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Rachel and Co. at Club Lavka day 1 in Prague&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Rachel in Prague, Friday day 1, from Club Lavka&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Rachel and C. in Prague, Friday, day 1, no I hadn't slept&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    There's our room in the "hostel", notice the floors have holes and Louis made the trip to our veritable dungeon&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Hallway of our "hostel" in Prague, this would be below ground level on "cell block 4", haha&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Rachel about to pass out, waiting in Nurnberg train station around 2 am waiting on next train to get to Prague, yes I look homeless&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Haha it says "Trink" coca cola instead of Drink- Munich train station&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    C. and Rachel at the St. Augustiner in Munich&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    C. and Polka at the Hofbrau Haus in Munich&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Rachel and brother DDOT at the Hofbrau Haus in Munich&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    haha it says Lederhosen- in Munich&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Rachel very bad pic, but humorous, I'm blowing away haha&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      javascript:rs("videoWin"," urlLink http://news.yahoo.com/p/v?u=/ap_av/20040801/av_ap_wl/09a43ceb49bedab9b949eeda0382fc2a&cid=452&amp;f=53746348",650,450 );  Okay so thats the video, here's a news link:   urlLink http://www.guardian.co.uk/worldlatest/story/0,1280,-4374976,00.html   Okay, so this is not funny, but some of you need to know what happened.  First of all, we are all okay.  Kris, I'm sure Todd has already emailed you, and/or called, but he is fine, he was in the back of the casino killing time with M. while C. and I were in the bldg on the left.       Nobody freak out.  Okay so theres a bldg the left, and these are all attached, they sort of grow out of each other, the bldg on the left housed a clothing store on the bottom.  In the videos and pictures its the glass you can see in the background kinda between the tables and the umbrellas.  The bldg on the right is called casino royal, in the middle is a cafe with nice looking umbrellas and rattan chairs wrapped around metal frames.  Also the street this is all sitting on is a pedestrian only thoroughfare, the place where the car was, was to the right of casino royal there was a small sort of service access street, I think it must be used for food and drink delivery and have a worker's entrance there.     We had dragged the guys around all day long, we were all tired anyway, but C. needed to shop for a couple things before we left that day, so we decided divide and conquer the guys to the casino, the girls to the store, meet in the middle outside.  We never got to that point, we thought initially it was a massive gun that had gone off and only sounded so loud because of the nature of the walled in with bldgs street and cobble foot way in the center, we thought this had made it amplified.  C. did think it was a bomb.  I yelled at her to get down behind the counter and tried to get the women standing at the door to lock it but they only locked the right door, so that really defeated the purpose. When we saw they weren't locking both doors, I turned and yelled at C. to get to the back and hide, I didn't know what what happening all I thought was that someone would come in and shoot the place up. We waited until it was quiet, but this stupid woman goes outside to get pictures, such a sensationalist, she got pictures of the guy with the head wound.  I wanted to punch her.   We walked outside to go into the casino, by way of walking next to the cafe, a scene I just cannot explain but would like to forget.  We got inside a couple of the people who had been at the cafe, sitting outside were inside the entry way, I recognized the little girl who looked like curly sue she had been outside standing next to the table alone screaming while people ran around the man who had been at her table.  Anyway so we walk up the stairs but in the heat and after seeing the effect of the explosion on people and the blood I started to faint and had to grab the handrail.  We got to the top and couldn't find the guys so I finally started crying, uncontrollably, and the woman at the bar gave us water.  We sat down, but in a moment of clarity we realized this was not a safe place to have a glass of water in, no matter how sick we felt, so we walked downstairs, I was still in hysterics and walk to the door in time to see the guy who was really hurt being lifted onto a stretcher, we stopped in place and hugged each other and covered our eyes until it was over then walked cautiously outside and saw the guys.  They had been in the back, whereas we were at the window and downstairs when it happened, so the guys never really saw or knew what was going on and M. couldn't seem to understand why we were hysterical and shaking, he even said we didn't have to go, but both C. and I said yes we did.  I couldn't eat more than rice cakes after that and I didn't sleep last night.  But none of us were hurt, thank God. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>