<Blog>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    sure ... he may look cute ... reveal the brat within!  Posted by  urlLink Hello  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    aaarrrggghhh!!!!!!!!!!  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    I just thought my first post on my new blog should be one of my favorite pictures. so here you go.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    someday, that'll be ME  Posted by  urlLink Hello  
     

    
</post>


<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      listening to:  urlLink jet : are you gonna be my girl reading:  urlLink the catcher in the rye ,  urlLink catch 22  hey so for now i've finally sorted out the mess i had w/ my template.  it's nothing fancy, but i'm still teaching myself this stuff!  hopefully soon i'll get some time to make it really my own.    i haven't heard from one of my friends, liz, who i met @ camp last summer.  i'm getting kinda worried.  i sent her a x-mas card and a letter since then but she hasn't written.  i hope nothing's wrong.  school was pretty normal 2day.  nothing out of the ordinary, but i really can't wait to get my own wheels.  the bus sucks.    i probably won't post till sometime next week, if anyone out there is actually reading this...pretty unlikely.  anyway, 2morrow night i've got church and a friend's b-day party, which should be fun.  no school friday, thank god.  i seriously need a break.  i'm leaving for my gma's fri, then to my sis's mass for joining the church, then back 2 my gma's for easter dinner and the like.  i can't wait, haven't seen my little cousin leonard 4ever!  check this out, it is really hilarious.  urlLink    no more deep thoughts.......later
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      okay, so i've got a blog....  i guess i'll tell you somethings about myself. name:jade age: 15 fav food: mac & cheese fav band:  urlLink jet  shows i watch:  urlLink one tree hill ,  urlLink angel ,  urlLink charmed , friends hobbies: photography, hanging w/ friends, digital graphics, net surfing,  urlLink SIMS!!! ;-)  astrology:  urlLink libra  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      nothin much happening here.  This is my last day of school this week cause I'm going to a Taekwondo Tournament tomorrow.  I'm not competing, cause I can't, but I'm going to take pics and vid.  I have to take my uniform, but I don't think it'll be very easy to take pics in it (a little bulky) so I hope I don't hafta wear it all day.  Our school Prom's this weekend on Sat.  Some of my friends are going, you should see them.  Freshmeat going to prom!  Yaaaay! [insert sarcasm here]  Whatever, I guess it's their deal.  I got a letter from L yesterday, so I'm not worried about her any more.   Okay, I deserve a vent.  Since I'm gonna be gone tomorrow, I'm missing my science test.  So my teacher's all like, (yesterday) "you HAVE to make it up thursday" so I crammed pretty much all last night.  ugggh.  To make it worse, I get there before school like he said, and he's like "well, I'm changing the test so you can't take it now cause it's not done. (this is at like, 7:30) you can take it 7th period during your class." so I'm thinking, okay, guess I can do that.  I get there 7th and he's like, "well, you have to take it monday. It's not done".  So, after making me crash-study, he's not ready.  [screams in frustration]  He totally lost all the respect I had for him at that moment.  (which was almost none anyway cause he acts like this all the time)  If he's gonna tell me I hafta take it and I study harder than I ever have for his test, he should have been ready. [end of vent]  Oooooohhhhhhh!!!!!!!! Psycho obsession time!!!  (To be warned, I am now going to talk about Tuesday's   One Tree Hill urlLink   So if you haven't seen it, I recommend for you to stop reading now.... ......can't say I didn't warn you.  Oh my gosh!!!! I CANNOT BELIEVE BROOK IS PREGNANT.  I personally think that it's not Lucas's kid, I think it's that guy's in the bar, but, you never know.  And Keith proposed!! Yay! I don't think she'll say yes though.  I don't know why, just an instinct.  Oh, and the whole thing w/ Jake and Nikki was kinda harsh.  I know she walked out on him and Jenny, but, ouch.  I can see where he's coming from though.  On a final note, I don't care how much you think you love your bf, you DO NOT let him make you think you need a tattoo.  Directly or indirectly.  I definetly can't wait till next week.  talk back later.....;-)
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wow...so many things have happened lately that I feel sorta overwhelmed...I'll try to make some sense...  Thursday- d's b-day party was fun...church ran longer than expected, so I was later than I thought I would be, but still not as late as k and h.  we watched, since she loves disney, the little mermaid, and then daddy day care since that was one of her presents.  Played some pool, ate some cake, got no sleep, the usual.  Friday- got home from d's party, took a shower, ate lunch (mac&cheese!), packed.  We left for my g-ma's house around 3:30...hey it occured to me I need to fix the time zones on this- anyway...got there around 5:30, fish for dinner...(ugh) Stayed up till about 11.  Sat- went shopping @ Target w/ my aunt, g-ma, and little cousin L.  I got this awesome new swimsuit, green w/ green and tan stripes and this fake buckle thing.  I got some flip flops too.  I am now officially broke.  In debt actually- 5 bucks to my mom and something else...  We had subcity for lunch, went back to the house and did some homework.  Sat night my mom and dad and I went out to eat w/ my sis and her fiance, and then to church.  It was awesome, I was so proud I thought i might cry.  We didn't get back to my g-ma's till midnight.    Sun- Easter dinner w/ the family, went home.  Stayed up and did more homework.   Mon- school.  Especially bad cause of how tired I was.  Plus I've now got allergies or something so I feel like crap.  Lotsa homework last night as well.  Today- Now I can get to the juicy stuff.  j/k.  School was boring, as usual.  I had a clarinet lesson after school but it was pretty short so that was ok.  Came home and did homework. Talked on msn for awhile, studied for my history test which is 2morrow.  Then L called me and told me some especially disturbing news.  One of my friends has this pretty steady bf.  She had gone farther with him than I thought she should have already, but L told me that she had showered w/ the guy and he had fingered her a couple of times.  This disturbs me to no end.  She said K said she wouldn't be as close w/ him as she is now w/o doing it, which I think is friggin stupid.  I'm scared she might go all the way w/ him.  She's only known him for 6 months, and she always struck me as one of those people who would never lose it until marriage.  I don't know what to think.  I should go do homework, but I feel a little better now that I've got it kinda out of my system.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Talk about the crappiest day ever.  Yesterday I had to go to the doc since I've been so congested, and she made me come get an appt. to get a CAT scan this morning. Quick, painless, uninteresting.  Anyway, I get home, and on the answering machine there was a message that I need to come in ASAP to get more scans done.  So my mom came home and took me, turns out they needed a test with an IV in! (FYI, totally hate needles) The scan took forever, the lady annoyed me, and the stuff in the IV made me feel sick.  Now my arm kills, and I've got a band concert tonight. Fabulous.  Angel last night was pretty good for this season.  Bringing Conner back was hilarious, and I was hoping he'd keep his old memories once he killed that dude.  But I think he didn't.  Unless he did and is faking it.  This shall be interesting.  Although I'm slightly confused on what happened to Gunn, since I missed last week. ??  Okay, I suppose I should probably go and do homework...
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey...had a pretty bad couple of days. one of my friends totaled her car a couple of days ago, she's a lot better than she could have been.  just stiches, she didn't break anything.  she was really scared about it yesterday, she's doing better now. i worked a babysitting gig last night pretty much all night, so i missed one tree hill...wahhhh...i get to see angel tonight though, i can't wait since conner's coming back.  i'm watching that 70s show right now, and seth green's guest starring.  it's hilarious. i have nothing better to say. bye...
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      okay, so I've been thinking.  Screw the whole fake name thing. I highly doubt anyone's reading this anyway...so yeah, my name's alex.    The tournament was pretty fun. I took about 5 rolls of film.  I can't wait to get them developed, they're gonna be awesome.  The funniest part about the whole weekend has gotta be when the guy I was riding with ran out of gas on the interstate.  We were like 3 frickin miles from a gas station.  So we just sat there hoping the super troopers wouldn't drive by while we waited for the other car to get a tank of gas.   well, I've got a crapload of homework that I need to do....so....bye
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i realized just tonight that the deadline for using free songs from itunes was tomorrow, so i am crazy downloading....i'm gonna end up crashin my system, downloading, talkin on msn, surfin....it's crazy. plus my hand hurts like crap cause i got kicked in the wrist during karate 2nite. band's gonna be hell tomorrow.  oooo, anybody seen those previews for helter skelter? looks sooooo good. (cbs movie, i know, but still) I totally realllllly wanna see Van Helsing, but of course, being where i am, that's not gonna happen. we never get any good movies. even if we get it next week, doesn't matter cause it's tulip time and you never go to movies during tulip time. o well.  i am soooo psyched. we're gonna get a new music store in town, opening sat., that sells vinyl. i have been dying to expand my collection and maybe get a record player, but i've never had the oppurtunity. now i do. yay!!!  i really need to clean my room. well then, moving on...  angel was pretty good last night. it almost killed me when i thought everybody was dead. i knew they couldn't do that at this point in the season, but still. scared the crap outta me. next week looks really good though. i know buffy isn't gonna be on, but a buncha others will.  you know what really irritates me? when people, who have NO idea what they're talking about talk trash. like, being the loser w/o a liscence i am, i'm riding the bus home today, and some middle schooler asks what a hacker is. so another one of them's like, oh, they're a loser who gets into people stuff and wrecks it. i'm sitting back there thinking, what a buch of ignorant people. not everyone w/ the ability to hack does that. it's like this one time. there were only a couple of people in the classroom (i don't remember why) and my teacher said something about not being able to eat. a kid asked why, and she said it was because she was getting blood taken. then the kid's like, 'oh, i thought you were one of those crazy catholics'. and i, being catholic, was 'like, yeah, us crazy catholics' he kinda shut up then. his look of embarassment was enough for me.  i'm totally wiped. shower time.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This week's going by really fast.  Monday school was boring, just your average. I felt like crap all day, but I didn't wanna miss any more classes risk being even more behind. I went home and took Motrin, which helped. I had taekwondo monday night, and i ripped some of my nail off. Bloody mess. Literally. Hurt like hell, I might add.  Tuesday, school. We had these army guys come and teach us 'self defense'. It was a joke. Like, we did everything once, not like I need much more self-defense training, but nobody w/o training is gonna remember. I blew off my clarinet lesson, which backfired, as my mom and my teacher found out. My mom gave me this big lecture on responsibility. Screw responsibility. One Tree Hill was pretty good. I don't really feel like talking about it though.  Oh, and, screw the government. They suck. Get us into wars, kill people with the death penalty, abortion. Keep secrets, and kill more people to keep those secrets. What brings this on, you ask? Well, I already thought they always talked BS, but after watching some movies in history about the death of JFK, they officially suck. Royally. Anyway, I firmly believe we need Bush outta office. Not that I like Edwards or Kerry.   ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- My ideal candidate:  -agianst death penalty  -pro-life  -get us outta iraq  -get us in no more wars  -agianst gay marraige (nothing personal, just don't think ya'll should be married. i'm good w/ civil unions) -----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------  Crap. Just found out I've got surgery on the 12th of May. If it interferes w/ the ONLY history trip this yr. (which will be a blast btw) I am going to be royally pissed off. Plus I've got 2 doctors appts next friday for pre-surgery. waaaahhhhh!!!  School was crap today. Luckily I've got Angel tonight to help me throught the next hour of studying.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow. I am really tired. But I'll blog quick.  Friday I had my follow-up appt. for my CAT scans. Crappy news. I have this thing called an antrochoanal polyp in my sinuses, and I have to get it removed. Thank the Lord I won't be awake during it, but it is going to hurt a crapload afterward. Only nice thing about that is I get to miss P.E., which is a waste of my time, so that makes me happy.  I worked at Work of Our Hands yesterday. It was really nuts cause of Tulip Time coming up and all. At least I finally learned to use credit cards there. Oh, tourists. Driving around at 5 miles an hour. Don't ya love 'em! Still, I can't wait till Tulip Time, even though I've gotta march, which will, as always, suck.  I cleaned today and did some homework. Hehe. Now I'll have money. Plus I cleaned out a buncha crap from my room to get rid of for the church garage sale next week. Boy, I've got a lotta crap.  btw, if you haven't see  The League of Extraordinary Gentleman , the title will make no sense. Although it's quite possible it still may not even if you've seen it....
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey y'all.  before i forget, just wanted to say if anybody ever wants to give me an earful, you can catch me at a.jae77@gmail.com. my msn profile is  urlLink here  check out my launch radio  urlLink here   i just got a call on my cell. i am not a big phone person, yet i still do have a phone. strange. anyway, i didn't answer it because it was an unavailable number. they left a message, and to be quite honest, i haven't the slightest idea who it was. very likely a wrong number since they said they hoped i had a good day @ work. and i was @ school. strange...  i just heard the news about Nicholas Brendon. he's really brave for checking himself in. my prayers are with him.  my band lesson went unusually well today, which was nice. he didn't think i did too bad. yay!  i have just discovered your new favorite cd. i know this because it's mine. check it out  urlLink here  It's Modest Mouse. ya gotta get it. thanx to kayla w/ hooking me up w/ that one.  that's all today.  btw, does anyone know what kind of car peyton on one tree hill has? 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey. so I know I havent't posted in awhile. and, no, it's not because of my surgery, which didn't even end up happening after I went to the doctor and she said we could postpone or maybe even cancel it. yay! anyway, I haven't posted in awhile because every time I get on to post, I got sidetracked into messing with my template. which, since I am slowly teaching myself to code, is a longer process for little results. hopefully this summer I'll have more time to work on this.  you know, nelly furtado is not a bad singer. I used to listen to her, but then her songs started to annoy me (too many poppy happy ballads). I just saw here on t.v. though, and her knew stuff isn't bad. may have to check her out.  I am so incredibly sore. I lifted quite a bit in p.e. yesterday, and then we did a lot of stretching drills in taekwondo last night. I can live with that though. the only thing that annoyed me last night was the fact I couldn't get my jump ax break. I went through perfectly last class! arghh. but we may have some new recruits. these juniors that go to my school. one of them is waaay hot. wonder if they'll join.  tgif. exept the fact I have to play at the graduation tonight (way too hot to play!) the weekend is great. I can't believe that this was my last friday as a freshman. it's crazy, the year just flew by.   I may also be starting a just photo blog. I'll keep ya posted.   later.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      forgot to say....BOO YA BABY! I GOT A CAR!
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      you know, it annoys the hell out of me when people assume things. for example, I was just eating dinner with the parental units, and my dad decided to share this e-mail(which by the way, was very annoying) during which he talked about how kids listen to hard rock and then kill themselves. oh, come on! just as many people kill themselves while listening to mozart, I'm sure. it's just people pay more attention to 'those punk/rock kids. they're trouble'. arghhh. then, he started talking about the number of kids who cheat on tests. now wait a minute. first of all, how many of those were proven. at our school, even if a student gets accused because a teacher 'thinks' that they're cheating, then they get a zero. even people who don't cheat! how is that fair?  weekend up at gma's was okay. the grad party yesterday pretty much sucked since I didn't know anybody. a whole lot of babcocks. I felt pretty akward. but today I got to go to hot topic and convince my dad to buy me some dickies since I'm now broke from paying for a $50 camera bag yesterday. worth it, but expensive.  I have a huge paper due in history tomorrow looming over my head. hope I get done with that soon. I've still got other homework to do.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this week is going by impossibly slow.  I never realized how slow that the days would go without school. I've had driver's ed starting on tuesday. really boring. one hour lecture and one hour movies, plus driving every other day. I drove today to harvey, and I am sooo happy I didn't screw up terribly. I went a little too far to the side of the road once, but other than that, it's all good.  I got my grades today in the mail. I pulled off all a's and a-'s for everything except science, which I got a B+. I am so relieved since I worked my but off on these tests. I also made honor roll w/ a 3.816 gpa. I still can't believe freshman year is over.  planning a bridal shower is nuts. first of all I really don't even like bridal showers. I get bored since I'm really not interested in what is talked about or what games are played. and know I've gotta plan one! good thing I love my sister so much.  I found an article ripped out of the classifieds in our kitchen. it's for a job offer in ames at cy-ride for my dad.  I wouldn't think much of it except for the fact that since he's worked at cy-ride before, and cause of that I would say he's got a pretty good shot at getting the job. and if he does I know we'll move. my mom is miserable with her job all the time, and my parents love ames. don't get me wrong, I do too, but I really don't know if I wanna move. It's such a change. I'll have to keep thinking about it...
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      man, I never realized it before, but ellen degeneres is an amazing woman. she has overcomed so much- coming out with a t.v. show, major attacks by the media. it's amazing. she never fails to make me laugh, which is an amazing gift. she makes so many people so happy every time they see her. she can turn so many situations into jokes. I don't know where she comes up with half of it, but it is just amazing. check out the link to find out more about her.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      man...why do I do this to myself. I get bored, make chocolate chip cookies, and then eat so much I feel sick. oh man..  anyway. this war in iraq is making me sick. I keep hearing about all these people who are killed over there, soldiers, civilians. I think it's just so stupid. I wish I could do something about it by voting, but there's just that minor inconvience that I'm only 15. 3 years to go.  well, I'm halfway done with driver's ed, thank god. I am way sick of getting up early for class. but at least it's not all summer.  my bridal shower for my sis went okay. everyone said it was great. I didn't think it was, but then again I'm really not into that type of party. I just would rather get some pizza and have my friends over. this type of party is just little tea sandwhiches, lemonade. ugh. but I love my sis.  to do: >buy ninja turtle pillowcases >learn sims object building >work in darkroom >work w/ savings >clean out car
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just finished watching peter pan. (the new one).  I was about ready to cry through half of it.  I would love to have someone take me away, away from school, stress, everything, and just stay a kid (well, teen anyway) forever.  there are so many major decisions I have to make. what college? what major? where do I get the money?  I just don't want to make them. is that so wrong?  I just want to fly away. away to a place where these decisions don't have to be made, and I can just relax and party all the time. I know what you're thinking, but I know I'm not alone in thinking this.  but I can't. not ever
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      you know when you get on the net to look at something and then you get distracted by flashy headlines and completely forget what in the world you wanted to look at in the first place? I really hate that.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got one of those e-mails today that's supposed to tell you about yourself. since I have nothing else to really write about, I thought I'd write about this.   OCTOBER:   Loves to chat.  Loves those who loves them.  Loves to takes things at the center. Inner and physical beauty.  Lies but doesn't pretend.   Gets angry often.   Treats friends importantly.   Always making friends.  Easily hurt but recovers easily.  Daydreamer.   Opinionated.   Does not care of what others think.  Emotional.  Decisive.  Strong clairvoyance.  Loves to travel, the arts and literature.  Touchy and easily jealous.  Concerned.  Loves outdoors. Just and fair.  Spendthrift.  Easily influenced. Easily loses confidence. Loves children.  the bold is what I think I am. you can't always tell about yourself though.  and another e-mail I seem to constantly get. you know, feel it out about yourself. so I'm gonna do it here. 1. Starting Time: 10:28 2. Name: alex 3. Friends: you know who you are 4. Sexiest Friend: ld...lol  5. Most out going Friend: hmm...kayla...danielle...  6. Smartest Friend: I dunno 7. Dumbest Friend: let's just say...everyone every once in awhile 8. Most Boring Person: nobody  10. Who Do You Get Advice From: who ever happens to be there at the time 11. Height: 5'3" about 12. Date of birth: 10-16-88  13. Eye Color: blue/gray  14. Shoe Size: 8.5 15. Shoe Brand: vans 16. Do You Crack Any Body Parts: fingers, toes, back 17. Pets: dog...Rowdy 18. Siblings: 1 bro...michael, 1 sis...jenny 19. What is your point of view on LIFE: illegitimus non carborundum...don't let the bastards grind you down 20. Boy Friend/Girl Friend: not lately 21. Crush: pretty much any british guy 22. Favorite Teacher: mr. emmert  23. Killed Someone: no 24. Laughed So Hard You Peed Your Pants: don't remember..don't think so 25. Ran Into A Glass Door: nope 26. Went Into homestarrunner.com? never heard of it 27. Hobbies/Interest: photography, taekwondo, hanging w/ friends, listening to music  28. Gotten Hit By A Car: nope  29. Ran Into A Parked Car: no    ****Girls Fill Out About Guys****  30. Boxers or Briefs: boxers  31. Tall or Short: doesn't really matter, although nobody way tall or way short 32. Six-pack or Muscular Arms: doesn't matter 33. Body or Personality: personality  34. Ear Pierced or not: i'll go either way....prolly w/  35. Sporty or Outdoorsy: neither 36. Good Guy or Bad Guy: bad guy...but good enough to bring home to parents 37. Hat or No Hat: doesn't matter  38.Long hair or short: either    ****Guys fill Out About Girls****  39. G string or Regular:  40.Tall or Short:  41. Long Hair or Short:  42. Dark or Light Eyes:  43. Light / Dark Hair:  44. Ears Pierced or Not:  45. Curly or Straight Hair:  46. Good Girl / Bad Girl:  47. Hair down or up:  48. Sporty or Classy:  49. Chicken or Not Afraid:    ****Which One Is Better****    50. Coke or Pepsi: pepsi  51. KFC or McDonald: neither 52. Cats or Dogs: dogs 53. Coffee or Tea: coffee  54. Sour or Sweet: sweet  55. Vanilla or Chocolate: chocolate  56. Cake or Cookies: frosting  57. Day or Night: night  58. Lights on or off: off  59. Summer or Winter: summer   ***Favorites**   60. Food: black olives, tomatoe and cheese sandwhiches, TACO PIZZA  61. Animal: tigers  62. Holiday: halloween...yummy candy! 63. Radio Station: Lazer 103.3 64. Place: in the city...under the ocvers 65. Do You Believe In God: yeah of course  66. What Do You Want To Be When You Grow Up: digital graphics person...photographer...journalist...web designer...haven't quite narrowed it down yet 67. Define True Love: someone you can feel totally comfortable with 68. Hugs or Kisses?: depends on who's giving 69. Favorite Day Of The Week: saturday  70. Who Was The Last Person You Received Mail From: something that wasn't a forward...ld 71. Bedtime: depends on when I wanna get up...but usually as late as possibly 72. Time Finished: 10:46 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so, I finished driver's ed today. I got a b+ in-class and a b- in-driving which came to a b overall. my dad said that's good because that means insurance will be lower. I'm just happy I didn't get a must drive. then I drove 3 hours today on the interstate in and out of rush hour on our way here (kearney).  so today I found out for sure my dad downloaded the application for the job in ames. what if he gets it? what if we move to ames?   ahhhhh!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      woooooohooooooooo!!! I am finally done with driver's ed. well, not officially, since I have to go tomorrow and get my completion certificate. but I took my final test today and passed! even though I'm not sure if I have a must drive to get my permit, I don't think I did. yay!!!! although this also brings to light the fact that june is over. went sooo fast. I'm gonna be back in school before I know it! yuck. oh well.  I am soooo sick of hearing and seeing all this weight and dieting crap. all you see anymore is sticks on tv followed by dieting ads. it's all over. and then you hear about mary-kate olsen being anorexic. it's so depressing everyone thinks you have to be super-skinny. *screams in frustration*  I leave for vacation tomorrow. I'm not sure how accesible net lines will be, so I'll just have to wait and see. my major goal for this vacation is taking pictures. I always take pictures, I know, but I never take pics of stuff we do. I always take pics of, you know, artsy stuff.   I am so dreading packing. I am HORRIBLE at it. seriously. it's gonna take forever. bye then.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        summer is sooo boring. I have no job, no liscence, and ld is out of town. arghhhh. &nbsp; the only thing that really occupies my time is jen's upcoming wedding. I still have to write a toast, which I have to idea how to do. that should turn out interesting. me &amp; mom are going up to jen's this weekend for fittings for my dress. I don't really want to have to stand for half an hour to get people poking around the dress, but I will get to see my neices, and I haven't seen them for awhile, so that should be fun. on sunday I'm leaving for C.I.A. (Catholics in Action). I'll be doing some service projects with another town since we couldn't get anybody from here to go. I'll get back on tuesday night. &nbsp; I really should practice my clarinet...I haven't played it since school got out, and blair will be on my back once school starts, probably to audition for all-state. damn, I need to get some dress clothes for audition rounds. I totally forgot. maybe we'll go shopping tomorrow.  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so we had a great workout at taekwondo last night. really intense, which is what I want, but man, this morning.....pain. I'm defintely feeling it.  c.i.a. was awesome. I was nervous about not knowing anybody, but it was all good, everyone was really nice.&nbsp; we did a lot of work, but it was fun. although I am&nbsp;sooo sick of weeding though. I did that a lot.&nbsp;&nbsp;monday night we went to a park/pool for&nbsp;dinner.&nbsp; we had a water&nbsp;fight (partially my fault). good times.  the dress fittings were crazy. mine fit, although it was too long. (not surprising). melissa's didn't fit at all, but that's prolly cause her measurements were wrong. isabelle and rayanne's dresses were size&nbsp;fours since they couldn't get threes, so there's needed a lot of work. anyway, they had to&nbsp;order a bunch of extra&nbsp;material to fix her dress because they didn't before. crazy.   I guess not a whole lot else. just crazy busy getting ready for the wedding. i still have to mow, clean, iron, and write a toast. aaaagggghhhhh!!!!!!!!!!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am sooooo getting obsessed w/ Roswell right now. I always liked the show before, but man, I am crazy obsessed w/ watching it now.....hmmm possibly blow money on dvd sets?....  anyway, taekwondo sucked tonight.  we spent practically the whole time doing our forms for the whole class, which, gotta say, I get practically nothing out of because I'm always the highest rank.  I was the only chick in class tonight, as is most nights. I don't usually mind, but marlyn was gone too. arghhh. (but I can still kick all the guy's buts...hehe)  I finally did some practicing today on my clarinet. and found out I forgot a ton of my scales. CRAP!!! now I have to relearn them! *mutters*  not much else going on...of course when school starts I'll be so busy my head will explode....but anyway.....later    
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well, the wedding was CRAZY. everyone was totally stressed out, which was NOT fun. like, once, we were waiting to go to the church. someone asked me a question, and when I went to answer, my mom put her hand over my mouth and SHUSHED me! then when I confronted her about it, she started crying! so I was like, okay, there's nothing I can do. that night though, my aunt gave me all this crap about me disrespecting my mom. HELLO! I was not! any other person would have said the same thing I did. anyway, if you push aside all the emotion crap, it was fun.  I went and got the superintendent's signature for my driver's permit, which I didn't wanna do, but I got brave and faced the scary man. so on friday I'll go to the DOT and get the school permit so I can get my car insured and drive to school. FINALLY! *smiles*  later
     
    
</post>


</Blog>