<Blog>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Reflecting on that horrific deed where friends become taunting rapists and homosexual at that, I must say that getting elected as Drum Major or Band Major is not a good thing because it is almost certain that you'll get gangraped. Even the great Dictator Rim Jia Chen got cold feet. Brr....
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      According to howie, my blog sucks because there were no links and very few posts. So I must post more often. Something remotely interesting happened in band prac today. The Sec 4 ex-Drum Major and ex-Band Major were er... gangraped by everyone else. I, however was but a curious onlooker so I cannot to be blamed. It was the Sec 4 farewell party, you see and my seniors wanted to see off my senior seniors with something grotesque. According to Jie Han, a Sec 2 senior, this gruesome deed happens "almost every year". Their clothes were torn off and words were scrawled on their chests with markers. Both their trousers' zips were spoilt. They were hysterical and it was the first time I had heard anyone shout so loudly. Some perverted fellows went so far as to take pictures with their handphones. Urk.  Sick , right?
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today Hiippy was very angry at the so-called "evil" people who filled out Doofus' survey because they all wrote "Han Chang/Hiipy/IHC/HC loves you/u/CK/chermaine". Whatever. But hey, he just doesn't want her to know that he likes her,  right ? Anyway, got my term progress report today and my MSG improved by 2.3! From 5.17 to 2.83! Yay! I'm euphoric! Hard work pays off at last! Baargh, band later at 2.45. Damien (my SL) says that its the Sec 4 send-off day so no practice and hopefully, no PT! We also get an early release thanks to Family Day. Yahoo! 2.45 to 5 compared to the usual 2.30 to 6.30 is a lot of difference indeed. Can't wait to get home, got to pack my bags fomr my Trenggannu trip and check on my Utopian provinces to check they haven't died and I don't have to create new ones. Matter of a fact, I have to put them on Vacation mode as I'll be away for 72 hours and a province ungoverned for 72 hours is a disaster waiting to hsppen.  More on my Trenggannu trip. That's in Malaysia and further north than KL. Its an overnight trip in a coach. Going diving again. Hope the chalet won't be as crappy as the last time in 1999.  That's all for now. Won't be blogging for a long time too...
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A new personal blog after the Orc Haven has been taken up for my journal. Hope to post more often. Long live Thrall!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nothing much to say today unless you want this blog to become a Utopian update. Provinces jumped in networth, Kevalinor, my WOL account jumped from 121k networth to 136k while the other, Kevalinorn (pretty unoriginal, wot?) rose from 52k to 57k. Kevalinorn's in  big trouble while in my WOL kingdom, we're preparing for war once more. Piano lessons fairly routine today, did ok. Band tomorrow, baaargh.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Back from my trip at last. Fairly nice trip though. The coral was beautiful and the variety of fishes was dazzling. Also had my gba along with me so that added on to the fun. Well, all's well again. Details about the trip are in my other blog. 
     

    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I advertise  the wonderful game Kingdom of Loathing in these spaces. Today I also uploaded a counter into my blog. Guess I'll be able to see who else other than myself actually visits this page. Heh. I am not a frequent blogger and this is my landmark 10th post!!!! A joyous occasion that must be celebrated!  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I arrived too late today to get a ticket to Spidey 2, nooooooooooo... I so much wanted to watch it and even finished my homework but alas, it was not to be. Knowing the diabolical teachers, homework would be in such great quantity that there would be no way for me ever to find time to watch it. Today was my only hope... It was not, my destiny.  OK, so I'll try again. I'll buy one... two days in advance. Anyone see a problem with that? If so, call 999 and tell the person who picks up the phone why.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've actually written a grand total of 2214 words! Besides that, I have to say very loudly to Howie that I DIDN'T RUN AWAY!!!!!!!!!! Would you like me to go to Jeffrey Lim and tell him it was all my fault, I instigated this mess, before you're happy? I'm a bit of an idiot ("What a bit? You are a big fat idiot!" Marcus Tan the moron would surely say) but why would I run away from a non-life threatening matter? I told Wee Keat and Jia Guang (or at least somebody) that I was going to the com lab. Or was it Charlton? Don't be unreasonable. And that was to Marcus because surely he will not listen to me even if I said the sun rises from the east and sets in the west.   And that brings me to the subject of Marcus Tan. For no reason at all, he snaps at people and the usual encouragment during soccer play has turned into sharp, digging ("Oh, so I dig into people? Ha hah hah, how can I dig them? Stupid!") comments like "Nice pass!" when someone misses and throwing someone out of his position just because of one mistake has also been done by him. Does he think he's the best 1O player that he can boss everyone around? ("No, but at least better than you!") If he starts yelling at people, I, supremely childish of course will yell back. It continues in a never ending chain. Yuck.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I haven't blogged for ages, guess blogging just isn't part of my daily routine. Compared to Pantsofsky's record of maybe 50000 words (?), I haven't even written 2000 yet (I think). Sad. And I inted to continue with this. Nothing else to say, except that I going to watch Spidey 2 tomorrow, yay!
     

    
</post>


<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ho ho ho and a bottle of rum... Checking in...
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       (The cheerful, irrepressible git)   Halloa, what do we have here?  My very first entry! Today has been quite a significant day because I improved from an E8 to an A1 (barely) in Math! And if I get an A2 for English, B4 for Chinese, and C6 for IH, I might get a sub-3 MSG! Yeah! But of course, the Maths test was fairly easy but at least I studied and got proper marks. However, I regret to say that I neglected my IH in all my fervour and frenzy to improve my Math and Science, so lower points for Lit and F9 for Geog (I think). History untouched though, 20/30 both tests. Anyway, today was my German test too and there have been varied opinions over it. Ashton the moron claimed it was easy and I thought it was moderate while Clement Wee said it was "like shit, meaning damn tough". It was moderate namely because I have quite bad hearing and I couldn't get the Listening Comprehension accurately. So sad. Think, think, what else have I to say? Urk... I'll be back, soon.  (A reversion to the droning, monotonous geek)  Okay, now for a coupla reflections on the current situation of the band (obviously my EP3). We just had our elections and though all Sec Ones weren't entitled to vote, the winners were actually quite satisfactory. The difference was shown clearly in our PT today. The old regime of cruel taskmasters (thankfully retired) would have thrown us into long hours of drills and made us run 2 km in seemingly impossible timings. The new DM (Drum Major) and the new BMs (Band Majors [Brass and Woodwind]) gave us only 3 laps and an achievable timing. Furthermore, no drills and only one fellow got pumped and he was getting out of hand anyway. All in all, a most refreshing change. On a personal note, I deilberately failed my musical theory test because I didn't like the tester, who, by the way, is a Sec 4 from the old regime of evil demonic monsters and was the one who set impossible timings for the 2 km run and the one who drilled us endlessly and the one who dealt out a hundred pumpings to every Sec One and the one who said:" PT is not meant to be enjoyable." and the one... The list of his daring doings is never ending. Inflexible and sadistic is the word. He is also a bit thick, which is why he can never come up with any new changes to improve our lives, and is also why I reckon he's from 4P. He had the audacity to throw a completely unbelievable garbage lie in my face, something about being self-voluntary for the morning run. I've never heard of such a case and anyway he isn't the athletic type, making his lie all the more ridiculous. Er... Well, enough of my ranting, shall we stop then? I hope this kind of entry is all right or I'll be dead for the rest of this journal. Signing off, see ya in good time! Hasta la vista, baby!
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Note: I will be assuming the persona of a fellow with split personality disorder so... don't get lost. 
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The Durotar Annals thus begineth...   From henceforth, all the glorious deeds and deeds of the Warchief shalt be recorded in this new text that will revolutionize the whole of orckind...  So, as you asked, Mr. Cheng, here my journal shall begin, and the world shall TREMBLE BEFORE THE HORDE!
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The Warchief has returned triumphant! For the Horde has come home over the fallen corpses of their enemies, the Remedial demons!The battle is won!  A most trying week. Remedial was sheer torture and definitely an experience I shall not want to repeat ever again in the course of my lifetime. Although Chinese was fairly fun, the inferioty of the other teachers to the Ispark ones was there, clear or not so clear the distinction. I don't wish to sound rather arrogant but the fact is that the Ispark teachers are better although I can't say the same for some students (like me).  Teo CC taught my mum in 1977 at Crescent Girls's School and my mum says she was a good teacher but I  think  that perhaps she has become (bit offensive here, sorry) addled with age. But the greatest distinction in quality comes from Mr. Alvin Tan and Miss Ong. Mr. Tan is a bit on the normal side, as in he follows the textbook like the Bible while Miss Ong teaches us a quite a few things that are outside the curriculum and tells us a few interesting things that have nothing to do with history at all.  But... one black sheep in the herd of brainless white ones. Our remedial Chinese teacher Ji Lao Shi (Kee HE) is definitely much more of a character than Cao Lao Shi, who is rather soft. Ji Lao Shi is loud and clear, and also regularly strays away from the main topic matter like a (ha ha) true Ispark teacher should. Or is she an Ispark teacher? I certainly hope so.  My fellow so-called bodohs included (surprise surprise) no dummies at all but instead studious fellows who were overloaded with commitments and couldn't cope and ultra-slackers like myself. The first category included two waterpolo guys who clearly coudn't cope with the peak period trainings for the nationals. So you can't really blame those.  However, I  DID  catch a whiff that some of them might be back next term, implying that they're still slacking. Ah well. I hope this time gave them a wake-up call for them to work harder in Term 3. Or else they're really gone.  In conclusion to this issue, I should say that everytime I see some of my classmates scurrying around happily in their respective sabbaticals, I disintegrate and blow up. I never know if I've written enough, so more on the Bilingual Project. Needless to say, it's in a mess. Last minute work is being completed even as of now. I certainly don't expect more than 3CPs, but that's taboo around Marcus, so clamming up, I am. I dunno, but I should try and make my IRS a bit better than that and my MRP too. I should consult Mr. Cheng sometime soon. Like perhaps in Term 3 after I've completed my 3rd submission. As for IRS, I'll be popping in to see the dreaded Mrs. Ng next week. OK? And that's all. I don't care about the damn word limit anymore. Gonna sign off right  NOW .
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      On a more academic note, heh heh, true to prediction, I made the amazing leap from over 5 to sub-3 in my Term 2 results! The terror of 5.17 to the safe heights of 2.83. An improvement second to one! An improvement of 2.3 points, only Pantsofsky has done better with 2.6! I'm in the clear once more but musn't lower my guard or it'll drop again in Term 3. Readying myself for a new challenge- sub 2! Kudos to all my teachers except Geog and Chinese where I dropped and maintained respectively. Can't seem to write anymore on this subject so signing off...
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm back from my trip in Trenggannu. There were many sights and sounds and definitely it is worth a single journal entry. You (the reader) might consider popping over there for a vacation some time.   Of course, I whined about the lodgings. No air-con, blah blah blah. But the splendous coral and marine life more than made up for that. But the fact that I had my Game Boy Advance with me might also have something to do with it, heh heh.  So, first day or should I say first evening on Saturday, boarded the coach with some trepidation about the lodgings and the food. Also felt a bit homesick. The food worry was dispelled by the fact that my aunt was  bringing  food there to cook. And she is a fantastic cook. Sleep was a precious commodity that night and I got to see much of rural life and most of all realised how fortunate I was...  Arriving in Pulau Perhentian, saw that the people were simple and happy while life was pitiyingly small, monotonous and likewise simple. There was nothing much to do except glimpse marine life and swim and sail. If you do that for all your life... You get my point. But blissfully unknowing to the big world out there, these people are happy. I both pity and envy them. All except one. This fellow speaks exemplary English and the menus and boards around that part of the island are probably his work. He's clearly educated and perhaps he realises the small lives of his friends. Speaking in German (dumme kuh over and over again to my brothers, that means stupid cow), I wonder if he misunderstood (for he definitely heard) that he couldn't understand the language anymore and that the educated world was slipping away from him. A misspelt word on one of the boards perhaps reinforces my belief. Can't help feeling sorry for him. I would feel the same in his situation.  But one thing that challenges my perception of their lives is the coral. So beautiful it is that perhaps life is worth living there after all. And snorkelling enhances its beauty, although my poor snorkelling skills could have diminished my enjoyment. Able to stare underwater for more than a minute makes it unreal, more like Underwater World than anything else, that's how clear the water is. And watching the fishes swarm around you trying to get to that piece of bread you're holding is wonderful too. The sand, real unlike Sentosa, soft like a carpet beneath your feet. And the sound of the waves at night crashing unto the beach and the clear clear night sky with its stars... You should pop over there some time. Idyllic is the word.
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I passed Dunearn Secondary on the way home from lunch. So? What's the significance, you might ask.   ... I was in Choa Chu Kang. The problem is, since the school has shifted its premises, their name is no longer valid. I remember reading somewhere that someone was calling for the schools to change their names to something more appropriate. Needless to say, they didn't, or I wouldn't be writing this now. How could the MOE not realise this idiocy? Ah well, the mysteries of life and the government. Anyway, no one seems to care anymore until a bumbling CHS student comes along and brings it up, namely me.
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ACE POINTS  Heck, my ACE is in a complete mess. I don't think I've maxed out for anything yet and the most I've got is somewhere around 8-10 for IH (I think). I have only myself to blame for my predicament. From next year I have to manage my time better what with ACE, MRP, Project's Day, CRP, CIP and so on all co-existing on the same sphere... However, there's still time left for me to hand up a few last assignments, like this one. So am rushing out this despite not being an active blogger. Thus far I have been suffering from writer's block. The sabbaticals also hold the key to maxing out. I should go for either Science or Chinese ones. maybe also for Maths. 
</post>


</Blog>