<Blog>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      updating because i can and it's 4:30 in the morning. i hate this. and i want people to go jump down a well. guess what movie i just watched. the ring! yay. 2nd time i've seen it and i still hate it. it scares the shit out of me and i'm sitting in a dark basement and rob and meg are off cuddling or something and kevin's sleeping. FOR GOD SAKES WHY CAN'T YOU DIE NOW. anyways. i stole the computer, and up until about half an hour ago, i was having an okay day. spent most of it with meg... we went starbucksing cuz we're cool, and all that jazz.;0 and went to old navy and i got clothes because i can. and hmmm the carnival last night sucked so much. i don't think i've ever gone through an experiance like that one. i'm typing to fucking dilegently. if i turn around and they're making out, screw life. me and meg tried to come up with a philosophy about choking on life. and it started to make sense, and then it died. well, she killed it. maybe this is supposed to teach me something. but i doubt it. i think it's offical that he hates me and i have to get over it. i shouldn't be mad at meg, she's like my best friend, well one of them, and i'm always shunning her or something and it's not fair to her, and i always feel really bad. and i want to jump on them but then again i'd get shot. so whatever i'll sit and type. mr. deeds is on this is like the 3rd movie we've watched. i want to go out. i need more nicotine. roar i have one left i'm going to cry or something like it. i love this songgg. well i'm offically retarded or something like it because tears are like, filling my eyes and if they see me i am SOO screwed OVER. :) WOW I HATE LIFE MORE THAN ... ANYTHING. why must they really be. this is like my venting stage right here. i think i've tied like 80 string bracelets or anklets i'm ready to go make a choker or some sort. oh my FUCKING word. i can't be selfish. robin stop being a stupid bitch he's just a guy. that you just happen to be in love with. i... am so fucking retarded it's so cool. i'm contemplating going home. going out that window and in through my basement window. like, seriously. i want to go to my own bed. i just realized something. i won't be able to sleep. i didn't read those little dudes. and i don't have them with me. SHIT. i have to go home and sleep. and i need my cuddlingness. i could fall asleep in his arms if i could. ew. why must meg really replace me. i'd rather that faggotity dutch girl. no wait, no i wouldn't. i hate her too. i just watched shania. i love that woman she's so awesome. ew it's almost 5 can we like, unlock ourselves from eachother PLEASE. i'm done with this i'm gunna go mope. i know i know. you hate me. well, fuck you.
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well it's finally sunday night, the weekend is over. this is the first weekend in a while that i've gone without seeing rob once, and it feels really wierd. this is going to take a very long time to get used to, but i'm trying to be strong, and i guess it's working. i have health with him tomorrow, and i actually am looking forward to seeing him. i've decided that, way back before we used to go out, i'd be happy to see him, not upset because he had no idea who i was. so now, i'm just happy to see him, not upset because it's over. i've learned a lot of important lessons from him, and i'll take them with me for the rest of my life. even if he's not with me anymore. i wish i was able to thank him for all of that. i don't think he has much of an idea of how important those 2 months were to me. i'm so happy it happened, i can't be sad that it's over anymore. anyways. i had a pretty good weekend actually. friday, hung out with my cousin, girls night, could have been out with kevin, rob and the red one, but kelly just wanted to be with me, so we had a shitload of fun. walked all over, made racist jokes, we were insane. it was really fun. i love my cousin, she's my fucking life. i don't know what i would do without her. oh yes. she tends to throw her phone when she's drunk. wow, that was, so funny. anyways... saturday, hung out with kelly and kevin, then went to the mall with kelly o'brien, hung out with her and dandan and chris and people... it was fun. then went shopping later that night. got a new bag, i'm so excited. and then today, went to an unnaturally long mass, then dandan showed up at my door with my lighter which i accidently ran throyugh the laundry, so he needs to take me to buy a new one... by the way, i'm quitting smoking. i'm so sick of it already. i mean, i had no reason to do it in the first place, i just did it when i was upset about rob. and i mean, i have to try and move on now, because well, it's over right. i need to get over it. anyways, i want to try and change a lot of myself around now. and fix what's wrong with me. like my obsessiveness. it needs to die. if i ever get into another relationship, my god i am going to be soo much different about that. now the whole hoobastank songs makes sense. wow. realization time! "i've found a reason to show, a side of me you didn't know, a reason for all that i do. and the reason is you. i've found a reason for me, to change who i used to be, a reason to start over new. and the reason is you." wow it all makes sense. haha anyways. i'm going to go watch punk'd, do my homework, kind of, and finish painting my toenails. i have a feeling tomorrow might be a good day.
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i love this song. switchfoot rocks my socks almost as much as racist jokes. dude me and my cousin were looking up like 80 million racist jokes online and it was really hysterical, we're both going straight to hell. it's going to be a party, everyone should come and join us. yeah well today was okay i guess, i'll admit it had it's strong point. like calling anthony zumstag a fucking loser. at the top of my lungs. while he was in a car. driving away. i fucking hate that cock sucking loser. anyways. i discovered today that i have a lot of work to do. school work, for one. and work on myself too. and don't be a sick perverted freak, you know what i fucking mean. at this point, i'd change anything about myself, i'd accept myself, i'd do anything, just for a person. that's a pathetic thing to say, but i don't care. i just don't give a fuck what other people think of me. people used to love me for that. but that had to come down too. i don't want to be obsessed anymore. i don't want to be affected anymore. i don't want to be fazed. i want to be me again. i kind of miss the old me, but not really. yeah and i'm never smoking again. i never realized how nasty it was, and yeah i'm just sick of it already. and i don't really have a reason for it. except to calm me down. but singing does that too. i love singing, i don't want anything to ruin my voice, it's a part of me that i'm seriously learning to love and accept. maybe i'll just work a lot harder on music and see where that takes me. it's a distraction at least. i don't have to think about him. well, i don't ever have to think about him, he just comes to mind sometimes you know. well, yeah. i want to work on my music right now, but it's like, 12:30 in the morning and that would be stupid because my cousin is like, half asleep when we said we'd stay up all night. dude i used to listen to this song 90 times a day last year. dumb girls by lucy woodward. i miss this song. it's really, hmm, memories. OMG GUESS WHAT EVERYONE DON'T MAKE PLANS FOR ALEX'S BIRTHDAY WE'RE ALL GOING TO SEE SHREK 2 OK OKAY!!! :) you're jealous and you all want to come and see alex the sexy beasty. ;) peace easy fuckers i'm fucking bored of this shit. 
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hello everyone. blogger changed around, this is fucking awesome. anyways, i've been thrown into a lot of huge situations over the past couple of days, and i'll admit that i had no idea how to handle anything like that. i have never literally felt myself fall apart before, it was the weirdest feeling that has ever like, consumed me. it was so, friggin crazy. god, i'm an obsessed annoying little nutcase aren't i? haha i'm just kidding. you all know you love me more than life. well i'm trying to keep on the cheerful side since yesterday was just awful and i couldn't contain my emotions one bit. well, i'll get over it, i'm going shopping tonight, and tomorrow is friday. i gotta find something to do though, cause my cousin has to work and crap and it's just not fair, i want to get out of the house. maybe i'll convince kevin to come buy a pack or two with me and we can go sit in the woods like loser stoners or something like it. well what ever i just want to get out of the house. maybe the weegster and i can go and free bozz from jail. i want to go visit him and see what he says. i'd laugh like crazy. tomorrow is going to be great, we're going to post 27 free joey posters around the school with pictures of the cheshire cat. he didn't do anything wrong anyways, so everyone we know is going to get a poster on their locker or something of that nature. i am going to laugh when like, dodig yells at us or something. it was a joke i swear! whatever. okay well i'm sick of typing so fast and this computer not keeping up with me. peace easy fuckers. i'm going SHOPPING BITCH. ;)
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sitting in my room at the moment. my cousin is here, but she's in the shower. dude, i am so fucking scared about tonight, don't ask i just had to share that i was scared. anyways... we had a pretty long day today, rob king and kevin the red one came over at like 3 and we hung around until we got my cousin and kevin. we went to rachels for a little bit. and we hung out at owen fish for majority of the day. oh yeah, rob's little brother was with us too. entertaining. well anyways. i don't have much to say, i just felt like updating. it's going to be a long night. a long long night. it'll be interesting. peace out fuckers.
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ever thought that everybody was out to get you? like, out to destroy who you are, and shatter your feelings? because lately it feels like even the people who claim that they're going to be there for me forever, have turned against me. they love to criticize every single move i make, and every single feeling that i have. apparently i'm just a big joke to everybody. it's not fun to be a joke. like even when i call someone when i'm upset and need help, whatever i'm upset about is just something to laugh at. i'm always the dumb one, the stupid one, the idiot, the mockery. and i'm starting to hate it more than ever. i don't know what to do with myself anymore, every thing i make is just something i'm unsure of. i'm always wondering who'll criticize me next. i'm starting to think it would be better off if i just didn't bother with other people anymore. they just laugh at me and think i'm retarded anyways. there's always something wrong with me and what i do. and i'm so tired of it. sometimes i feel like crying just because i can never be right about anything. i guess nowadays, just caring about someone is stupid. caring about someone more than anyone else. that's pathetic. and wishing for something... that's just retarded. i hate this, and i can't take it anymore. and now, i need to go. and think about this. 
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      it's already sunday. we've only been off from school for 3 days, and it feels like we're going to be going right back there tomorrow. it's wierd to think that i can sleep until noon again, without it being a major issue. it kind of makes me sad, because there are so many people that i would normally see everyday, that i won't see for weeks at a time. and there are people who i won't see everyday come next year, and it's going to be harder than ever to be around them. so many things are starting to change so fast. and it pisses me off sometimes. like now. because today i'm grounded for going to owen fish park last night when my dad told me not to. which is stupid. and pointless. and it's 5:00 and i've been lazing around all day. i wish i could have called people and gone out. had a life. i'm sure there will be many days like this one this summer. my throat hurts. it hasn't hurt all week. until i went to meg's house and she's been sick. thanks meg. i have to clean my room today or i can't go out tomorrow either. my parents are working all week, so i'll probably have to have people over here. haha, party! well, everyone knows they can call anytime to hang out. i still haven't gotten my cell phone back, which REALLY pisses me off, but i'm slowly working on getting it back. roar. i need it. it's like my lifeline or something. it makes me sad. i'd probably talk to a lot more people a lot more often if i had it. eh HEM. whatever. i'm leaving now peace out. 
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Basics  Name:: Robin Salata Birthplace:: Woodbridge, Virginia Birthdate:: 12/15/88 Current City of Residence:: Fairfield, CT Family Members:: Mom, Dad, Melanie, Jojo   Favorites  Color:: black Beverage:: alcoholic anything. Movie:: anything with orlando bloom. Musical:: grease, bitch. Board Game:: um, monopoly? Computer Game:: um, does solitare count? Game to Roleplay:: roleplaying is, strange. Animal:: umm, penguin. Sport:: softball and baseball. Book:: harry potter, or lord of the rings. i'm a geek.  School:: i hate it? Typical Mood:: um, bad. Usually Found:: computer or school. Collects:: nothing.   Have You Ever  Had Sex:: no. Done drugs:: yes. Eaten an entire box of Oreos: no. Eaten sushi:: no. Been on stage:: yes. Been in a car accident:: yes.   This or That  Cold or Hot:: hot Blue or Red:: blue Rain or Snow:: snow Wool or Cotton:: cotton Private or Public School:: public  Chocolate or Plain Milk:: moo moo juice. Celsius or Farenheit:: farenheit  Spring or Fall:: spring. fall means school. Science or History:: science. Math or English:: english.   "Love Life"  Do you like somebody:: yes. Do they know:: they're too thick to understand. Do you want them:: no.  Are they hot:: yes.   Random  Who do you e-mail the most: fiftal. sad to say. Who do you IM the most: meg. Who are you talking to now:: kevin, meg, and owen. Are you currently in love:: yes. Is this survey lame:: yes. Isn't bzoink! nifty? =) :: no.   In 24 hours have you...  ...Showered:: yes. ...Had a serious talk:: yes. ...Hugged someone:: yes. ...Gotten along with your parents:: no. ...Fought with a friend:: yes. ...Done something kind for someone: yes.   Do You Like To...  Give hugs:: yes. Give back rubs:: sure. Take walks in the rain:: yes. Cook:: yes. Eat::  no. Sleep:: yes.   Who...  ..Knows you the best:: rob king, meg roberts, and melissa lombardo. and kelly vornkahl. ..Have you known the longest:: katie jones. ..Do you know the most about:: um, i can't really say. because i'm not sure. ..Do you consider your friend:: a lot of people. ..Is most likely to end up in jail:: rob berry and kevin kernan. ..Can you go to with your problems:: rob king and melissa lombardo usually. ..Do you want to get to know better:: rob king. ..Do you spend the most time with:: everyone at the corner.   Have You...  ..Been to a concert:: yes. ..Loved someone so much it made you cry:: yes. ..Cheated on a test:: yes. ..Ever stalked someone:: ... yes. ..Done something you regret:: nope. regret nothing.   Random Questions  Single or Hooked:: single. What is your worst habit:: biting my nails and smoking. Scariest moment:: a lot.  Do you swear too much:: yes. How do you feel about homosexuality:: it's okay to be gay! ^^ Where are you right now:: my room. Are you sitting by anyone:: no. What song are you listening to:: it's quiet now. What is the last thing you said:: "go kill yourself." What's on your mousepad:: a lot of writing. it used to be my cats. What are the last four digits of your phone number:: 9199 What was the last thing you ate:: um, an ice pop. If you were a crayon, what color would you be:: grey. How many buddies do you have on your list:: 200. What's the weather like right now:: dark. What do you feel like doing:: sneaking out. What is your favorite quote:: life isn't about the breath you take. it's about the moments that take your breath away.  wrote that quote for my 8th grade yearbook. little did i know that that moment would come a long. and then i'd lose it. what a loser i am. well, that was just another random splurge of pointlessness. still haven't studied.
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I WANT:  school to be over.  I HAVE:  to go buy cigarettes.  I WISH:  death upon certain people.  I HATE:  the dutch.  I FEAR:  him never talking to me again.  I HEAR:  baby birds chriping INCESSANTLY underneath my air condicioner.  I SEARCH:  forrr a key to fhs to get my books to study.  I WONDER:  what is going to happen with ... people.  I REGRET:  nothing. everything happens for a reason.  I LOVE:  ... people.  I ALWAYS:  get lazy around exam time.  I AM NOT:  happy.  I DANCE:  ... never.  I SING:  constantly.  I CRY:  every night.  I AM NOT ALWAYS:  obsessive.  I WRITE:  down every feeling in my black notebook.  I WIN:  ... never. usually. unless it's poker.  I LOSE:  everything worth keeping.  I CONFUSE:  everyone who says a word to me.  I NEED:  to kill those birds so they shut up.  I SHOULD:  get over him.    YES or NO:  - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - -  x. YOU KEEP A DIARY:  yes.  x. YOU LIKE TO COOK:  yes.  x. YOU HAVE A SECRET YOU HAVE NOT SHARED WITH ANYONE:  yes.  x. YOU BELIEVE IN LOVE:  yes.    THE WEIRDEST PERSON YOU KNOW:  meg.  THE LOUDEST PERSON YOU KNOW:  my cousin.  THE SEXIEST PERSON YOU KNOW:  rob king.  THE CUTEST PERSON YOU KNOW:  rob king.   THE PERSON THAT KNOWS THE MOST ABOUT YOU:  rob king. my cousin. meg. melissa.  THE LAST IMAGE/THOUGHT YOU GO TO SLEEP WITH:  lately? it's been a bad one. which is why i end up crying.. which explains all of the nightmares about glass boxes i'm trapped in screaming at people who can't hear me and i'm trying to get out of the box but i can't break the glass and i start crying when people on the other side yell at me? yeah.    DO YOU...?   HAVE A CRUSH: yes. WANT TO GET MARRIED: yes. GET MOTION SICKNESS: no. THINK YOURE A HEALTH FREAK: no. GET ALONG WITH YOUR PARENTS: no. LIKE THUNDERSTORMS: yes. CURRENT HAIR COLOR: too blonde for my liking. EYE COLOR: hazel.  BIRTHPLACE: woodbridge. virgina. ******   FAVORITES:   NUMBER/s: 420. COLOR/s: black. DAY/s: weekends. MONTH/s: june, july, august, december. SONG/s: yellowcard - cigarette, only one, stabbing westward - high, angel FOOD/s: bacon egg and cheesesss. and strawberries. i am wierd. SPORT/s: softball and baseball. DRINK/s: anything alcoholic.   IN THE LAST 24 HRS, HAVE YOU...   CRIED? yes. HELPED SOMEONE? yes. BOUGHT SOMETHING? yes. GOTTEN SICK? yes. GONE TO THE MOVIES? no. GONE OUT FOR DINNER? dinner? no. lunch? yes. SAID "I LOVE YOU"? yes. but they couldn't hear me. WRITTEN A REAL LETTER: no. TALKED TO AN EX?: not of my free will. MISSED AN EX?: yes. a lot. WRITTEN IN A JOURNAL?: yes. HAD A SERIOUS TALK? no. wanted to? yes. able to? no. MISSED SOMEONE? yes. HUGGED SOMEONE?: yes. FOUGHT WITH YOUR PARENTS? yes. FOUGHT WITH A FRIEND? yes.   Would you ever:  1. Eat a bug? for money. 2. Bungee jump? yes. 3. Hang glide? yes. 4. Kill someone? at this point in time? yes. 5. Kiss someone of the same sex? only because i love sam. 6. Have sex with someone of the same sex? no. 7. Parachute from a plane? yes. 8. Walk on hot coals? yes. 9. Go out with someone for their looks? no. that's dumb. 11. Be a vegetarian? no. 12. Wear plain with stripes? sure. 13. IM a stranger? yes. 14. Sing Karaoke? yes. 15. Get drunk off your ass? yes please! 16. Shoplift? yes. 17. Run a red light? yes. 18. Star in a porn video? no. 19. Dye your hair blue? streaks maybe. 20. Be on Survivor? no. 21. Wear makeup in public? yes. 22. Not wear makeup in public? yes. 23. Cheat on a test? yes. 24. Make someone cry? yes. 25. Date someone more than 10 years older than you? orlando bloom? amen. 26. Stay up all night? yes.   this is my pathetic way to avoid studying for finals. :)
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last cigarette: friday night. :( Last car ride: back home from the metro's game with melissa yesterday. Last kiss: friday night. Last good cry: last night. Last library book: do i go to the library? no. Last movie seen: harry potter. biiitch. Last book read: harry potter. :) hey, i was inspired! Last phone call: uhh rob berry? Last song you sang: i surrender - celine dion. :/ Last shoes worn: WELL NOT MY SHOX THAT GOT STOLEN. > Last cuss word uttered: fuck? Last item bought: either pot or cigarettes. :) Last beverage drank: orange juice... hehe Last food consumed: haha bacon egg and cheese sandwich. my life.  Last tv show watched: real world. because i can. Last time showered: just stepped out of the shower. Last cd played: celine dion. so sue me. Last downloaded: yellowcard - only one Last annoyance: my father. Last disappointment: ... something involving dutch people. Last thing written: poem. hmm.  Last sleep: uhh last night. woke up at noon, went to bed at midnight. Last weird encounter: joanna. that was strange. Last time amused: natalie and rob berry on a 3 way phone call. amusing. highly. Last time hugged: yesterday?  Last chair sat in: this one. Last underwear worn: i'm wearing boxers at the moment. O_o Last show attended: i totally do not remember.  * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * LAST PERSON WHO...  x. Slept in your bed: me.  x. Saw you cry: shannon and katie griggs and kelly o'brien at beachfest. x. Made you cry: ... the same person who i've cried over every night for the past month. x. Spent the night with: my cousin. x. You went to the movies with: janelle, michaela, kelly o'brien and rob berry. x. You went to the mall with: dandan, rob berry, kelly o'brien, melissa, janelle... x. Yelled at you: my father. x. Sent you an email: FIFIE! ;) x. You kissed: ... i won't comment.  ********************************************** What CD is in your CD player? celine dion, i told you. What color socks are you wearing?: none. What Color underwear are you wearing?: black boxers. because, i can. What's under your bed?: 2 boxes i'm not supposed to open, a make-up case, and a lot of dust. ********************************************** CURRENT Current mood: pretty bitchy actually. Current music: sugarcult, yellowcard and stabbing westward. Current hair: um. meg beachblonded my hair. it's BLONDE. o_O Current clothes: my pajamas? that say i hate boys. :) Current color of toenails: pink. i need to re-do them. Current time: 12:58 p.m. Current hate: THE DUTCH. THERE'S ONLY 2 THINGS I HATE IN THIS WORLD. PEOPLE WHO ARE INTOLERANT OF OTHER PEOPLE'S CULTURES.... AND THE DUTCH. > Current hero: the first person who manages to bomb holland successfully. :)  sorry, bored out of my mind. and i have nothing to do today. not even study for finals, because all of my books are in the high school, and i need them to study, so i'll probably walk up there later to see if i can break in and get them. because i need to study because i have western civ and bio tomorrow and i am going to fail, and i have to weite a slide thing for english... and fuck me in the asshole, i am totally screwed. and i have plans to make. god damn it. save me. peace outtt.
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well it's saturday night. beachfest came and went so quickly i barely remember any of it. but i remember that some of it was fun, and most of it was hell. i got there around 4 with kevin and kelly, and pretty soon, i couldn't find them anymore. i was hanging around brittany and her people for a while, waiting for rob berry to show up. he finally did at like, 7:30 or something like it. and i got in so any friggin arguements. everyone seemed to choose the night robin's in hell to get pissed off at her. i couldn't really help collapsing on the beach, breathing through cigarettes, only way to calm me down now apparently. but then i went swimming in my clothes with shannon and kelly o'brien. that was really fun. then i came up with about 500 million ways to kill someone. which was amusing as well. then my southerness came back to me for a little while, until i was called annoying and had to shut up. but it was okay after that, until a few visions were engrained in my head, so i had to go and clear it out. 45 minutes later, i was done beyond all speaking. kelly's face had molded together until she had one giant yellow cat-like eye and giant green looking fangs. i was bugging out to no extent. then i almost fell asleep in the pavillion and i lost a shoe. one of my shox too, i am so pissed off. well, at least i can get new shoes now. whatever. i'm still pissed. i didn't go to bed until like, 2 in the morning. and then melissa called me at like, 10 and made me go to the metros game. anthony, davis, ryan, and alex all present. which was cool. then we went out to lunch at friendlys with her grandma, then i went over to meg's and "studied for western civ." yeah right. i hate studying, i left all of my books in school, like a smart person with a western civ and bio final on monday. :) i am the genious. i'll probably go see if the school is unlocked tomorrow. after that, i'm bombing holland. :D PEACE OUT. 
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ... enough said.
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      my entry titles always seem to match the song i'm listening to. anyways, beach fest tonight, i'll have too big of a fucking hang-over to type anything tomorrow, and probably the next day too, so don't talk to me. it's gunna rule. everyone better be there. yeah well it's the last full day of school. cut study hall. cut bio. and most of chorus this morning. how fun. they accused me of going to smoke instead of going to bio. my ass. i was in the caf, yelling at rob king for being a stupid shit bag. don't tell him i said that. anyways. damnit. my teacher's here. leaving. peace.
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sitting in the library. bored out of my mind and waiting for athena to come back. she has to take her health final. it's so nice and cool in here, it was such a friggin oven in english. i had double spanish this morning, it blew so badly. and now i'm really tired. and i want to go home right now, but i have lunch right after bio, which is next, and i have 2 frees today, yay! beachfest is tomorrow!! i am so excited, you have no idea. oh my god my dad is just a bitch. i asked him when i'd get my phone back, and he said as soon as i mark up the bill trying to find any mistakes verizon made. it was $200 since he took the phone away. and so i did it all and i guess he got pissed off, as usual, and i said, can i have my phone back now? and he's like NO I WANT A NORMAL BILL RAWR I'M FAT AND STUPID!! i was just like, okay i hate this guy and i hope he tries drugs soon. anyways... i cannot wait for tomorrow, oh my god you have no idea. i really, really want to hang out with rob king this weekend, since i haven't talked to him in so damned long. i really miss hanging out with him.i told him that in a letter i wrote him about a week and a half ago, but he hasn't said anything to me about it since. and i want him to sign my boot-leg yearbook, but i'm too scared of what he might put in there. something about how much he hates me no doubt. well, he can be like that. what meg wrote made me cry. her and sara and athena signed so far, i must find my senior friends. they have to sign before they leave me all alone :(. well  i have no idea where athena is, that final didn't take THAT long did it? it took me like, 15 minutes, literally. and i got an a- on my chorus, because i rule. well this is getting long. and oh yeah, i have sophmores who think they have the right to call my best friends sluts. :) and apparently now i'm a "gothic freak". that is so hysterical. it almost made me funny. don't ask. peace easy fuckers.
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      in the warde computer lab with rob wes and ashley. bored right now, got nothing better to do than listen to music and type in this damned thing. i'm having a pretty damn terrible day, if i do say so myself. rob is trying to read over my shoulder, stupid shit, cutting study hall on a pass to the nurse. typical. well whatever. i should be doing my western civ homework, but i'd rather kill myself. i have it next period. ahh. air conditioning. thank god i've been dying of heat all day, and i want to go to rachels and swim, but i can't because i'm wearing a white shirt and black pants, for one, and for two, i have to walk to my mom's work after school to pick something up. after that, going home, and doing NOTHING. i'm missing rob just to go to my mother's friggin store. i'll just go smoke, all be better. sick of this. bye now.
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well, what a long and entertaining weekend and week so far. i got home from lake goerge with melissa, kevin and porgie on sunday, and it's been like, insane since then. the weekend with melissa and her family was really fun, we went go-carting like, almost everyday, played mini-golf, went out on the town at night, and went to the great escape during the day. awesome roller coasters, let me tell you that much. it was really awesome, i miss hanging out with them. yeah, but sunday night was about the only rest i got. yesterday, was absolutely crazy. kevin woke me up, and then i went and met him up at the high school. we went down to tunxis and out to dunkin doughnuts and shit and met up with rob king. we were really bored, until he showed up that is. that kid never fails to put a smile on my face. we bugged the shit out of a bee's nest, because one of them stung kevin, and then we went to kevin's and jumped on the trampoline. then rob completely ditched me and the red one, so when he had to go to baseball practice, kevin came back and we went to my house where i was going to get my hair low-lighted, but then it didn't work out. but i got to see tara, so it was okay. we went out for a walk because me and kevin needed a cigarette, and natalie, rob berry, cassidy and andrew jump out of a random car. so we were all hanging out, bugging out some little kids, and then sam came with her girlfriend. and we were all hanging out, then people got pissed off and i had to go home. then my cat attakced some other random cat that kevin accidently let in the house, and then kelly o'brien and bern and dandan showed up randomly and kelly jumped out of her car like a smart person. yeah that was a crazy night. well anyways, kevin woke me up at 9 today and he came over. we hung out for like, hours. and he got his tongue stuck in a bottle. it was the funniest shit ever. and then we went to the mall with kelly, bern, gerry, rob berry, cassidy, natalie, and andrew. big ass party. well, it was fun at least. that was my day. you know you're all jealous of my life. and now i'm going to go play with my new zippos. fire is fun. remember that kids. :) 
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      la la la, going to lake george with melissa and porgeh and kevin tomorrow. how exciting you are all jealous! :) yeah so melissa's packing at like, 10 at night because she does everything last minute! yup. this is going to be veryyyyyy interesting. i'm sure melissa will have fun. you will. you will. HI ANTHONY! anyways. yeah i will be coming back on sunday night, but i will have my cell phone with me. ;) talk to you later. i'm being sacared my melissa and some sort of lion that sings. great now she's hyper. pray for me!  
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hello ... well, today, well, yesterday now, was really, well, interesting. i don't know why i'm awake at 2 in the morning by the way, i think i'm just really stressed out and really wierded out. i'll explain that all later probably. well, yeah yesterday, i got woken up against my will at like, 12 by kevin. who insisted that he was my wake-up call. so, i had a good morning cigarette, and dragged my ass out of bed. made myself breakfast and invited kevin over for another good morning cigarette. we hung out for like, a couple hours, and then kelly magically appeared in my doorway. how exciting. we hung out until my dad got home, and kelly and kevin got into yet another fight, over something stupid no doubt, so they left my house and told me to meet them at owen fish in a half an hour so they could, "talk". what they meant by talk, i do not know, but i went. and stayed for about half an hour before i left myself. and they went out to dinner together so i just stayed home. until kelly o'brien called, and then we went to the mall. which was entertaining no less. it's always entertaining when kelly is around, let me tell you that much.  it seems like at 2 in the morning, fuse just wants to play all of the songs off of my playlist, nothing new, or entertaining. why do i feel the constant need to be entertained now. i have no idea. i need to get up at 8 in the morning, why am i sitting at my computer, i should be sleeping. yeah, again with the stressed and wierded out. well, kelly and kevin, they keep getting into these fights over the stupidest things. like, drugs for one thing. or attitudes. i mean, i'm supposed to be the one with the troubles in my life, and they get to be the happy couple that's always around. boy almighty, i think i've run into some shit this time. hopefully everything's fine now, i told them that they were the reason that i was going to get lung cancer. oh well. yeah and wierded out because some people decide to be extremely nice randomly and i love it insanely, but it's really kind of freaky sometimes, maybe it's that whole men are from mars women are from venus book that my mom is making me read. that says like, men pull away and then come back all nice like nothing happened. but i doubt it. if he has any feelings for me, it's feelings of either extreme pity, extreme neglect, or extreme, i feel bad for you you pathetic loser, which is the same as pity. i don't know, maybe i belittle myself too much. whatever. that's just the way things tend to work out for this insane fucker at 2 in the morning. i think i just might go smoke my last cigarette. that's right, my last cigarette. now i need another pack. i don't feel like riding my ass to the god damned felt. whatever, if i want them, i will chase them. maybe i'll go to sleep now, i feel nocturnal.    OH YEAH I GET TO GET MY CARTILAGE PIERCED AND I GET MY BLACK LOW-LIGHTS! be excited.     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      there's so much to say in such a short amount of time. i don't even know where to begin. everything is changing so rapidly it feels like my entire world is spinning in circles. i don't even know who to trust anymore. and that's a really sad feeling. i feel like i only have 3 close friends that i can trust. that's about it. those are the people who i know are going to stay with me and support me through all of the shit that's going on right now. as my cousin so blatantly put it, all of this "bullshit". and it is bullshit, it's just that i really don't feel like having to explain the way i feel over and over again. it doesn't seem like anyone will ever understand me. you see, i have a horrible tendency to live and love in the past. i spend my entire life chasing what the past was. and suddenly i realize that i am never going to catch it. once something happens and changes everything, you can't ever get what you had back. and it's really depressing to think about, but it's true. i hate thinking that i can never have back what i had. and i hate thinking that maybe it was all a lie. thinking on back on that one time, that one time when i really thought he truly meant that he loved me, i can't even fathom thinking that it was all just a lie. i mean, i don't feel like i can ever trust anyone again. people change their minds so quickly, and they don't stand up for their feelings, let alone tell other people their feelings. i hate the fact that some people are so terrified of love that they will do anything in their power to chase it away. i don't know why they're afraid though. it might be because they never had anything true like that before, because they think that it will end up stabbing them in the back... for whatever reason, people need to try and stand up and tell others their feelings, and not keep changing their minds, and backing away. it's not heathly, and it's not helping anyone. if you set your mind to something, you should do it. and never back out of it. i should talk right... i'm not one to stand up for myself. i'm more of the one to believe what everyone else says, and not even think twice about my own self esteem. God, i just wish all of this could go back to normal. that everyone could decide what they want to happen, and everyone could get their way. but that's impossible, because everyone wants completely different things. and i pray to God that no one leaves. i was seriously thinking about flying myself down to south carolina just to get away from all of this mess, but my mom told me that running away doesn't solve anything, because your problems will still be here when you get back. no matter how long you stay away. so i pray to God that everyone stays here. because we all need eachother more than ever right now. even if some people have really hard feelings for others right now, we need to stick together through this. no matter what tries to stand in our way. i really beg and wish of everyone that we can put the past behind us. because i've finally learned that i can't love and live in the past anymore. because it's not doing me any good at all. i love the one who used to come into my room almost every day with a huge smile on his face, always looking to make me smile and laugh. i love the one who called himself cookie monster and spazzed out about every little thing. i love the one who used to help me clean the dishes and ended up spraying me with the sink hose. i love the one who made fun of me for the hip thing. i love the one who was always by my side. i love the one who held me when i was crying, and the one who whiped my tears away. i love the one who i could stay with in complete silence and feel whole. i love the one who made me feel like an angel. that's the one i love. i don't love the pain and the hurtful words that come from him now. i'm always wondering where all the love from all of those poems and all of the love in his eyes went. because everything just seems cold now. and i wish someone would turn on the god damned heater. sure, i miss the past. but that doesn't mean i need it back. it doesn't mean i'm going to spend the rest of my life chasing after it. because i'm not. we all need to move on with our lives. together. as friends. and i hope it all works out. for the majority of people reading this, you will have no idea what i'm talking about. well you know what, don't ask me, because you're not supposed to know.
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hello fuckers. i am home at the moment with kevin, waiting for my cousin and benevelli and rob and j.r. then we're going out somewheres in the shitty weather like classic stoners. we have nothing better to do with our lives. well the week has been interesting. i went to the mall with rob and rachel the other day. and i talked to gerry for like, ever. and we went swimming after we got back. hmm and then yesterday i slept over kelly's and that was fun too. we went to the mall and crap and found gerry again and dandan came after a while. and then we went back to her house and watched club dread. that was a funny ass movie. and then me and kelly had a party in the basement. we played pretty pretty princess dude! i miss that game i used to play it when i was like, 5. well this computer is pissing me off and i want to wait for people and i wish my mom would stop being a fuck head and stop "thinking" she smells cigarette smoke. which makes me angry because she's being a stupid shit faced, god damned loser. hermf. fuck that shit.
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      home once again, got back from the mall about an hour ago. went with kelly o'brien. it was fun. i haven't hung out with her in a while. we're such stupid fucks. we spent half the time telling stories ending with, "fuck that shit!" we are cool. other than that, i slept until like, 1:30 this morning, and then i did chores, and went to the mall at like, 6:00 or something. yesterday was kind of wierd, my cousin slept over, and we went to the red one's to swim. well, his aunt's house. kevin came over early in the morning, and we walked there. and then we swam for like, 3 hours. rob and his brother showed up for a little while too. benevelli got his cast off, we were excited. me and kelly and kevin went to starbucks and mcdonalds and the felt later that night, and we started a fire. in the brush. and then i ran to go put it out, and there was a hole in the fence i jumped through, hitting my head on the overlying pole in the process, falling flat on my ass, which hit the bottom part of the broken fence. i put out thre fire after that, and then we walked home. it was fucking hysterical, my cousin pissed herself laughing. we ran into connor, justin and elliron, and then some guy yelled at us and calling us fucking potheads and told us to get the fuck out of the road. we laughed. well that was the story of my life so far in the past 2 days. it might get more interesting if anyone wants to pay attention. i'm out now, fuck that shit! :)
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      how interesting the past couple of days have been. my my my. my life is just a whirlwind of tears and cigarettes. hey that's a good one, i like it. well, yeah i definately have gone through like, 3 packs in the last like, 48 hours. my cousin is here. we were so pathetic last night. oh my word. we sat at my window, went through 5 cigarettes each, and sang stupid love songs like assholes. we sang tell him, and i was celine dion and she was barbara strisand. which was very amusing. i bet all of you would have laughed your little white asses off. kevin fixed my computer kind of. he's still working on it. all of the extra programs are gone, and my computer can actually keep up with my typing. which is very good considering what an utter piece of shit this machine is. whatever. i deleted kazaa. that helped. got bearshare. that sucks too. but i got some of my songs. which is good. i love this stabbing westward song, what do i have to do. the words hit my heart. damned straight. i was so hyped on time released drugs last night that i couldn't sleep. 4 in the morning, i was writing shit in my notebook. and i wrote my cousin a letter. and i drew a picture. and wrote some stupid emo shit that only she's seen. she's the only one who will see it. i'm the most pathetic shit faced loser you will ever meet. :) i am so glad you all approve. well, i look like i'm stoned right now, so i have to make my eyes stop being red. maybe another cigarette will cure me. i'll go do that now. have a fucking delightful day! :D
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      just got back from the fireworks about an hour a go. happy 4th of july fuckers! it's been the best one of my life. if only life could be like that... wow. i barely remember what happened after i found him. i'm kinda sober now... flashes of the night are coming back when i try to remember them now. that was fucking fun. oh my word. i'm contemplating going to sleep now, but i think it'll be easier to pass out in a couple of hours. iwalked barefoot from penfield beach, to jennings beach, and back to penfield beach, not to mention my detour in the woods. and i totally lost my cigarettes somewhere during the walk back to penfield, which pisses me off, because i had like, 10 left. no, more like 7. it's still a waste and i now have to steal money to get myself another pack. yuck. and i almost lost my lighter. and my balance. several times. i am so fucking grateful, oh my god, i am loving existance at this point in time. i think i just might have to bask in the summer a little longer. waking up at noon, getting dressed, having people over, and then going to the best fireworks show of your life? amen to that everyday. and coming home to a nice bagel with creamy cream cheese. how yummy, how perfect. and i'm still fiddling around the the acoustic guitar kevin's letting me use. i'm kind of getting the hang of it, my goal is to be able to play something before the summer is over. it'll be awesome, brittany gave me a pick with a turtle on it. it's sweet. yeah i hung out with brittany for a couple hours today too, she owes me big time because i found her people for her. i discovered a tick on my about on hour ago. i knew i'd get one. well i'm going to go relax now, and try to remember why tonight was so damned perfect. good night losers! :)
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well today was damned interesting. i slept until 2 in the afternoon on the count of being up until 4 in the morning waiting for a phone call for someone else that never came. so i just slept for as long as i possibly could. i woke up, made myself some breakfast, and watched thirteen. it was really good... it was about like, growing up and it had all these drugs and alcohol and sex and stealing and all this shit, and these girls are in like, 7th grade it's crazy. but they've got to prepare themselves for high school. everything changes. anyways, i took a shower then and i left gor kelly o'brien's at like 5:30. and we went and had a little pow-wow in the woods. then we went and bought my 27's  ) tata he's out having fun now so i won't bother el sexy uno. :) tata losers i am out.
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hello people. back from the best 2 and a half days of my life. and hopefully there's plenty more to come. i have never been so friggin happy. not in a long time. i don't think i've been anywhere but owen fish park, rachel's house, my house, or kevin the red one's house in the past couple days. it's quite exciting. i love summer. it's hard to believe that it's already here, but it is, and i can wake up at 12 and not have to worry about a damned thing except who i'm going to be hanging out with that day. and who's gunna call me and make plans. or who i'm gunna call. my dad left for pennsylvania and my mom is working all the time, so people are constantly in and out of my house. it's so fun. this song, oh my god. only one by yellowcard. it's like, the perfect song for right now. well, change some words around. but i still love it. it's gunna be weird that meg's leaving for like, 3 weeks on saturday, but it'll be okay. i just won't be able to call her on every single mexican story. which is depressing. well, on the upside, there are a lot of people around that i can bother the crap out of. oh my god this week went by so fucking fast! it's like it was just 3:00 on tuesday afternoon... it's fucking early friday morning now. ooo friday! good day right there. well i'm probably gunna go watch tv or something now. or be sketchy somewhere. i think my friends just scream the word. one guy asked us if we were causing trouble. that's how sketched we are. i think i've said that a grand total of about 90 times already. which is sad. SKETCHBALLSRULEYEAH! 
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hello fuckers! once again, i am still in south carolina. and yes, i am very happy here. GUESS WHAT ROB?! i went to the mall today. ;) you love me. you do. well yeah i got a ring that says i love orlando. (once again rob, you love me.) and i got this black bracelet thing. it's hott. i get to go clothes shopping tomorrow, more time at the mall. i went to the pool today too. i will be tan when i get back, i swear it. just you watch. yeah well i don't know what else to say to you fuckers, cuz i only get a half an hour on this thing, my sister has to get on apparently, she was supposed to be on now, but she chose not to, because her friends are never online. yeah well, i have to say that i am in love with new found glory's catalyst cd, and i want to go to the warped tour so bad it's sickening. and my parents are staying at a hotel tonight for some reason, it's like, my mom's "birthday present". yeah right. OH GUESS WHAT'S ON TONIGHT?!? true life, i'm taking adderall. HAHA. i really wish i could sit and watch it and pop pills like popcorn, but i don't even have any cigs. OH MY GOD. MARBS ARE LIKE, 2.99 A PACK HERE. and if i had any way to go get some, i would. because, i'm going to die. i was feening so bad earlier that i was chewing on a straw. a STRAW damnit! how pathetic. whatever, i'll go through a carton when i get home, guarenteed. and cartons are 20$ here too. roar and a half. well i'll go now. have fun in connecticut doing NOTHING! like me sitting here. :) but yeah i come home in 7 days, so don't fret. :P yeah right. byeee! 
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      AH CAN YOU BELIEVE I'M FINALLY IN SOUTH CAROLINA I GOT YOU ALL SCHOOLED! it's so fucking hott here though, christ it's unbelieveable, and this is a dial-up computer with no aim but it's all worth it, know why? CUZ I'M ABOUT 1,800 MILES AWAY FROM YOU! HA! no i'm just kidding, maybe i might miss a few of you. you have to be real special though. how come when i actually find a way to talk to people back home, there's no one online? you boring shit heads. i'm pumped, that was totally a 15 hour car ride. i'm running on a shit load of coffee and about 5 hours sleep, roughly. and me and my sister get to sleep in this office with the computer while my parents get the nice beds. losers. whatever i'm going to get tan tomorrow, it's all worth it. i don't think i'll be able to dress like myself down here people, too much sun, makes for very warm black clothing. not a fun mix, let me tell you that much. well, yeah you guys can still talk to me if you need me. just call my cell phone, which i don't have, but listen to my voicemail, i'll tell you what to do. let me tell you, it's all a part of my evil plan to get my damned cell phone back from my fucking loser of a father. :) have happy days in connecticut losers, I'M BACK HOME!!! well, not home, technically, but we did go by my old house in dale city. haha. i like, almost cried. it was sad. it was. i don't remember the shutters being blue. whatever, we ate at my old resturant too. red robin. hell yeah. but no one talk to me when i get home, please, the hickness will have rubbed off by then. i am not looking forward to it. BYE BYE FUCKERRRRRS. have fun being... bored shitless in that god forsaken state we all like to call home. muahaha i win. you know you love me. YES AND I WOULD LIKE TO HEA  R   FROM A FEW OF YOU. IF YOU KNOW WHO I W  O  ULD HAPPEN TO   B  E TAL  KING   TO. heehe. bye bye. 
    
</post>


</Blog>