<Blog>


<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dear Bylie,  Long time no see? not sure how long it has been..  Anyways, right to my story...  I am very unhappy and feeling down lately, I feel like breaking down to cry but sometimes I am not sure why or maybe its because there is no one besides you I can tell the truth to.  And sometimes I don't want to face such truths can show my weak side of me.  Bylie what can I do?  There has been many things on my mind, sometimes I wish the world would just stop and let me relax and take a deep breathe and let me do whatever I would like to do.... like some time out you know?  I have a full time job, I'm starting to feel that I am so different now and life is full of TOO MANY RESPONSIBILITIES. Sometimes I feel very old and all grown up but other times I really just want to be a kid again. Like no responsibilities... I worry a lot that one day or I mean what will happen to me in the future.... to be thinking very far I am very afraid to be alone and that one day all my family will not be with me anymore.  Other times, I feel so weighted down and so annoyed by others I just want to be left alone and feel like a bird and fly wherever my heart desires.  I sound very confused huh?! I'm not even sure or ready to admit what I am feeling deep inside.   I have a lot of problems if you want to dig deep but then I put myself to seem like I am so strong and everything is alright.  It is just too much pressure you know? I still want to believe I very young! aren't I? I'm only 25 right now? don't people my age have nothing to worry about and still party a lot? or maybe not? I dont' know..... I really don't know.....   All I want to do is stay home and be with my dogs, have nothing to worry about, nothing to think about, nothing to be yelled to me about, nothing to be complained about to me or about me.  More like I don't know what you call it.....  I would love to bring my dogs to travel or not even travel just to be with them..... to go to beaches, parks, walks and be very simple and happy.    But then, the most problem I face is I am very pressured that I need money, Oh well from last time I talked to you, I have paid off my bc student loan, and a interest that happend that my interest relief was not authorized last time I applied for canada student loan.  But anyways I owe less about 15 k and 600 bucks for my biggest debtor canada student loan which I can pay off later either save and pay off the whole chunk or pay it off in say um.. 9 years or something but anyways right now I got to focus to pay off my grant over award about another 1200 bucks and then my credit cards under 1700 then the big problem is the 5k for pet grooming........... that seems like so much money and too much time to be continue to work, sometimes feel like killing myself since I hate the job so dam much.  Why? I don't know, its just I don't like to be around people I guess and the job is like I don't know how to describe.    Or maybe I just need a break, I need a long break....... I don't want to work anymore....... but then I need the money that is the conflict that makes me so unhappy I guess... I mean if you work and know you don't need the money and just working to waste time and know you can quit whenever you want it would be happier, but when you don't want to work and force yourself to work because you need money that is a different story.  Another thing is I really am not sure what I'm going to do with my future. I mean its kind of scary when I think of it.  Sometimes I think that I will not be able to make it I mean like I don't know what my career going to be nor can I imagine what I would truly enjoy doing and it even scares me more is thinking of the years to come. I mean if I live to 80 years old then there will be another 55 years left and I don't think I want to do the same job for the next 55 years or say if I retire at 50 there will be another 25 years!!! I mean having me stay to do the same thing for a few months is so HARD already! 25 years? I sometimes think if that day comes and I am alone and can't make it, I'll just kill myself and get it over with since I can't make it.  I think of my future husband, and then I think of my ex and then I think of where the hell is my future husband? I don't see no sight of any potential person around nor that I think I will get a person that would love me entirely around.......  What am I going to do? I am so lost........... I have these dreams and predictions, these things just keep coming and sometimes in my mind I hear these voices I don't even know is it my brain thinking or someone is saying something to tell me my future!  I am soooo lost and tied down..... I feel so tired........ so tired........... I just want to give up somtimes and forget everything and worst is kill myself.....   Ok maybe you should have a better plan. Nothing is worth risking your life, I mean if you feel that bad then just get rid of what is causing you feel so unhappy.  Well now you say you have another 1200 bucks then you just need to work another 6 weeks to pay off this and then you probably want to pay off your credit cards before you quit then that be another 10 weeks so just hang on for another 16 weeks meaning 4 months and that be september before you quit.    Then have yourself a long break and vacation and then find another job that you enjoy perhaps being a cashier at ikea or perhaps a part time pet groomer or just a relaxing part time job, just enough to pay for your living.  And then find yourself another full time job paying enough that at least you can save 800 bucks per month and work for another half an year and go to pet grooming and then after work at home or also part time as a pet groomer.  Hey look it will just take another year in order for you to have all that you wanted to come true and then by then probably you find yourself a potential husband and then by then you and him can make some goals and dreams to follow to share and be happy........ not that long you know... so now hold on another 4 months til september, just another 80 days of work! just about 1/5 of your year you need to use to get that vacation....... but then it'd be great if you can hold on to another half year, 6 months to be working at that company for an year, that'd pay off on your resume and pay off say half on your pet grooming tuition.  If you can pay your tuition that'd be great if not forget it...... its okay.  Don't listen to what others say just do what you feel like doing that makes you happy and your life worth living and to continue to live. It's okay...... life won't end just because of something so little like your job you dislike!! ^_^
     

    
</post>


</Blog>