<Blog>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          urlLink Create your own!   I love how the fact that I've been to Moscow/St. Petersburg twice hands me over the entire continent of northern Asia.  (Never mind that Russia spans eleven time zones and reaches halfway across the globe and practically touches Alaska...)  Ooh, that was fun.  What else can I do instead of virology??
     
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Panera Bread   The other day, I was perusing  urlLink amarPod 's blog, and I took the scientifically-proven voting predictor (amazing!).  Now, I think it was mostly because I shot the KKK guy instead of the French nationalist, but the words on the screen told me that I am voting for John Kerry.  Holy moly! said I.  That is amazing!  I wasn't 100% sold on Kerry just yet, but I was very pleased to not see Bush's name up there, mostly.  But Kerry is from Boston, and if he's from Boston, he's probably a Red Sox fan, which is (let's face it) the only baseball team that is acceptable to love.  Bush is in all honesty probably a Yankees fan, even though he is from Texas and therefore the antithesis to the historical image of a 'Yankee'.  But I digress...  Now, what this voting game thing told me was that I hate the 'idea' of Starbucks, which I took to mean that I am against large conglomerates that exercise their financial and political power and form the structural basis of the power elite that, in effect, is what really rules this country.  So, yes, I do hate the 'idea' of Starbucks, but let's face it: (a) they make good coffee that lots of people like to drink; (b) they started in Washington state, which just seems cool; and (c) my boyfriend used to work there.  In fact, the nearest Starbucks around here is 20 minutes away in a little strip mall across from the only Target in the area, and I really wish they would build one that didn't require a massive pilgrimage.  But some people are like (voice of Eric Cartman): "oh, no.  I am *so* glad there isn't one here.  They are so terrible and so commercial and mainstream and terrible and everyone goes there."  This coming from one of the most annoying people I have had the misfortune to meet, but there you have it.  [Note: Ben & Jerry's is also really big, and does that make them evil?  No!  Because they are from Vermont.]  What I really want to talk about, though, is Panera Bread.  A Panera Bread just opened up about 3 minutes from here, just down the road from the huge medical center where I attend school.  Being that there is lots of commercialism here already, but only in the most standard and typical form possible (McDonald's, Papa Johns, and Turkey Hill [we're in Pennsylvania]), the fact that they opened something that resembles moderately healthy food is a huge step in what, in my opinion, is the right direction.  The first week of class, I learned about a very important medical diagnostic criterion, the 5 F's: female, forty, fat, farm, and fertile.  These characteristics form a group of people, many in this area of hearty central PA, that are susceptible to many sorts of diseases (diabetes, heart disease, the things that have gone hand-in-hand with large food conglomerates/nationwide fads like McDonald's and the Atkins Diet).  Without going too much further into a huge discussion on the health/fast food plague upon our nation, I ask you this: Is it wrong that I have eaten at Panera bread five times in the past four days?  I say no.  Their sandwiches and soups and salads really bring a much welcomed change to my diet of late, seeing as sometimes I eat nothing but Kraft mac n' cheese and two mini Reese's PB cups for dinner.  That, my friend, is NOT healthy.  If I would rather eat a Tuscan chicken sandwich with lettuce and tomato on foccacia bread with a small salad than a bowl of cereal for dinner, methinks 'tis an example of good judgment.  And I like eating bread, especially since that whole Paris thing when I ate real baguettes every morning and took that life for granted.  Why do I feel the need to defend myself in my eating habits?  Just to prove that I am really a democrat vying for leadership by the people, for the people, and so forth?  Sort of.  But mostly because I like just their food.  So, in the (semi) words of Marie Antoinette, I say,  let them eat bread! 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       In the beginning....  ( Hmmm, where to start?  What should I write? )  In the beginning, Alison created the blogspot that.... ( no no no that's lame and plagiarizing the Bible )  Um, hi?  My name is Alison and I live in Hershey, Pennsylvania where there are cows and chocolate and the 5 F's.  ( haha )  Uh... ( think think! )  I am in medical school.  I, uh, am studying micro and immuno right now for a test on Monday.  Well, I'm not really studying anything *right* now, cause I'm making this blog, but I do have an exam on Monday and.... ( dear God, you are SUCH an embarassment.  Just shut up. )  Sorry.  That's boring.  Let's start over.   Brief interlude : Hey Hey Let's go, protect my balls.  So let's fighting!  Let's fighting love....  I am finally starting one of these.  Considering I spend most of my time screwing around instead of actually reading and learning stuff the proper way, this new bloggy-blog of mine will probably fail me out of med school.  But Amar and Viv both have very excellent blogs, and they are still in school.  Grad school and med school, no less.  So there you have it.  Let's see how this blog goes.  [Here is a short prayer: Please help me to make my blog worthy of other bloggers with funny things and humorous things and amusing things that will make people happy and bring joy to them.  Also, please help me pass medical school so I can pay off my loans.  Amen.]  Here goes nothing.  And...........................  action! 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Really, I have absolutely nothing to say.  It's one of those days where you are totally like "bleh" and feel like an utter unaccomplishment of the world, pointlessness hovering around you like a cloud of bloodthirsty gnats.  I found out yesterday that the summer job for which I have been gainfully employed the past three (3!) summers is probably not going to happen, despite yearly reassurances of being guaranteed a job the next time around, and now, three weeks from the end of school, I am facing the despondent notion of being unemployed for the next three months.  Apparently, bad things really do come in threes...  Without going into too much detail and angst over this unjust "job loss," let me just say that now I am trying desperately to find something to actually DO with myself for this summer.  I mean, three months, man!  Three months.  That is a lot of time in which to do many amazing things, especially considering these are going to be the last free months of my entire life until I am once again toothless and in diapers.  What an amazing opportunity, a bright, shining silver lining to my gray new raincloud!  My first thought (naturally) was to go back to Paris and be "un bum" and live in the metro at St.-Philippe-du-Roule (can I get a what what? for my former hood of Rue de Courcelles/Blvd Haussman).  But sadly, I cannot even afford that, as a McDonald's cup full of euros probably won't pay the 3 months of rent I owe here in Hershey.  Dommage.  I would write more, but a) I don't have anything really to say, and b) I have to go.  Sorry this is so depressing.  FYI, if you need a personal summer slave, I am available for 2 cents/hr.  (Viv, can I still autoclave your things and get 2nd author on your paper?  Let me know...)
     
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Saturation kinetics.  The only thing I remember from this portion of basic biochemistry is: enzymes, cell transport, and the name "Michaelis-Menten."  In (very) laypeople terms, saturation occurs when every enzyme active site, cell surface transporter binding site, you name it, is bound to a substrate or material.  At this point, the system has reached "saturation," where the rate of the reaction or transportation has reached its maximum rate.  The only way to increase these properties is to add more enzyme/transporter/whatever.  Hooray for Michaelis and Menten for figuring that one out 200 years ago.  Mad props, guys.  MAD props.  At this point, I would like to try and apply these concept to something to which everyone can relate to, not just biochemistry freaks who spend their entire existences trying to penetrate the mysteries of enzyodynamic physics or whatever the study of this stuff is really called.  There is another very important arena to which saturation kinetics can be applied: studying for exams.  (* Note: the ensuing discussion applies best to those in heavy science-oriented curriculums (curriculi?) such as medical school or graduate school.  Nonethess, it can still be considered relevant to other intellectual pursuits of a strict you-either-know-it-or-you-don't nature, maybe like economics or history, but NOT English or studio art .)  Now, I have reached saturation kinetics for my exam that starts in less than two hours, so I am speaking from experience here.  In fact, I feel that I am truly qualified to talk about exam saturation kinetics because I have experienced it for almost every test I have taken here in medical school and most college finals.  (Even for my exam ON saturation kinetics, but that is another story, my friend.)  The sequence of events usually goes something like this:    - Early on, very little studying is accomplished, as there is very little pressure/incentive, as exam is still safely three weeks away.  (This may be akin to the scant selection pressure bacteria feel when not threatened by antibiotics.)    - As exam time approaches, the pressure increases and you begin to start studying more and more vigorously, but not with the same panicked fury and desperation as when...    - You finally reach saturation kinetics.  This usually happens either one or two days before the exam, possibly hours beforehand.  This period is often accompanied by feelings of guilt, shame, and A.D.D.  It is very difficult--if not impossible--to study any more, despite the panicky feeling inside that screams out "You still don't know anything!"  Nonetheless, the books and papers are cast aside and other, less important things begin to occupy the handicapped parking spaces of your mind, like: "Did I mail that letter?" or "Shit, I forgot to include my W-2 in my tax return!" or "I think it would be most productive to write something about how I'm feeling right now on my blog..."  If you have experienced this chain of events before, you are probably suffering from what I would like to henceforth refer to as "exam saturation kinetics (E.S.K.)."  It is not a disease, nor a physical or psychological abnormality.  It is merely proof that many things in life follow prototypes, and E.S.K. is no exception.  Indeed, it is probably a premiere example of this phenomenon.  So technically, I am not procrastinating right now.  I am just naturally experiencing E.S.K.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       In honor of my exam tomorrow afternoon....*  ( urlLink I didn't write all of this , I just edited it to fit medical school and BBD exams tomorrow....) *  Major  procrastination...   Professors : Ma chere tuition-payers, it is with deepest sadism and greatest power that we welcome you this morning. And now, we require you to get tense, let us pull up a chair, as the faculty proudly presents - your exam.   Take your test Take your test Are you nervous? Are you stressed? Summer's just around the corner now We love this time the best Immuno Micro, too And the goddam fucking flu What's the formula for Keflex? You should know this, you're pathetic! B-cells here T-cells there Let us offer you a prayer. You'll be writing with such energy and zest Go on and take some blue books You'll at least need two books Take your test Fake your test Take your test  IL-1 IL-2 You'll be chugging Mountain Dew As you scram back home to cram And stay awake the whole night through If you're here and you're scared Then you're prob'ly unprepared Don't tell me about your party You should study, Mr. Smarty Pneumonia And the Clap Let us run you through our traps Did you ever get the feeling you're oppressed?  Don't question our regime How could you dare blaspheme? Now take your test (You've B.S.ed, But you'd rather say you've "guessed") Take your test Take your test Take your test  Life's all smiles and smirking For a student who's not working It's a gas without a class to load him down Ah, those good old days way back in college Suddenly he wants his med degree While he's been busy learning Curiosity's been burning What's it like to have a minute to himself? He won't know 'til after he retires... They came here so lazy Now we're driving them all crazy!   Students : It's a test! It's a test!  This can't be! I still need rest!   Professors : You want sleep, you little creep? That's very good. That's quite a jest Leukocytes on parade And the complement cascade Yes, we'll give you quite a beating If we catch you while you're cheating If your poop Is bloody Then you've got dysentery  Student : Help me please! I'm having cardiac arrest!   Professors : Somebody check his heart!  Then label every part! It's on your test...  Course by course, One by one 'Til you shout, "This isn't fun!" Then we'll laugh at every place that you digressed We've done our best to fail you See you all in year two! Take your test.... Take your test... Take your test...  Now, take..... your...... TEEEEEEEEEH-ST!!!!!!!!!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      First of all, on a completely unrelated note, there are two guys sitting behind me in the computer lab speaking French.  It is so awesome but disconcerting and irritating.  Irritating in that I want to BE IN FRANCE right now.  RGRHGRRR...  But moving on.  Tomorrow at literally the ass-crack of dawn (7am), me, Brett, and Geneva are driving to Cincinnati, Ohio to run in the Flying Pig Marathon/10K.  Brett (the crazy-ass dedicated one) is running the marathon, and Geneva and I are running the 10K = 6mi.  Yee haw.  I therefore need to go run 3 miles outside right now to complete my panicked, hurried 3-day training schedule, as I decided early Wednesday afternoon that I was in fact going to try and run this thing.  Holy shiite.  Although I did do 5 miles yesterday on the treadmill at a decent clip, so in theory I should be able to drag my ass 6 miles through Cincinatti--and, it's rumored, part of Kentucky (ooh, I've never been to Kentucky).  So yeah.  But I am seriously considering not running this afternoon, and yet desperately need to to get used to running outside instead of inside on a treadmill with climate control and Oprah blaring on the TV in front of me.  As for other aspects of life, eh.  It's amazing that despite almost a full year of medical school, I have STILL not learned enough to stay on top of studying.  By the time I actually start studying next week, it will have been two full weeks since our last exam, and two full weeks since doing any real sort of work.  I guess it's a good thing that I can afford to be this lax during BBD, but part of me is screaming: "GODDAMMIT YOU SHOULD BE GETTING HONORS WHEN THINGS ARE THIS EASY!"  Then I quietly tell that little anal voice to shut up, and life is sweet and blissful yet once again.  I watched Friends last night, which was my special treat to myself after "studying" and running 5 miles.  Unfortunately, I also ended up watching Will and Grace and ER, as well as the second Friends episode they showed that night.  But it was sooo worth it.*  And I found myself wondering how many people in this country were actually sobbing themselves as Rachel was saying goodbye to each and every Friend (except, as we find out later, Ross).  I found even myself feeling a little chokey, until I realized that I was watching a fucking TV show.  (Note: this criticism doesn't apply to when Dr. Green died on ER.  That is totally different.)  Not to mention the fact that that bitch Rachel is supposed to be moving to Paris.  PARIS!!!?!?  Wtf.  HOW can you cry over that!?  HOW!?!?!  I am sorry, but if I were given a choice between Ross and living in Paris, I would gladly shoot off my own big toe in addition to choosing Paris over whiny Ross.  Is it kind of bitchy of her to just up and leave and take Emma, I'll admit, but in the long run, Emma is better off growing up French.  She just is.  You may think that I am obsessed with Friends since I've managed to squeeze them into my ever-growing and all-important blog.*  But I am really not.  I am just commenting on what I saw last night for the first time in months.  I am happy that Monica and Chandler are finally getting their baby, because Chandler is funny and the only 'Friend' that I would actually want as a friend.  Monica, on the other hand, is an anal retentive bitch who really, really, REALLY needs to chill out a little.  Phoebe is and always will be the same character as Michelle Weinberger (sort of), and Joey has his own show coming up soon, so criticisms will be further delayed until his show takes off/is canceled.  And Ross and Rachel will OBVIOUSLY end up together, because about a million female viewers will shit their pants if Rachel actually does the right thing and ditches him.  And in the infamous words of Julie Sharbutt, don't nobody want that.  *Note sarcasm.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
            You're  The Poisonwood Bible !   by Barbara Kingsolver     Deeply rooted in a religious background, you have since become both isolated and schizophrenic. You were naively sure that your actions would help people, but of course they were resistant to your message and ultimately disaster ensued. Since you can see so many sides of the same issue, you are both wise beyond your years and tied to worthless perspectives. If you were a type of waffle, it would be Belgian.      Take the  urlLink Book Quiz  at the  urlLink Blue Pyramid .    Dude, that is really weird.  Every time I read The Poisonwood Bible, I am left awe-inspired and speechless by what an amazingly crafted and beautifully written book it is.  I never really was religious, am not schizophrenic, and if I were any sort of European pastry, it would be a Nutella crepe, but nonetheless, I am amazed at the results of my book quiz!
     
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       (Note: If you are Mike I***, please don't read this.)   I hate it when people say life isn't fair.  I understand that it isn't, okay, but seriously.  It totally sucks, dude.  ESPECIALLY when things like jobs and life are at stake.  I hereby submit Chapter 104.b of Vivienne and Cam's soon-to-be-bestseller "How the World Is Unfair To Me."  Now, something that has recently been concerning me is job security.  This is mainly due to the fact that I was recently informed that my longtime summer job may no longer actually be my longtime summer job, thanks to changes in hiring policies that have gone on while I was away at school.  Without going into the issue of future job security as doctors are rammed up the asshole by medical malpractice insurance and lawsuits, let me rather focus on the present situation.  For the past three years (that's three, as in 1-2-3), I have spent my summers working full-time in a certain ER in a certain hospital in a certain city on a certain cape in Massachusetts.  Simple.  Every summer's beginning I have been welcomed back, and every summer's end I have been assured of a job for the next summer.  "Just give us a call in April and we'll arrange your starting dates."  Simple.  Easy.  The complete opposite of things like health insurance and IRS tax returns.  These next three months comprise the last free summer of my entire life.  Come August of 2004, I will be working until I have reached old age, taking no lunch breaks or U.S. holidays or bathroom breaks till then.  So needless to say, I pretty well better fucking find something worthwhile to do this summer.  Unfortunately (as always to normal people), money IS an object, and my aspirations of living in a flat in the 8e arrondisement in Paris and reaffirming my desire to acquire French citizenship over the summer months are dashed.  Dommage, man.  Tres dommage.  I could spend my summer completing my mandatory medical student research project (MSR) and getting that shit out of the way.  Unfortunately, all the work-study positions were gone approximately 52.4 months ago, I am way overdue for submitting a proposal, and I think I would likely commit seppuku if I were forced to stay here and sacrifice my final freedom.  (For a definition of seppuku, see comic #1354 by Cara L. Franken.)  It doesn't take a rocket scienctist to figure out that working at my fun and awesome job in the emergency room (possibly the speciality of medicine I would like to enter) on CAPE COD would be a very pleasant, rewarding, educational, and fulfilling way to spend my last summer ever.  One might think that having established myself over the past three years as a reliable and cheerful employee might assure some form of job security, right?  WRONG.  Earlier today I received some suggestions from my dear friend Vivienne on how to reapply for my job.  Ahem.   Please tell us about your work experience.  I've beeing working at CCH for three full summers now.  How do you think you'll be able to adjust to the CCH atmosphere?  Um, pretty fucking well.  Will you require training sessions and a 6 hour orientation?  No, you fucks.  Give me my job back.  So there you have it, folks!  In the infamous words of the Joker, "What kind of world do we live in, where a man dresses up as a BAT??"  You said it, Jack-o.  Life's a bitch.  Get used to it.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ooh, my turn, my turn!   urlLink This  is what came up when I typed in MY name into the google search engine.  WTF???  I also got  urlLink this lil' link , which is quite nice.  I must say, I do enjoy sharing the correctly spelled version of my name with a very talented singer/songwriter (one of whose songs I actually did sing!).  And  urlLink WHO IS THIS ????  (*NOT* me.)  I am about to lose my spot  urlLink here .  Poop.  I want my name emblazened in this HKiss athletic archives for ALL of ETERNITY.  Is that too much to ask? 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
            urlLink What Famous Leader Are You?    urlLink personality tests by similarminds.com  
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Holy moly bejoly krapoly fatone!  In less than seven (7) days, I will be done with my first year of medical school.  However, within those remaining 7 days (more like 6.5, actually), I need to organize my MSR project for next year, organize my independent humanities research project for the next three years, figure out what the hell I am doing for work this summer, and cram 4 weeks' worth of micro/immno/path/pharm in before my 1pm exam on Friday.  (And clean my room, which may prove to be the hardest of them all.)  But in precisely EIGHT (8) days from now, I will be scott-free, blissfully and intellectually liberated.  That's right, ladies and germs.  We're going to Cedar Point!!!  Among other news in my life, last night I went to the absolutely creepy mall in East Harrisburg (the closest one 'round these parts) with the intention of going to the Gap.  Unfortunately, in the time between last night and our previous visit to the HBJeezy mall, the Gap closed!  I am confused.  I thought it was a law somewhere that every mall had to at least have one Gap--King of Prussia, the 2nd-largest mall in the country, has two!  It doesn't matter how small or how ritzy or understaffed or what.  I mean, there are Gaps in airports now, too!  Naturally I was very disappointed.  However, I consoled myself by buying me a pair of jeans and a cheap yellow T-shirt with a banana on it and some Spanish writing that says "Ninos" which means "little boys."  I bought these at American Eagle, aka Cheap Abercrombie.  And let me tell you, there are some T-shirts there that really have some pretty perverted things written on them.  Like one T-shirt that says "Go Down" with an arrow pointing down.  "It's pretty nice" and then underneath that "Costa Rica."  Don't think I can't pick up on THAT double meaning.  I mean, give me some credit here.  I DID, after all, attend The Hotchkiss School.  Well.  Library time.  I have a lot to learn, about syphilis and gonorrhea and herpes and stuff.  Did you know that chicken pox is caused by herpes??  Oh, awesome.  Casa Bonita!  And I also bought 2 DVD's last night at Best Buy (also in an attempt to console myself over the loss of the closest Gap).  I bought "Big Business" for $5.99, which is the best 80's movie ever made (starring Bette Midler and Lily Tomlin) and then "The Ninth Gate" for $10.99, which is a very creepy and well-made Roman Polanski film about old books and the Devil.  Hooray for purchasing things!  In other news, I have also made up my mind to buy a digital camera.  I need to sell my body to another research study, and there is one I've set my sights on.  It's a bed-rest study, where you lie in bed for 24 hours and they pay you $250.  Amazing!  If only making money were always that easy.  And 7 days from now, I'll actually have 24 straight hours free.  7 days and counting...
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I heard a great quote from one of our professors today who was teaching us about the microbiology of bioterrorism.  In other words, we learned why it is not a good thing that Saddam Hussein and pals may be cooking up batches of anthrax spores in the "chocolate chip factory" going on over there.  We also learned about the Ebola virus, and our brief lecture on that topic was bascially a rehash of the greatest movie ever made, "Outbreak."  Dr. Courtney talked about the CDC and USAMRIID, as well as that hot-shit "level 4 biosafety" stuff where you wear spacesuits to work with those viruses that will basically liquefy your organs if you let them.  Did you know that Dustin Hoffman and Kevin Spacey work there?  And Rene Russo?  And Marcel the Monkey?  Well, he doesn't work there.  He just goes around killing people innocently with the death virus he carries around in his system.  Marcel the Killer Rhesus.  So apparently, Atlanta harbors two coveted secret "recipes" within its city walls.  One, the famous formula for Coca-Cola is tucked away, locked safely away within the factory walls in a safe whose combination is apparently known to only a select few.  And inside the CDC resides the last viable sample of smallpox in the world (besides one more in Russia).  You can imagine how Pepsi and Osama must salivate after those two Georgian treasures.  Apparently a while back, some research building somewhere was contaminated really bad with  Yersinia pestis  (aka, the bubonic/pneumonic plague agent), and I guess it can't be used anymore, for reasons that you or I could probably guess.  Getting back to that "great quote" thing I was talking about earlier, this morning Dr. Courtney proposed an interesting solution to the problem of whole-building contamination, which I will reproduce for you here: "The simplest solution would be to autoclave the entire building, but unfortunately, I don't think it's possible to autoclave entire buildings."  Haha, could you IMAGINE????  This GIANT bubble goes over a whole building and heats it to unimaginable temperatures to kill every living organism within.  Dude.  Autoclaving is the fucking shit.  He also called the Ebola virus a "stupid virus," since it kills everything so quickly that it can't even facilitate its own spread.  Oooh, them's sounds like fightin' words to me.  So in summary, boil your jars before canning, don't eat the white powder you find in your letters, and if there is a 5-inch black, necrotic ulcer forming underneath your chin, go to the hospital.  You just might have cutaneous anthrax.  You just might.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I decided to go ahead and give my blog a makeover, but ended up pretty much f*cking everything up.  I've managed to fumble my way through some basic html, but have only thus far managed to figure out some links and stuff.  I also managed to delete all of your lovely comments, too!  V. sad.  So I need to figure the following out: 1. how to put those HaloScan comments back in 2. how to put pictures into html 3. how to get that stupid profile sidebar to the top of the page rather than at the bottom 4. how to read/write/interpret html  If you can help me out on any of the following, it would be much appreciated!  And offer short prayers here for my exam tomorrow at 1pm.  Obviously, nothing much is getting done right about now....
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am writing a study guide for molecular carcinogenesis right now.  (For those of you that actually read this blog and visit my fotolog, can you sense a pattern to my artistic creations of late?)  However, I anticipate it to be very boring, and thus, will periodically switch back to writing thoughts of the moment whilst I am belittled by that little fucking paper clip that always tells me I'm doing things wrong.  (Thank you.  I KNOW how to type...)  "mutation duration and tumor formation"    Well.  I finished the study sheet.  It wasn't that bad.  I think I am going to quickly take a test on  urlLink theSpark.com .  As a little mental break.  I am 59% pure, but they didn't have one of those little html things that I could post on here.  Crap.  I guess I'll have to take another one.  Shit.  I guess they don't give you little pictures thingees anymore.  Poop.  And by the way, 'Weikl the Weapon' is from one Fear Factor's female contestants last night.  She was apparently the "secret weapon" on her high school's swim team.  Now, we won't go into the fact that she barely scraped by and made it to the last round on FF last night, despite the fact that 2 out of 3 of the challenges involved swimming.  She basically sucked, and her voice was really weird, too.  Freak.  She called herself 'Weikl the Weapon.'  Haha.  Dumbass bitch. Well.  Back to my carrel over there.  It's calling my name....
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow!  They changed all this blogger template setup stuff!  Looks pretty good, other than the fact that my own, personal blog still looks like the crap.  But then again, that's why it's called "Oops, I crapped my pants," now ain't it?  I just wanted to write something to get that stupid Canadian flag off the top of my blogger.  Seriously.  It's like "log on to cool alli_oop blogger and then---holy fuck!  It's CANADA!"  Didn't want that no more.  Nope.  Nuh-uh.  Well.  Now I need to write up a study sheet on cancer, predisposition to cancer, and tumor progression thereof.  Fasinating, to be sure.  Actually, it is, but despite my mundo exam on Friday (last one of first year of med school--hurrah!) I am only sitting here studying to fill my pre-set quota for the day.  After arriving here at nine, I said to myself "Self, you must work until 11pm."  It is now 10:30 pm.  Only one half-hour left.  Hurrah!  In other news, I watched Fear Factor tonight for the first time, and was pretty much fed up with all the anorexic bitchy girls who sat there and were like "oooh, $50,000."  I mean, that's a lot of money, yeah, but the only way I would eat the shit they put on there (literally) is if they paid me mucho dinero.  And in further other news, there is this older woman sitting at the carrel just opposite me who is studying on her laptop, and by studying, I mean clicking the friggin' mouse button like it's the only thing she knows how to do.  Every.  Two.  Seconds.  Click!.... click!.... click-click!.... click-cla-click-click!!  I seriously almost started screaming.  That would have been funny.  "Alison explodes in pent-up rage at some innocent woman studying in the lirbary."  Yeah.  But on her goddam computer with a fucking 101,356 decibel mouse!!!!  ("How The World Is Unfair To Me" is slowly being written...)  Cancer and metastasis.  If your cells start dividing like crazy shit, tha's no good.  Tha's one baaaaaad motha-fucka....  Use the Force, Alison!  (Ummmm, okay...?)  PS - visit my fotolog!!!! -->
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In case you were wondering, the reason I am so awesome is that I figured out how to add links and things in the right-hand column over there! Go look! Play with them! Click on the links to instantly transport yourself to faraway websites and funny homepages! Navigate through our fotologs! Check out the stunning comic art and photography that we have created! Be inspired and awestruck, BECAUSE I FIGURED OUT HOW TO MANIPULATE HTML. MUAHAHAHAHA!!!!  In case you couldn't tell, I am very proud of myself. Incredibly, extremely, overabundantly... Mostly it is just because I like to play on my own blog for my own amusement, clicking on the lil' linky-links to websites I have already visited/seen a million times. It is good that I can amuse myself. This is a handy attribute to have, especially if you are fearing nuclear winter, the apocalypse, or isolation in places like the Penn State College of Medicine library.  I found myself pondering a few important things earlier today. One was that Super Mario Brothers 3 for the original NES was honestly probably the best game ever created, followed closely by Bond for N64, Mario Kart for N64, Street Fighter for Super NES, Turok for N64, and Kirby's Great Adventure for the original NES. Getting back to SMB3, I tried to alliterate to that timeless classic by heading my "links" column with the word "warp." Remember all those secret warps to the Sky World (6) and the Pipe World (7)? And the Giant World (4)? Seriously, man. That game rocked the party like nothing else rocks the party. Maybe I'll take the time tonight to dig out my old dusty NES and play a few rounds. The original Game Boy also kicked a lot of ass, especially games like Dr. Mario. But nothing, I repeat, NOTHING, comes close to the genius of Super Mario Brothers 3.   Except perhaps, of course, King's Quest and Leisure Suit Larry, the super old-school versions of the computer games where the only colors were yellow, magenta, and blue, and the artistry consisting entirely of pixelated squares. (See below image.) These were made by the Sierra game company, along with others like Space Quest and Police Quest, games that I played very little, or not at all. However, some of my favorite childhood gaming memories involve these two particular games, Leisure Suit Larry for its obvious naughtiness and allure where children are concerned, and King's Quest because it really is cool. For further inquiries or reminiscence, visit   urlLink http://www.vintage-sierra.com/kingsquest.html . But don't try to take any of the pictures on this website. I attempted to 'borrow' such an image in the hopes of beautifying this blog entry, but was severely reprimanded by the pop-up button.  Visit, right-click on an image, and you'll see...
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    King's Quest: possibly the best computer game EVER.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Uncle Brian's boat, named Loretta C. for my grandmother.  Dad and I took it out yesterday in the harbor for a bit.  It was a gorgeous day...
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    On the docks at Hyannis Marina...
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Sailboats.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Out via the channel from Hyannis Marina.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Me and Brett at a nice party.  I am wearing a nice dress and he is wearing a tie.  Ooooh.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    This is my room in Hershey, all nice and clean.  And very white.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dear Lord, it has been a long time since I've done anything with this godforsaken blog.  Fortunately, I decided to spend this sunny day inside reconstructing my poor, neglected blog.  Thanks to the help of Viv, in between her bouts of PCR and agarose gel sculpting, I managed to figure out how to: post pictures to my blog, update my profile, add the comments sections, and prevent Canada from eternally screwing up my blog's dimensions.  In the meantime, since my last desperate and angstful post, I have: successfully finished my first year of medical school (unless I failed the last stats exam), bought a sweet, sweet digital camera (*very exciting*), visited Cedar Point in Ohio, spent a week in Michigan with Brett, acquired a new, large television for my house in Hershey, packed up my life and driven to Cape Cod via Connecticut, where I visited Uncle Brian and Vivienne, arrived in West Hyannisport with Dad at the mercy of the freezing cold rain, cleaned the house, moved in, gotten a cold, built several fires to keep warm, gone shopping, been called into work in the ER at begging of boss (despite longtime previous doubt that would not actually have ER job this summer), gotten over cold, eaten Four Seas ice cream, watched half of The Fellowship of the Ring, had an interview for a part-time job at Gap Kids, driven to Chatham with Dad and drooled over $$ oceanfront cliffside houses overlooking the sea, thereby coming to conclusion that must pursue some lucrative form of surgical subspecialty, coincidentally met an anesthesiologist at Blockbuster last night who works at Cape Cod Hospital but went to Penn State College of Medicine (introductions prompted by obnoxious navy blue Penn State College of Medicine T-shirt I was wearing at the time with bright blue sweatpants), and watched Mel Gibson's Hamlet.  Plus I ate a leftover taco for lunch today.  Yes, as you can see, things have been quite exciting in my life.  I start full-time work at the hospital June 15, so I have more time to relax before plunging into employment.  Hotchkiss 5-year Reunion up-and-coming June 18-20, needless to say an exciting venture.  Hurrah!  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    She walks tall...
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Max and Bowser
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just returned from seeing 'Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban.'  My verdict?  Very cute.  Along the same lines as the previous two, with same artistic design, same characters, and come to think of it, the same plot as well.  Except that Voldemort (lit. French translation meaning 'flight of death') was a no-show in this one, unless you consider VDM the embodiment of all evil, in which case the Dementors could have been considered as such.  Nevertheless, a very cute and enjoyable, albeit irritatingly likeable.  WHY must it be that I actually  like  the Harry Potter movies?  And not only like, but  really like ???  They really are so cute.  But would my life be so much better if I resigned myself to be a non-conformist in such ways as declaring myself anti-Harry?  Probably not, because then I would be forced to dislike the Lord of the Rings films, and that is one trend you should not be ashamed to conform to.  What is the deal with non-conformism, seriously??  Why do we find ourselves obsessed with being different?  Is it that we really fear the concept that endorsing commercialism is the American way to express individuality?  (Thank you, Bill Watterson.)  Or does it just make us cooler?  Like in the 'You Got Served' episode of South Park: "We Goth kids dance to express pain and suffering.  We are total nonconformists.  We would never dance in a competition.  But yet I am going to noncomform to your noncomformism.  I'll do it."  That being said, I also saw 'Mystic River' last night, which I enjoyed very much.  Which brings me to another point.  If everyone was so anti-conformist, then we wouldn't have things like the Oscars, or cars or hamburgers or even the wheel.  Does that mean civilization is founded entirely on the principles of conformism, that the popularity and adoption of ideas is the driving force behind evolution?  Without going all Darwin on you, I would hesitate to label the occurrence of spontaneous mutations and the ensuing natural selection as 'adopting good ideas.'  But whatever.  J.K. Rowlings just needs to make sure she's got all 7 of the books written before the movies come out.  The movie producers need to make sure they've got them all shot before Harry, Ron, and Hermione hit puberty.  Though it would be funny to see two hulking, surly 24-year olds who need to shave play Harry and Ron, and a Hermione with DD-boobs.  I can imagine it now.  In year 6, does Harry switch to contact lenses?  In year 7, will Hermione miss a you-know-what?  Oh, the suspense!  The drama!  I can see it now: Malfoy driving around in daddy's Beamer with Goyle and Crabb, with the system up and some major bling-bling going on.  Hahaha.  Imagine what would happen if I was in charge of Harry Potter now.  Voldemort would end up to be a villian like Dark Helmet.  Hahaha.  'Spaceballs' is such a great movie...
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    You see, the great thing about science is that, unlike math, you technically can never really  "prove"  something.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     This is what I bought today at the mall.  A khaki coat (which I just realized eerily resembles a white lab coat) and shoes.  The coat was on sale, marked down $80, and the shoes were only $50.  And I suffer from a wardrobe severely lacking in posh city-girl clothes, so take pity on me.  Sometimes it is fun to pretend you belong on 'Sex and the City' or 'Mean Girls'.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Jon Stewart's William and Mary 2004 Commencement Speech   urlLink Will Ferrell's Harvard 2003 Commencement Speech 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     urlLink See more of this sort of thing on Engrish 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink      urlLink Find out.   Image (c) Michelle Au ( urlLink ScutMonkey )  Christ, not a month out of school and I've already resorted to writing blogs about being a med student.  Were it not for the fact that I am unemployed (til Monday) and addicted to playing with this evil, evil, EVIL blog that has probably had the effect of lowering my exam scores collectively by about 503.5 points, rest assured I would not be writing about things as dull as medical school, but rather exciting things like being back on Cape Cod for the summer (hooray!) and going to the  beach  and   eating Four Seas ice cream!!!    But I've already posted pictures of and written about all of the aforementioned, so I must resort back to my once-routine-and-soon-to-be-that-way-again lifestyle.  And seeing that the three people who actually read this blog are either in medical school or grad school (you know who you are...), they can at least understand and identify with my funny albeit strange sense of humor.  (For more of that, check out my  urlLink Post-It art , artfully drawn and inspired by procrastination.)  Anyway, Brett (excuse me, 'Rhett'), the 2004 recipient of the 'Most Likely To Not Be Able To Say Breast Without Laughing' Award, already knows what type of med student he is.  And though I walked away (almost) prizeless from this year's Teacher Appreciation Awards and Student Superlatives ceremony, I can safely say that I, too, am 'the Twelve-Year old.'  (This may explain why Team Brett & Alison won the 'Cutest Couple' award, second only to Patrick and Curtis.)  But seriously.  My philosophy (as a survivor of year I) is that you must have a sense of humor if you are to survive anything, including medical school.  And even if it means laughing at words like "schizont" (much to the confusion of poor Dr. Courtney) or even being as brash and outright disgusting as Dr. McAllister and her Spinburkitt index ("Never date a gynecologist girls.  Don't do it.  StAR is *not* an enzyme..."), then so be it.  There are others less fortunate than we, however, who sadly are not endowed with the ability to laugh at pretty much anything (including themselves).  I used to be the 'Painfully Enthusiastic' med student, but that was before I cleaned up after a man who drank himself into a seizure and suffered the unpleasant side effects of simultaneous regurgitation and defecation.  (God bless whoever is excited to take on that one.)  I hope I don't turn out to be 'the Crier' or 'the Perpetually Enraged.'  My sweet disposition naturally inclines me towards being cheerful and accomodating (I can hear my father laughing in the background...), so I feel confident that even if I did opt to pursue something like, say, a cardiothoracic surgical subspecialty, I would not turn into a PMS-enraged bitch (who is holding a razor-sharp scalpel and someone's beating heart in my sterile-gloved hands).  No.  Instead I strive to achieve my goals with grace and dignity, to become a physician worthy of what we swore in the Hippocratic Oath, all of which is very important and very, well.... Hippocratic.  But I also believe in the importance of  not taking yourself too seriously.   Dedication and diligence will steer you along the road towards success, but enthusiasm, happiness, and good humor will give you the energy to see it through to the end.  "The person who knows how to laugh at himself will never cease to be amused." ~ Shirley MacLaine  Amen, sister.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Taken this evening down at the end of my street, at a place called "the Creek."  See that house in the picture??  Just to the left of the picture, it overlooks the ocean.  One day, I tell you.  One day, I will live in that house.  And when I do, I'll throw a huge kegger for everyone I know.  And it'll kick ass.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    "I Am Better Than Your Kids."  Now a permanent addition to my links.   urlLink Amazing. 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    I *really* want one of these.  Like for Valentine's Day or something.  Order here:  urlLink http://www.tomatoalligator.com/index.html 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    ...at Cedar Point.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Three words: Pink Peppermint Chip.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Here's another house I wouldn't mind living in.  Overlooking the Centerville River.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Ninad (presently in India) and myself doing battle with the "laser pointers" a la Darth Vader/Luke Skywalker.  Skit performed in honor of the recipient of the "Jedi Laser Pointer Master Award" for this year's Class of 2007 Teacher Appreciations Ceremony, Dr. Richard "Dick" Roth.  Very adept at using the laser pointer, he came close to blinding a few students in the audience this semester.  But all in the name of good, clean fun.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As I watched helplessly as an elderly woman spewed brownish liquid fetided with hot dog and bean chunks in the style of Old Faithful earlier this evening, I decided that I really don't like to see people vomit.  I'm sorry, but it just makes me queasy.  I can handle buckets of blood and mutilated body parts, shredded genitals (for those in Sweden who try to stop chainsaws with their "down-theres"), and even, though to a lesser extent, shit and cysts and the smell of urea.  But for some reason, I just don't like to watch people throw up, much less vomit with a force that comes with a large mass and an even larger acceleration.  I feel bad when I see people throwing up, because that has to be the shittiest feeling in the world.  (Why some people are bulemic is beyond me.)  I have thrown up, gotten sick to my stomach, barfed, upchucked, rolfed (ralfed?), vomited, regurgitated, and blown chunks.  And yes, it totally sucks.  But tonight, as I watched this poor woman's vomit headed directly for my face, it was all I could do to gang way.  Once I was taking a man upstairs on his stretcher, and while waiting for the elevator, he vomited with such force that it managed to cover the elevator door five (5) feet from his face.  This event happened right in front of the custodian's eyes, in the exact same spot he had finished mopping not 2 minutes before.  Once I took away an emesis basin filled with blood.  And once someone threw up in our shower when we were having a party.  Apparently, he had had ribs for dinner at Dana, and I'm guessing a lot of EtOH.  I heard from a vascular surgeon that you tend to choose your specialty based on which body fluid you like the most.  He went on to say how beautiful and wonderful he thought blood was.  I was like "Ok, Dracula."  But despite his Anne Rice/vampirish tendencies, the most I thought about it, the more I agreed with him.  I would much rather work with blood, with its clean, metallic smell, than with GI fluids, which include shit and snot and vomit.  I've heard that amniotic fluid smells real bad and stays with you, and purulent cysts, though just dead neutrophils, smell revolting.  I like the heart.  I like blood vessels.  I like blood.  At least blood won't eat away your mucosa and give you peptic ulcer disease, unlike the acid secreted by the parietal cells in your stomach.  I'm sure there will come a day when I won't be able to move out of the way fast enough and will get drenched in vomit.  Hopefully it won't be soon.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Earlier today, I finished reading a book called  What I Learned In Medical School , a collection of essays by medical students who had their own very unique, "non-traditional" stories to share about their experiences during (and for some, surviving) medical school.  Most of the essays were very intriguing and original, and all were well-written.  They each discussed many aspects of medical school that all medical students should recognize, while at the same time, and even more poignantly, highlighting many of its features and hidden challenges that only certain students face: the struggles of identity and acceptance, illness and disability, obesity, "non-conformist" or "alternative" thinking, sexual orientation, discrimination, and the everpresent question of abuse that is inherent and often considered essential to the current system of medical education.    I think my favorite essay, and also the most creative, was one written in SOAP note format about a 3rd year beginning her surgical clerkship at the mercy of the fearsome chief of surgery.  "SUBJECTIVE: Twenty-four-year-old woman presents on her first day of surgery rotation with complaints of anxiety, agitation, and apprehension."  The essay that most left me with a sense of happiness and hope was entitled "Urology Blues," also about an African-American 3rd year beginning his surgery rotation.  His first patient, upon seeing his black caregiver, immediately refused treatment from a "nigger" and dashed from the room, protesting affirmative action and the right for this young medical student to practice his art.  To make a long story short, the result of this encounter brought a realization and an understanding of intolerance and diversity to this student's sheltered classmates, so some good was brought forth from this embarassing and sad occurrence.  I finished the story impressed by this man's open and accepting attitude toward himself and his colleagues, especially given that it is something he has often not received in return.  This is an excellent book, written by people that other medical students can identify with.  It stresses the importance of and need for humanism and compassion, not only on the part of physicians but the entire medical profession and educational system.  Should those who have been in the shoes of their patients be the only doctors capable and willing to give their patients more than just scientific remedies?  Such individuals may be the only ones to fully understand what their patients are enduring, but from their stories, perhaps others can learn to appreciate their experiences and become the sympathetic classmates, teachers, and physicians that are needed in this world.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You know that dream?  The one where somehow you end up in a crowded room (or at school) either partially or completely naked?  I guess I had that dream last night, only I walked into the room half-naked of my own volition.  I am scared to question what this dream might mean.  In my dream, I was having a fancypants cocktail party in my University Manor East apartment (in which I no longer live), and arrived late for my own party.  I wasn't properly dressed yet, so I went into my room and took of my jeans, only to realize that my fancypants clothes were in the closet in the living room.  (Wtf???)  So, oblivious to my partial nudity (apparently though, I was wearing nylon stockings, which I haven't donned since I was 14), I waltzed out into my living room, thinking I would go unnoticed while I searched for the perfect, chic, black ensemble.  I soon realized that most of the people in the room were staring at my nylon-clad derriere.  So I grabbed something and hurriedly put it on and ended up looking like crap for the rest of the night.  WHAT the hell is wrong with me???  Deep down in my subconscious, is this another manifestation of my emotions concerning the approaching Hotchkiss reunion?  Haha, I don't know, even though we DO have a really uppity party to dress the part for on Saturday night.  To welcome myself back to the world of reality, I am going to take my shower and eat Cinnamon Toast Crunch for breakfast.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Me, Dad, and Uncle Brian on the boat today.  (Well, technically we're standing on the dock next to the boat.)
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    A beach rose on a sand dune off the Centerville River.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Today while doing laundry at the laundromat (it sucks not having your own washing machine), I got hungry and decided to drive over to Main Street in search of ice cream, leaving Dad in charge of guarding the clothes from any crazies that might steal my underwear and wear it as hats.  My goal: Ben & Jerry's or BUST.  Being not too familiar with the order of things on Main Street, though having a vague idea of where certain things may or may not be located, I stumbled precisely upon the doorstep of the B&J's boutique, where an open parking spot lay open and gleaming in front of me!  Fate, you ask?  Indeed, say I.  After an embarassing 5 minutes of inching my car back and forth into the parallel parking space, I leapt out of the car and into the store, mindful that my clothes only had about 10 minutes of drying time remaining.  The only thing wrong with Ben & Jerry's is that it is next to impossible to decide which flavor to get.  There are some that I have never bought or tried, like Cherry Garcia and Chunky Monkey, because let's face it: bananas (except when they are in bread) are gross, and pretzels don't really belong in ice cream.  There are some flavors for which I am repeat customer: Chocolate Fudge Brownie and Sweet Cream & Cookies.  There are some flavors that I associate more with pints than actually getting at the counter: Phish Food and Chocolate Chip Cookie Dough.  And that leaves about 26 other delectable and indulgent and agonizing choices.  It may not seem like a huge big deal, choosing your ice cream, because in the grand scheme of things, it's not like buying a house, choosing your college, or deciding whether or not to have kids.  But ice cream is ice cream man, and unless you visit Ben & Jerry's once a day, you'd better make this one count.  I've heard that if you come up with a cool ice cream flavor and a creative name for it, and if the company actually uses your idea, then Ben and Jerry will give you a free lifetime supply of their ice cream!  I have already come up with two clever flavors, though be forewarned: they are of a Gross-Out/Halloween/Garbage Pail Kids nature.  The first (originally devised by my grandmother Pat Helmer) is ice cream with dried cherries and syrup in it, called "Blood Clot."  The second (thought up by yours truly) is chocolate ice cream with peanut butter and fudge swirls in it, with chunks of Reese's Pieces and Peanut Butter Cups throughout.  This one's name?  "Reese's Feces"  I propose that Ben & Jerry's release a new Halloween line of flavors, limited editions, selling this October at a store near you!  Getting back to earlier today, where I am standing in front of the counter, mouth gaping and eyes wide with wonder and rapture.  There is a new flavor on the board: Dublin Mudslide.  The guy behind the counter tells me it is made of Irish cream, fudge, and Sweet Cream & Cookies ice cream.  I say "let's go for it, man."  He is really weirded out by how seriously I am taking this ice cream thing.  But when you appreciate good food as much as I do, you end up striving for beyond perfection.  This quality usually yields disappointing results, as it is truly a rare occurrence when your attempts to achieve divinity are reciprocated.  Dublin Mudslide is one of the best ice cream flavors I have ever tasted and is currently tied for first with Four Seas Pink Peppermint Chip.  Ben and Jerry: I would like to thank you on behalf of everyone in the universe for making ice cream.  And if I do end up winning that lifetime supply, please don't ever discontinue Dublin Mudslide.  And please bring back Cranberry-Orange Sherbet, too.  Thanks.  I owe you one.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am totally stealing these links from Amar's blog, but these are some of the coolest internet interactive game/designs I have ever seen.  Not that I have seen that many, but all I have to say is: WOW....   urlLink 6+=1   urlLink Quest for the Rest   Very, very cool.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     They really need to invent a drink and call it  the Hotchkiss  or, more ironically,  the No-Chance .  I mean, while in my tender young years as a high school senior, I always knew that there would be a free-flowing river of fermented beverages that awaited the fresh college graduates back on the steps of Main Building.  And it was actually funny, when you thought about it, that if you had dared to engage in such behavior (and stupid enough to do it in such a prominent place) you would be immediately and without question expelled, and your name forever erased from Hotchkiss history.  Perhaps that is part of the allure that calls us back to Lakeville, Connecticut, to participate in what is a most striking example of irony and rebellion.  How suitable that we, the Class of '99, was housed in Dana.  How fitting.  If I were a drink called  the Hotchkiss , I would be made of: 2 parts Malibu coconut Rum, 4 parts JD, 3 parts Corona, 2.5 parts NyQuil, 6 parts grenadine, aerate with Lysol Air Freshener, and garnish with a lime and one of those pretty little Chinese umbrellas.  Not to mention blue dye for coloring and an accompanying cigarette and/or bong made out of a Coke can and pen.  Top it off with a dozen donuts to distract Security, and there you have it, my friend.  The most traumatizing event of the weekend, however, was the loss and impending destruction of the English Quad where we all used to hang out, "we all" referring to any or all of the following: Seth, Becki, Amar, Brian, Geoff, myself, Viv, Morgan, Jen, Julie, Izzy, Joanna, Patrick, Yan, Monty, and Ken.  Now it is closed off but visible through a tarp in the wall that stands between us and the growing $19 million Music & Arts building.  Fortunately, we found that if 5 of us contributed $2,000 apiece, we could afford to name a Piano Storage Room or Guest Dressing Room after us.  We decided on the McRotHoDeliAnginis '99 Guest Dressing Room.  If we could somehow pull together $19 million, we would have definitely tried to get the whole building named in our honor.  Alas.  We all opted to pursue careers in fields other than finance.  The most interesting conversation I had this weekend was a very one-sided one with By LaMotte, who spoke about his admiration and support for President George W. Bush and his utter contempt for John Kerry.  It is hard to argue with a drunk Republican, and I decided not to try.  But it was funny.  By: If you are reading this, I suggest you visit  urlLink this site .  You may learn something.  All in all, a great, awkward weekend, expertly planned and executed, and full of fun for the whole Hotchkiss family.  Plus blue and white M&M's.  (Though I am of course now a stark supporter of Hershey's, Inc.  I can't smell Mr. Mars's chocolate in the air every morning on my way to school, now can I???)  In the end, when we drove away from the blinking red stop light and towards the temporary comfort of Chai tea, berry cobblers and whiskey cake, it was definitely time to go.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Flashback:  A long time ago, when I was about 12, my aunt bought me a jean vest from Banana Republic for Christmas, and I was like "what the fuck, man?"  I thought Banana Republic was some crappy store and even though I told her that I loved the jean vest, I really didn't.  Now, even though jean vests are no longer  la mode , so to speak, I am quite the fan of Banana Republic and like to support their fashionable endeavors whenever possible.  Like today, when I bought a pair of "Martin Fit" white-and-black pinstripe size 6 cuffed pants marked down to $43.99 from $88.  I don't think I've ever bought something that was not on sale from there, because I can't afford it.  Come to think of it, I couldn't really afford spending almost fifty bucks on a pair of pants today (nor the $60 New Balance shoes I purchased not 10 minutes thereafter), but I need dressy clothes.  There.  Have I gone and turned into a city girl, despite my current and future status as central Pennsylvania resident?  What will become of me?  Must I wear my new pants to the library, or to a night of closet drinking in UME, or (at best) a night "throwin' it down in HB-Jeezy?"   [Note: Being preoccupied for the majority of the year with heavier and more important subjects like muscles and innervation of the rotator cuff, how to grade and stage a biopsy sample, and generally memorize everything that happens and can go wrong with the human body, all in the pursuit of one day becoming a physician and saving oodles of lives, I think I am allowed to be shallow and ditzy about clothes for at least a few days here and there.  And I really must say, my ass looks great in those pants I just bought today.]    The Present:  This weekend is the Fourth of July!  This is the time when America gets to put up flags everywhere, have huge sales, pay 10c more per gallon of gas, light dangerous explosive fireworks, and barbecue burgers and hot dogs and chicken and eat pie and ice cream and just generally be gluttonous as a way of celebrating the founding of our country.  I need not delve into the irony of this.  It's funny to think of the whole Constitution Crew pulling an all-nighter to write the Declaration of Independence.  If they could've, you know they would've sent someone on a Dunkin' Donuts run.  I worked yesterday from 3-11pm in the ER.  It was one of the first really crazy days of summer that supposedly makes Cape Cod Hospital's ER the busiest in New England during the summer season.  Sounds like something cool to boast about, but when there is a 4+ hour wait, no admitting beds available, stretchers in every available corner of the department, and crazy people walking around naked and swearing, it is not.  Last night was one of these nights.  At the risk of majorly violating HIPPA and being banned from practicing medicine, I've got to say something about one very special lady there last night, who I'll affectionately call Bucktooth.  She had 'em, and also smelled SO incredibly bad and was all bloody and eventually left the emergency room with homicidal tendencies toward me.  It was sad, because she obviously had no idea wtf was going on and was very confused, but belligerent and offensively odiferous.  One of her neighbors, an unpleasantly bipolar gentleman off his meds, called me an ignorant bitch, and later a man-hater.  This was after he called me beautiful, asked me out, and then hit on Niki, another tech.  While driving home that night, I noticed that it wasn't even a full moon.  What's it take, man, huh?  Humor, Alison.  Humor.  Laughter is the best medicine.  Maybe that's why we all died of tuberculosis.   SNL:  I've got to say, it really breaks my heart that Jimmy Fallon is leaving SNL.  He is so funny, partly because he is cute and clever, but mostly because he can never keep a straight face.  It is so endearing when he does it, unlike Horatio Sanz, who is quite honestly not funny most of the time.  The "Italian Cork Soaking" skit last Saturday was funny, though.  I think it would be so amazingly fun to be on SNL.  If I could have any job in the world, I would definitely choose to be a cast member on SNL.  Of course, I would have to suddenly be endowed with the gift of humor, but nonetheless, it would totally rock.  I could bring a lot to the table.  Like my impression of Jan McAllister and her "StAR is not an enzyme" bit.   Something Else:  If you're looking for something to do and are only reading this because you are mad bored,  urlLink here .  This may help.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    It looks like Rupert is doing that funny sideways-turn-and-look-at-the-camera stance that photo subjects do when they're trying all cram into a picture.  The best is when they actually don't need to be doing that, but they are still in that pose.  It looks to stupid!  I have done it, you have done it.  "Oooh, I want to get in the picture!  Let me bend over and stick my ass out sideways and my face as close to the next person as possible!  Let me in!!!!"  Luckily, the camera person managed to capture your ass as well as your face.  No wonder photos make good blackmail.  Rupert is so cute and fuzzy.  Vivienne is also cute.  But not fuzzy.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have only TWO weeks of work left.  Then a week of summer vacation in Florida, then a week of relaxation at home in Pennsylvania.  Then a week of orientation.  Then classes start.  Holy shiite.  WHERE the hell did summer go???  As it happens with any sudden realization of the imminent end of something, I have managed to accomplish absolutely zilch this summer.  Or at least that's how I feel.  Looking back on things, as I think through it logically, then yeah, I have gotten some things done.  I worked in the ER for a few weeks, managed to earn some cash and maintain my learning curve for a bit.  I've reviewed some anatomy, learned some drugs, and helped save a few lives.  I've gone to beach, gotten a new bikini tan, bought a few new choice articles of clothing, gone on the boat, visited with family, seen a lot of movies, and even managed to get my ass up and running a few times.  (Albeit a VERY few times.)  And yet, I still feel as though I have nothing to show for it.  I felt like I've just broken even.  Yeehaw.  But I am really excited to go back to school for several reasons.  The first is that the 2nd year of med school is going to start, which means that I am going to start learning really cool, really relevant things.  We've got heme to gently ease us back into the chilly waters of full-time intellectual exertion, then all our powers will be put to the test as we fall before the mercy of Dr. Zelis' cardiology.  I can't wait.  Another reason I'm excited to head back to Hershey is for orientation.  I'm excited to see the new 1st years, to see their apprehension and excitement, and to wonder whether I was really as terrified as they are going to seem to me in three weeks' time.  Plus two of my Colby pals are in the incoming class.  Third, I can't wait to see my house again and start living with Geneva and Brea again.  And the two new cats!  What did Brea name them, I wonder?  I hope Calvin and Hobbes.  I am so excited to have kittens.  I have recently been whining to my dad about how much I want a dog.  I need a pet in the house.  Something with fur that walks and has lots of personality.  Like Robin Williams.  Fourth, the boyfriend.  Brett, if you are reading this (though I doubt you are), I can't wait to see you back in the context of our psycho lives in Hershey.  Fifth, my desk in the library.  By now I'm sure some nursing student has "claimed" it for her/his own.  Not for long.  Soon it will be mine again.  And covered in post-it notes and crazy books and papers.  Muahahaha.....  Well, time to go to work and make some money and learn things.  Maybe that way I'll get something accomplished today.  Only two more weeks till Florida!
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      About this time last summer, I found myself having some serious second thoughts about starting medical school.  Not the kind that are like: "You are going to fail out" or "No one will like you there" or "This is insane, woman."  They were more the type that questioned whether I was really in my right mind to be streamlining the rest of my life into that path which all eventual doctors follow.  Like that crucial moment atop a slide, the Point of No Return, if you will.  Cause let's face it: once some things get set in motion, they can be hard to stop or put on hold.  I can't take a sabbatical anytime soon...  Last summer I vocalized these thoughts in a sudden two-day span, and convinced myself that it the smart thing to do was to defer my acceptance for a year, and travel to Africa with nothing but a backpack, a Nalgene, shoes, and sunglasses.  And live for a year by working and traveling.  I proposed this idea to Vivienne (do you remember this?), who politely said "oh that sounds like fun but you realize that's insane."  It probably was.  But as my last summer of freedom draws to a close, I find myself wondering yet again: did I spend my time wisely?  Last night I watched two movies, both of which ended up using Paris as a central figure to their plots, both as an happy ending place for rich people who live on Long Island.  Needless to say, the enticements of Paris for rich people are quite expansive: the fancy apartments on Ile-St-Louis, private tours through the Muse d'Orsay, the best and most famous Alain Ducasse food money (or at least reputation) can buy.  But these things--fancy apartments, chi-chi receptions, and premiere restaurants--can be found elsewhere in the world, too.  And these things have nothing on the poor man's Paris: the  Quartier Latin , aimless wandering in through the Louvre, window shopping at La Samaritaine, and most of all, discovering the thousands of nameless  patisseries ,  boulangeries , and cafs that line the streets.  I would say "screw being rich," but the problem is that wealth is needed to sustain any sort of lifestyle in Paris.  Especially if you need a first-class Air France ticket to get over there in the first place.  My God.  How did places like this ever come into existence?  Yes, yes, I'm aware of all the cultural phenomena that have steered Paris's evolution from a little church on an island of the Gaul countryside into a mecca of cuisine, culture, literature and lights.  And I doubt that Americans today would be as fascinated with Paris were it not for the famous expatriots who found themselves in Paris: Gertrude Stein, F. Scott Fitzgerald, Ernest Hemingway... Now it is almost a reliving of the past, or a desire to experience it, or to become it, to eat oysters at  Les Deux Magots  while reading 'A Moveable Feast' or write in your journal on a bench overlooking the Seine.  To embrace someone on the Pont Neuf under a dark sky and lights shrouded by mist.  To order a  caf au lait  and watch the world go by...  Okay.  Let's stop kidding ourselves here.  For one year when I lived in Paris, I woke up every morning to the sound of jackhammers tearing down the building across the street from us.   C'est trs romantique, n'est-ce pas?   There were places in Paris that I was not allowed to go without my parents, notably the Pigalle and Chartres areas, one known for its sex shops and peek shows, the other for its drugs and questionable inhabitants.  Now there are probably as many McDonalds as  bistrots , and for most of my four years there, Notre Dame was hidden by scaffolding.  I would love to watch a scene in a movie where a young, rich couple is lovingly walking down a tiny, deserted Paris  rue , oblivious to everything but themselves, including a small pile of  caca de chien  that awaits them 2 meters ahead.  No director in his right mind would let that scene make the cut in a romantic Paris love story movie--except perhaps the Farrely brothers.  Despite the fact that both movies made me ache to go home to Paris, I remain embittered by how Paris is repeatedly romanticized in films, books, travel documentaries.  There are only so many couples who actually make out on bridges or atop the Eiffel Tower, where it is windy and cramped and nauseatingly sways back and forth in the breeze.  It is lovely to enjoy a view of the Seine from your  5e tage  apartment, but having to take the metro to get there every day makes it more appreciable and more beautiful.  Despite what the movies may say, you do not have to be rich to experience Paris, and if you are rich, this doesn't mean that you will enjoy Paris more.  In fact, you will probably experience it less.  Be original in Paris.  Don't pretend to be Hemingway.  That gets really old, really fast.  And besides, Hemingway practically starved himself while there, partly to heighten his senses and sharpen his writing, but mostly because he couldn't afford it.  The irony is that now, a caf at  Les Deux Magots  costs three times what it would anywhere else.  I guess you are paying for the experience, which is why you see nothing but North Face jackets and L.L. Bean backpacks when you walk by.  This American expat obsession with Paris is ironic given the history of disliking the French for being, well, French, and then childishly renaming all the fries and breakfast toast in the Capitol builing to be more patriotic.  God forbid that France should have a different outlook on vengeful war than our own W-loving citizens.  Does this mean that we thought that France was simply an appendage to America, or that it should be?  Is America invading and taking over?  The new  rsistance  is fearful of just that: that McDonalds and 50 Cent are rapidly replacing the nameless cafes and Charles Trenet.  I am fearful of this, too.  There is a Chili's on the Champs Elyses, and a Ben & Jerry's boutique.  When people complain that America is slowly infiltrating and "revolutionizing" the rest of the world, I think of the irony of how its picking away at Paris, a culture that has fascinated Americans for so long and lured them towards her city's streets.  Next up is that Farrely brothers movie: Super-Size Paris.  I doubt that  le paradoxe Franais  could really take on  le Big Mac .
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       "...then laugh, leaning back in my arms, for life is not a paragraph, and death i think is no parenthesis"  ~ e.e. cummings   "Life is pleasant.  Death is peaceful.  It's the transition that's troubling."  ~ Isaac Asmiov  Last night, on Wednesday July 7th, two people in this world faced death.  An Old Man, and a Young Boy.  One was 62 years old, the other 17.  The unconscious brought into the same room one after the other, beneath bright lights, wires, and countless pairs of gloved hands poking and prodding and touching, invading private spaces irrelevant to the moment suspended, hovering precariously near death, yet clinging and clung to by those pairs of gloved hands pulling back.  The Man's heart stopped to rest, to take a breather you might say, beneath the weight of his massive body, until forced begrudgingly to start keeping time again, after a ten-minute break after a lifetime of endurance.  A rigid tube thrust down his windpipe.  This man needs a breather, too.  The Boy was flying at forty on his motorcycle and fell and in falling, fell unconscious.  Frightening, his frailty and four doctors fighting for him.  He, too, needed to breathe.  Down goes the same tube, in is pumped the same O2 air.  His body is small, his feet are clean and toes perfectly shaped and still.  His teeth have braces on them, and his body shows barely the traces of young hair.  Both bodies, drowning on their backs beneath a sea of snakelike wires and tubes, some filled with black blood, others with cool salty water.  Their arms, dead weight, would fall off the thin bed if not for the doctors and nurses and others tightly surrounding the stretcher with busy hands and purposeful, harried movements.  A clumsy ritual, unrehearsed but still knowingly performed.  Talking, words, cooperation, willingness to help, to succeed.  Smiles even are there, though it is hardly a time to smile, since the wife and the family are out in the waiting rooms, insistent to come in but kept out by those who know that now is truly not the time.  Hours later, the neurosurgeon enters the quiet, dark room, empty but for the peaceful, pink, warm patient lying on his back, head cocked slighty towards the machine that breathes for him.  A nurse follows him, and they begin to test the man's reflexes.  He blew his brainstem, they say, from the hypertension, and then set about their business.  He presses the jagged edge of his keys into the cuticles.  Nothing.  He runs his pen along the underside of the foot.  No toe movement.  He pinches the flesh on the chest with sharp precision and no relent.  No response.  He opens the eyes, whose pupils are wide and black and motionless.  The swick of a dry tissue against the moist surface.  Shooting ice water into his ears.  Still nothing.  The eyes remain motionless.  I want to ask what this means, but I cannot voice the question that demands such a harsh and definite answer.  The Boy's fate is still unknown to me, but something suggests hope despite his expected paralysis.  Earlier, amidst the hurried bustle and noise of the crowd trying to save his silent body, as I held his head, I saw his left eye cry a single tear.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The hydrangea plants in front of our house are finally starting to bloom!  They are so beautiful when they are just beginning to flower: the insides of the blossoms are a light green which fades into white and then into a beautiful periwinkle.  The blue color of the petals is so perfect against the rich green of the huge leaves, and the tiny flowers make up a large, rounded hydrangea blossom.  My camera simply doesn't do them justice.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Earlier on in the summer, when my Sprint POS phone was giving me grief, I made the absolute final decision to once and for all make the switch to Verizon.  Having previously visited a Radio Shack in Hershey, I was assured that I could indeed keep my Florida number and import it to Verizon, all done by their computers in central Pennsylvania.  Upon my arrival on Cape Cod, I immediately raced to the mall's Radio Shack, was showered in good forture by the current availability of an amazing $120 LG phone on sale for only $29.99, and decided to make the switch.  However, seeing as my phone number is part of Sprint family plan of which my mother is the official owner, I needed a) both her consent and signature, and b) to be sure our 2-year contract with Sprint was up.  I was assured by the gentleman behind the counter that they had enough of those phones in stock that if I came back the next morning, I would be able to get it.  Lo and behold, I return the next morning to find that 1) there are no phones left, and 2) I can't switch a Florida number from one server to the next up in Massachusetts.  Apparently, their nationwide digital prowress doesn't apply to the actual services they offer apart from someone in Alaska talking to someone in Fort Meade, Texas with less static and longer battery life.  However, rest assured, they said, the actual Verizon store over by Toys 'R Us store can access the Florida computers to import your number.  Today I went to this Verizon store reputed to be the all-in-one-super-access store and found a phone, of which I could get ANOTHER one for free if I bought it (amazing!), only to discover that no, Alison, you CANNOT do all the Florida-number shit here in Massachusetts or anywhere else in New England or the WORLD.  I even brought the mother/owner of my number to sign it away to me, but no.  NO.  No???  NO.  Not here.  "We can do New Jersey," he bragged.  "But not Florida."  Um.  Okay.  I guess the plan is, yet again, to keep waiting until I go home.  But I am afraid that even once I am actually IN Florida, they may not even be able to do it!  This fear may seem irrational, but given the wild goose chase I have been sent on lately, with my luck, they will probably discontinue this whole "keep your number" dillyo.  Also they will probably socialize health care sometime during residency, but the government will insist that we remain saddled with student loans and refuse to help us pay it off as we work for peanuts.  I want my phone number!  Give it to me!  And don't tell me things that aren't true!  Screw you, Verizon!  Can you hear me now???    GOOD!!!  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think that every time I see a movie starring Tobey Maguire, I fall a teensy bit more in love with him.  I think, however, that he has been genetically engineered to have that sort of appeal, you know, the innocent cute boy kind.  The kind who wears red and blue spandex when he goes out.  Spider-Man 2 was awesome.  I am probably the 50 billionth person to concede that fact, but it was actually really, really, really good.  I remember not really liking the first Spider-Man when I saw it in the theaters.  Maybe it was because I found Kirsten Dunst's character annoying and high-pitched.  Or maybe I just wasn't ready to handle this sort of action flick.  Whatever the case may be, this time I was primed and ready, and I definitely enjoyed the ride.  One thing I noted during the movie is that everyone in NYC was wicked friendly and pro-Spider-Man.  This in an age where cynicism is respected and admired and serves as popular entertainment, such as in the case of George W. Bush and Simon Cowell.  In this NYC, everyone loves Spider-Man despite the media's continual portrayal of him as a menace/terror.  The irony!  The complete opposite of reality, where the media often successfully brainwashes the public a la "Jedi Mind Trick."  So does Mr. Whats-His-Face-Head-Of-The-Newspaper in Spider-Man 2, but luckily, no one in NYC believes him.  All in all, a great movie with a great personal story depicting Peter Parker as a youth split between two agonizing decisions of identity.  And Doc Ock as a proud intellectual yearning to benefit the world, only overtaken by evil machines a la Matrix and forced into devising a fusion bomb that will catastrophically destroy half of New York City.  Obviously the writers went to great lengths to find out new ways of blowing up the world's most famous hostage city.  I also found it ironic that while Doc Ock had the 8 arms characteristic of all arachnids, Spider-Man, despite his namesake, still has only 4.  Spider-Man 3: The Discovery Channel Meets Nip/Tuck (aka, "Peter Parker has 4 more appendages surgically attached").  I can't wait.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Right now, I am embarassed to even admit that I have met David Bouley, chef-proprieter of two of the most fantastic and highly-rated-by-Zagat restaurants in NYC,  urlLink Bouley  (formerly Bouley Bakery) and  urlLink Danube .  Moreover, I'm sure that if he knew what I just did in the kitchen, he would be loathe to admit his knowledge of my existence, much less the intimately close connection we share.  (This "close connection" being that my Uncle Brian does consulting for him and that we've met once or twice and also counting the fact that me and my trusty pal/cuisine aficianado Viv worship him.)  Getting back to my recent personal catastrophe, apparently I cannot even follow a simple recipe for banana bread.  It is simple: no unexpected difficult hand mixing or temperature readings or sniffing to see if the yeast is still working.  In fact, there is no yeast in this quickbread recipe at all!  And thanks to my amazingly wrote memorization skills (painstakingly tried and perfected during my first year of medical school), I can reproduce the entire recipe from memory for you here:   Cream 1/4 cup of butter and 1 cup white sugar.  Add beaten egg and 2 mashed ripe bananas.  Sift 1-1/2 cup of flour with 1 tsp baking soda and pinch of salt.  Add nuts if desired (yes, in my case), pour into greased glass loaf pan and bake for one hour.  Simple.  Easy.  Deliciously banana-y.   AND I STILL MANANGED TO FUCK IT UP!!!!   What!?!?!?  you exclaim.  How on earth did you manage to screw that up!?!?   Well, I just remembered, after the dishes were cleaned and the bread baking peacfully in the 350 F oven, that I added an entire stick of butter intead of just a half of one!  Apparently somewhere between reading step 1 of the instructions and unwrapping the butter, I managed to experience cerebral flatulence, or, to the crude and un-medical layperson, to have a "brain fart."  Dear Lord.  I mean, I'm sure the bread will taste even more delicious now that there is TWICE the amount of butter in it than needed.  Atkins dieters rejoice, because butter, fat, and lard are not the enemy here.  The sugar, flour, and 2 bananas (no fruit! no fruit!) in there are, however.  I'm sure the bread will taste simply deliciously buttery and good.  Again, taste is really not the issue here.  The issue is that my body apparently acted independently of my brain for a few seconds there, or worse yet, that my brain stopped paying attention.  And that, my friends, is not good.  Suppose I become a surgeon.  God in heaven, help us all!  There I am, 137 steps into some poor patient's quadruple bypass, and then (just like the banana bread fiasco) instead of sewing the proximal portion of the great saphenous vein to distal to the 98% blockage of the left anterior descending, I sew it proximally!  I add a whole stick of butter instead of just half!   Aaaaah!   Horror of horrors!!  Next thing I know I just got served (with a lawsuit, that is).  Jeez oh man.  Maybe I am reading a little too much into this.  But seriously: do they make  Beano  for brain farts, too?  Anyway, the bread smells delicious and is turning a lovely golden brown.  Only 26 minutes left to go until I can try my double-fat, brain-fart bread.  Haha.  If it's delicious and I decide to permanently modify my recipe to take a whole and not a half stick from now on, I'll rename it "Alison's Brain-Fart Banana Bread."  And when you think about it, innocent errors aren't all that bad.  I mean, Alexander Fleming discovered pencillin by screwing up his experiments and doing a piss-poor job of keeping his workbench sterile.  As a result, he ushered in the antibiotics era.  And the driving force behind evolution is mutations to the genomic code.  So I ask you: where would we be, then, without screw-ups?  In a land without delicious, buttery banana bread or antibiotics.  And that, my friends, is a world I just don't want to live in.  Later on today's agenda, we'll see how I can screw-up/improve pumpkin cookies.  Stay tuned...
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Reverse the Curse!
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Boston skyline viewed while heading north on I-93.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Tomorrow is my last day of my last summer ever of working here! (Note incredible sadness and despondency in my voice over prospect of my imminent permanent departure.) After four years of working here, I never knew that ER was really called the "Lyndon P. Lorusso Emergency Center." I wonder who that guy is. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I can't wait for neurology.&nbsp; Most people tell me that neurology, unless destiny has you slated to be a neurologist, is nothing short of torture.&nbsp; Memorizing slides of this tract and that tract, this special visceral afferent or that general somatic afferent pathway, not to mention all the delicate intricacies of psych diseases (that  IS  included in neuro, right?) that have seemed to taken hold of us all these days.&nbsp; Mostly, though, I am interested to learn where my brain's sleep center is, how it operates, and finally, why it is that I can sleep upwards of 14 hours straight.  Touching upon what little I know about the human body's sleep patterns, I heard somewhere that you can make up for lost sleep by oversleeping, that in the end, if you sleep 3 hours one night and 13 hours the next, then you average your 8 hours a night, and everything's square.&nbsp; I also heard that this doesn't just work for two nights in a row, that you can be sleep-deprived for a few days, or weeks, or months (say, for example, during medical school), and that after steadily and faithfully "sleeping back" those lost awakened hours, you can get even with Mr. Sandman.&nbsp; I seriously wonder if this is true.&nbsp; Perhaps verification for me comes in the form of an article in JAMA (of which there probably already is one out there), something using big, science-y words that make it hard for me to understand or even concentrate on reading.&nbsp; (My favorite is all those long rants inside parentheses, the ones with italic capital letters and numbers showing references and standard deviations and all that stuff:  GLU-C2.5 SD: -0.13; GLUC2.6 SD': 8.24; R )&nbsp; Maybe that is why, left to my own devices and now with a newly-installed air conditioner in my room, I just slept almost 12 straight hours and still feel like I could go back for seconds.  Let's do the math here: I was awake all day Wednesday, went shopping, went beaching, and then went to work from 11 p.m until 6 a.m.&nbsp; Thursday morning I came home and slept soundly (new AC!)&nbsp;from 7 a.m.&nbsp;to noon.&nbsp; 5 hours.&nbsp; Thursday night I slept from 1 a.m. to noon.&nbsp; Eleven hours.&nbsp; 11 + 5 = 16.&nbsp; 16/2 = 8.&nbsp; EIGHT HOURS!  Mother Nature must have gotten an 800 on the math SAT's. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          &nbsp;   FUCK   FUCK   FUCK   FUCK   FUCK   FUCK   !!!!!!!     I just wrote an absolutely brilliant poem about Four Seas ice cream.&nbsp; It had everything in there from lipids to carbs and even shit about the Red Sox at Fenway Park!&nbsp; I was so inspired because I just ATE some, and for Chrissakes and goddam internet explorer just navigated away from the page I was working on, and I LOST the whole goddam entire fucking thing!!&nbsp; (* Pant Pant! *)   In the grand scheme of things, it isn't such a big deal, and I've moved past it now, but I wanted to artistically capture the fury I experienced in that single moment of realization that I had lost something pointless that I was wasting time working on.&nbsp; I did so by repeatedly typing in the word "fuck" in capital letters and then highlighting them in different colors to make a pretty rainbow.&nbsp; So artistic!&nbsp; And so cathartic at the same time.   
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Today:  I woke up at 10:30 after a pretty sleepless night thanks to the heat and humidity, and felt pretty exhausted.&nbsp; Nevertheless, I hauled my ass to Covilles Beach and enjoyed a few hours of a sunny, slightly overcast day with a light shore breeze.&nbsp; All in all, a very nice day, though I ended up leaving because I think I got too hot.&nbsp; Either that or my halter top bathing suit is whats giving me these headaches by being tied too tightly around my neck.&nbsp; I felt so guilty leaving since it was such a perfect beach day.&nbsp; Anyways, I am still working on the tan, though it seems that only my knees, chest, arms, shoulders, and face are all that are getting tanned.&nbsp; Works for meso long as I dont end up flirting with a melanoma (as Debbie Downer would say).   Tonight: &nbsp;  Dinner with Dad and Aunt Susan, who is in&nbsp;Sandwich for a few days, I guess.&nbsp; The proposed restaurant is Spanky's Clam Shack&nbsp;by the water.&nbsp; I am so sick of eating seafood and ice cream.&nbsp;&nbsp;In fact, I am just sick of eating.&nbsp; I&nbsp;never thought I'd feel that way, but today I do.&nbsp; I think it's because of a certain thing that arrived today.&nbsp; Amazing what hormones can do.&nbsp; Some women become ravenous.&nbsp; Others&nbsp;swear they will&nbsp;never eat again.&nbsp; And some unfortunate few end&nbsp;up being tormented&nbsp;to&nbsp;the point of being bedridden by their evil, hormonally-charged uteruses (uteri?).&nbsp; Then later tonight, hopefully without the unpleasantness of femininity nipping&nbsp;at my heels, I'm shadowing in the ER.&nbsp;  Not  working, which means I get to wear blue instead of green and do things other than empty out old people's bedpans, which is what I did all day yesterday when I was Alison the Tech.&nbsp; When I return home tomorrow morning at 7 a.m., I'll have the freshly installed&nbsp;AC waiting to cool my room down to the temperature of a meat locker so I can actually get some sleep. &nbsp;   Currently Reading:   The Lovely Bones  by Alice Sebold.&nbsp; I started reading it a while ago but found it hard to get into.&nbsp; I probably wasnt in the right mood.&nbsp; I dont like reading books that were heralded as so wonderful and then toted in every females pocketbook at one point (like  The Da Vinci Code , which I confess to reading but ONLY because Mom recommended it, NOT being swayed by societal peer pressure).&nbsp; But I guess that everyone liked  The Lovely Bones  for a reason, including Cedric Bryant, one of Colbys head English professors, who highly recommended it.&nbsp; It is very well written and easy to read (which always seems to prevent people from thinking that its good literature), and also a very interesting topic.&nbsp; I like it very much and am taken in by it every time I pick it up.  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Other books I have read this summer include  Reading Lolita In Tehran , and  The Man Who Ate Everything  (part of it).&nbsp;  urlLink  Lolita  &nbsp;was a very original take on life in Tehran during the revolution and Islamic Rule, written from the point of view of a female literary who teaches Austen, James, Fitzgerald, and Nobokov in her English literature classes in several Tehran universities.&nbsp; What is especially interesting is the class she forms with her prized female students from her university classes, a private book group that secretly meets to read and discuss these works of literature, but also their own lives within their home country.&nbsp; Eventually they relate their own lives to these works of literature, turning to its main characters and topics to help them better understand or analyze their own lives.&nbsp; It was a slow, sometimes uneventful read, at times dry and literary, at other times exciting and an insightful view into the life of an Iranian woman during this time period.&nbsp; (I also associate it with the flavor of Healthy Choice Chocolate Chocolate Chunk ice cream, having eaten it so many times while reading the book.)&nbsp; I would recommend it to anyone truly interested in learning about women in other cultures, particularly to recognize both the similarities that make us all and the differences that render us unique. 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      At about 9 o'clock the other night, a patient's visitor asked where the hospital cafeteria was.&nbsp; I told them that they were about 2 hours late in asking, that the cafeteria closed at 7 p.m. every night.&nbsp; But, I said, the vending machine in the E.R. waiting room has a lovely menu.&nbsp; I love it when I say funny stuff like this.&nbsp; They didn't really laugh all that much, but I felt smug with satisfaction nonetheless.&nbsp; Sometimes I wish I had pursued a career in stand-up instead.&nbsp; But I'm not always funny.&nbsp; Just occasionally when inspiration hits. &nbsp; Anyway, I think I am going to buy  s  u  s  h  i  for dinner tonight.&nbsp; Something that steers clear of heavy food that's acidic or too rich.&nbsp; Raw seafood and rice are nice and healthy.&nbsp; Unless you are worried about all those weird diseases that are uniquely prevalent in the Japanese that you can acquire from eating raw seafood, like  Orientia tsutsugunami.&nbsp;  But I'm not too worried.&nbsp; I have faith that Shaw's wouldn't do that to me. 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dude.&nbsp; What a summer.  The first defining characteristic of the summer--any summer--is that it has to pass by at absolutely light speed.&nbsp; I swear, it feels like I only arrived and began working on the Cape less than 2 weeks ago.&nbsp; And yet, I've been working since early/mid-June... and here we are at the end of July!&nbsp; The proverbial "they" say that time flies when you are having fun, which I guess in this case is true.&nbsp; As is always true of Cape Cod summers (especially ones where I spend my days and nights working at the hospital), early on the going is slow, but suddenly, after oodles of procrastination justified by the endless amount of summer I think I have&nbsp;left, I find myself with less than one week, one day, one hour until I have to leave!&nbsp; It's crazy, man.&nbsp;  Cray-see  like Agador Sparticus would say.   All right, I'll bite , you say.&nbsp;  Where are you going? &nbsp; Well, I am not going to Los Copa with a toothbrush.&nbsp; (How Egyptian!)&nbsp; I am going back to school in Pennsylvania, but only after a week of fun- and sun-filled Florida fun with the family.&nbsp; (Yes, Alison, "fun-filled fun."&nbsp; That's good and not redundant at all.)&nbsp; We are headed to Universal Studios to stay at the  urlLink Royal Pacific Resort , which looks totally kick-ass.&nbsp; The best part, apart from having a divine-looking pool and housing Emeril's eponymous restaurant, is that our room keys double as fast-passes for the park!&nbsp; In the timeless words of Willy Weir, "cake."  But back to this summer.&nbsp; What the hell did I do, anyway?&nbsp; Did I accomplish anything?&nbsp; Or did I just screw around and make some extra cash?&nbsp; Well, time will tell, but judging from where I sit now and looking back on four (4!) years of working in the ER on Cape Cod, I am pretty sure that this was a summer well-spent.&nbsp; For fear of violating HIPAA regs or endangering the careers/medical licenses of certain ER docs, I won't go into too much detail other than to say I got to do a helluva lot more this summer than in the past.&nbsp; I imagine that my status as an actual med student now rather than someday-doctor-hopeful may have had something to do with it.&nbsp; Or maybe it's my quick wit or nice rack.&nbsp; At any rate, I got to do some pretty neat stuff, stuff that I doubt any of my classmates have ever done.&nbsp; (Forgive the gloating.&nbsp; But I'm done now.)&nbsp; For example, yesterday I got to suture not once, but twice!&nbsp; The first lucky gentleman was pleasantly inebriated, so much so that no anesthetic was necessary.&nbsp; He received 23 staples, 8 stitches, and 2 drainage tubes to the lateral aspect of his left upper arm.&nbsp; The second victim of the day was also noticeably buzzed.&nbsp; He received 8 stitches of 5-0 prolene to close the 2 cm, full-thickness wound on the posterior aspect of his right forearm.  What I took away the most from this summer is confidence.&nbsp; Jesus, you say, I  hope  you'd have some confidence, already being a med student and all!&nbsp; Perhaps what I should rather say is that I feel now like I can really do this.&nbsp; Seriously.&nbsp; I totally can.&nbsp; I think I've gotten smarter.&nbsp; My hats don't fit me any more.&nbsp; I don't know what happens to your brain if you work it out, but I would imagine that some sort of anabolic process must beef up your neurons, especially if you don't overload them with caffeine (to which I have blessedly not yet become addicted).&nbsp; Dr. Kohler told me yesterday that caffeine makes you smarter.&nbsp; Given that I don't drink coffee, does this mean that I'm stupid?&nbsp; Shit,&nbsp;I hope not.&nbsp; Just in time for year II.  There was a 14-year old boy who was hit by a car the other night.&nbsp; He came into the ER at 11 p.m. by ambulance on&nbsp;a backboard and a giant splint on his left lower leg.&nbsp; When the splint was removed, the entire inferior condyle of the tibia was visible through the soft tissue, giving me a whole new mental picture to go with the term "open fracture."&nbsp; (Miraculously, I could still feel a strong pedal pulse and the boy could still wiggle his toes.)&nbsp; CT scan later showed a left pneumothorax, which was corrected using a chest tube, and there was an 8-inch full-thickness laceration to the medial aspect of the right thigh.&nbsp; Despite the severe injury to his left ankle, all in all, there was nothing life-endangering to this lucky young man.&nbsp; The worst was seeing just how scared he was, this chubby young kid flat on his back on a hard backboard, his head and body held down by tape and straps, unable to move or do anything but sit back and trust the unfamiliar people helping him.&nbsp; He was scared, and I didn't blame him.&nbsp; I really wanted to just sit and hold his hand, tell him he would be fine, that we were taking good care of him, and that he was amazingly brave.&nbsp; I wanted to tell him not to be scared that he would die, that he was going to be okay, but these are things I didn't know and therefore couldn't say to him or his parents, who later came in to see him still on his back, his foot still splinted up, his head still immobilized.&nbsp; When I saw his mother and father standing over him, holding his hand, rubbing his chest, wiping away his tears, telling him he was going to be fine even though they didn't know that, I imagined how for them, at that moment, nothing else in the world mattered to them but that moment between them.  What an amazing privilege to have been in my shoes this summer.&nbsp; I am still always amazed and in awe of the doctors that work there, and now, more than ever, I want to be one of them.&nbsp; Someday.&nbsp; They tell me to come back fourth year and do a rotation.&nbsp; Others tell me to come back when I'm all done and be their personal physician.&nbsp; Dr. Kohler told me not to come back a bitch.&nbsp;   Ha ha, okay, I won't. 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Where I've been the past few days!
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Me and Alex admiring our catch of the day... (also at Universal)
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink      The HULK.    This is seriously the best roller coaster I've ever been on.  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>