<Blog>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Welcome everybody to my new home...take off your shoes before entering, cause I don't want anyone tracking shit all on my new shag carpeting. First and foremost, I'd like to thank my blog mentor, Cal of www.killacal.net for inspiring me to take this step. I'll hook up a design soon, but for now, my new place will have to remain unfurnished for a sec.   I must warn those who are unfamiliar with my past writings...I TALK BIG SHIT.   I trust that you will enjoy my shit...because it is quality shit. Fantastic shit. The Shit of Legend. You know how folks think their shit don't stink? Well, that's how my shit is. This shit is aromatic shit. It's the type of shit that if you use it to fertilize a garden of daisys, a patch of giant redwood trees would grow out that bitch. High potency, been eating greens and steak kinda shit that makes you have to courtesy flush or put a sign on the bathroom door.  Now that you know the level of shit talk to expect, brace yourself, prepare to laugh, smile, and possibly learn you something that you didn't know before.  P.S. One more thing...Please don't make me have to slap the shit outta you. My pimp hand is made of steel. I've broken three keyboards just trying to type this shit...that's how heavy-handed I am. So don't let it happen to you. 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       One More Thing...   "That's IGNORANT! It's IGNORANCE!" - Michael Jackson  That's the quote for the weekend.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Spring Fever!!!   I got it bad, y'all. Every time I go outside these days, I start smiling like the Kool Ade Man and thinking of happy shit. It's funny how sunny days and 70 degree weather affects my mood so much.  Apparently, my hormones didn't get the memo that I'm a grown-ass man, cause I've been breaking my neck checking out every sexy woman that works in the general vicinity of my job. I blame this on the weather, too. I swear, the office women of the DC Metropolitan Area have stepped up their wardrobe game over these past couple of weeks. I mean, phat asses EVERYWHERE! It must be something in the water here. I can't go anywhere these days without thinking about humping someone. I want to personally thank God for the weather being the way it is...Thank my parents for their good genes that got passed down to me, which has in turn made me the un-fuck-wittable phenomenon that I am...Thank Express, BeBe, Victoria's Secret, Burberry, Urban Outfitters, Ny & Co, even low budget spots like Rainbow and Target for providing the wordrobe that has all kinds of women out here from High Class to Hoodrat looking sexy on their lunch break.  On an unrelated note...two of the "consumers" that are at my job got to fighting today...LOL  "Consumers" = mentally challenged workers...LOL  I know I'm wrong for laughing at that shit...but I'm saying. If you saw it, you'd have laughed, too.  HustlemanL77  P.S.   urlLink Inspirational Words For The Day 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Why Me, Dammit?   For those who haven't heard these before, I'm going to tell my three stories of getting approached by gay dudes out here in DC. Not that I have anything wrong with gay people...Just leave me out of your "lifestyle activities" and we're cool. These took the cake, though.  Story #1: The Gym near Dupont Circle  About 3.5 years ago, I started working in downtown DC and decided to join the nearest gym to my building. The Ballys that I joined is located right near Dupont Circle, which is a part of town with a large, affluent gay community. So basically, 65% of that gym is hot women and gay dudes. The rest are regular straight gymgoers such as myself.   So one day, I'm setting up a curl bar, getting ready to do some standing bicep curls. I've put about 30 pounds on each side, so it wasn't really heavy at all. As soon as I lift up the bar, this one guy with a thin beard down the middle of his chin runs up to me in limp-wristed fashion and says "You OK? You need a spot?"  Now this would have been cool had I actually needed help, but it was my first rep on my first set. Plus, dude was standing so close to me I could feel his breath on my upper lip. I don't like ANYONE in my personal space like that...so I yelled out "WHAT THE FUCK IS WRONG WITH YOU?!?! GET AWAY FROM ME BITCH!"  So dude backed up really quickly, and said "I just thought you might want a spot"  To which I replied "I'll ask you if I want a spot. No get the fuck outta here."  Then some other dude was like "That gay dude was all up on you! I don't blame you for calling that bamma out. I'd have dropped the weighs on that nigga's foot"  Believe it or not, the stories get worse from this point forward...  Story #2: Maurice  One morning, I was going to my job after an early interview someplace else. So since I had some time, I went to get breakfast at The Corner Bakery. There were a couple of cute women working there that particular morning. Once I got my food, I st down and began to eat. Next, one of the ladies working behind the counter came over to my table and gave me a piece of paper saying "My friend wants me to give you this."  I smiled, thinking it was the little Puerto Rican girl with the nice booty working behind the other register. So I the letter and to my dismay, it says "MAURICE" and had a phone number on the middle of the page. I looked up, and the at first normal-looking brother that was cleaning up back there was smiling and waving like a little schoolgirl...LOL. I looked at him, then back at the note, then balled that shit up with a look of horror on my face. I was kinda upset for the rest of the day that the girl behind the counter set me up and didn't warn me that she wasn't talking about the Puerto Rican lady...Sneaky bastard.  Story #3: The Serenade  This story is the worst one. I was coming from the laundromat one Sunday morning after having worked all Saturday night and just staying up to get my clothes clean. While I'm waiting at the bus stop, this old guy who looked like ReRun from What' Happening came over where I was and sat down to wait for the bus, too. The guy was trying hard to make conversation, but I was tired so I kept giving him responses like "Uh huh", "Yeah", Nah, and "Alright."  When I did finally turn and look at ReRun, he looked me dead in my eye snd stared at me longingly. I was thinking to myself "I KNOW this motherfucker didn't just give me a look?!" but since I wasn't sure, I just let it go.   Next he says "Say man...have you ever heard that song by Mint Condition called 'Pretty Brown Eyes'?"  Then the fool proceeds to break out into song, right there at the bus stop. I mean, singing his heart out with passion and conviction. Singing like Tyrese was singing to that bottle of Coca Cola in the old commercial that used to come on. It was the straw that broke the camel's back.   I stood up and said "Motherfucker, are you SINGING to me?!?!"  Dude tried to save face and was like "No...I. uh, wasn't singing to you. I just wanted to know if you knew the song"  For real, he doesn't know how close he was to catching a beat down...If anybody else were out there to witness that, I would have had to hit the guy, just to save face and make sure folks knew that I had nothing to do with that flagrant display of punk assedness.  I hope these amused you all. Hopefully, I won't ever have to update this with another story of being approached in that manner...LOL  Leon/HustlemanL77    
     

    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My Shirt Is Too Big.   I wish I noticed this shit before I left the house this morning. One of my favorite dress shirts is actually too big for me to wear like a dress shirt. Before today, I had only worn this particular shirt untucked with jeans, which received numerous compliments and kudos...Unfourtunately, I cannot wear it as the makers of the shirt originally intended for it to be worn.  As I walked back from lunch today, I was in high spirits. I had just finished snacking on two of the greatest $1 double cheeseburgers ever made by a McDonalds employee. Plus, I was giving pretty ladies the eye as I walked back to the office with a George Jefferson swagger.  Then, all of the sudden to my dismay, I looked across the street at my reflection in a store window. The wind was blowing my shirt up like a helium balloon. I looked like a negro stay puft marshmellow man. With pinstripes. IT was serious...Had the wind really picked up I would have been floating through the air like Farnesworth Bentley in that Big Boi video. Folks would have looked up and been like "That nigga can fly!"  All those women I smiled at and said hello to on the way back to work were probably laughing at me as soon as I passed them...I guess that's what I get for trying to pimp my pinstripe dress shirt on a work day. From now on, I must reserve that one for the weekends or for casual occasions where I want to make folks think I'm grown & sexy. Oh well...Tough titties. Lesson learned.  Leon/HustlemanL77
     

    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       CURRENT AFFAIRS   Not feeling too creative today...but I have to make up for the last couple of half-assed posts I put in here. So I'm going to comment on current events.   Leon On Disney and the Micheal Moore documentary -  FUCK 'EM. They're showing their true colors by not putting that film in theatres out of fear that the big bad Republicans are going to get them...Punk ass bitches.  Sorry for the foul language...Exscuse my German. I'll try to refrain from cursing on my next topic   Leon on the Guatanamo Bay Prison Abuses -  I have no sympathy for these idiots who humilliated the prisoners and had the nerve to pose for pictures...Fuckin idiots. Especially that woman that posed with the thumbs up with a bunch of Iraqi Taliban dicks in her face...I hope they send THOSE folks to jail for awhile so they can see how being a prisoner feels.   Oops...I dropped the F-bomb up there, didn't I? My bad...I promise this one will be clean.   Leon on Bobby Brown standing trial for beating Whitney Houston -  Damn Bobby...I want to be on your side, but come on now...The only hits you've had anything to do with in the past decade, came from your crack pipe. Yet you STAY in the news.   How come my childhood heroes became crackheads?!?!  Favorite baseball player growing up - Darryl Strawberry Favorite boxer - Sugar Ray Leonard(even though he only snorted...but still) Favorte TV Star - Willis on Diff'rent Strokes Favorite member of New Edition - The aforementioned Mr. Brown  I blame Ronald Reagan for all that stuff. I don't know why, but I do. Him and Alan Thicke. 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I know I haven't given folks much to read(or look at) over here lately, but I promise that I will do a better job of it. Thanks to the 5 or 6 people that actually look at this site on a regular basis. You all are the best, and you obviously were blessed with Job-like patience(I think I spelled that Biblical dude right...).  Let me just sum up my weekend...Friday, I hung out with my sister and got a little angry when I overheard some punk talking about how sexy she is and making comments about her body 5 minutes after he was kissing my ass trying to get in my good graces. Little sneaky bastard. I know he was just being a man, but at least TRY to appear respectful around a woman's brother until he leaves or something. I just had to chalk it up to alcohol and ignore it. Hell, I'm sure I've done the same thing to someone else's sister before at some point, so I can only get so mad.  Saturday was a FULL day. I went to the Holocaust Museum, National Zoo, Ben's Chili Bowl, and African American Civil War Memorial & Museum with a couple of my friends from www.kthxbi.com/xmb. It was cool getting to spend a day with folks that I pretty much mainly know from that messageboard and getting to actually talk in depth with them about things. Resha and Hassan and I have had lunch a few times before, but this was the first time we all just hung out for the day.   Let me just say this first...With all due respect, Resha has the Breasts of Life. The Grand Tetons on that woman had me fixated for the first half of our trip...I hate to admit this, but the only thing that took my mind off those things early on was the fact that we were in the Holocaust Museum and it was sad as hell. Had we chosen one of the other places first, it would have been hard to keep my focus off of my favorite member of A Tribe Called Breast. Yep. Resha, A.K.A. Busty Rhymes, could get it.  Hassan is just a cool customer. That's one of the most laid-back, intelligent, and funny people you'll ever meet. It was cool hanging out with him, too. Since he has no ovaries or Reshatits, I'm going to leave things at that...LOL.  I found out that one of my ancestors may have been one of the soldiers that made General Lee surrender in the Civil War. I also saw a friend of mine at the Zoo whom I hadn't seen since 9th grade or so. The only negative from the trip was the fact that I was TIRED afterward. I had to call in from the Club job becasue I knew I wasn't going to have the energy to be alert until 4 in the morning after a busy day like that. Next time, I'll have to plan better :)  Oh yeah...I started taking the protein shake stuff before my workouts a week and a half ago, and I'm starting to notice results already. Fuck around, and in a month I'm gonna be like LL Cool J and stop wearing shirts altogether...LMAO
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Since I see that my sister is now a reader of my weblog, I may have to tone down the subject matter a little bit...Cut out some of the sexual undertones and clean up my language a bit.  Then again, she's grown. So fuck it. I'm not changing a thing. I will, however, dedicate today's topic to her favorite show...Martin.  "Yeah. I had a dream one time. I was climbin' this fire escape, and I couldn't make it to the top. So I climbed through the window of this fly ass crib!. With a big see-thru 'fridgerater. It was full of sammiches! But..., but... I couldn't open the door Martin! So I just stood there and cried man. Oh yeah! Bro'man cried."      Was this great television, or what? I know EVERYONE who reads this has a favorite episode, favorite character, favorite memory, favorite quote etc...  -Remember when Cole damn near knocked Gina unconscious with his crusty-ass toenail?  -Remember when Tommy was in the car accident, and when they found his business card, it was transparent?  -Remember Mymommasbird?  -Remember Mad Dog striking fear in the hearts of everyone hanging out at Nipsey's? "Mad Dog's a comin'...I SAID MAD DOG'S A'COMIN!!!"  -Remember some of the names he had for Tommy? Dome Thugs In Harmony, Heady Murphy, among others  -Remember when Gina gave Martin the ass scuplture?  -Remember when Marin went Nino Brown on everybody looking for his stereo? Had the stuffed Rottweiler and everything LOL  I can go on an on, but I'll let you all reminisce and remember one of the funniest shows of all time in my humble opinion.  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I know, I know...I did an entry on http://www.killacal.net with the a similar title. Since I have my own shitty version of a blog now, I figured it was time to for me to make myself known to my new viewers and folks who haven't gotten to know me yet.  "Allow me to re-intoduce myself, my name is..."  Leon. But I have many nicknames, as given to me by my friends, family, and people who want to kick my ass. Here are a few:   Hustleman  - Cause I run and hustle non-stop on the basketball court   L.L.L.L.(Ladies Love Little Leon)  - My old boss gave me that name LOL. Mainly because I used to flirt with customers in the store and I'm 5'8" tall...on a good day...with Timberland boots on.   Niggerache  - Cause of my musical gifts(or lack thereof). Here's a few samples of songs from my debut album "Music To Dry Hump Your Lady To"  urlLink William Hung ain't got SHIT on me   urlLink The Ralph Macchio Gangster of Love Theme Song    Bad News Brown  - Cause I talk shit like an old school WWF wrestler. Plus, you gotta respect a grown man who would get on the mic in a crowded arena and talk to the crowd like "Shut your mouths you bunch of sorry sharecroppers!" Then kick someone in the head and call it the Ghetto Blaster...LOL   Potty Mouth  - For obvious reasons. I'm working on it, though.   Mighty Mouse  - Another basketball one. Based on my stature and the fact that I do things that I'm not supposed to do out there due to my height.  I know there are more...but I actually have work to do at the job right now. Hopefully you all enjoyed getting to know me a little better. Thanks for reading this entry  HustlemanL77  a.k.a. Ronnie DeVoe of the Internet a.k.a. The Black Phil Collins a.k.a. The Man Sitting Next To The Man a.k.a. Arnold Drummond II a.k.a. Sammy Davis Jr., jr. a.k.a. President of the Black Delegation a.k.a. Governor of Washington, DC a.k.a. Pimp by Blood, not Relation a.k.a. Everyday Avereage Joe just like you ;)
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Loooord, I'm so tired, I'm so tiired, my feet feel like I walked most of the road on my ooown...all on my ooown" - Cee Lo Green on Outkast's "Liberation"  But for real, I could use a good nap. Like that comatose sleep where you wake up and don't even remember dreaming about anything. Ever sleep so good, that you wake up from your nap a few hours later, but feel so well rested that you think it's the next day? That's happened to me a couple of times. I'll look at the clock and be like "9:00!!! I was supposed to be at work by now! Wait a minute...why is it still dark outside?...Oh. 9:00 PM. WHHEEEEEEEEEEWWW!"  Yeah, that's the kind of rest that I'm talking about. I do have to hit the gym for awhile first, though. I have to keep up this routine. I'm looking like Michalangelo's "The David", only with a smaller head and a bigger johnson.   That reminds me of a story...I had this African professor named Ampofo-Anti for my Introduction to the Arts class. He would always get upset at how European artists from Greek times all the way up to Picasso would be "influenced" by African art and incorporate these styles into their own are which would then be revered. All the while the original African art and artists would get none of the credit or respect. He's always go on a tangent and say shit like "The Europeans. They  STEAL  and they  BASTARDSIZE OUR ART!!!  They fear the srong black man. That is why they make the penis and testicles so small on their scupltures. They did not derstand the physical superiority of the black man, so they feared it and praisedthe opposite in their art!"  Then a year later, I had his sculpture class. He would comment of people's art with his thick West African accent like "This sculpture...It is like a cow with no balls. It does not PRODUCE. YOu must make your art PRO-DUCE!!  Man, Ampofo was cool as shit. I have to visit him this year at Homecoming.   
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What can I say? This weekend has been great. For starters, I finally replaced my stolen cell phone with a better one. I still haven't gotten around to using all the little features this bad boy has. I feel like a little kid with a new toy right about now. I've been taking pictures of all kinds of dumb stuff with it just because I can...LOL. the only drawback is I lost so many phone numbers when the old phone was taken, that now I can't reach most of the people that I know unless I run into them somewhere or get their numbers again from someone else.  Saturday at the club was super busy, but it was cool becasue I ran into my boy Taz, whom I used to study king fu with. He told me about the barbecue our teacher from Hampton had lined up for Sunday and invited me to go. That cookout was great, because I really missed hanging out with Taz and Phil, our Sifu(teacher).   Let me tell you all about Phil. Phil is like a 5'6" lightskinned whup-ass machine. That brother looks mild-mannered, but if you test him and make him hit you full blast....you WILL get lifted off your feet and end up on your ass somewhere. He's cool as shit, though. You'd REALLY have to push Phil to the limit to get him to lay hands on someone. But if he does lay hands on someone...God bless that poor motherfucker, cause dude is fully capable of breaking every bone in your body twice LOL.   The biggest development is that I am starting my training back up again. I've been keeping myself fit, but this is going to take things to another level. I'm ready for the challenge, though. Other good developments from Sunday are I got to see one of my old crushes from Hampton again over there. She looked good in school, but now she looks fan-tastic. Had a brother about to holler like Pharrell, talking 'bout "GOT-DAAAAAAMMN...WHOOO-O-O-OOO!!!!....WHOOO-O-O-OOO!!!!". I maintained my dignity this time, though. I also got my best friend E ready to train with us. If you all can't tell, I'm excited about it.   Met some more Hampton folks this weekend throughout my travels...so that was cool. I'm getting ready to go to a cookout shortly. It's been raining and drizzling all day, but the man throwing the cookout said "I dropped $300 on this. THERE WILL BE A BARBECUE." Hell, you gotta love that attitude. It's actually looking sunny outside now, too. Hopefully things will work out, cause dude is real cool. I guess I'll talk to you all later. Time to go do the barbecue sauce thing :D
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I need to make another entry, because I am tired of looking at that picture of Marques Houston's punk ass every time I come here LOL. The problem is, I didn't think of a subject before I started typing. You all know that never stops me from making miscellaneous rants and raves...So here goes another one.  Who would have thought the combination of chicken and feta cheese would tase SPEC-TACULAR! I ordered a medium pizza with that on it, and another one with pepperoni and sausage(for my swine-addicted cohort in the other room). The aforementioned chicken and feta pizza was some good stuff, though. I was very tempted to run out into the street and sing it's praises for my ghetto bretheren whom may be outside and hungry. I then decided that sacrificing my dignity over a slice of pizza was really not all that cool. I may as well be dancing for popcorn chicken like M.C. Hammer back in the day. Not that there's anything wrong with popcorn chicked, cause there isn't. Just don't resort to coonery in order to get your point across.  Speaking of coonery, here's the interactive fun for the day: We're going to play the Magical Negro Game!  This is the game where you name off your favorite magical negro from a movie or TV show. It's a staple in Hollywood moviemaking, so this should be easy.   Magical Negro = Black character who is either subservient to the main ones, a buffoon, or the  mysterious one who leads the white main character to the ultimate answer, truth or dignity. I shall give a list of examples below. Feel free to add your own and join in the fun!  Bagger Vance = Magical Negro Steve Urkel = Magical Negro in suspenders Morgan Freeman in Driving Miss Daisy = Magical Negro Radio(for that matter, Cuba Gooding Jr himself) = Magical Negro John Coffey = Big ass muscle-bound Magical Negro Meshac Taylor on Designing Women = Effiminate Magical Negro Webster = Pint-Sized Magical Negro Thirst from the Sprite Commercials = Little Plastic-Ass Magical Negro The dude from Finding Forrester = "You're the man now, Dogg" Magical Negro The dad from Moesha = Nappy Head, Flat Top Magical Negro Slick from the old WWF = Pimped out Magical Negro Huggy Bear = Snitch-Ass Magical Negro  Special thanks to my boy P for helping compile this list    
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What's happening everybody. Hope everyone is having a good day. If not, I'll try to brighten it a little if possible.  First off, let me comment on this photo right here for folks that haven't seen it yet...Marques Houston, WTF were  YOU  thinking?!?!    That is quite possibly the corniest, tackiest, fruitiest, most J.J. Evans-ish outfit I've ever seen. Whoever his stylest is needs to be fired, then banned from ever picking out clothes again. Who in the hell comes up with the idea of making a tailor-made suit out of your grandma's plastic slipcover from her favorite couch? I mean seriously...I'm sure this was in California, too..So that fool was probably sweating like Patrick Ewing at the free throw line in the 4th quarter. Suit probably got all sticky and irritating...He should have just went hard and wore the same boxers and wifebeater, only this time put on a robe, some house shoes, and some black church socks. Now going to an award show like that would have been gangsta LOL.   Since I mentioned Jimmie Walker in the second sentence above, let's talk about Good Times real quick. That show was wild, because something messed up happened to them EVERY episode except the last. Then all the good shit happened all at once LOL. J.J. found a steady job, Thelma's sexy ass got knocked up by Keith(who by the way, signed a big ass NFL contract in the episode), Michael came out of the closet(ok. That didn't happen. But I'm saying...), Florida  and  Willona moved up out the projects and into the same exact building in the good part of Chicago, Penny showed her titty at the Super Bowl, Bookman continued to be a cheap ReRun ripoff, SweetDaddy was still pimpin hoes, all the while James Evans Sr. looked down at everything from heaven and was like "Why the fuck did they have to kill off my character before all the good shit happened?." All of this in one episode.  It provided plenty of television history...  Greatest Black Dramatic Moment EVER - When James died and Florida dropped the punch bowl yelling "Damn...DAMN... DAMN!!!    Oddest Sex Symbol in TV History - Jimmie Walker. J.J. got much ass back in the '70s. The only funny looking cat that was pimping harder than him was Rudy Ray Moore(Dolemite). Oh yeah, Yappet Kotto is a strange, distorted looking motherfucker, too.  The Most Unsung Musical Genius of the 20th Century - Michael Evans...LOL. His rendition of "Rock You To Your Socks" was sheer...Crap. Ok, I tried to play along with the Michael thing, but I can't. Michael Evans was the Ambiguously Gay member of the Evans family. I heard his sweet ass is working as a fashion consultant for Marques Houston nowadays.  But enough random trash talk for now...I'll try to be more focused next time I post in here.  Leon
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I know blogs are supposed to be in chronological order, but I'm writing today about something that happened last week.  What? It's  MY  gotdamn blog. If you don't like it, you can getthefuckout(to paraphrase Eddie Murphy's dad on "Raw").  Last week, I had a life-changing experience teach me a valuable lesson. Sometimes you really do have to buy name brand shit. The generic versions of stuff will not always get you by.   For years, when I'd buy grocery and household stuff, I'd always get the cheapest version of a product that will still get the job done. Sometimes I'd slurge and get the "Downy" fabric softener instead of the "Xtra Fresh" store brand...but most of the time I wouldn't care. Thafuck I need some $2 Bounty paper towels with floral patterns on them, when I can get the Giant brand for like 75 cents. So the paper towels will be a little thin and crispy...Who cares. It's not like I was going to wipe my ass with them(unless I ran out of el-cheapo toilet paper and was in dire straits).  So last week, a lot of rainstorms came through the area. I was prepared, though. I had my umbrella that I bought at the value store for $1.50. I felt like the man, beacause everywhere else in town wanted at least $8 for one of those compact umbrellas.  When the rain hit, I put up the umbrella and was chillin. Not a drop got on me. I was c-walking on Mother Nature's face. "ON TOP OF THE WORLD, BABY!!!" Dryer than a sonofabitch.   So when the rain stopped, I tried to put the umbrella down, and upon doing so, half of the little thin metal rods holding the thing together snapped and popped loose. On the other side, one decided to stay up and poked a hole in the top of the umbrella. Of course, as soon as this happened, the rain picked up again. I had to think fast. My almost made it to Boy Scouts/Ghetto MacGuyver instints set in. I opened what was left of the floppy remains of my umbrella, took out some tape(thank God I chose that day to steal office supplies with my gym bag), and ripped off a branch from a nearby tree and temporarily fixed the wobbly side and hole. I made it two blocks with that contraption before it fell apart and I got rained on again...LOL.  So the lesson from this, my bargain shopper readers: You just can't buy generic alternatives to certain items. Here is a list of a few things that I recommend you don't short change yourself on:  Umbrellas - See story above  Shoes - Because I will make fun of you if you wear a pair of skips around me.  Deodorant - Buy a name brand, especially since it's the Summertime.  Underwear - Again, if I see a woman wearing bloomer panties around me, I'm clowning you even if you are sexy.  There are more thing to add to this list, but I am stopping it here because I am hungry and a McDonalds Steak Egg & Cheese bagel is calling my name from down the street. I hope you all have a great day, and thanks for reading.  P.S. LEAVE COMMENTS! I like knowing more than 2 people look at this thing. Thanks :)  
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello all my wonderful readers out there in cyberspace. Today's topic is Amazon Beast-Women. First off, let me clarify things...I don't have a problem with tall women. Or big women. Or even tall, big women for that matter. You all are cool as far as I'm concerned. My problem is when you see a vertically-challenged dude like myself(5'8") and try to assert your dominance over a motherfucker.  I have two stories. I'll start off with last night. A couple of ladies I know were celebrating their birthday, and we all met up at a strip club to drink and look at women do ungodly acts like making baseball bats fit in places that you would not believe...LOL. So when I'm coming through the door, I see my old barber in there. We talked for awhile, and I remembered that he frequents grimy spots like that on a regular basis. After that, everybody sat down, drank, and chilled.   Then, this HUGE 6'3" stripper comes onstage to do her act. When she needed someone to take onstage, guess who she chose. Yep. The 5'8" nigga with the office work clothes on who was trying to play the background. So I tried telling her that it was the girls' birthdays so that she would go after them, but she was like "Nah nigga, I wat YOU up here!" She pulled my arm so hard, I had flashbacks to being a child and having my mom pull my arm like that just before I'd get an ass whupping LOL.  So she grinds on me, then literally puts me on my back on the floor and took of my belt. All the while, I'm like "This chick is REALLY holding me down with one hand!" All awestruck and shit...LOL.   The emcee knew what was about to happen. HE was like "I hope you have a pair of clean draws in the car". I was thinking to myself "Why would he say this?" Then I found out. This bohemoth of a woman put both of her hand on the small of my back, and ripped a giant hole in the back of my boxers  with her TEETH!  At that point, I was thinking "Oh shit! This bitch is gonna take my booty, jailhouse style! Someone help me pleeeeeeeeeze!!!" So since she was on top of me, I had no choice but to lay there while she put a cup of ice on my ass, licked my ass crease, rolled me over and put her mouth on my johnson through the part of my boxers that was still intact, and then let me up. It was funny as hell, but at the same time, I was thinking that this woman could very well beat the living shit outta me if I pissed her off.  Afterwards, I found out that my barber set me up and told her to pick me to go onstage...LOL. He said he wanted me to have fun to repay me for some good advice that I gave him last year. It was funny, but I'm gonna get his ass back. I don't know how I can top that prank, but I will somehow.  The second story is my WNBA one. I was at this dive bar in DC that I go to from time to time...  Actually, I go there more than just from time to time. My picture is on the wall in that bitch, so I'm like the Norm Peterson or Cliff Claven of that bitch. But that's neither here nor there. One night, around 11 or 12, about five 6 foot tall and over ladies roll in there together. They're looking all masculine and thugged-out...I even think one had a goatee and pork chop sideburns pencilled in. The ringleader was the biggest one. She looked like Karl Malone with a perm, all diesel on some Arnold Swartza-nigga shit. She had a fine girl with her though.  So then in walks Chamique Holdsclaw from the Washington Mystics with another 6 foot woman. It's then that I realize that these must be WNBA players, or at least the folks that they practice against. When Chamique walks over near where I am and goes to the bar right in front of me, Karla Malone decides to slap her on her ass really hard with her big, ball crushing man-hands. So naturally, she looks at me like I did it. Then the four that were at the bar who didn't see anything but heard the slap all turned at me and looked at me like they wanted to take it outside. I had my hands in my jacket pockets at the time, so I said "Don't look at me. My hands are in my pocket."  That's when Karla Malone started laughing and gave her a hug telling her it was her. I was like "Let me get the fuck out of here before these big butch bitches try to kill me again." Now, I don't hit women, but if Karla Malone or any two of the others had attacked me, I might have been able to handle myself and whup that ass. If I had to fight all seven of those big 6 foot tall, husky, bench-pressing, chest hair-having, Macho Man Savage looking chicks, that would have been my ass. I would have lost my dignity, my self-respect, and most likely all of my teeth and the use of my legs LOL. Thankfully, it didn't come to that.  So nowadays, I'm drinking milk and working out in a effort to overpower the next WWF wrestler looking woman who tries to manhandle me. I might have to hire a female bodyguard or some shit like that LOL. Wish me luck everyone.  Leon 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What's happening, my wonderful blog reading folks out there. Hope everyone had a great weekend. Mine was cool. It put me in the mood to entertain you all today with another glorious entry into this very blog. Allow me to touch on a few things that went through my mind on the Metro train ride over here this morning.  I'll start things off with this one. A friend of mine named Mailaika(don't ask me how to pronounce it, cuz I've known her for a year and still mess it up) pointed out something for me about a week ago which I've found to be true. Brandy really looks like a Cicada. Look at the evidence, people. These first one is the current cover of Vibe magazine, and the second is her without her makeup from the Norwood Family Reunion:     I rest my case. They even pose for pictures alike.  Why the hell does the banana I'm eating right now have a sticker avertisement on it for "Garfield The Movie"? Have they NO shame?!?! I can see if it was in the newspaper or something...but please don't advertise your movie on my produce. Some things should just remain sacred and untainted.  Speaking of untainted, I learned of the existence of a almost 22 year old virgin(and a good-looking one, at that). That's like discovering a living sabretooth tiger or wooly mammoth...You know they existed once upon a time, but you thought they were all extinct in this day and age LOL. I commend that beautiful young lady's willpower to avoid giving in to the caulk.  Ronald Reagan. Aww fuck it. There's enough on the news about him right now, so I'll leave that alone.  One more thing before I go...One of you blog experts out there, PLEASE help me figure out how to allow people to sign this blog and have their info visible as opposed to signing it anonomously...Send me a link to somewhere where I can copy & paste the script in here, or just tell me how to do it. Thank you :)  Leon       
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't know if I ever told you folks this, but my part time job on the weekends is doing security for this club in DC(which shall remain nameless). So I am officially the World's Smallest Bouncer. It's cool, though, cause I'm stronger than I look, plus I fight dirty LOL.   Just playing about that last sentence. I actually haven't had to slap the shit outta anyone there yet. I just use my communication skills to manipulate the people in that club into doing what they are supposed to and behaving. That's neither here nor there, though.   Last Saturday was particularly annoying...I had to throw out some loud-mouthed big dude with an open shirt and six thin-ass gold chains on. I guess he figured that 6 little gold chains = 1 big ass gold chain. Either way, the brother looked like the type of guy you'd see behind the counter in pawn shop in the heart of the ghetto. At least that would somewhat explain the tacky jewelry...Then after that, some skinny drunk motherfucker decided to say something smart to me when I asked hom not to block the path of the waitresses. So I kinda bumped his ass over the next time a waitress had to pass through...That felt good, but I he did a very good job of pissing me off earler. To top off the night, I saw a dude literally get a hole kicked in his head outside the club in plain view of the police. There was so much blood that somebody came out there and hosed off the part of the sidewalk where that shit happened. Dude lived, but that shit was CRAZY. It's fucked up, cause it was the guy's own fault that he got his ass whipped. He went and took his drunk ass ovre to swing on somebody and missed badly. Unfortunately for him, the other guy didn't miss. That shit looked like when Deebo hit Red with that uppercut in Friday. The dude was lifted off his feet.  So after the crazy night, I got my paycheck and left. Fast-forward to yesterday around noon. I went to Bank of America to cash the check, since I use that extra money to put to my phone bill...Well, when I gave the lady the check, she told me that they don't have enough money to cover that bitch in their account. So I said "But it's only $65!"  The teller then said, "Yeah, they seem to have this problem a lot"  I couldn't believe it. I'm at this club, risking bodily harm to keep the peace...and the check they gave me bounced like a basketball. The motherfuckers in the back started doing And 1 tricks with the check...Bounced the shit off my head, ally ooped it to a motherfucker, then threw a no-look between the legs pass through the teller glass and back to me. The lead teller took the check, bounced it between her legs about four times real quick on some vintage Tim Hardaway shit, then bounced it between MY legs and made me fall down.   Well, at least that's the mixture of shame and anger that I felt when I realized that the check was rubber. The teller told me to ask them when would be a good time to cash it, then go immediately to the bank LOL.   I was like "Fuck it...If they're going to shit on me, at lesat I'm going to get some perks out of it." So I took my black ass to the club last night since I have today off, then proceeded to go straight to the kitchen and get a free dinner, then hit up the bartenders that I'm cool with for free drinks all night LOL. That's the least those fuckers could do for me after setting me up like that. I spoke to my favorite bartender there about it, and she told me that she's walking around with three checks from the club in her purse since the same thing has been happening to her for a minute...LOL.  Either way, I feel that my days there are numbered. So folks, if you want free passes, you better hit me up soon while I still have the hookup...and before this check thing makes me fuck around and burn bridges LOL  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Don't you hate it when you run into somebody, and that person remembers you from somewhere, but you have no fucking clue who the hell they are or how you know them? That happened to me today.  It's about 5:15 in the afternoon...I'm leaving the metro station on the way to the gym, and I see this woman with dreads staring at me. As I was getting ready to pass her, she yelled out "Leon!"  Now the first thought in my mind was "How the fuck does this person know my name?" Then, my second thought was "I hope I didnt meet this person hanging out drinking with my friends in the city and just never called her ass." The next thought was "Let me play along and see if something comes back to me."   So as I awkwardly made small talk, she mentioned someone from Hampton. I was like "Ok, this narrows it down a bit...I know her from school, but from where...and how?" Then I thought "She knows John...wait a minute...THAT'S IT! URETHRA! I HAVE FOUND IT! THAT'S THAT CRAZY BITCH AUTUMN'S ROOMMATE!" After that, I was able to kinda ease my way out of the conversation and get to my workout.  This girl's roommate used to flirt with me all of the time...All the while, she had a boyfriend that lived two doors over from me in my dorm(yet, my black ass had no idea). Ole girl was sexy...but one incident turned me off and made it impossible for me to ever look at her the same way again. She was doing her laundry one night when I was visiting her room, and we went down to the laundry room. She left her clothes down there for like an hour and a half, but when she saw that someone had taken them out of the washer and put them on top of it, she went OFF. Started cussing like a sailor...or better yet, cussing like a comedian on Def Comedy Jam. "Fuck that bitch" this, and "She's gonna pay for that shit" that, and so on and so forth.   So she gets her bottle of bleach, walks over to the machine, and pours bleach in with this poor woman's color clothes. when I saw this, I had to grab her arm and ask her "What the fuck is wrong with you? Are you crazy?"  Never call a crazy person crazy.   She then proceeds to go on anothther cursing fit and literally throws her semi-wet clothing from the washer into a basket and goes upstairs. She is so lucky that I am not a snitch, because I found out that it was one of the women's basketball players who got their stuff all messed up. The B-Ball player would have beaten her ass up and down the dormitory...All I know is, my visits to her dorm room ended that night.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's a pretty damn nice day outside...I think I may sneak out and make my return to the basketball court. this will end my retirement # 4. I'll let you all know tomorrow if I break any ankles, or get dunked on LOL.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tomorrow and Sunday = Death By Swine  I am making a point of going to the National Capital Area Barbequefest this year. Last year's event was great. You could smell barbeque sauce and grills from about 3 or 4 blocks away. It was beautiful. for someone like me who loves barbecue ribs, it was like going to the promised land. I'm excited.   That means I'll have to make up for all of my barbequed indescretions this weekend and next week in the gym, but it'll be well worth the extra work.   VIVE LE BAREBEQUEFEST!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Someone called me "niggerish" yesterday.  I was telling her about my experience this past Friday when my phone lost power after hanging out with some friends. I was in the middle of a residential part of DC on 18th Street, with nowhere to charge my phone. Mind you, I'm desperate to get that thing charged, because a beautiful bisexual lady friend of mine left me a voice message telling me that she wanted me to go with her and her friends to a strip club and drink with them. As soon as I got this  hour-and-a-half old message is when the battery died.   Murphy's Law like a motherfucker.  Then, God leaves me a sign that he likes lesbians, too. I look over at the building that is the headquarters for planned parenthood and see that over behind their flowerbed is an outdoor electrical outlet. So me, being the guy that I am, I go up the steps, climb over the side rail, plug in my phone to charge, and sat on the balcony smoking a cigar that my boy Vince The Cigar Man gave me a week ago.*    *Note:I am not a smoker(those cigars are the only things I seem to be able to tolerate), but this was cause for celebration! I was about 10-15 minutes of charging away from drunk, naked Hot Lesbian Action.  Folks walked by and looked, and I looked back at them...sometimes waving...sometimes even engaging in breif conversation. Once I got the feeling my phone was done, I called my friend back, only to realize that I was too late to make the trip out there. Oh well. I decided that knowing I could get away with charging my phone at the planned parenthood building and making the friends that I did sitting on the steps smoking was well worth the missed opportunity. There will be more H.L.A. in the future. Until then, I'll just have to stay prepared and notice where ALL outdoor electrical outlets are.    Now I ask you, was climbing a rail and plugging my phone in the electrical outlet behind the flowerbed at the Planned Parenthood building niggerish in your opinion? I like to think of it more as "resourseful."  Leon 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Since you all seemed to like my Brandy comparison the other week, I thought to myself "Maybe other people notice the same shit I do"  Today's thought is one that I noticed a few months ago...I think Lloyd Banks and Craig David are the same person. Think about it...you NEVER see them in the same place at the same time. Plus, Craig's last album didn't do too hot over here in the states. I think he got pissed off, streched his face out a little, put some bass in his voice and decided to go hard, rhyming about the shit he saw on the mean streets of Manchester, England(or wherever the hell he's from). Judge for yourself:         Let me know what y'all think.  :)
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I love my momma to death, but I don't know if I can forgive her for dressing me up like this when I was a baby...       What in the hell possessed her to put me in that Black/Puerto Rican Buddy Lee outfit?!? I'm still kinda bitter that this Kermit The Fag looking photo even exists. She shouldn't be suprised about why I used to fight all the time back in elementary school. You know I had to be ready...You send your kid to school overly dressed up on some Farnesworth Bentley shit, don't be suprised when them niggas line up at recess to kick his ass. I had to fight back then LOL.  Let's fast forward a bit...Up until January of this year, I lived in a pretty rough area of Southeast DC...Right near the intersection of Martin Luther King Ave. and Malcolm X Ave.   Now you KNOW shit is rough when you live near TWO streets named for black people who got assasinated...LOL.  So anyway, my ex girlfriend used to go shopping with me sometimes, and constantly try to get me to buy some Wayne Brady-esque metrosexual-ass clothing to make my wardrobe more "funky." I would look at her and be like "I'm straight...you know this. Dahell I need to look 'funky' for?" Sometimes the stuff would actually look good on me and I'd get it. Other times, it would be just plain ridiculous.   Like she would constantly insist that I get some sandals. To which I would usually reply "You've seen my feet, right?* Besides, they're not practical in the hood."  She would dispute this, but I had to break it down to her...When you live in an area infested with drug dealers, where you witnessed 3 high speed police chases  right past your house in the past month, and where there are more than a few negligent dog owners...You don't want to wear any shoes where you can't effectively run for your life in. I'll be damned if I get fucked up trying to look like some nigga at a Will Downing concert.  So the moral of today's post(before I go off on another tangent) is: It's cool to be stylish and have your own look, but when you live in a rough area, you don't want that look to set you too far apart whereas you bring unnecessary attention to yourself or hinder your ability to whip a motherfucker's ass or run your stankin ass away from trouble.  Hustleman  * Note: My feet are not horrible, but they are not pretty either. It's not like I have crusty, ashy Jesus walking the Earth barefoot for 40 days and 40 nights type of beat up feet. They are just a little sub-par in my opinion. So rest assured the ash is not of Biblical proportions, I do not have Hammertime, and I cannot stop cars with my feet like Fred Flintstone. I hope that calmed some of your fears.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...last week fucked around and had a triple-double"  I just got through busting some dude's ass on the court. Too bad my team lost all three games by one point each...But I was truly an un-fuckwittable force of nature out there LOL.  Just thought I'd share that real quick. Now let me get back to stretching and putting a bandage on the blister I now have on my left big toe.  Hustleman
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Due to a conspiracy and the treacherous conspirators that conspired against me, my 4th of July travel plans have fallen through...  It's not necessarily a bad thing, though. I'll have more time to rest. Plus, I already have the weekend off from my part time jobs, so I need to find some parties/cookouts to attend.   I was pissed last night, though...I had to take out my frustrations by writing a play. Not any ordinary play, but one of those black plays that make the rounds on the Chitlin Circuit, starring some past-his prime actor or singer. Mine is entitled "Yo Legs Too Short To Slap-Box With Satan."   It's about a young man's struggle to overcome the white man's opressive society, all the while figuring out how he's gonna pay the rent so Big Momma won't get evicted and also prove his love to the finest woman in the neighborhood, Corolla Jackson.  I have already begun the casting process. Take a look at some of the stars I have in mind for roles.  Kel from "Keenan & Kel" as Enron Hodges  Tatiyana Ali as Corolla Jackson  Kim Whitley as Big Momma...who is 7 years older than her son Enron  Jeffrey Osbourne as Uncle Melvin  Fredro Starr as Clarence  Tracee Spencer as LeTegra  Alexander O' Neal as Pastor Elton Cash   Lou Bega as Hector the Pimp  SWV as Hector's "Whore Thugs N Harmony" stable   Adebesi From Oz as...The angry Inmate who tries to fuck Enron in prison  Lil' Zane as Prison Bitch #3  Stoney Jackson as O.G. Big Dookie Loc  MoKenStef as the tellers at the check cashing spot  The Bass Dude in Boyz II Men as The Voice of God  Joey Lawrence as Whitey  Ronnie DeVoe as Singing Bus Stop Man #1  Keith Sweat as Singing Bus Stop Man #2  Montell Jordan as Singing Bus Stop Man #3  And a special appearance by Oran "Juice" Jones as himself   Now...Tell me THAT lineup doesn't have hit written all over it. I hope these megastars can put their egos aside and coexist for the greater good: That is, to spread this message of triumhp over adversity, ghetto love, and peace to the many stage audiences of the world. Let me know if any of you all want discounted tickets or anything like that.   
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I checked out the Gold's Gym over where I live yesterday, and I must say, it is a pretty nice gym. It has most of the stuff that I like aboutmy Ballys, plus a basketball court and it's closer. The only thing that's keeping me from switching is the fact that I've been with Ballys so long that I only pay $10 a month now. It doesn't make sense for me to pay $40 a month again, basketball court or no basketball court.   The funny thing is, the women in there are something else. A lot of these women were made-up, walking on the treadmill posing for the dudes in there lifting. It was funny, because some of them reeked of desperation. I don't see why they'd choose the gym as their place to meet new dudes...Then again, I guess since folks are half naked in there, it makes some sense.   I never was big on macking women in the gym. I guess this is because when I'm in there I end up getting sweatty, and having veins bulging out of all kinds of places and shit like that. I don't think I look too flattering on workout days LOL.  I did try once, though. There was this lady named Elizabeth who used to work out at the same time I did on most of the same days. I would catch her looking in my direction sometimes, so I figured she must kinda like me or something...Normally, me being sweatty and tired from my workout would have stopped me, but this woman was FINE. She looks kinda like Tiara from http://www.tiaraxclusive.com, and I have a big-time crush on that Tiara chick.  So I went up to her and opened up conversation, cracked a few jokes, etc., etc...so when it came time to get the number, she told me "Well, I kinda live with my boyfriend."  I was thinking to myself "WHYYYYYYYYYYYY!!!!!!!!! DAMMIT!"  I just kinda eased my way out of the conversation and told her it was nice meeting her...Then proceeded to swear off ever hollering at anyone in the gym again. That was the first time I'd been shot down in months. I didn't know how to take it. Part of me wanted to go holler at someone else just to see if it was a fluke, and part of me came up with an elaborate get-back scheme...Which was to not wear any draws, spot her on the weight bench one day when she's lifting, and then teabag the shit outta her...LOL. I decided that she didn't do anything to me that warranted me putting my sweatty ballsack in her face, but I did hold fast to my vow to never holler at anyone in the gym again, regardless of how fine they are.* If I ever get a gym number again, that means the woman came up to me and volunteered to give it to me.  *Note - If Tiara happens to read this, she's the exception to this rule...with her fine ass...LOL.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This morning, a fat person in a black top competely ruined my white short-sleeve shirt.  I really try to be sensitive when I refer to the overweight and their issues, but this time, a fat motherfucker crossed the line.* I was already kind of in a sour mood this morning upon finding out that Metrobus and Metrorail fare raises went into effect yesterday and my trip to work is going to cost me more now. Then I end up on a really crowded train chock full of big folks. Once I was able to procure a seat, this big lady in a black outfit sat down next to me. I wasn't all that uncomfortable, but she was pretty much pressed against my left side due to her girth and circumference. Once I got off the train, I did a little stretch to get the blood flowing to that side of my body again, then went about my business.   It wasn't until I got to the office that I noticed the woman's black outfit left stains on my white shirt. THE white shirt that I have gotten NUMEROUS compliments on since I bought it. The one that gives me that suave "black Sinatra meets doo-wop barbershop quartet singer" kinda sex appeal.   First of all, what kind of cheap-ass suit rubs off on people? Suits like that are the ones that come with caution warnings telling the wearer to aviod open flames and high temperatures.   Speaking of high temperatures, it may have been that the woman was sweatting so hard that she made the dye come out of the suit fabric...You know big people tend to sweat like crazy from the slightest bit of movement or fat-on-fat friction. This leads me to wonder how two big people do it to each other...They probably have to devise a game plan and strategy going into the act. I'd be scared that I'd end up doing something embarassing...Like sliding in and talking shit like "You like that, huh!"...Only to find out I was humping the shit outta her navel or some random crevice or fat roll and hadn't even found the real vagina yet...LOL.  There...That's my angry rant since I didn't get to say anything to the big lady in the cheap black suit who ruined one of my favorite shirts. Thanks for reading. Hopefully this negative energy will make you all laugh as opposed to bringing you all down to my level, too.  *Note: Leon does not hate the fat, obese, big-boned, or sloppy people of the world. Leon feels that people with weight problems deserve to be treated as human beings. That said, Leon also feels that big people need to be mindful of their status, and take measures to respect the rest of society, who should not be inconvenienced, pushed aside, and made to suffer from the unjust tyrrany of the stout and the portly.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My Holiday Weekend - The Recap  Friday:  Didn't do a damned thing, other than get a haircut. Rested and relaxed after that...  Saturday:  Saw my grandma and her husband Lesse over at my mom's house. It's always fun seeing them. Grandma is probably the single most encouraging and loving person in my life. She always helps me to put my problems in perspective. Her husband Lesse is a character, too. Dude is always trying to get me to drink with him. His preferred beverage of choice is E&J, or as he so eloquently calls it, "Easy Jesus." I proceeded to drink with him while watching a Clint Eastwood western. Then, when my little cousin came over with his mom and sister, there was more comedy. He's 15, and his mom mentioned something about his little girlfriend. So once she left, Lesse walks over to him and said "You got a girlfriend, huh? You got you some stank yet?"  He kept on with that line of questioning for about 5 minutes LOL.   Later in the night, I went out with my sister and my co-worker Adam to "Cheers", or The Common Share, as it's more widely known. We basically shut the bar down, and along the way, my ex girlfriend, her roommate, and a few of their friends joined us out there. My sister and I are now both on the drunken wall of fame there. The one cool-ass white guy(I think his name was Steve) then mentioned a house party up the street where we could go crash. It sounded like a good idea at the time...  So we all walk in this place, and the first thing I saw as soon as I made it to the living room was two men on the couch with another one sprawled across both of them. I was thinking "WTF kinda party did this fool bring us to!?!?!" Luckily, there were other normal, straight people in there amongst the gay dudes, so I calmed down and gave it a chance. My sister saw some dude in there that she thought was really handsome and wanted to talk to, so my ex walked over to him to get his attention. This dude turned and said "Hello" in a manner that was so effeminate that Little Richard would have looked at that bamma, hit him in his chest and told him to man the fuck up. The night only went downhill from there.  After Steve asked someone "What's up with the dank?" at an inopportune moment, the gay folks started asking us all who we knew at the party, then telling us that it was over. So as I was leaving, some lady put some mardi gras beads around my neck. I didn't think anything of it, until one of the gay dudes and this big, pumpkin-headed big butch lady asked me where did I get the beads from. I told them, and they started bitching and having fits over the cheap-ass $2.00 beads that were PLACED AROUND MY NECK. So I gave them back with no problem. Upon me giving them back, one of the gay dudes decided that he had something smart to say...So I threatened to slap the shit outta him in front of his punk-assed houseguests on my way down the stairs. They got scared and shut the door as I started to walk back towards the apatrtment(in a effort to make the dude look like even more of a bitch). I don't know what pissed me off more...Getting kicked out of somewhere I didn't want to be, or getting accused of stealing $2.00 beads. Bastards.  Sunday:  Went to a cookout in the rain...Luckily it was under a canopy in this park, so the party went on despite the elements. Paul, D'angelow, and everyone else involved with setting up the cookout proved to be some dedicated, barbequeing mofos. Made me proud to say that I know such men of distinction.   I kinda think my ride there was bitter that she came with me, because she kept threatening to leave me LOL. Ah well, fuckit. She brought me back, so I guess it doesn't matter. Overall, the cookout was really fun. I even turned folks on to that good Sam Adams Summer Ale :)  Later that evening, I went to a strip club with the bisexual friends I mentioned in my "Resourseful" entry. Let me just say this: You get way more love and spend way less money when you go to a strip club with pretty women LOL. That was a wild evening...WHEEEEEEEEWWWW!!!!!!  Monday:  Rest and recovery from not getting much sleep Saturday and Sunday. Then I went swimming. I need to do that more often. It's great excercise.  Overall, the weekend was great, save for the house party incident. Hope yours was great, too.   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Don't you hate it when you're instant messaging someone, and they misunderstand what you're saying and get offended? That seems to happen to me all the damn time. It's messed up, too, because whatever was typed and misinterpreted is right there in print on that person's screen, too. Right there in front of their faces, taunting them and pissing them off even more.  &nbsp;  Maybe I just need to stop talking so much shit so folks don't think I'm being mean to them when I'm misunderstood.  &nbsp;  Nah...fuck that. Talking shit is too much fun. Plus, it's one of the things in life I can truly say that I'm good at. Why mess up a good thing?  &nbsp;  Either way, to all the folks whom I've ever pissed off via IM on accident, please don't take that shit personally.  &nbsp;  To those who read this and are still pissed off...fuck you if you can't take a joke. God wants you to be forgiving. So if you don't forgive me you're going to burn in Hell...then you're gonna die from the whooping cough. Or scurvey. Or the gout LOL&nbsp;  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just a few things I felt like sounding off on before folks leave work for the weekend...&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Anthony Hamilton: The brother has a GREAT album. Really soulful and well written. I recommend it. All that good music does not make him immune from getting clowned on my blog.  &nbsp;&nbsp;  Is it just me, or does dude look like he just doesn't give a fuck in all of his pictures and videos? He looks as if he just wakes up in the morning, throws on a smedium t shirt and hat&nbsp;then just goes to the video shoot without even getting the cold out his eye, shaving, or combing his hair. That's a TRUE example of when keeping it real goes wrong. IT'S YOUR VIDEO, MAAAAAN! At least groom yourself since your stankin ass is going on television. I swear he looks like a heroin addict in his videos.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  One more thing about his latest video for "Charlene." Why does everyone in that video look&nbsp;excruciatingly pained&nbsp;or shocked to the point of cardiac arrest?!?! The song is great, and I'm sure he wanted to add an element of drama to the video, but that was the worst overacting I've ever seen. Even the people who didn't say any words(especially Charlene's momma when she comes over) look like they&nbsp;are&nbsp;in agony. I think Mr. Hamilton might have been between fixes, which&nbsp;would explain the tension and pained expressions.&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Kobe Bryant: If he's not someone's bitch in prison next year, he is leading the NBA in scoring...easy. The&nbsp;Lakers won't win&nbsp;as much as they did in the past, but since Kobe will have all the shots he wants, that dude is going to score a shitload next season.&nbsp;I'm glad Shaq got traded, too. Also, am I the only one who thinks Jerry Buss, the Laker's owner, looks a lot like Jerry Stiller(George's Dad on Seinfeld)?  &nbsp;  &nbsp; urlLink http://www.lequipe.fr/Xml/Basket/Dossiers/Media/stern_buss_jerry_titre_60.jpg    &nbsp;   urlLink http://espn.go.com/media/pg2/2002/0612/photo/i_jstiller_m.jpg   &nbsp;  Jim Jones: Yeah...I know Cam'ron's boy is a skinny&nbsp; gang-bangin bamma with bitch hair, but his song "Certified Gangstas" has one of the hardest beats I've heard in a minute. That shit makes you wanna walk up to someone random in&nbsp;the grocery store&nbsp;and slap the&nbsp;SHIT outta 'em...just&nbsp;because they there and shit.&nbsp;Like "Fuck you AND your fabric softener, nigga! This MY aisle motherfucker! FROZEN FOODS, BEEEYAAATCH!"  &nbsp;  Have a great weekend, and don't let me catch you in the grocery store when that song comes on.  &nbsp;  Has bitch hair --->  urlLink http://store6.yimg.com/I/mixtapesusa_1799_2397140 &nbsp;  &nbsp;   &nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I know you're all wondering about that title, but read the post and give it a chance before calling me a woman-hating chaeuvanist pig.  I have to come to terms with whether or not I really want a girlfriend again or whether I'd rather just keep that "I don't give a shit about 'em" mentality that I keep finding myself sinking into since me and my ex broke up for good.   Sometimes I miss having someone there to hold at night whom I can be totally open with, show affection to and share all of my feelings with. Then others, I remember all the arguements, the half-truths, the stress and the pressures that came along with everything else. That brings me back to reality. I wrote a poem about it...Like 'ta hear it go:  I've searched low and I've searched high, trying to find myself a cutie pie. My destination leads me to a dead end, over and over and over again. They say when you look one never finds. They also say that love is blind. It ain't that blind that I can't see, somebody out there who's perfect for me. It seems as if every time I find the right girl, she turns out to be the very wrong girl. Tell me y'all when will this madness stop? I want somebody to love me for me not because I'm emcee Heavy D. Sombody out there who's perfect for me.  Ok. So I didn't write that. So what. You know it would have came off a lot smoother had I said it instead of Heavy D...Big 350 pound ass dancing across the stage in Used Jeans, Cazal glasses and a hi-top fade with parts cut into it and shit. I won't hate, though, considering I did buy the album and played it to death back when I was a kid.   Now, the explanation of the title: Since I am currently free from the tyrrany and oppresion of pussy at the moment, I am giving my motivational asshole quotes so that some reader out there may use these gems of wisdom to get a good laugh and vent some frustration. Here goes:  5. "Nice guys finish last. Be a dick and finish first" - My friend P, the scholar and gentleman.  4. "But I'm saying...I treat ALL my bitches with respect and dignity" - Me talking shit after jokingly trying to initiate a threesome with these Baltimore women a couple of years ago   3. "Never gamble against someone named after a city" - Heard this one in a movie, and I live my life by it. Think about it...someone named "Orlando" or "Chi-town" is probably some kind of hustler waiting to bust your ass and take your money.  2. "I hate you,I hate you, I don't even know you and I hate you...I wish all the bad things in life happen to you, and to you only" - Dave Chappelle during his "Player Hater's Ball" sketch.  1. "The bitch set me up!" - Marion Barry. Remember, he's running for office again pretty soon(City Council) :)  I hope these amused you viewers out there. If I offended anybody, just blame it on the fact that I haven't gotten any tang in awhile and my dick is dryer than a crackhead's lips in the wintertime right about now. I'm going for my Smooth Magazine so I can be a kinder, gentler Hustleman next time I type...  Vida Guerra(and Jergens lotion), you're my only friend :(  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am a fuckup.   I have been chillin, and neglecting this blog. To all my dedicated readers, I apologize for making you wait on my oh-so-marvelous commentary on life. Since I've neglected you all, I will give you two posts for the price of one. Only cause I love you sons of bitches :)  Post 1: I BUSTED FABOLOUS' ASS ON THE B-BALL COURT  Friday evening, I ended up playing an impromptu pickup game of ball at this outdoor court. It just so happens that the guy talking the most shit happened to look JUST LIKE the rapper Fabolous. So of course, I decided to guard that guy once I got on the court and fuck with him.  For some reason, he thought he had a handle and was trying all this And 1 bullshit, but since I knew he couldn't really dribble well with his left, I kept on stealing the ball from him or knocking it out of bounds every time he tried to be on some showboat shit. At first he was in awe like "Damn, he's fast as shit!"   He started to get irritated when I decided it was a good idea to say "F-A B-O, L-O U-S" every time I took the ball from his ass or make him take a bad shot. I even had his teammates laughing at him.   The coup-de-graw(or however you spell it) was when he tried to run me over. He was a little bigger than me, so one time he tried to push me out the way with his forearm on his way to the basket. I just stood my ground and brushed his forearm off with mine and sent that fool flying halfway to the three point line. He put up an airball while he was flailing about in the air, then opened his mouth like he was going to call something. The funny thing is, he realized that he tried to push ME out of the way, so when he opened his mouth to call a foul, no sound came out LOL.  Either way, it felt good to shut that loudmouth up.   Post 2: VIDA LOVE  I fell in LUST, everybody.  Too bad I can't do shit about it, though :(  The object of my carnal affection is Vida Guerra. She's on the cover of Smooth Magazine, and I bought the shit without even looking at the inside. THAT's how good her little Cuban ass looks on the cover. I have dated women with asses like that, so I know Vida would be attainable if she ever ran into me at Target or Best Buy or some random shit like that. Only thing is, a broke-ass entre-po-nigga like myself might be a step down for her from a social and financial aspect. I'm confident that I'd wear her ass out, though.  Then again, I say that about everybody. I'm a natural-born shit talker. Don't hold that against me, though. I am a nice, kind, friendly person. I just have this thing about thinking that I can turn out any woman that ever lived, unless she's gay or just has bad taste.   I feel that if a woman says no to me, it's a form of discrimination...LOL. I'm calling the NAACP on her ass, regardless of whether she's black, white, hispanic, or whatever ;)  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Readers, today I am allowing you to influence me in making a very important decision. I am running out of my Versace Blue Jeans cologne, and I do not know what fragrance to purchase next. Blue Jeans has been good to me. So has regular Burberry. Issey Miyake, Jean Paul, Aqua Di Gio and Dolce & Gabanna have also treated me right as far as the smell goods go, but a lot of people in DC seem to wear these. Hanae Mori and Givenchy are also great, but I can only find them in department stores and never in the cheap stores like Filene's Basement(where my average cologne purchase is around $22).   I need you all to comment(even anonymously if you want) and let me know what scent you think I should buy. You all can also add suggestions if you have a particular scent that you like. Here's the list:  - Versace Blue Jeans - Burberry - Jean Paul - Issey Miyake - Givenchey(if I can find it on sale like the rest) - Polo Sport(yeah, I took it back to high school with this one) - Other(Name another cologne that you prefer)  Thanks for your input, folks. Have a wonderful weekend.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      No, I'm not talking about the man with the platinum encrusted teeth that goes "Prrrrrrrrr"...  I'm talking about people who walk around downtown with bread feeding pigeons during lunch hour. I'm all for loving nature, but have some common courtesy. Some people don't like pigeons(or sky rats, as my ex calls them). These animals carry germs, so I do not want to be bombarded by them while I am walking around trying to mind my own business or look at T&A pass by.  Today, I was sitting in the park at McPherson Square, chillin in the shade enjoying DC's "scenery" when I see a Bird Lady in the distance. She was steadily throwing bread all over the park with no regard for the folks out there eating. I shot her a glance that said "Bitch I'll slap the shit out you if you throw those crumbs near me." It appeared to work, too, because she stopped throwing crumbs as she came closer up the walkway.   As she came closer, she kinda tried not to look in my direction. I could tell she was avoiding eye contact, so I kinda started to feel bad for giving her the mean look. I went ahead and smiled at the lady in an attempt to calm her fears of me saying anything mean to her. As she walked past, she gave me a little half smile and kept on walking.  Then, the sneaky Bird Bitch threw breadcrumbs right next to my bench. About 7 pigeons flew out past me from all over and every direction...So I yelled out "WHAT THE HELL IS WRONG WITH YOU! YOU CRAZY LUNATIC!" By then, it was too late...She had started to walk faster and was halfway across the street. I swear to God if I ever see the that Bird Lady again, I'm going to have my revenge. I'm not a truly spiteful person, but I need some revenge...some get-back. Maybe I should tie her to a tree and crazy glue bread crumbs to her ass so so can get to know all the pigeons she wants.  Sorry to put another hostile thread venting frustrations again, but I felt violated...LOL. Suppose I had some kind of bird phobia or something...I'd be scarred for life thanks to that gotdamned Bird lady.   So Bird People, if you're reading this, have some consideration for other people outside before you go throwing bird crumbs. Thanks.  Leon
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Any of you heard that Eightball and MJG single "You Don't Want Drama" from their current album? It came on the other week in the club, and the lyrics made me think.   The hook goes "Bust a nigga's head, smack a hoe, shoot the club up." I was thinking to myself, someday this song may be one of the ones that my generation considers one fo the classics. Then I pictured myself sitting down with my grandchildren playing the song like my parents used to play Teddy Pendergrass and the Delfonics for me. I'll be talking to them saying stuff like "This is good music here, boy! What you know about that! BUST A NIGGA'S HEAD, SMACK A HOE, SHOOT THE CLUB UP!"  For real, that's just a funny concept to me. On that note, I'm going to list some of my future classics for you...  The Songs I Want Playing When I Walk Down The Aisle at My Wedding: What These Bitches Want From A Nigga - DMX Gz Up, Hoes Down - Snoop Dogg  On that note, I'll end this with a classic from Devin The Dude  "I'll be sittin on top of the ride, drankin and smokin some weed Just checkin out the bit-ches,  trying to see what I can see I didn't know there'd be so many hoes 'round here Parking lot kinda full Just checking out the bit-ches, trying to see what I can pull"  LOL You all have a nice afternoon, and remember to listen to the modern-day classics ;) 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm going off of 2.5 hour's sleep.  My post today might be just a LITTLE incoherentttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttyyyyyyyyuuuuuippp[[[[[[]  Oops. My bad...Damned drowsiness.  I'm moving, and I spent last night packing up shit and watching DVDs. I should have gotten some sleep instead of watching 8 Mile battle raps and other random crap...Hindsight is 20-20, though.   Speaking of hindsight, I saw an ass or biblical proportions earlier today. Moses would have needed a staff to part an ass like that. That shit protruded like Dizzy Gilespie's cheeks...LOL. Just expansive...but in a good way.  "Yes! YES! FUCK YOU TOO!!!" - Eddie Murphy, Coming To America  Time to leave the office and get ready to move. Talk to you all later.  "What do you mean 'my equipment?' Are you saying something's wrong with my fuck stick?" - Billy Bob Thornton, Bad Santa  Alright...I'm gone for real this time. Good evening ;)
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Since this is entry number 33, I decided to pay homage to all of the great 33s which have influenced my life in some form or another...  &nbsp;  Patrick Ewing: Sure, he rocked a flat-top haircut WAY past it's expiration date...Sure he got dunked on by damn near every up-and-coming star in the league(almost as if dunking on Patrick Ewing was a sign that you've arrived LOL)...Sure he shuffled his feet and traveled a lot...Sure he shot too many jumpers at times(as well as one infamous finger roll I'm sure he wants to take back)...But I respect the hell out of Patrick Ewing. The man was a warrior on the court. Busted his ass defensively, inspired his teammates, and won a lot. He didn't get that NBA title, but he earned the respect of everyone who played with and against him. Plus he was one of the most intimidating college players ever. His Georgetown teams are what got me watching basketball in the first place. They are the first basketball games I can remember watching, anyway...      The only man known to have kept a flat-top longer than this man, is the actor who played Moesha's Dad     Larry Bird: I hated this&nbsp;guy back in the day, since his Celtics always went up against Magic Johnson's Lakers. Only when I started taking pride in playing ball and got serious about it did I notice&nbsp;the greatness of&nbsp;Larry Bird's game. Dude is flat-out among the top five to seven players to ever step on the court, in my opinion. So what if he was a country ass white dude playing for one of the whitest teams in the NBA at the time...He was impressive, as were a lot of his teammates. They played great team basketball.  &nbsp;  Dookie: This guy played on my school team LOL. This one isn't about basketball, though. Dude would come to high school every day in a dress shirt, tie, slacks and dress shoes. Sometimes, he even had on a sportscoat or entire suit. Just since he went against the grain and rocked the professional, grown folks style before Jay Z even thought of buying dress shirts, I have to give the man his trendsetting credit. Don't let the suit fool you, though...Dookie didn't take no shit(no pun intended...LOL).  &nbsp;  Ok y'all...my clothes should be dry by now, so I'm going to get them from the laundry room. That means it's also the end of my #33 tribute. So to Patrick Ewing, Larry Bird, and&nbsp;Dookie, I salute you.&nbsp;     
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What makes a person go into hair denial?   Bald men: Stop being in denial and accept your baldness. Stop combing the shit over...I had an old boss that used to do the comb-over thing. Plus he had a hair transplant, so his shit looked like the hair on a cabbage patch doll or one of those toys like a barbie or something. Just sprouting out like a sickly, dying chia pet or something. His Elmer Fudd looking ass was pathetic.   Toupees are bad, too. Very rarely do those things look convincing. The old mayor of my hometown has one. The sad thing is, the rest of his head is grey, but his toupee is black. He has that reverse skunk look going on with his head. But dude refuses to let it go. I even have family guilty of this. My uncle is the president of a pretty big company, but this brother had been walking around with this super round Apollo Creed 'fro. He's had ti so long, that I just started to accept that it was real. My sister had to be the one to break it to me. I was heartbroken :(  Don't dye your shit, either...Go grey with grace. To Hell with a "Grecian" or "Just For Men." Old people with super-black hair just look freaky.  Brothers: Avoid products like "Duke" and "S-Curl" altogether. That Eddie Kane, Jr. hairstyle is not cool in the continental United States...Or any other country for that matter. Ok. Maybe in the Dominican Republic(see Pedro Martinez), but not too many other places.  My sister was telling me she read in someone's blog that cornrows are going to become this generation's jheri-curl. Sadly, I have to agree. I think some people are going to hold on to their cornwors for dear life. It's bad wneh you see old men with grey 'rows...or dudes going bald getting them and having the shits start halfway on top of their heads.   Women, y'all aren't exempt from this. If your going to get a weave, get a quality one. I literally could see the glue on this one lady's head yesterday. Just sitting there in little clumps. It was kinda nasty, even...  Those weaves that sit up really high mess with me, too. Your hair should not look like it's just hovering over your head as opposed to sitting on top of it.  Natural styles are cool....but wash them, please. "Natural" does not mean "Neglected Hygene." Stank hair is never cool.  If you change your hair color, be smart about it. Really darkskinned blonde women scare me for some reason. I think it's just because I KNOW it's not natural. Ladies, be yourselves. I love your natural black ass. You don't have to try that hard to Europeanize yourself for me.  Asymettrical cuts: I thought this went out back in the day with MC Lyte, but there are still women rocking this style. I went to school with this girl that we called Bald HEad Mushroom, because her hairstyle looked like one. I expected some smurfs to climb out of her shit.  That's all the messed up hair I feel like talking about today. Just wanted to give a wake up call to those who may have been led astray to believe that one of these looks are still cutting-edge. Hopefully, this witll save some souls from embarasment. Good day, people.         
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      How many of you all ever take public transportaion?   If so, I want to know if I am the only person that smelly people want to sit next to when they get on the bus/train. Yesterday, this man sat next to me...he must have bathed in urine. It was almost as if he had on some French cologne called Le Piss or something. The worst part was, he only sat there for about two stops before he left, but his smell lingered for 5 more.  The thing about that was, I was scared people who got on the bus and didn't get a chance to see where the smell came from were going to think I was the pissy one and try to blame that shit on me. I wanted to stand up and yell "IT WASN'T ME!!! I TOOK A BATH THIS MORNING AND I DIDN'T PISS MY PANTS!"  Ah well...fuck it.  Seriously, though...The smelly people always find me on public transportation. I think they think someone who smells good will cancel out their smell.   Dammit I have to get back on the road again.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>