<Blog>


<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Faerie Crossword  Answers for Saturday, August 7, 2004  Across: 4. hunt 5. roar 8. two 9. charlie 10. haiku 11. ntv 12. ice 13. lupe 14. dart  Down: 1. toughskin 2. bat 3. cho 5. royal 6. anchovies 7. pinkswirly
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The following are the times that  urlLink the Snowager  is asleep. Be verrry careful and quiet and maybe you'll be one who's lucky enough to get some of his treasure!  urlLink     6:00 to 7:00 a.m.  2:00 to 3:00 p.m.  10:00 to 11:00 p.m.  All times are NST, which is the equivalent of PST, so adjust accordingly for where you live. Just remember, he goes to sleep for an hour about every eight hours. Good luck!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Right now Neopets has a game called  urlLink A Cinderella Story . Actually, I hesitate to call it a game because it's more like advertising. It's a tie-in to hopefully get you interested in seeing the movie. But, whether or not you're interested in the movie, it's an easy way to pick up an extra 600 neopoints a day. Granted, the questions are all a bit on the silly side, but you only have to answer five of them per game. There are no wrong answers, so you're guaranteed a perfect score just by answering them. At 200 points a game, times three games and that's 600 easy points.  I also have another game to add to this section. It's called  urlLink Star Sisterz: Sisterz Speak . This game is also a marketing tie-in, so they've made it pretty easy. It's a very simple matching game. I would suggest playing it through once or twice to get an idea of what you're supposed to do. Then, after you're sure you have the hang of it, play it for a score to send. They recently cut the scoring back to 75 neopoints per 100 game points, but you should be able to make 1000 points daily from it fairly easily. You are given the option now of making another 50 neopoints per e-mail address you provide to them for referrals (up to three times a day). Personally, I'm not comfortable signing up my friends' e-mail addresses for advertising.  Now you're on your way to being a Neopets tycoon! 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink BVI Trivia Answers   I've played the game about thirty times through, and these are all the different questions I've seen. If there is one that I've missed, please neomail (FloridaGirl_82) me and I'll add it to the list. If you're not sure where the game is, you can find it  urlLink here . Each perfect score is worth 300 neopoints, for a total of 900 nps. daily. Good luck!   Who is the director of the movie King Arthur? Antoine Fuqua  Who is the blockbuster producer of the movie King Arthur? Jerry Bruckheimer  Who is the writer of the movie King Arthur? David Franzoni  What is the name of the actor who plays Arthur in the movie King Arthur? Clive Owen  What is the name of the actress who plays Guinevere in the movie King Arthur? Keira Knightley  What is the name of the actor who plays Merlin in the movie King Arthur? Stephan Dillane  What is the name of the actor who plays Lancelot in the movie King Arthur? Ioan Gruffud  What is the name of the actor who plays Cerdic in the movie King Arthur? Stellan Skarsgrd  Which movie is not from the producer of King Arthur? Reign of Fire  Which movie is also produced by the producer of King Arthur? Pirates of the Caribbean: the Curse of the Black Pearl  Which movie is also directed by the director of King Arthur? The Replacement Killers  The writer of King Arthur also wrote an epic blockbuster in 2000. Which movie is it? Gladiator  The actress who plays Guinevere also starred in an action adventure blockbuster in 2003. Which movie is it? Pirates of the Caribbean: the Curse of the Black Pearl  When does King Arthur open in Singapore cinemas? July 15  What famous historical landmark is shown in the movie? Hadrian's Walls  The movie King Arthur depicts a climatic battle that would decide the future of Britain. This battle is referred to as "The Battle of __________ Hill". Badon  What is the name of Arthur's sword in the movie King Arthur? Excalibur   *note: Check the spelling carefully before answering. The choice "Excalibrator" looks very similar, but is the wrong answer.  Who is the oldest Knight of the Round Table in the movie King Arthur? Bors  Who is the youngest Knight of the Round Table in the movie King Arthur? Galahad  Which knight in the movie has five children and three wives? Bors  Which knight is Arthur's right-hand man and also a deadly warrior in the movie King Arthur? Lancelot  Who does not belong to the Knights of the Round Table in the movie King Arthur? Cerdic or Cynric. *note: this question may appear with either of these answers being the correct choice  Cerdic and Cynric are from the invading __________ forces in the movie King Arthur. Saxons  In the movie King Arthur, Merlin is a master of guerilla warfare and also the leader of the __________. Woads  In the movie King Arthur, Arthur is half British and half __________. Roman  Guinevere is an expert __________ in the movie King Arthur. Archer  What is Arthur's full name in the movie King Arthur? Lucius Artorius Castus  In the movie King Arthur, Picts or pictus actually means "the Painted People". What do the Romans call them? Woads  Who is the commander of the invading Saxon forces in the movie King Arthur? Cerdic
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The  urlLink Cliffhanger  answers are broken down by how many words they have and then into alphabetical order. When you copy and paste the answer into the answer box, do not add a period. Many, many thanks to Scott of  urlLink Snorkle Cheese's Neopets Help  for his permission to reprint these answers here!   3 words: Happy gadgadsbogen day   4 words:  Better late than never  Meercas despise red neggs  No news is impossible  Scorchios like hot places  Super Glue is forever   5 words:  All roads lead to neopia  Dr Frank Sloth is green  Dung furniture stinks like dung  Keep your broken toys clean  Koi invented the robotic fish  Nimmos are very spiritual beings  Today is your lucky day   6 words:  A buzz will never sting you  Be nice to Shoyrus or else  Carrots are so expensive these days  Chia bombers are mud slinging fools  Chombies are shy and eat plants Faeries are quite fond of reading  Flotsams are no longer limited edition  Fuzios wear the coolest red shoes  Garon loves an endless challenging maze  Great neopets are not always wise  Kacheekers is a two player game  Korbats are creatures of the night  Moogi is a true poogle racer  Mr black makes the best shopkeeper  Number six is on the run  Only real card sharks play cheat  Skeiths are strong but very lazy  The beader has a beaming smile  The techo is a tree acrobat  Tyrannians will eat everything and anything   7 words:  An air of mystery surrounds the acara  Asparagus is the food of the gods  Chombies hate fungus balls with a passion  Faerie food is food from the heavens  Frolic in the snow of happy valley  Jubjubs defend themselves with their deafening screech  Kauvara mixes up potions like no other  Kyrii take special pride in their fur  Mister pickles has a terrible tigersquash habit  Maybe the missing link is really missing  Most Wild Kikos Swim in Kiko Lake  Neopian inflation is a fact of life  Never underestimate the power of streaky bacon  Poogles look the best in frozen collars  Some neggs will bring you big disappointment  Some neggs will bring you big neopoints  The Cybunny is the fastest neopet ever  The pen is mightier than the pencil  The Snowager sleeps most of its life  Tornado rings and cement mixers are unstoppable  Uggaroo gets tricky with his coconut shells  Unis just love looking at their reflection  When there is smoke there is pollution  You cannot teach an old grarrl mathematics   8 words:  A miss is as good as a mister  A neopoint saved is a neopoint not enough  A tuskaninny named colin lives on terror mountain  An iron rod bends while it is hot  Children should not be seen spanked or grounded  Doctor Sloth tried to mutate neopets but failed  Do not bathe if there is no water  Dr Death is the keeper of disowned neopets  Faerie pancakes go great with crazy crisp tacos  Flame the Tame is a ferocious feline fireball  Have you trained your pet for the Battledome  If your hedge needs trimming call a chomby  Kacheeks have mastered the art of picking flowers  Keep your pet company with a neopet pet  Kikoughela is a fancy word for cough medicine  Kougras are said to bring very good luck  Pet rocks make the most playful of petpets  Scratch my back and I will scratch yours  Snowbeasts love to attack grundos with mud snowballs  The advent calendar is only open in december  The Alien Aisha Vending Machine serves great good  The big spender is an international jet setter  The Bruce is from Snowy Valley High School  The healing springs mends your wounds after battle  The hidden tower is for big spenders only  The library faerie tends to the crossword puzzle  The tatsu population was almost reduced to extinction  You should try to raise your hit points  Whack a beast and win some major points  9 words:  An idle mind is the best way to relax  Congratulations to everybody who helped defeat the evil monoceraptor  Do not open a shop if you cannot smile  Do not try to talk to a shy peophin  Enter the lair of the beast if you dare  Every neopet should have a job and a corndog  Get three times the taste with the triple dog  It is always better to give than to receive  Let every zafara take care of its own tail  Look out for the moehog transmogrification potion lurking around  Magical ice weapons are from the ice cave walls  Meercas are to blame for all the stolen fuzzles  Mika and Carassa Want You To Buy Their Junk  Neopets battledome is not for the weak or sensitive  Plesio is the captain of the tyrannian sea division  Put all of your neopoints on poogle number two  Poogle five is very chubby but is lightning quick  Poogles have extremely sharp teeth and they are cuddly  Stego is a baby stegosaurus that all neopets love  Sticks n stones are like the greatest band ever  Take your pet to tyrammet for a fabulous time  Terror Mountain is home to the infamous Ski Lodge  The barking of Lupes does not hurt the clouds  The battledome is near but the way is icy  The meat of a sporkle is bitter and inedible  The quick brown fox jumps over the lazy dog  The tyrannian volcano is the hottest place in neopia  Treat your usul well and it will be useful  Uggaroo follows footsteps to find food for his family  Your pet deserves a nice stay at the neolodge   10 words:  A chia who is a mocker dances without a tamborine  A chia who is a mocker dances without a tambourine  All neopets can find a job at the employment agency  Become a BattleDome master by training on the Mystery Island  Better to be safe than meet up with a monocerous  Bouncing around on its tail the blumaroo is quite happy  Chias are loveable little characters who are full of joy  Faeries bend down their wings to a seeker of knowledge  Grarrg is the tyrannian battle master that takes no slack  If you live with lupes you will learn to howl  Kyruggi is the grand elder in the tyrannian town hall  Love your neopet but do not hug it too much  Meercas are talented pranksters that take pride in their tails  Oh where is the tooth faerie when you need her  Only ask of the Queen Faerie what you really need  Please wipe your feet before you enter the Scorchio den  Some neohomes are made with mud and dung and straw  Store all of your Neopian trading cards in your neodeck  The best thing to spend on your neopet is time  The kindhearted faerie queen rules faerieland with a big smile  The lair of the beast is cold and dark inside  The meerca is super fast making it difficult to catch  The pound is not the place to keep streaky bacon  There is nothing like a tall glass of slime potion  The sunken city of Maraqua has some great hidden treasures  The tyrannian jungle is full of thick muddle and mash  The wise aisha has long ears and a short tongue  To know and to act are one and the same  Under a tattered cloak you will generally find doctor sloth  With the right training Tuskaninnys can become quite fearsome fighters  Yes boy ice cream sell out all of their shows   11 words:  A journey of a million miles begins on the marketplace map  Ask a lot of questions but only take what is offered  Be sure to visit the Neggery for some great magical neggs  Bruce could talk under wet cement with a mouthful of marbles  By all means trust in neopia but tie your camel first  Count Von Roo is one of the nastier denizens of neopia  Do not wake the snowager unless you want to be eaten  Every buzz is a kau in the eyes of its mother  Faerie poachers hang out in faerieland with their jars wide open  Give the wheel of excitement a spin or two or three  Grarrls are ferocious creatures or at least they try to be  Have you told your friends about the greatest site on earth  If a pteri and lenny were to race neither would win  Jetsams are the meanest Neopets to ever swim the Neopian sea  Kaus love to sing although they only know a single note  Listen to your pet or your tongue will keep you deaf  Make certain your pet is well equipped before entering the battledome  Only mad gelerts and englishmen go out in the noonday sun  Poogle number five always wins unless he trips over a hurdle  Space slushies are just the thing on a cold winter day  The bluna was first sighted under the ice caps of tyrannia  The Neopedia is a good place to start your Neopian Adventures  Tyrannia is the prehistoric kingdom miles beneath the surface of neopia  When eating a radioactive negg remember the pet who planted it  When friends ask about the battledome say there is no tomorrow  When the blind lead the blind get out of the way  You cannot wake a Bruce who is pretending to be asleep  You know the soup kitchen is a great place to go  You know you can create a free homepage for your pet  You probably do not want to know what that odor is   12 words:  A kyrii will get very upset if its hair gets messed up  By all means make neofriends with peophins but learn to swim first  Catch the halter rope and it will lead you to the kau  Cliffhanger is a brilliant game that will make your pet more intelligent  Dirty snow is the best way to make your battledome opponent mad  Do not be in a hurry to tie what you cannot untie  Do not speak of an elephante if there is no tree nearby  Do not think there are no jetsams if the water is calm  Eat all day at the giant omelette but do not be greedy  Everyone loves to drink a hot cup of borovan now and then  Experience is the comb that nature gives us when we are bald  Fly around the canyons of tyrannia shooting the evil pterodactyls and grarrls  If you see a man riding a wooden stick ask him why  If you want to have lots of adventures then adopt a wocky  Jarbjarb likes to watch the tyrannian sunset while eating a ransaurus steak  Krawk have been known to be as strong as full grown neopets  Myncis love to hug their plushies and eat sap on a stick  Quiggles spend all day splashing around in the pool at the neolodge  The Grarrl will roar and ten eggs will hatch into baby grarrls  The Snow Faerie Quest is for those that can brave the cold  The wheel of mediocrity is officially the most second rate game around  There is only one ryshu and there is only one techo master  Uggsul invites you to play a game or two of tyranu evavu  When an Elephante is in trouble even a Nimmo will kick him  You should not throw baseballs up when the ceiling fan is on   13 words:  A Scorchio is a good storyteller if it can make a Skeith listen  Bang and smash your way to the top in the bumper cars game  Do not be greedy and buy every single food item from the shops  Faerieland is not for pets that are afraid of heights or fluffy clouds  If at first you do not succeed play the ice caves puzzle again  If you go too slow try to keep your worms in a tin  If your totem is made of wax do not walk in the sun  It makes total sense to have a dung carpet in your dung neohome  Myncis come from large families and eat their dinner up in the trees  The Neopian Hospital will help get your pet on the road to recovery  We never know the worth of items till the wishing well is dry  You can lead a kau to water but you cannot make it drink   14 words:  Building a neohome is a way to build a foundation for your little pets  You know you should never talk to Bruce even when his mouth is full  Your neopet will need a mint after eating a chili cheese dog with onions  Why beg for stuff when you can make money at the wheel of excitement   15 words:  Bronto bites are all the rage and they are meaty and very easy to carry  The beast that lives in the tyrannian mountains welcomes all visitors with a sharp smile The whisper of an acara can be heard farther than the roar of a wocky  You really have to be well trained if you want to own a wild reptillior   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      If anyone has been wondering where I've been, that's where! A friend (thank you, chikichicky!) suggested I check out the site, and I've been there ever since. I thought it was only a kiddie sort of game. Boy, was I wrong! As it turns out, it's  much  more than that.   For those who aren't "in the know"  urlLink Neopets  is a huge online community. The pets themselves are only a small part of it. The basis of Neopets seems to be in earning Neopoints, which function at the currency of the land. One of the easiest ways to start earning is by simply playing the games on the site. With over 140 of them there's something for everyone. For instance, I'm not always the most coordinated of people, so I do much better in the puzzle type of games.   Once you've gotten started with some points, the next move is up to you. You can choose to open your own shop by searching for bargains and reselling them. You can play the stock market, or open an account at the National Neopian bank and stockpile those points to buy something special for your pet.  If you're feeling competitive, you can train and outfit your pet for the Battledome. There are six different arenas where you can test your battle skills against some of the characters from around the site. Or, if you'd like, you can challenge another Neopian to a battle.  If you'd like to meet people who have interests that are similar to your own, you might consider joining a guild. I personally believe the one I belong to is the best so of course I want to give it a little bit of a plug, so here's our ad.  urlLink     { TFC }  We have a reliable and dedicated council plus tons of activities for our members!  - Active & Friendly Members - Newbie Packs - 1NP Auctions - Wishing Well - Avatar trades - Guild Mall - Weekly gifts - Useful links and tips/hints - Quick-loading layout & website - No donations required    urlLink       If this sounds like fun to you, why don't you check it out? We really have a great time and you'd receive a warm welcome from the guild members.  Take a look at Neopets, and if you decide it looks like something you'd like to try, I'd be very grateful if you used a link from this page to sign up. If you don't already know someone who you would like to credit with the referral, I'd really appreciate it. Just use  urlLink this link  or the one at the bottom of the page (the pic of my Neopet) to get to the site and I'll automatically get credit.   Thanks so much for reading. I've really only touched on the high points of the community. I really hope to see you there. And if this post helped influence your decision to join, please drop me a Neomail to say hi! My Neopets screen name is FloridaGirl_82. Hope to hear from you soon!
     

    
</post>


</Blog>