<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, on my way to Lunker's on Tues. night, as I was following the speed limit (at 55 mph), at least 4 drivers in stupid cars flashed their brights at me. This attention immediately sent me into a panic. What was wrong with my car? What did I do? How come I didn't notice anything wrong before?? Eeeeee! Upon getting out of my car to check its front, I noticed that the little orange light on the front left side of the car was out. Oooooh! I'm scared! Yes, that could potentially get me a ticket, but is it really worth it to flash your lights at someone who has NO idea why you've flashed your lights? Does it really help the situation? Yes, I did figure out why they were flashing, but it's not as though flashing lights can be deciphered as Morse code or whatever. I can't read your flashing lights mind buddy. I think it's an ego thing, really. Tee hee, I'm the guy (or girl) with ALL of my car lights in working condition, so I'm going to give that irresponsible nitwit a FLASH, so s/he knows what's up, even though flashing lights can be annoying and disturbing. So please, just don't bother flashing your lights at me. Unless you'd rather give me a heart attack, of course. Or unless I'm dragging a deer carcass that has attached itself to my bumper. Or unless there are 5 or 6 blue dots trailing my car and they may or may not be aliens. Or unless I'm driving down the center line of the road instead of staying in my own lane. Or unless I have a HEADLIGHT out. Then by all means, go ahead.  All right, on to less important things. He he.  I've been having some bad dreams lately. I know other people who've been having bad dreams lately. A virus?  I might go see Fahrenheit (am I spelling that damn word right? Sheesh.) 9/11 tomorrow or Friday. I'm not sure what to think about going to see the film or even about  wanting  to see it. It's obviously been a lightning rod for controversy--duh, Michael Moore!   Okay. Sinus headache. Good night.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Should I even comment on today's events in Iraq, the "legal transfer of power in Iraq"? Transferred 2 days earlier than planned? I guess they didn't want to compete with the opening day of "Spiderman." Can I comment without commenting? I think so.   F*ck.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Who knew that Angela Lansbury could play such an evil, conniving bitch? I like it! To hell with the Teapot! To hell with Murder, She Wrote! SHE wrote evil, and lots of it! And it's a cliche to say that, in terms of movies, they don't make 'em like they used to. Laurence Harvey or Brad Pitt? Frank Sinatra or George Clooney? Duh.... I wonder if the Denzel Washington/Meryl Streep version will hold any water next to the oldie. Duh....  Can't sleep, again. Thinkin' about the past, again.  I've begun my love affair with Krispy Kreme donuts. I fear for my thighs.  Starting to get organized, i.e., slowly moving everything I own out of the living room and into my old bedroom. But I'm trying to keep myself from getting too comfortable. I do want to get outta here eventually. I'm sure for some people, in their mid-twenties, it's nice to live with their parents. Uh, right. Anyway, love the queen-size bed, blush at the massive amounts of stuffed animals crowding me out. At least I get to listen to my dog Rosie snore. It's so sweet. Definitely sweeter than hearing a human snore.   All right, will try to sleep...
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Living at home again is so strange. Partly humorous, partly joyous, partly annoying (severely annoying). I really have a good relationship with my parents, but I'm so frustrated by my dad's love affair with Fox News. He's become so indoctrinated by those self-serving, lying, bullshitting neo-cons that hardly anything he says about politics makes sense anymore. He keeps worrying about how his 401k will be affected if the Democrats get control of the White House (Senate, House, and all) in November. I'm stunned to realize that my dad (who I once thought of as incredibly intelligent, thoughtful, and unwavering in his ability to see the wrongs done by Republicans, yeah, and Democrats--I still think he's intelligent and thoughtful, just misled) seems to believe that Bush and his cronies REALLY care about us at all. It's so fucking obvious that I don't even need to go into any of the myriad reasons why that's so not true. Urgh, pisses me off! And I dare any of you out there to watch Fox News for even one minute. If you don't puke within the first 15 seconds, you have a stronger stomach than I do. I mean, my mom deals with it pretty well. I guess after 29 years of marriage, she's learned to view my dad as a largely humorous figure in her life. I'm like, "crazy old man."   I'm so confused about a lot of stuff! I hate that.   For some reason, I really like Mandy Moore. Don't hate on me! I wish I had her hair and perfect skin.  Good night all.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Nader Flyer 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So my puppy Rosie is fine. She has a nail-bed infection, but that should be cleared up within a week. I was so worried about her. I hope you were too.  I saw that lovely boy again tonight. Ahh. Swoon. I'm stupid. Did I look cute tonight? I'm stupid.  My favorite pen: Bic Velocity. How much velocity you say? Who the fuck knows? But it's a fuckin' awesome pen.   Still addicted to bad pop, light rock, and the occasional awesome 80s song (Hello!?! The Eurythmics rock!--sp?). What is happening to me???
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm worried about my puppy Rosie. She hasn't been able to walk on her left front paw for about a day or so. My dad and I cleaned and dressed her paw, but if it doesn't get better, we'll take her to the doctor. Poor girl. She already suffers so badly from allergies.  Keep my baby dog safe...
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Urgh, my mind is in overdrive again.   I'm mostly antsy because I'm trying to figure out what the f*ck to do with my life. Anyone have any suggestions? Serious ones, I mean. Oh well, I'm sure it'll come to me sometime, in a dream or while I'm taking the dogs on a walk. Boom! There it is!  I do like being back in my hometown (well, IL is technically my 2nd hometown, but most of my friends will laugh at me if I go any further with my explanation), and it's hilarious that I'm probably more busy here than I was in NY, and I don't even have a job here yet! Chicago awaits, I think.  I love love love seeing my friends, reconnecting with old ones and gaining new ones. Am I one big arrogant bastard for feeling so loved? Where do the commas go?  Currently reading:  How to Be Alone , a collection of essays by Jonathan Franzen. He really seems to think that he's god's gift to readers and that he invented the contemporary novel, but the essays aren't too bad. I think he's a pretty good writer and so far, he seems to be revealing himself in bits and pieces. Time will tell if there are any revelations. There is one essay on the Chicago postal system that unnerved me.   Currently listening to: bad Central IL radio stations. I fear I'm becoming addicted to bad light rock music. And forgive me for liking that Maroon 5 song that's currently on the radio.  Currently watching: just TV. TV sucks, but I'm watchin' it. 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nope, I don't regret anything I've done lately, or ever. Sh** happens, life happens. I'm way too analytical about things that shouldn't ever be analyzed. Just shut up Lisa!  Finally got that links thing figured out. Duh!  Hung out with some pals tonight (I love sentence fragments). I felt "tha luv." I mostly felt happy. I mostly felt comforted. I mostly felt cool and well-dressed. She mostly felt I was weird. But she never felt me in the first place.  Good night. Or should I say, good morning.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why why why do I drink the drink? Or drinks? I. Feel. Awful.  Why do I do things that maybe I'll regret in the morning? Not that certain things are bad, and not that I do certain things all of the time or even most of the time, but for me they're contentious. I don't know how to feel.   I DO want to feel better. Sh**.   Blogs can be soooo weird. In one sense, they're a form of expression, but people also may often tiptoe around what they really want to say. So just say it. Like I'm NOT doing. 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ever since I got back, I've adopted strange sleeping patterns. Well one, actually. Usually on weekends or when I don't work, I'm a lazy ass, going to bed late and then getting up reeeeeally late. But now, for some reason, I've been going to bed extra late and then getting up extra early. 9am is early for me. I suppose it's because I have a tendency to keep my mind going even when I'm exhausted--I've got a lot on my mind. My mind therefore keeps me up. A mind is a terrible thing to waste, no? Or I'll go to bed really late, get up really early, and then fall asleep on the couch for a few hours. I'm still a lazy ass.  Why am I writing about this?   I watched "In America" last night, late at night of course. I watched it on my laptop which is for me so much fun to do. I don't know why I get giddy thinking about watching movies on the laptop. It seems more intimate than watching a movie on TV, even though it's not high definition or surround sound. Whooooo. Anyway, I thought "In America" was sweet, although definitely bordering on mushy and melodramatic. The acting was fabulous. The children were incredibly believable and gorgeous. I kept thinking, I wish I looked like that little girl, now! Kidding! I know, I'm strange. What's even stranger is that sometimes, while watching terrific child actors in movies, I think about having children one day. This is a big deal for me since for the longest time, I never wanted to have children. So if I could have children that act like the well-behaved, sweet, introspective child actors, then I would be set. Am I really kidding? But Samantha Morton was genius as usual.   A friend recently told me that having a crush on someone or REALLY being into someone (before dating possibilities present themselves) is like talking to yourself. How true...      
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's been so surreal being back in my hometown. I'm so fortunate to have such a great family and wonderful friends. I canNOT say that enough. Or write it enough. I'm not sure where I'll go from here, but for now, it's nice to not be so concerned with, well, anything.   I've thought a lot about my time in New York, wondering if there's any value in simply having lived in a place like NY. Like, what did I really do there? Is it enough to "be" in another place? And what did I really expect I would do with my time there? I had originally thought that I would make my mark on the publishing world, while carving out a niche for myself filled with friends and oh yeah! lovers too. And it turned out that I wasn't so sure what I wanted to do with my life. Realized that merely changing the scenery isn't enough. I guess NY served a purpose for me. To throw me off course a bit. NY certainly makes you question yourself. And I needed to be questioned. But it was an amazing experience, one that I feel all the stronger for having experienced. I have more confidence, I think, in myself and what I'm capable of. I've nurtured a passion in politics and that may be an avenue I will wander down. I don't know, still thinking...  Don't you know that Chris Rock is brilliant? Have you watched his comedy special on HBO? Should you feel bad for not having watched it? Yes.  So many people to see. It's great...
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I saw the newest Harry Potter movie today. Yes, I'm 24 years old and I did. I thought it was wonderful, and the fact that it was directed by Alfonso Cuaron, well, I don't have to say anymore. I thought the movie had more depth of characters and emotion than the previous films. It felt like a real movie, as opposed to just a recreation of the book. And of course Alan Rickman is always brilliant. It's worth the price of admission to see him slither and grimace.  I saw the movie with my papa, who also enjoys the books. For me, they're just pure entertainment. I see nothing wrong in indulging. And I think it's so funny that my dad likes the books too. He's an incredibly sensitive guy, but he can also be a manly man. It's nice to share something sweet and silly with him.  Ahh, to have a crush. Ahh, for butterflies...
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, hello again everyone. It's only been a few days, but the journey felt even longer.  I just want to say a quick thing (or not so quick) about my previous blog, if any of you out there read it. While I was writing often on pure emotion, I wasn't always being ME, and I'm here to do that now. I was immersed in a situation filled with cattyness and that's all changed, thank goodness. I'm out of that unhealthy situation and I already feel that I'm back on the right track. No negativity (well, except towards Bush and the Admin. and other, more important, issues). I do have to say that, except for these past few months, I'd never been around such racist, ignorant, insensitive people in my life. Some people will never change, will never see that the words I wrote, however uncouth they were, had big veins of truth in them. Those people were just as much at fault as I was. But that part of my life is over, another chapter completed. And I'm ready to begin another....  My parents are amazing, okay?
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Did you know that there's a place called Bushkill Falls, the "Niagara of Pennsylvania"? Weird. Appropriate. To me, at least. (Well, it'd be even more appropriate if the place was called "KillBush Now," but, what can you do?)   I should explain. When I was journeying back home to IL with my parents, we stopped off in the Poconos to refuel and reenergize. And I picked up 2 pamphlets for "things to do in the Poconos" at the hotel we were staying at. One was for the place I mentioned in the previous paragraph. The other was for the "Paradise Shooting Center," and yes, I quote, "This may be the most F U N you have in the Poconos!" Here's more from the pamphlet:   "You can try all of the guns you've seen on TV and in the movies. We have .22's, Glocks, .44 Magnums, UZI's (Are they kidding? REAL UZI's???)...."   Well, at a sport shooting center, I suppose it makes perfect sense to equate reality (the reality that shooting guns in the "real world" is not necessarily the same thing as shooting guns in, say, an Ahnold movie)&nbsp;with fantasy (as in, the fantasy of guns depicted in movies and TV, say, in any movie or TV show where the actor is holding a gun in each hand and shooting them sideways). Does anyone else see a problem with this? And I think it's pretty presumptuous of the Paradise Shooting Center to think that "this maybe be the most F U N you have in the Poconos!" And does sport shooting really involve an UZI? I'm not gun person, so if I'm wrong about this, please shoot me.   So John F. Kerry accepted the Democratic nomination. Really? Up until the last second, I thought it was going to be Sharpton. At any rate, I have to admit that I'm really uncertain about Kerry. Of course he's better than GW (a ham sandwich is better than Bush, and I don't even really like ham), but&nbsp;I'm really concerned about what Kerry will do if he does win in November. If he doesn't turn things around, I'll just have to...shoot him.   P.S. Yeah, yeah, I know the theoretical and philosophical implications of using the word "reality" to describe this world and all sorts of other post-pomo boo boos I made in this post, but bear with me, okay? Or just...shoot me!  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The hardest part about moving forward is not looking back. God, I sound like Felicity or something, but it's true.   I made a big change moving to NY and then I changed things again by moving back to IL. But what now? Part of the reason that I can't sleep is because I have absolutely NO idea what I want to do next. I'm not even sure what I'm capable of anymore. So, okay, it's not completely true that I have  no  idea what I want to do next. There are several things I'm pondering: moving to Chicago (if I can find a job there, I'm goin'); going back to school for a political science degree (then what, asshole?); applying for jobs at political organizations even without a political science degree; changing my name to Ninja Shufflepants-Savage.... But is there any bit of me in there? Can't I just ask someone what I'm supposed to do?   Let me explain a little about the first sentence I wrote in this post. I know that I wrote in previous posts that I wouldn't discuss my personal past in my blog. I even made a pact with myself not to think about my past in my everyday life too. But for someone as neurotic as me--maybe neurotic is too strong a word, I just overanalyze things too much--it's very difficult to just, well, maybe, let go. I know the past will just be the past soon enough. For now, it's an extreme nuisance. One that keeps me up until 3 in the AM.  It's also hard not to think about not having someone--you know. I can't help it. Even Jason Bourne had someone. And he's a trained assassin on the run from the CIA. Ha ha. Okay?  But when you've never had  it , it's difficult to think nonchalantly about  it , l-o-v-e. Well, gotta go finish watching  Felicity , Season 2.  Muhahahahaha.  P.S. Went to local bar Lunker's tonight. Thought I saw someone who looked like someone I once knew but it turned out not to be him/her. Almost gave me a heart attack. Good thing I only saw my friends. 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink The Butcher Cover   Welcome. 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just recently I learned how to play Texas Hold 'em (proper spelling?). It's pretty fun, and I've done all right, even though I still only have a vague idea what I'm doing. Almost won $25 buckeroos a couple of nights ago. "Almost" is awesome enough for me. And I might've secured me a nickname. See if you can guess what it is.  I must admit that I was never a big fan of playing cards. But when it comes to games, I'm not the most competitive person in the world, so I guess my play-by-the-seat-of-my-pants style is well-suited for just playin' cards with my pals, kind of thing. Although I do have friends who are extremely competitive when playing cards. Some wear dark glasses. Or grumble about every missed hand. I wear a confused grin. I like to make stupid bets, win some hands, AND make my friends laugh at my stupidity...or is it my supreme cleverness? Muhahahaha. Whatever, it works for me. Well, until we start playing for loads of cash. Then I'll have to get serious. Or get out while I still have $$ in the bank.  I really really want to see "The Bourne Supremacy." Don't hate me. I have a thing for that Matt Damon. I also want to see "The Manchurian Candidate" and yeah, even "Napoleon Dynamite. I need a frickin' job!  Mourn the dead, I said as much.  &nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I can't help but laugh at myself for posting twice about Coach K possibly leaving Duke and then not writing about the fact that he's NOT leaving Duke after all. I guess there's no furor over that. Well, at least in my mind. &nbsp; Poor Martha (insert Martha Stewart joke here). Even though I've got major issues with Martha (although her sheets are sooo soft), I don't believe that she should go to prison. I mean, if Ken Lay doesn't get the noose... &nbsp; Don't you hate looking at old (and possibly new or new-ish) pictures and seeing people whom you're not in contact with anymore? It's kind of sad. 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here are some thoughts about my friends' wedding last weekend: &nbsp; 1. I didn't trip. 2. The ceremony was short and sweet. 3. I teared up, twice (once during the ceremony when the groom started tearing up and then during the best man's speech at dinner). 4. I realized just how amazing my friends Sarah and Mark are.  5. Bright pink lipstick looks good on me.  6. I can't smile for very long w/o my cheeks shaking. 7. I hate the song "Rump Shaker." 8. Sarah looked sooo beautiful. Luminous. 9. It's kinda nice not having a date at a wedding. 10. I didn't make out w/ any boy(s). 11. Sarah's best friend is awesome, as were the other bridesmaids. 12. Open bars are rockin', and more importantly, very generous additions to weddings. 13. The Mark Twain is a nice hotel. Sage is a good color for hotel rooms. 14. Getting your makeup done is fun. Getting it done at 8 in the morning is not as fun. 15. I like dancing w/ my male friends. Also my female friends. 16. Vodka and watermelon Pucker is a bit much for one drink. 17. Kingsley and CJ are delightful cats. (Oh wait, that's not part of the wedding!) 18. Now what do I do? &nbsp; I hope they're having fun on their honeymoon. See you soon! &nbsp; Good night. 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Can I say (write) that I really really like that Ashlee Simpson song? Yes, I can.  Weird day at the eye doctor yesterday. Mostly weird because I met with a doctor named Robert Lee (sadly, his middle initial is M) and a contact tech named Kermit. Then I had strange confrontations with a woman who had been in a coma after a car accident and a man who thought he was a modern-day prophet. Okay, so maybe that doesn't sound so weird, but I started the day by coming into the family room where my dad was watching CNN and giving the thumbs-up to John Edwards, who had just been announced as Kerry's running mate. If you've read my previous posts, you'd know why THAT was weird.  The wedding march is playing like a broken record in my head. I wonder why. Oh, that's right! One of my good friends is getting married on Saturday! Yippee! I think it's going to be one, rockin' affair. Details on my bridesmaid abilities next week. He he.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Man Says He Shot Dingo That Snatched Baby By MIKE CORDER, AP  SYDNEY, Australia (July 5) - A distraught mother's scream 24 years ago that a dingo snatched her baby from a camp site near Ayers Rock in the Australian Outback ignited one of Australia's most enduring mysteries.  An elderly man's claim that he retrieved the infant's bloodied body from the jaws of the wild dog has revived the case and - if true - could finally lead to the discovery of Azaria Chamberlain's body.  Two-month-old Azaria disappeared from a campsite near the giant Ayers Rock monolith, also known by its Aboriginal name Uluru, in 1980.  Her mother, Lindy Chamberlain, now remarried and known as Lindy Chamberlain-Creighton, was convicted of murdering her infant but later released from prison and cleared of the crime after fresh evidence supported her claim that a dingo took the child.  The mystery took a startling turn Sunday when a newspaper in the southern city of Melbourne published claims by 87-year-old Frank Cole that he shot the dog with Azaria's body still in its jaws while on a camping trip with three friends in August 1980.  Cole told the Sunday Herald Sun that he did not tell police what he did, fearing he would be fined for shooting the dog, thinking it was a rabbit he could use for pet food.  He said one of his friends took Azaria's body and never said what he did with it. All three of Cole's friends from the camping trip have since died, he said. Cole said he believed one of the men could have buried the baby's body in his Melbourne garden.  Police said Monday they would investigate the claims, which Cole said he made to clear his conscience.  "I think that we now need to make some inquiries to determine whether or not it's a valid statement or whatever it might be," said Christine Nixon, police commissioner in Victoria state, of which Melbourne is the capital.  "This is a matter that the whole of Australia has watched for many years, and it seems to me that we need to just go and establish the fundamentals, whether or not there's anything that we should be concerned about," Nixon said.  Lindy Chamberlain, who served four years in prison after being convicted of murder in 1982 and before being cleared of the killing, said through a spokeswoman on Sunday that she was aware of Cole's claims and believed they were a matter for police.  Australians avidly followed her trial in the 1980s and were split over whether to believe her story.  "The Dingo Did It" and "The Dingo Is Innocent," were common bumper stickers while she was on trial.  Azaria was the first recorded fatality attributed to a dingo attack in Australia and there has been only one fatal dingo attack since.  While police plan to investigate, Cole's claims also have been met with skepticism.  Paul Everingham, who was political leader of the Northern Territory province where Azaria went missing, said he doubted the claim.  "I find it hard to believe, maybe it's right but I'm not buying it. Certainly not at this stage," Everingham told Australian Broadcasting Corp. radio. He suggested the timing of the claim could have been linked to an Australian television network's movie, which is being made about Azaria's disappearance.  "I found it pretty amazing that someone would come forward at this late juncture, more or less coincidentally with the launch" of the television movie, Everingham said.  The story of Azaria's disappearance already was made into a 1988 Hollywood movie, "A Cry in the Dark," starring Meryl Streep and Sam Neill.  Everingham also cast doubt on Cole's claim he feared prosecution for hunting near Ayers Rock.  "I just find it very hard to believe that someone would have felt it necessary to hide the fact that he was hunting around Ayers Rock, if indeed he was," he said.  "And I would imagine that a gunshot in the vicinity of Ayers Rock would have had the rangers hurtling like a speeding bullet, if I could use a bad pun, towards the sound of the shot," he added.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Letterman’s Top Ten List: “Top Ten George W. Bush Complaints About "Fahrenheit 9/11":  10. That actor who played the President was totally unconvincing  9. It oversimplified the way I stole the election  8. Too many of them fancy college-boy words  7. If Michael Moore had waited a few months, he could have included the part where I get him deported  6. Didn't have one of them hilarious monkeys who smoke cigarettes and gives people the finger  5. Of all Michael Moore's accusations, only 97% are true  4. Not sure - - I passed out after a piece of popcorn lodged in my windpipe  3. Where the hell was Spider-man?  2. Couldn't hear most of the movie over Cheney's foul mouth  1. I thought this was supposed to be about dodgeball 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I should've explained why I was mad that the LA Lakers are in "serious discussions" (why serious? Would the alternative be "comical discussions"?) with Coach K (men's coach of the almighty Duke Blue Devils--don't send me hate mail!) in regard to the head coaching job vacancy at the Lakers. Do you all really want to hear this? Well, several of you who I think read this blog know why I'm mad, but I'll just explain it again.  Okay, since the early 90s (the Grant Hill, Christian Laettner era), I've been a fan of Duke basketball. I can't completely explain why I'm a Dukie. I really disliked basketball before that time. I think part of it was because my brother and father were (and are) so into sports, and I wanted to establish some common ground with them. I wanted to be able to bond with them on another level, besides the basic blood relative, obligatory bonding level. Call it cheesy or stereotypical (ooh! Boys like sports! I want to like sports too!) or whatever, but that's how I felt. But I also really liked how basketball is played at Duke, a school centered on academics as well as college b-ball. I liked how many of the players stayed all four years at college (until very recently of course, but I won't go into that frustration now), earning a degree that would be their "something to fall back on" in case NBA Hoop Dreams didn't work out. Call me naive or simple, but that's how I felt. I thought Coach K was an honorable coach, and his players were articulate and poised on and off the court. I loved their fierce rivalries with Michigan (Fab 5 era) and North Carolina. I just came to LOVE Duke basketball!  Well, it did take me awhile to realize that a lot of basketball fans hate Duke and all that they stand for. Some people even compare them to the Evil Empire of the Yankees, even though Coach K hasn't had to buy his players to win. Conspiracy theories and hate websites may abound for Duke, but it just comes down to the simple fact that they can get it done.   So I'm a little pissed off that Luol Deng left Duke after only one year there, giving Duke fans only a brief glimpse of his burgeoning talent. I won't even mention Shaun Livingston. I hope they both fair well in the NBA, although according to several of the commentators covering the draft, it seems that the only people who will win are the agents.  Can one possibly become a Bulls fan again?  I did hear that Carlos Boozer is doing very well in the NBA. Let's hope that the Cavaliers give him the contract he deserves. Well, he may not deserve all of that $$, but you know what I mean. Maybe you don't. Oh well, I'm just a crazed Duke fan talking.   Can't wait for November. Well, unless Coach K leaves Duke. Perish the thought!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink  The Nation 's review of Michael Moore's "Fahrenheit 9/11." 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm going to stop talking about negative events in the past right.....now!  Ahh, I feel so much better now.  I should clarify. I mean negative events that have occurred in the past in MY LIFE. It's all boring, right?  Okay......now!  (I've also made some changes to my previous posts. Out with the old...)
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I won't comment any more on the film, "Fahrenheit 9/11." I, oddly enough, commented on it a lot even before I saw the film. I will admit that it was so much better than I thought it would be. For the most part, Moore let the images speak for themselves. Like I've always said, we don't need anyone to make Bush, Cheney, Ashcroft, Rummy, etc. look like fools. They do that so well all on their own. But I think you should go see the film. And there are many people who've commented on the film much more eloquently than I can.  Okay, now I've said too much.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I'm going to try and see "Fahrenheit 9/11" with my mom tonight. It'll be interesting to see and hear my mom's reaction to the film and its gruesome images. She doesn't know a lot about Moore, and she mainly gets her news from mainstream news sources, but also has to suffer through watching Fox News, which my father watches every night. Right now though, she seems to be very open to alternative viewpoints. She hasn't been indoctrinated by Fox News, thank goodness. She was/is also very much against the invasion and occupation of Iraq. I think at this point, it's important to take into account the type of filmmaker Michael Moore is, but to also see the images for what they are, singularly, and within the context of the film. I know that a lot of what I'll see will be shocking (from what I gather from friends who have seen it), but I won't be at all surprised. In reading and listening to alternative news sources, I've learned a lot about what the corporate media isn't revealing to us. And I don't have much sympathy for those who cry "bias" when talking about "Fahrenheit 9/11." I think it's much more dangerous to call yourself "fair and balanced," while being totally biased to the extreme right. Yeah, I'm talkin' about you Fox Not-Fucking News!  So go see "Fahrenheit 9/11," and then to balance it all out, go see "Spiderman." Because both movies certainly need your money!
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lakers, Krzyzewski in 'Serious Discussions' Duke Coach has Won Three NCAA Titles By AARON BEARD, AP SPORTS   DURHAM, N.C. (July 1) -- Duke's Mike Krzyzewski met with Los Angeles Lakers general manager Mitch Kupchak on Thursday and was in "serious discussions" with the team about its coaching vacancy.  Krzyzewski, a 57-year-old Hall of Famer, has led the Blue Devils to three national championships in almost a quarter-century at the school.  "Coach K has informed us that the Los Angeles Lakers have contacted him and entered into serious discussions to fill their vacant head coaching position," Duke athletic director Joe Alleva said.  Lakers spokesman John Black said Kupchak met with Krzyzewski. "They talked about our coaching vacancy," he said.  Black said the team hasn't made a decision, and was considering several other candidates to replace Phil Jackson.  Alleva said he didn't know if the Krzyzewski and the Lakers were close to a deal.  "I haven't been privy to their conversations," he said. "But obviously, they are a great franchise."  Duke spokesman Jon Jackson said Krzyzewski was in Durham earlier Thursday. The Lakers declined to say where the discussions were held.  An attempt to reach Krzyzewski by phone was unsuccessful.  By Thursday night, about 100 students and fans gathered at "Krzyzewskiville" -- the grassy plot outside Cameron Indoor Stadium where students camp out to attend Blue Devil basketball games -- with signs and flags urging the coach to stay.  Duke president Richard Brodhead told The Associated Press he and Alleva had dinner with Krzyzewski on Tuesday, after Brodhead became aware that the coach had talked with the Lakers.  Brodhead said he didn't know if the Lakers offered Krzyzewski the job.     "If he has the offer, he's going to have a big decision before him," said Brodhead, who officially took office as Duke's president Thursday, succeeding Nan Keohane.  Brodhead said he and Alleva urged Krzyzewski to finish his career at the school.  "He means more to this place than the record of his victories, impressive though that is," Brodhead said. "He's a real teacher. He teaches character as well as basketball."  Krzyzewski has a 621-179 record in 24 seasons at Duke, leading the Blue Devils to NCAA championships in 1991, 1992 and 2001. Under Krzyzewski, the Blue Devils have 10 Final Four appearances, eight Atlantic Coast Conference tournament championships and 10 conference regular-season titles.  His Duke teams have been ranked No. 1 in 12 different seasons, including each of the last seven years.  "If he decides that he's had a great ride at Duke, but something else calls out to him now, we'd have to understand that," Brodhead said. "In the meantime, you can be sure we'll do all we can to persuade him that Duke and the college game are the right place for him."  The mother of incoming freshman David McClure, said her son was first informed of the news in a call from assistant coach Steve Wojciechowski on Thursday.  Betty McClure said she spoke with Krzyzewski over the weekend when the family brought the 6-foot-7 swingman to Durham for summer classes, and the coach gave no indication of leaving.  "They said that every year he gets approached by some team or another," she said from her home in Ridgefield, Conn. "And so, how can you really expend a lot of energy being angry or anything until you know what he's going to do?"  David McClure, reached Thursday night, said he had been told by the coaching staff not to comment.  The Lakers announced June 18 -- three days after losing to the Detroit Pistons in the NBA Finals -- that Jackson wouldn't return as coach next season. Jackson, who signed a five-year, $30 million contract with the Lakers in June 1999, guided them to championships in his first three seasons.  Former Rockets coach Rudy Tomjanovich has been considered the front-runner to succeed Jackson. He met with team owner Jerry Buss and Kupchak last week.  Former Lakers coach Pat Riley, an executive with the Miami Heat, also met with Buss and Kupchak, but issued a statement saying he wasn't a candidate.  Among others mentioned have been Kurt Rambis and Jim Cleamons, members of Jackson's staff. Kupchak said he planned to interview more than one person and less than 10 for the job and hoped to have a coach in place as soon as possible.     Last month, Detroit Pistons coach Larry Brown became the first coach to win titles in both the NBA and NCAA. But Brown is the exception to the general trend of college coaches struggling in the NBA.  Rick Pitino went from two straight appearances in the national title game with Kentucky to the Boston Celtics, before quitting in 2001 and later returning to the college ranks with Louisville.  In 1992, Jerry Tarkanian, whose UNLV team won a national title in 1990, lasted just 20 games before being fired by the San Antonio Spurs with a 9-11 record.  More recently, former college coaches Lon Kruger, John Calipari, Leonard Hamilton and Tim Floyd have struggled during short tenures with the Atlanta Hawks, New Jersey Nets, Washington Wizards and New Orleans Hornets, respectively.  07/01/04 22:25 EDT
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There's this person in my life, and I'm not sure why I keep holding on to him/her. Do you have those kinds of people in your life too? It's just that we shared moments, good ones and probably bad ones (on my end, at least), but we never talk about those moments. It's like they never happened. (Remember, these are things you  should  talk about.) And yet this person is still in contact with me. Why? For what? I've never confronted the person about how I feel, so my confusion keeps going. And going.  I like Billy Crudup.  I HATE calling people long distance. And talking for a long time. Sometimes.  I can't decide if I like baseball. I've said in the past that I dislike it, even hate it.  The weather was beautiful today. Cool wind.  I wish it were still my birthday. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I can't sleep and that asshole from Creed (well, they're all assholes, but especially the lead singer) has a solo album coming out. I've officially entered the Twilight Zone. Or, the "Here's Another Reason Why I Shouldn't Listen To The Radio" Zone.  Maybe I'll take a trip to that Poconos sport shooting center.  In other news, I can't sleep. Any suggestions?
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Damn it. Can't sleep. Again. For probably the 20th night in a row.  This is bad. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You put the beer in the coconut and throw the can away. You put the beer in the coconut and throw the can away. Throw the can away.  Some thoughts regarding my birthday fun on Sat.:  1. I only had 2 Blue Moons to drink, I swear! 2. Yeah, right. 3. Grady's Pizza and Mini-Golf sucks! They wouldn't let me and my friends eat a birthday cake (made deliciously by a pal), unless it was a part of their birthday package deal. We sat on a picnic table at a nearby animal hospital and ate the cake with our fingers (I forgot to bring the plates and forks). My friend carried the knife around in a paper towel roll. 4. If you do go to Grady's, make sure you smoke on the golf course and swear a lot. They like that. 5. My friends like to celebrate my birthday by getting me plastered. They succeeded. 6. I like to kiss people, whether on the cheek or on the lips, when I'm intoxicated. 7. No more Lemondrop shots!!! 8. No more lemon slices with sugar on them!!! 9. Tom Ridge raised the terror alert because of my drunken disorderly-ness last night. It's now a lovely shade of baby poop green. 10. I love my friends. They like me. 11. Thanks Salina for driving me home last night! 12. To anyone and everyone, I apologize for anything I said or did that was indecent, excessive (except the drinking part, of course), or unusual. 13. I have a mosquito bite on my forehead. 14. Thank you! 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>