<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      XP recovery console Imagine the situation, you are about to start your days work on your trusty computer when blimey, the thing won’t boot up. The reason could be a dodgy driver or an unknown virus may have the master boot record all in a tizzy, the first thing you do is try the automatic recovery to try and return to the last know configuration (Usually f8 when booting then choose safe mode from the menu options then all programs/ accessories/system tools/system restore ). If this doesn’t work you will have wished you had installed the little know recovery console supplied on the XP disk. This tool is not installed as default by Microsoft so you will have to do it yourself. It takes a mere 7MB and will take about 30 to 45 minutes. Insert your XP disk and from the run box and type in or browse to d\i386\WINNT32.EXE /cmdcons and press OK (d being shown as the letter drive your XP disk is in) . You will be prompted through the installation process which when complete will add the option to boot into the recovery console upon start up. HOW TO USE IT Once selected from the boot up screen you will have to choose a which installation you want to go to, this is for people that have multiple systems on their computer so if you only have 1 press 1 and enter. You should now be at the system root which is usually C:/windows A full list of commands is available at the HELP section, just type help and enter and you will be told everything that the recovery console can do, Pressing the space bar continues the list. The important tools that don’t require much technical knowledge are the ones you may already of used in DOS such as diskpart, format and chkdsk. Chkdsk searches a disk or file for errors and repairs them. Diskpart is a partition tool for creating / deleting partitions and format is exactly that, a format disk tool. If you are having problems getting past boot up then try the fixboot command. The other common problem is a virus infecting you master boot record or MBR and the solution is to type in fixmbr although it is important to get it scanned with an antivirus program if you can as this can lead to partitions you might not be able to access. Another Useful command is the listsvc command which lists all services and drivers so if you have an idea where your problem may lie you can simply type disable / followed by which service you want to stop and the same with the enable / command. You should be able to save yourself having to re-install windows so it’s worth having , even if you never use it. More help is available at the Microsoft site.  urlLink Support.Microsoft.com/?kbid=314058  As with all tools which enable you to change the registry please exercise caution, take it to a professional if at all unsure. Mark white  urlLink http://www.sunspeks.com   urlLink http://www.phone-bits.com   
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A guide to buying stock for your site and not losing your money!!   Very important  There are a large amount of valuable resources on the web, any information you want you can find, no problem.  There is also unlimited access to suppliers more than happy to sell you their wares.  There are a huge amount of people who will do anything to take your money and give you nothing! These people do this for a living and can seem VERY convincing.  Here are a few pointers so you don't get scammed.   1. Anyone who says please pay me via western union is to be viewed with suspicion, western union say you may ask for a password to be given by the collecting party to ensure your money is collected by the right person, some scammers will send you copies of fed ex or UPS emails asking for your password so they can release the goods for delivery to you and as proof that you will pay for the goods,walk away from the deal and count your lucky stars. Reputable suppliers will not use western union, no matter how safe it seems you will not be protected against fraud, large dealers only deal in telegraphic / bank transfer or TT as it is called and ALWAYS check the account name is a company, NOT an individual.   2. Stay away from people that trade from free pages such as geocity, persopages etc, these are free pages given to subscribers of internet ISPs NOT dot com businesses, proper agents and brokers of manufacturers will have a web site of their own outlining terms / conditions and products,usually without prices (you will have to email them for that information).   3. Always make sure that you can contact at least one or two other people at the company you are about to deal with, the cost of an international call could save you thousands.The email address used when you to contact the seller should not be a free one I:E @yahoo , @msn and alike, always check the contact link at a web site gives the same send to address as you are sending your mail to and email someone else at the company asking if your contact works there.   4. Never email your passwords to anyone!! ,This may be basic internet security but you may be duped into trusting the scam artist , he/she will call you friend and you may believe they are genuine and trustworthy. Never return a form which has been sent via email and requires any of your personal information as you never know where it is going, the senders address can be faked as can the supposed return address . Right click on any email, go to properties / details /message source and see for yourself   5. If a deal seems to good to be true, it usually is. Don't believe for a second you can buy £1500 laptops for £500, you can't and you won't. Expect to make 20 to 40% on a really good deal. Less if you cannot afford to buy the minimum order quantity or MOQ.   6. Don't end up paying other people for trade lists or wholesale directories. They can be quite expensive and as long as you follow the guidelines I have set out above then you should be ok. I will give some useful suppliers links to whoever asks for them in the forum on my site.  Not all doom and gloom.  Let's not end on a low.  There are some amazing deals out there in www land and some superb companies to deal with, most of them are solid as a rock and will give you all the help and support you are looking for when you want to set up your little business empire.  I believe the internet buying public will not forgive us if we make a mistake so we must all strive to offer the same service to our customers that we as business people expect from our suppliers. This is a sure way of ensuring our success.   &nbsp;  PS  Western union is the idea solution for auctions or for sending international money transfers to friends/family or reputable companies you know and trust.  Kind regards  Mark White   My sites if you want a look are  urlLink sunspeks.com  and  urlLink phone-bits.com   Please feel free to copy these articles, all I ask is that you make reference to the source and the author.    
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          A Beginners guide          to websites and traffic. Part 2. By Mark White              Now you have decided what to sell and have the skeleton            of a website you must customise it so it looks good and does what you            want it to.            You either pay some one like me to spruce it up and personalise it,            or do it yourself, either way you have ended up with the basic format            for your online shop or forum or whatever.            Now for the important bits, content and ease of use for the potential            customer and getting seen by as many people as possible so you can get            some money rolling in.             Tags n&#8217; things             Very important the next bit so please pay attention.            Search engines all work in different ways but your pages MUST include            meta tags ,titles and a good descriptive section with all your key words            in. These keywords are absolutely vital to getting people to you.            Two of the best resources around are the meta tag generator here              urlLink www.freewebsubmission.com             and keyword generator here              urlLink http://www.wordtracker.com/             More freebies are available at www.sitepronews.com . urlLink www.sitepronews.com              Traffic             No, not car and trucks and things on wheels but real people            who really want to part with their hard earned money for something you            are offering.            How do you keep a track of all these people? Well those nice people            at  urlLink www.bravenet.com             are going to give you a counter so you can get a true picture of how            you are doing.            The counters and registration are free and you can subscribe to a newsletter            that is full of really good stuff for your new creation.            For a newbie to the programming world bravenet are an absolute must,            these are real experts and the links are a valuable resource so take            your time to have a good look at their site.                      The look             Don&#8217;t go over board with loads of flashing, spinning            icons, these just distract the viewer from the main point of your site            which is to look at your stuff.            That said it never hurts to try an get some revenue from people who            offer affiliations, one of the best sites around in my humble opinion            is  urlLink www.tradedoubler.com             .             This is a site packed full of major players on the web and the high            street who will pay you a small percentage for getting people from your            site to theirs to buy from them.            Registration is free and easy and as long as you pick carefully and            make sure that the items they sell complement yours then you should            get a small amount of revenue coming your way to help pay for the maintenance            of your site.            Just remember ,DON&#8217;T overdo it, You are not a fairground full            of distractions you are a professional online retailer of either goods            or information .             The shop             There are a lot of ways to sort out a way of taking money            in your cyber shop but the one I swear by is paypal&#8217;s online shop.            You must get an account sorted out but it is easy and free and once            done you can accept money in any currency and transfer it straight into            your bank account. Their customer service is good and both you, the            seller, and the buyer get a lot of protection against fraud. You can            get set up by visiting this link.             www.paypal.com. urlLink www.paypal.com              Your generous host             With your site all optimised ready for the engines and            the shop front looking spick and span you can take the step towards            going live. Pick a good name and then pick a good host.            I have used  urlLink 1&1.com             for my sites and they have never let me down with excellent customer            support. They are very competitive with their prices and have hosting            plans and bundled software to really get you started in the best possible            way.              More traffic             With everything loaded onto your host&#8217;s server and            the public waiting to storm your paypal account with money you can just            sit back and count the readies right?&#8230;. Wrong, search engines            need to be fed and told you are out there waiting to do business. First            job is to get some advice from a genius, no ,not me but my cyber guru            / genius, mentor and all over good egg ,Tinu AbayomiPaul.            The website of all websites for search engine busting advice from a            person who really knows what goes where and why is an absolute must            for anyone wishing to succeed in today&#8217;s market place and you            will get the chance to meet other people in the same situation as you            so you don&#8217;t feel all alone in the big bad cyber world.            The site is  urlLink freetrafficdirectory.com             as the name implies it wont cost you a penny for all this free advice            and the services offered to its members go on and on and on and on&#8230;&#8230;,            you get the picture right? So just subscribe to the news letter by sending            a blank email to  urlLink ftdsecrets-subscribe@topica.com             and get that traffic thundering to you down the telephone line. Just            remember, she&#8217;s my guru so don&#8217;t upset her.              Result !!!!!             After a while ( 1 to 6 months ) you should start to see            some results and next time I write I will talk about reciprocal linking            (joining forces with other sites )and its importance in getting noticed            and Ebay , the best place to find a massive audience. 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A Beginners guide to websites and traffic. By Mark White   When you take the first step into the scary world of business online everything seems to be against you and very, very unnerving . You search a few forums and get hit with sentences like “ search engine optimisation “ , “ reciprocal links “ or “ meta tags “ and all of a sudden you are cast into the harsh world of computers when you have to learn a whole new language just to move forward. Well, here I go and try and make those first few steps a little easier with the aid of some of the most useful sites and pieces of information I have found.  Me  I am not an expert, just an average bloke who wanted to work for himself and have a bit of freedom with his work and now my workplace.  My first site was based on a friend of mine’s unfortunate redundancy from an optical factory which used to make the lenses for some of the high end sunglasses market telling me that there was an enormous profit to be had by buying fashion sunglasses and selling them on. I tried for over three months to get these factories I had found on the internet to sell me a selection at wholesale price but at every corner I was given an absolute no!, not to be put off I went the way of replica sunglasses and found the opposite happened and everyone wanted me to buy from them, great , I found my supplier’s, now all I had to do was sell them.  The 1st step  This happened with the help of an ex-pupil ,( I used to be a driving instructor in the UK ) who worked as a website designer. He started me on the path of owning your own website and I thank him for his patience when he tried, and I am pleased to say, succeeded in teaching me all about website design and macromedia dream weaver.(.macromedia.com) If you want to try and design your own site dream weaver is very simple to use although a little expensive. There are cheaper and, if you are lucky free programs for designing your own site to be had out there in cyberspace and a good place to start is one of my favourite freebie and useful information sites around site pro news ( urlLink  www.sitepronews.com  )  Sitepro news  When I stumbled onto this site I couldn’t believe my luck, they have everything a person on the web could possibly want, need or desire. This ranges from a newsletter full of really excellent tips and information to a range of resources from site engine submitters to optimisation tools, all of them free or very cheap to use. The adverts for services and tools that are available to you are subtle and you never feel that you are being pressured into buying something you may not need. They often feature links to sites that will be happy to sell you a template for a website , each to their own I say and if you want to get your site up and running as soon as possible then pre made templates are the way to go if not then sitepro news also offer superb HTML (programming language) snippets which you can cut and paste in your site.  My sites if you want a look are  urlLink sunspeks.com  and  urlLink phone-bits.com     Please feel free to copy these articles, all I ask is that you make reference to the source and the author.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>