<Blog>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
          Time has really fly, In a blink of an eye.. It seems now we have to cry, As its time to say goodbye…  I know how it feels like deep down inside, I can tell from how you smile… I can tell that you heart is opposite of your smiles…  This little things here, Are all stuffs I’ve not let you hear.. But this little things here, Are all that I want to tell your ears.. Please hold on to your tears, As I’m afraid I’m not here…  Thanks is part of my says, But cries will be all it takes…  You’re that little stars in my dreams… You’re that little shines that made me smile… You’ve done a lot I shall say, You’ve cured that little wounds that were still wet inside, And now it has partially dried…  “Thank You is too less for me to say”… But for how everything takes, These little poems are my show of gratitude to you…  Sorry I shall say too, In times I may be too much than usual… I may have hurt you, But I didn’t know… I might… But you kept quiet… Your silence has brought me to a mystery, Which I hope I can find out…   -Nisa-",  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
        You are all that I’m left with, Don’t leave me lying around in others arms, When you’re still around, And I can see you….       I find it hopeless,   To go high above... I find no way to feel that love, Cuz’ you seem to treat me like a stove… I can’t find replaces, As you are the only one that I seem to love...      Now that you’re gone, I thought life was easier… But I was wrong, Now that I’m caught in a middle of two… I feel so tight,  I feel like being someone new… It all happens because of you.    ^-Nisa-^", 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      WEehEeEe... Bez BasKetball Session I've had!...LoLz..  Guess wat? i Was stripped!! By the mOSt Awful Creatures of earth!!... Haaz...Couldn't believe it man!!...lOL..okie..was juX a joke aniwae..this Stripping game "invented" by daphne..(nvr tot of her wud b lyk tis) haha... First was rachel den Yanni Den me..Wah PowDerful Man!!..i tink mine lasted long..cuz' i was strugglin like Rats...(that wat they called me)hehe..i was kickin away..i tink i kicked daphne there*ouch* sorry..hahah.. but well they managed to strip me at the left..abit onie.. to see my undies.. Lyk Wad sia~~..haha..lucky i got ware PE SHORTS!!..hahaha.. then this CUTE little MEI of MINE..take picture of me..Humph!!..hahaha.. funnie sia..deN the game ended...daphne ran away..go home..wat sia..hahaha....wahh..My body was lyk jUx comin out of a hot bath..So Wetty and So hotty.hahaz!!...bt i noe was jUx a PRank...hahaz.. K den go HoMe time.. RAn Lyk CraZy Ger to catch the bus..hahaha... RachEl jie la..haha.. bud cannot blame her run slow~..she takin alot thin..Well..(file and deflated bball onie ma?)...hahaha.. okie okie...hMm..den got home..do this dat this dat..den HEre I am online..chat chat...do bLoggy...hMmz...nth to do tonite Siaz..tINk watch incredible tales and Smallville lor?..No ShoW liaoz....ahhhhh!!..i mIss suMoNe Sia.. -Barbie- ahakz.. okok.. dats' abt it for tonite!
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Monday Mornin 7th June...  Feelin fresh...A dae after 3 daes of band camp....... Listenin to 2 finale songs For the Investiture...Missing them (seniors) .. well its part and parcel of life in the band... My batch takin over..New Majorss.. My heartous congratulations to 4! .. Feelin bery happi for them..Potential ones..To all others' who haf got a post..Congrats too! To those who didn't..Its okie..there'll be next year... I believe the band will move on to a better Band and not forgeting CCA in the school... My mind still reads the nite of the Investiture..i Still can't forget about it.. But one still questions me... Why did "chilli" cried?..Izzit bcuz' of the Grand Finale too "feeling" or izzit bcuz' we've created a poem which has hurt her?... I hope that it wasn't bcuz' of a phrase dat she cried..I hope its bcuz' of the 2 finales... That nite, though there were laughters..tissues still filled the room.... Well, who would not feel sad? when you've to part wit your seniors.. especially when u are really close to them.. You shared alot with them..Ure tears,ure anger,ure laughters..Almost everythin...(that goes for me too)...hmm..well.. wateva it is... we haf to carry on our duties that has been passed down to us.... and make..   ...HSSCB a better home for all members cold but yet warm...  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>