<Blog>

<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well, thanks to Sheri sharing her blog site with me I decided to create one with the same web site host. Maybe, just maybe I'll update this more than I do with my other sites. 

						
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I'm about to head out to see Elvis and thought I should write a little about yesterday. I've begun to fully recover from my eye infection and the flu seems to have run its course. I was able to make it to football practice yesterday for the first time. It was nice having the whistle around my neck again. I got myself beat up pretty bad by the players in a hitting drill where I was the tackling dummy. I then played a full contact game with them, scoring two touchdowns, but paying the price in bruised arms and ribs.  After a short nap I was ready for a night out on the town with some good folks. It was an all right night but not busy enough for my liking. Even though I was sick and had pounded myself through a football practice, I outlasted the group, finally going to bed at 4:30.   I'm headed out again tonight alone this time. Greggie is in Lethbridge. I'm going to catch the Elvis show and then maybe head over to the Heritage depending on how I'm feeling come midnight/1 a.m.   

						
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I'm stealing this from Sheri as well.  100 Things About Me. 1. My name is Cody Wayne Todd. 2. I was born in Calgary May 16, 1980 3. I am the third generation in my family to be born in Calgary at the Holy Cross Hospital. 4. My middle name comes from John Wayne. 5. I lived in the same neighbourhood in Calgary for all but three of my childhood years. 6. Favourite colour is black followed by blue. 7. I wore two different numbers when I played football. #80 and #18. 8. The farthest I've traveled is Israel and Phoenix, Arizona. 9. I drove to Arizona in a Nissan truck worth $500 with no power steering. 10. I drink Pepsi. 11. I drink Coke with rum, never Pepsi. 12. Favourite candy is jelly beans 13. Favourite bands are Creedence Clearwater Revival, Beatles, and just about anything trip hop. 14. I listen to classical and opera music. 15. I have one younger brother. 16. I've only loved two women in my life (still do) 17. I never dated either one of them. 18. We are still close friends. 19. Favourite food is pumpkin pie 20. I don't like green or black olives unless they are on pizza 21. I like cats more than dogs. 22. I've had two medical conditions doctors have never been able to explain. One was swelling of my joints to a point where I could not move and screamed in pain for hours. The second was a lung infection of sorts that prevented me from doing anything more streneous than walking for almost a year. 23. I recovered from the swollen joints. I still have problems with my lungs. 24. Favourite sound is rain falling. 25. Favourite smell is cinnimon mixed with warm pumpkin. 26. Favourite feeling is soft skin 27. Favourite taste is anything sweet 28. I love to read. 29. I read War and Peace by Leo Tolstoy (1,600 pages) in Grade 8. My teacher didn't think it was possible. I even gave a book report. 30. I hate indecisive people. 31. I thought about being a professional dancer. 32. The first movie that made me cry was Pinocchio. 33. My first poem was published when I was 17. 34. My first newspaper column was published in the Calgary Herald when I was 17. 35. My first published photograph was in the High River Times. 36. I have never won money. 37. I think sex is overrated. Foreplay and the cuddling together after are better. 38. I write on a manual typewriter. 39. I think Winona Ryder, Helena Bonham Carter and Sophie Marceau are the sexiest movie stars in the world. 40. My favourite movie star is Robert Redford. 41. I hate Steve Martin and Julie Roberts. 42. A scar on my lip came from falling off a playground at age 3. 43. I have two scars on my left hand. 44. I ran away from home once. 45. I broke a kid's arm in Grade 4. 46. I can be ultra competitive. 47. I won second place in the Calgary Science fair when I was 12. 48. I have been single for 8 years. 49. The last real date I went on was five years ago. 50. I've never played hockey. 51. I never thought the New Kids on the Block were cool. 52. I only chew Big Red gum. 53. I hate rap music. 54. I use to have problems sleeping. I would go days without sleeping. 55. I had problems with depression and self esteem in elementary school. 56. I've gained 70 pounds since high school. 57. People tell me my best feature is my eyes. I tend to agree. 58. I notice eyes on a woman first. 59. I like short women. 60. My favourite season is summer. 61. I coach football. 62. I wear boxer briefs. 63. My favourite author is Hemingway. 64. I've never thought about suicide. 65. I've rescued two friends from suicide from pills. 66. I prank called teachers when I was in junior high school. 67. I want to get an English degree. 68. I am trying to write a novel. 69. I've never shared so much about myself as I've done on the this list. 70. I always sleep on my left shoulder. 71. I have one living grandparent and one living great-grandparent. 72. I've done nude photography. 73. I've never done drugs. 74. I hate shopping. 75. I love bookstores. 76. I've dressed up as a woman. 77. I once pretended to be dying from a rare disease. It was an April Fool's joke. Half the school fell for it. I was hated for weeks after. 78. I was part of security at a Default/Headstones concert. 79. I wish I could play the guitar. 80. I've never traveled to eastern Canada. 81. I like unhappy endings in movies. 82. I like sidekicks and not the heroes. 83. The ending of Braveheart makes me cry every time I watch it. 84. I bite the inside of my lip when I'm thinking. 85. I have a warrant in Arizona for an unpaid traffic ticket. 86. I have appeared in court on an alcohol charge and was fined $2,300. 87. My two best friends from high school are now drug addicts and I haven't spoken to them in three years. 88. I've never broken a bone in my body. 89. I have tore legiments in every joint. 90. I nearly lost both ears to severe frost bite when I was 17. I had blisters cover both ears blocking out sound for a week. The blisters took two weeks to go away and another month for my ears to heal. 91. I've lost most of the feeling in both ears. 92. My last hearing test said I can hear noises above that of the average person. I can hear sounds almost an octave higher. 93. My family was very poor when I was younger. Neighbours had to buy groceries for us. My parents never went on welfare. They worked where and when the could until things got better. 94. I'm proud of how well my family has done since those days. 95. I want to learn how to scuba dive and skydive. 96. I tried to join an expedition to Mount Everest as a photographer. 97. I don't believe in organized religion. 98. I believe people are inheritantly selfish. 99. There is no such thing as can't it's only a matter of what we are willing to do. 100. This was too hard. 

						
</post>

<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I was going to post a long entry on my feelings of tonight and the bar scene and that whole world but I decided sleep is more important. I will tell you after tomorrow night's birthday party bash I'm coming off the sauce. I have better things to spend my money on. I haven't sworn off going out to the bars, I'm just going to keep away from the bottle. Water will do fine.   

						
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Sorry, I just have to rant here for a moment. I was kicking around reading other blogs and I came across yet another person talking about U.S. interests in the Middle East who simplified it to one thing— oil. I get furious at people who point to this underlying policy as an evil thing. I'm not saying oil isn't the major focus of U.S. foreign policy, it is, but there are other motives for Middle East intervention and involvment from the U.S. To think otherwise, is childish and reactionary.  All those who think the U.S. should not be in Iraq, Iran, Saudi Arab etc. should consider why the government must protect the oil interests of the country. Why is Bush willing to spend billions of dollars to protect oil production in Iraq and stabilize the region? Answer: America's love of automobiles, television sets, fast food, warm homes, big buildings and everything else that has defined America and North America for the past century. Without oil North America does not move, does not produce. Factories run on oil. Transportation systems demand oil and gas.  All these bleeding hearts that call Bush's war on terrorism nothing more than a grab at oil are partly right for all the wrong reasons. Bush is trying to grab the oil. He's also dislodged the most evil man to walk this earth since Hitler. He's trying to provide something better for the Iraqi people. You can argue if he's succeeding in creating that better life for Iraqis. The point is he's trying. Where was the U.N.? Hundreds of thousands of Kurds were killed, gased, tortured and driven from Iraq. Iraqi people were killed, gased, tortured and driven from Iraq and yet the world sat and did nothing. But let's get back to the oil.  Those of you who want to convince Bush to leave Iraq and keep away from the Middle East I suggest you begin walking today. Get rid of your gas-guzzling SUVs. Forget about your factory build luxuries. I hope you like to read by candlelight. Those with strong backs will be needed in our new oil-free utopia. We will need you to harvest our food by hand like it was done before tractors. By now you should be getting the point. This planet runs on oil and gas. There is no turning back. We can move forward and are moving forward. We are finding more effecient ways of using oil and gas and have even come up with alternative power but we will always need oil.  I could talk about the shift in power which would result in not having direct control of  the Middle East but I might save that for another day.  He who controls oil, controls those around him.   

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   As you can tell from the post earlier, I spent most of the day resenting the work I do. I feel unsatisfied, disconnected and disjointed with my world. I say my world because we all live in our own world according to our perceptions, biases and prejudices. It's all about the glass half full or half empty. Those who debate which is which are missing the point. Who cares if it's half full or half empty. Fill it up or drink the rest because either way half is being wasted.  I finished reading Joyce's A Portrait of the Artist as a Young Man. Fascinating read. I fear I have missed some of the undertones and will have to re-read it again soon. It's a very dense book about many topics of concern to Joyce as an artist. At times I felt like he was writing about me.   "He would create proudly out of the freedom and power of his soul...there was a lust of wandering in his feet that burned to set out for the ends of the earth. On! On! his heart seemed to cry."  It's hard to imagine some people see very little power or beauty in words. I feel sorry for those who fail to see it, experience the sheer exhilaration of juggling a phrase on the tongue and rolling it around in the mind. Pure joy!  Take the beginning stanza from Poe's The Raven:  Once upon a midnight dreary, while I pondered, weak and weary, Over many a quaint and curious volume of forgotten lore— While I nodded, nearly napping, suddenly there came a tapping, As if someone gently rapping, rapping at my chamber door. "'Tis some visitor," I muttered, "tapping at my chamber door— Only this and nothing more."  How can someone not become overwhelmed with the grace of the author; the skill and talent showcased in so few words. Amazing!  Update on the Kool-Aid test. It worked but not real well. I was able to turn the copper tone to a light red. I think it would really work if I had bleached first as suggested. I've applied the Kool-Aid mix again tonight and will leave it on much longer (4 hours the first time). The directions said leaving the stuff on as long as possible is advisable for maximum colouration.   

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Ad Lib   At work, bored. Should be working, I'm not. I'm listening to some trip-hop, Archive. Soon will listen to Zero 7, good group. Thinking about supper, take-out. Trying to think of something to say, nothing. This is my day, a rhyme. Poetry is good, not always. Nothing rhymes with orange, except sporange. It's a form of plant spore, botanical. Knowledge is better than fact, that's a fact. Write to live, trying. We all live secret lives, spy games. Hide and seek, childhood. Stop pretending it's me, be. Second rhyme today, poetry. Sailing sky outside the window, white boats. World is turned upside down, twenty-four hours. End in sight, done. 

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I've decided I don't like the colour of my hair. It's a copperish red, not the deep red I was looking for so I'm trying something different. I'm currently sitting with a shower cap on and underneath is a mixture of conditioner and Kool-Aid mix. That's right, Kool-Aid. I read about it on the Internet. If the mixture is any indication, I should have fantastic results. I mean the thick paste was blood red and before I put the cap on it looked like the Kool-Aid was already going to work. The challenge now is leaving the stuff on as long as possible. The longer the time, the more vibrant the colour. I'm going to try for six hours and see how it works. If it works out, there is an endless number of Kool-Aid colours I'd like to try. For 88 cents it's definately the cheapest dying product on the market. I'm already looking at the lime packets wondering what I'd look like with green hair. It would freak everybody out at work.  I will be posting pictures of my hair later this week as I see I've already got requests flooding in.  I've been having trouble sleeping lately. Last night I didn't crawl into bed until 5 a.m. and had to be at work before 8 a.m. I sat up half the night surfing around the Net, watching some bad CBC television and gorging myself on Pepsi (which probably explains the sleeplessness). I've had this general feeling of urgency for a couple weeks now. I feel like I'm missing out on so much and if I sleep, the world will pass me by. I don't know if it's the changing of the season with the warmer weather and longer days or what. I wouldn't mind the long nights so much if I was getting something productive done. Instead I'm just wasting the extra hours. See, even with less than three hours of sleep, I'm not even remotely tired and it's 10 p.m. right now.  It's been a strange couple of weeks and I fear it may get stranger this weekend. 

						
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Two posts in one day. It's a new record. I was flipping through my poetry notebook (it's a little black and grey thing with a hard cover about the size of a wallet, I've got three of them) and came across a couple older poems I'd like to share, so here goes.   In The Midnight Mist  I drift out on the fog rasping at the windowpane; a sickly yellow cloud. I move past the standing fence of log, petruding from the shrowd. He is there bleeding from a vein.  Father has died in the midnight mist. My hand reaches out and makes a fist. "Murder," I shout. "Murder," I say. "The grieving son shall have his day."  The pale disc in the sky looks down with dry eye. "It's a crime," I cry. "It's a crime." "Revenge will be mine. It will only take time."  My father cradled in arm. I place my head on his chest. Silence at first but soon I weep. I kneel and wonder how he to harm. I shall not want to lay him to rest. I shall not want to sleep.  Father has died in the midnight mist. A single name, not much of a list. "My blood, my kin," I shout. "My blood, my kin," I say. "He shall not live to see the day."  I take the betraying blade, the weapon he had made. I move with grace, I move with ease. He shall die upon his knees.  Up the staircase, down the hall. Blood from the blade drips to the floor. I ease into the room. He is about to fall. My brother shall be no more. I hold in my hand his impending doom.  Father has died in the midnight mist. I punch him with a solid fist. "Now is your time," I shout. "Now is your time," I say. "Father's death you shall pay."  Humbled and bowed on the floor, I hit him once more. I raise the blade striking the chest. You know the rest.  My days are cold, dreary and few. Mother will be sitting in the front pew. My fate does not bother. Soon I will be with father.  This is a verse which I haven't done anything with:  I like the end of day, when the light fades and the sun goes to bed, when magenta streaks the sky and city lights twinkle, not yet illuminating, guiding the advancing night.  A possible second verse:  I like the cover of new dark, a blanket of hush, muffling the sound of bright day. Dreams sail on the horizon, out of sight, till deep into the night.  

						
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well, the Flames have made it to the finals and I'm busy dying my hair red right now. I'm hoping the dye I picked out will live up to its name— flaming red.  25 minutes later....  It's not flaming red, but it's red. My hair is too short to really show off the colour well.  Once again I finished writing several stories first thing this morning as the newspaper was being layed out. I can't seem to find any motiviation for doing any work during the week. I'd rather spend time doing anything else. I should be working on stories for tomorrow but I'm not. I'll do them first thing in the morning.  This past week has been very unproductive at home. Between battling the flu and a nasty eye infection, I haven't even looked at my manuscript. I should get some time later this week but most of that time will be reviewing the last couple chapters and making minor corrections so I still won't get a lot of new material written. 

						
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The hockey game  is just about to start and I'm nervous as a jitterbug. If Calgary can win tonight, I'll be dying my hair bright red. I can't believe they're only a game away from making the finals after so many years.   Game started, gotta go! 

						
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I'm a writer, so I suppose I should share some of my writing. The following is a first draft (almost never shown) of a poem I am working on.   The Wood  I stood in a wood where no birds sang. They did not fly, they did not perch, They walked the ground in search, of what I do not know, but it was too eerie to let go. I walked the creeping path laid by the knarled trees. Not a living one among these, yet somehow I knew, these trees still grew. I question to this day why, it felt like the trees had eyes. Though the sun did shine, no leaf, no vine, the light was that of a mine. No shadow nor light, it was an awful fright standing in this evil wood. My eyes played tricks, my ears did hear, all adding to my growing fear. The hum and buzz of things which creep,  bump and grind, twisted and pulled my mind. Rapping and tapping, twigs snapping. Search I may, search I might, the source remained out of sight. The birds did not sing. I stood alone surrounded by this strange thing. The wood closed near, along with my mounting fear. This place was no place to be. A banshee, a banshee, a banchee three. Through this wood I rush and flee. I crashed through this wood screaming with a yowl, for behind comes a growing howl. A sound unlike any heard before, I keep running but the sound gains more and more. This wood seems to never end, the path bends and bends but never gives. It is here that evil lives. Pushing harder and harder still, I make it to the edge of the wood by shear will. I turn to see the sight of my growing fright, but all I see is a wood where no birds sang. 

						
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I'm back from shopping and I've brought home some more music. A picked up The Tea Party's "the edges of twilight " album and a collection of trip-hop and downbeat stuff along with a discman carrier that goes around the waist.  Looking through the music stores I realized why I download instead of buy CDs. Who in their right mind would pay $26 to $30 for a CD?  Both CDs I bought were on sale for under $12 and $16 and I got four discs. The studios want to bring people back into the stores but they're pricing themselves right out of the market. There is no justification for charging $30 for something I do at home for one or two. Fuck the Man!  A friend was talking about how good it feels to lose weight and I agree and I also agree with her saying how difficult it is to eat right. Not everyone has the time to cook the healthy meals. It's very easy, especially with my job, to grab something quick and unhealthy.  I've made a conscious effort this week to make meals instead of grabbing takeout and I can feel the difference. I feel more energetic and thinner. I'm not bloated on salty food. I'm going to have to keep working on cooking healthy and increase my focus on fitness.  I've decided I'm going to try and complete a 10 km run in August during Cornfest here in Taber. Every year there is a roadrace first thing in the morning to kick off the event and I'm going to do it this year. I could enter the 5 km but I really want to challenge myself. It leaves me three months to train and get back into shape enough that I won't kill myself on the course. 

						
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Currently playing: Moist- Silver album Mood: Energized  Why can't music be like it was? I've been going through a bunch of old albulms from my high school days and the music was so much better than it is today. There was real talent. It wasn't prepackaged garbage. I can't name a single band today that I could really say I like. Not one, at least not on the Top 40 charts. Thank God for mp3s and the Internet. I can still find good music which no longer shows up on the shelves at the music stores.  I'm feeling much better than I did last night. Spent some time with D after work and it was going well until I had to leave to go shoot a comedy troupe for the paper. There was a moment of awkward silence after I made a major blunder (no kissing and telling here). It wasn't the best way leave her for a week while she's back in her hometown. I'm hoping the week will erase my stupidity from her memory and we can start fresh. But enough with looking backward, look ahead always. I must press on like a galliant voyeger into strange territory.  On a good note, D's mom seems to like me. Yeah! Getting on the good side of parents is always a very good thing.  Well, I'm going shopping again. I've got a few hours to burn before going back to shoot the grad dance and evening ceremonies for the local high school.  

						
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I just found out I didn't place in the Grain Magazine writing contest. I submitted a postcard story (under 500 words) and a dramatic monologue. I have yet to read the winning entries, the web site posted the author and title only, but I'm sure most of it will be some new-age, garbled crap with no structure, style or meaning. It will be disconnected thoughts leading the reader nowhere. Am I the only one who is tired of shit like this winning all the writing competitions? Perhaps I'm too disconnected from the pulse of modern literature to voice any kind of opinion. But I laugh when I use the term literature when describing the sewage celebrated as brilliant.  Am I a bitter loser? A writer who can't handle rejection? hardly. I just don't appreciate the appreciation people give to something which is less than art. I'm tempted to submit a story written by a Grade 3 student and see how well it does in competition. I'm certain it would win at least one award.  I'm becoming more convinced every day I would not survive long in a university English program. I'm too much of a traditionalist which would make me unique in a university atmosphere. All these people who think they're unique because they're creating this disjointed, "modern" art and live an unconventional life, are the most conventional, dime-a-dozen types today. Being a little bizarre and off-centre puts you in a very large group.  I will remain a tradionalist when it comes to writing and I will not change because the anti-establishment establishment will not accept my writing because it doesn't conform to their idea of free, modern literature. One day I will be praised for my innovation and vision while all these fad writers will fade into the background with the rest of the mundane. 

						
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I sent D flowers and a really cute little blue teddybear this morning. I've got a couple hours before she gets off work. I'm going to wait outside for her. She wants to drive my truck because it's a standard and she wants to get more practice driving one and she won a bet last week so I'm going to hand over the keys today.  I'm thinking about swapping my truck for hers. D drives a Ranger like mine but it's sweet. It's a sidestep, metallic blue with better suspension, tires and loaded with extras. I drive a plain black Ranger with no extras except a tool chest across the back of the cab in the box of the truck. I'm guessing her's is a four litre engine while I've got a wimpy 2.4 litre. Mine's better on gas (which is a good thing with gas at 88 cents a litre) but I've got no power.  Two hours and counting before I've got to head over and see D. I'm not nervous yet but I know it's coming. Introverts of the world unite. It's been so long since I've done anything remotely close to this. Just be me and everything will work out. What if I can't find anything to say? I can't chicken out. I've got to say what I need to say. Let the chips fall where they may, right? It's all about living life. Carpe Diem and all that.    

						
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Once again I'm sitting at my desk at work not working. It's a Thursday morning and I've already places some calls so I don't feel so bad for not working. I've got all afternoon and Friday to get some interviews done and maybe even a few stories written.  My roommate has left for Dallas so the place is mine for two weeks. I'm not sure how I'm going to celebrate my freedom. I think I'm going to sit in the middle of the living room, which is clean, and quietly take in the emptiness and solitude. It will be a glorious moment.  D called me shy last week and I admitted she was right. I know I'm shy, not painfully, but shy. It comes from a number of things. My choice of careers (photojournalist) requires me to go unseen and unheard if possible. I am use to blending into the background.  Second, I'm also a writer which means I would rather express myself and my thoughts on the written page instead of face-to-face. I'm no good at talking about things. I need time to think about what I want to say. I find myself editing my thoughts before saying anything. I'm also trying to speak like I write.  Third, I am socially awkward because I've had very little practice. I was never the most popular person and never sought the spotlight. It comes from being a Taurus. I like being sturdy, dependable and hardworking. Fanfare and the spotlight mean little to me. As a result, I'm not very good at showcasing myself in social situations. I never talk myself up. I prefer actions to words. People talk about what they are like or what they would do but never seem to do what they say. It goes back to not grabbing the spotlight. I'd rather people discover what kind of a good person I am on their own through things I do rather than me pointing it out to them. It feels like an act of desperation. "Look at me, look what I can do. I'm a good person and here are the reasons why..." It's not me.  But realizing I am shy, I do have to work on coming out of my shell a bit more at times. D had a point the other night. I did want to say something and should have been a little more forward but old habits held me in check.  Meeting someone has always been my biggest problem because of my shyness. Those who suffer from it will understand when I say I wish I could get pass the initial stages and move right into a relationship. I'm great once into a relationship, it's getting started that is a problem. Everyone is a little scared of opening up to someone they hardly know, but for someone who is shy, opening up is twice as hard. Not only is there the normal fear of being around someone new but there is that constant habit of closing up and hiding in our shells.  I admit part of being shy is a defense mechanism. Keeping to oneself doesn't require risk. I admitted on my list of 100 things about me (check the archives) that I have not seriously dated in almost eight years. I'm not ashamed to admit it. People may ask how I could live that long without dating. It's actually very easy for the most part. Shy people are very introverted and are comfortable with themselves and their world. Those who are not introverted spending time with themselves is scary. I know people who can't be alone for more than a few moments at a time. They are in constant need of company. Doing things along scares the crap out them. For the introvert, alone time is the best time. I can go days without seeing another living being. Depending on my mood I'd prefer not to see another living soul.  Striking a balance between needing other people around and hiding away is the challenge. I believe I'm making pretty good progress with crawling out from under my rock a little more often. I'm at least aware of my introverted self taking over. I know when I'm starting to recede back into my shell. If I can identify those times when I'm doing that, I'll have a better chance of changing how I handle myself.  I think it all has to do with fear. Introverted people have a lot of fear. I'm not saying it's bad or we're screwed up but it's a fact we have a deep seeded fear we may not even be completely aware of that prevents us from taking that one bold step. I remember a time when I had a swagger in my step. I wasn't afraid of speaking my mind. I didn't taking a risk. Somewhere I lost that side of my personality. I know a lot of it is connected to experiences through high school and college.  I have done a good job at hiding my introverted ways. I've learned how to mask my shyness. I use to be outgoing and I'm pretty good at faking it. When I go out with friends I seem to be the life of the party at times. At the bar, I'm usually loud and storm the dancefloor like someone possessed. What nobody realizes is being loud and the crazed party guy doesn't require me to open up to anyone. I'm like a tornado, there's nothing in the middle and everything whirls around the outer edge. And while I'm having a good time, I'm not meeting anyone. I don't form friendships (except with Sheri who made more of an effort than I did), I form acquaintances.   I couldn't hide from D. She quickly discovered I carry a shell around with me. But here's where it gets interesting. I know D has a shell of her own.  The question will be if we are able to come out of those shells long enough to find each other. I know one we do find each other, we won't have a problem being like-minded people. But until then it will be the blind leading the blind.  For someone who is shy, I write a lot don't I?  Several hours later....  Tampa Bay is leading the Flyers 2-0 and I'm waiting for the Calgary game to come on.  I found out my brilliant plan for D's birthday isn't going to work because she's not going to be in town. The timeline has been moved up to tomorrow. Everyone wish me luck.  I went shopping today and bought a couple pairs of pants, a shirt, a belt and a pair of shoes. It's a birthday present to myself. I haven't bought any new clothes in a long time and the experience was frustrating. I'm no shopper and having to sift through racks of and racks of clothes is one of the scariest things I can think of doing. I got through it and I'm happy with how well I did. I'll be on the front of GQ in no time.   

						
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The photo is gone. I 'm not going to deal with the headaches of trying to get it to work.   I've spent half the night trying to write one simple poem and I can't seem to get it done. I'm not sure where I want to go after the first couple lines. I keep doubting myself and the thoughts I'm expressing on paper. I'm working against a deadline which doesn't help. I'm trying to force the words onto the page and I know that doesn't work. I need to find my inner voice and allow it to speak before putting anything down on paper.  The tone never seems right. It's either too cold, too distant or it's too close and too hot. I'm trying to find a delicate balance between the two extremes and it's proving very difficult. I'm going to try again after I'm finished here.  Sheri will be happy to hear I've decided to postpone my escape to Scotland. I've been having doubts about the timing. I was thinking about mid-October but I've heard it's difficult to find a job or housing at that time of year. I'm also far behind in saving money for the trip. I won't be leaving until late April or early May of next year if things haven't changed before then.  The extra time also gives me time to try and get something started here with freelance work and maybe I'll get my book finished before I leave.  I've got some other writing to do so I'd better get at it. 

						
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It seems some people are having troubles seeing my awesome picture. I don't know what else to do. I can see it just fine. I wish Blogger would store photos so there wouldn't be a problem with linking and all that crap.  It's been a very strange few days for me. I'm in a place emotionally I didn't think I would be in. It's a very good place but also kind of strange because it's been a very long time since I felt this way. I never seem to stop thinking about D. It's like she's infected my brain. Sometimes she's right there in the front of my mind, other times the thought of her lingers in the background but she's never gone from my thoughts.  Infactuation? perhaps. Love? Time will tell. I have to find out because I swore to myself I would not live life with regrets and if I don't find out where things go with D, i'll regret them for the rest of my life. If nothing happens between us then I know it wasn't meant to be. If things don't work out in the end, I'll be disappointed but will still know it wasn't meant to be.  My roommate is leaving for Dallas at the end of the week. I'll have the place to myself for two weeks. It's going to be absolute bliss. 

						
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Blogger has set up a new look with a bunch of new options so I thought I'd change things up here at Cody's Corner. Do you like the new look. It's much closer to the feel I'm looking for.  Change seems to be a big thing in my life right now. I'm changing  my outlook on my life and how I am going to live that life. There are some changes on the horizon, at least I'm hoping there will be some changes which will be new and very exciting for me. Everyone will have to wait and see what happens.    

						
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I called D several times, left messages, didn't hear from her. So I went out on a bender last night with friends and hit almost all the bars in town. Went to a small house party and met my neighbours across the alley. Great people. We had an awesome time. We sat around drinking, talking and country line dancing (don't ask) until the sun came up this morning. I admit I'm still trying to orient myself. I had to shoot some pictures first thing this morning at a powerlifting competition and it was tough. Came back had a shower and some leftover pizza and I'm feeling much better.  I'm just waiting for my parents to arrive. It's still raining and I'm feeling pretty good about myself despite the disappointment with D. They just pulled up gotta go. 

						
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Currently playing: It can't rain all the time- Sinead O'Connor Mood: It's raining and I always end up being reflective and insightful.  It's a little after 2 p.m. and I'm at home. I did one interview early this morning which lasted over three hours. It was a good conversation. Checked in at the office for messages then picked up some snack food for tomorrow. I worked last weekend so normally you get the following friday off. I got half a day but then I work Saturday morning as well. Oh well.  I'm still waiting to talk to D since she got back. I've called her a couple times but she's been out. I'm starting to go crazy. I need to see her.  I puttered around on the typewriter last night. I got a couple pages written. It was good to feel the keys beneath my fingers. I hope Calgary wins the cup in four games so I can get back to writing at night. I spend all my time watching hockey games.   I'm going to go eat and waste away an afternoon reading while trying not to think about D until after 5 p.m. when she gets off work.  

						
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   THE FLAMES ARE GOING TO THE CUP!!!!!!!!!!!  GO! FLAMES! GO! GO! FLAMES! GO! GO! FLAMES! GO! GO! FLAMES! GO! GO! FLAMES! GO! GO! FLAMES! GO! GO! FLAMES! GO! GO! FLAMES! GO!   WHOHOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!!!!!!!! 

						
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Currently playing: Sweet Dreams- Eurythmics Mood: Sore and tired  I just spend most of the afternoon and evening cleaning the bathroom. It was a disgusting mess. My roommate is going to feel the wrath when he gets back from Dallas. I don't mind messy, I mind filth. Messy is leaving things laying around or letting the dishes pile up. Filth is when you let mold grow and don't bother cleaning up spilled pop that has run down the side of the fridge and pooled underneath ( I noticed the pool creeping out from underneath the other day).  So here I am, hand aching from hours of scrubbing, eating pizza, drinking Pepsi and listening to Sweet Dreams. I've got to be at work early tomorrow to catch up on some stories before the day gets started because I've got several interviews and write the stories before noon tomorrow.  After work I get to continue cleaning in preparation for my parents visit this weekend. I'm going to tackle the living room and kitchen. It should be fun.   D gets back late tomorrow. Yeah! My parents want to meet her already. We haven't even really begun seeing each other so I'm not going to make that happen yet. I know I've already met D's mom but my parents would ask a lot of embarrassing questions. They've been waiting for some time for me to date someone and they're just a little excited about the possibilities.  I learned a new word today which I'd like to share with the world.    Prostitots-  Young girls who take dance lessons and end up wearing hooker-like outfits and moving like a stripper. To identify a prostitot simply watch a dance recital and when you get a feeling you should avert your eyes in fear of being labeled a pervert, you have correctly identified a prostitot. They are usually found in groups and are often with parents oblivious to the transformation of their children into prostitots. Indeed, parents encourage this transfomration and even hand over large sums of money to prostitot trainers.  I need to get some sleep. Ciao. 

						
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I found this wonderful review in Saturday's Globe and Mail Book section.   Where's the context?  Review of  Rising to a Tension: New Short Fiction by 13 writers under 25.  By August C. Bourre  This second book in the Tendril Anthology series has assembled a solid, readable, if uninspired collection of stories by writers under 25. Most of the stories are well crafted, some, like Julie Kelk's  Sweet Cream , exceptionally so. Others, notably Paul Comrie's  Running at the Foot of Ararat , scream Creative Writing Seminar.  The problem with these stories is the same problem that plagues much contemporary Canadian short fiction. The writers seem to believe that an "issue"— the death of a family member, AIDS, sexual abuse and various crises of identity liked to sexuality, ethnicity or travelling abroad are perennial favourites— combined with witty or realistic dialogue, a few "gritty" details and some talent for diction, is all it takes to tell a good story.  What happens is that the characters become interchangeable without having the symbolic advantages of being archetypes, or even types. The personal, serious details intended to give the stories a touch of reality, a distinct tone, instead create a solemn grey fog that covers them and makes them indistinguishable from one another. An anthology like this is akin to a lecture on sociology or cultural anthropology.  Many of these young writers are recent graduates from university literature programs or are engaged in literary study at some level, yet their work gives no indiciation that they have read widely beyond their peer group. It's not so much that their work suffers from lack of allusion— there are a few, such as Sophie Levy's wonderful   C/O  — because for the most part such allusions would be cumbersome and unnecessary. Rather, these stories don't seem to be written in any sort of literary context. They don't engage with tradition or contemporary writing. They exist in a kind of literary limbo, neither timely nor timeless. With a few exceptions, such as the two cases which pixels are used as metaphors, it would be easy to believe most of them were written 20 years ago.  The book jacket calls these writers "the next great wave of young literary talent," implying they are on the cutting edge of short fiction. In fact, most of these stories either reinforce the literary status quo or rebel in scrupulously typical ways.   I am not the only one who feels the literary world of today is stuck in a rut of elitism bent on cliched topics of self-discovery, angst and rebellion.  Instead of focusing on content, these writers focus on form. I always think 100 years from now what will be remembered of the writing produced today: very little.   On a lighter note, today was D's birthday. I wish I could celebrate with her. Instead I will spend the night writing stories for tomorrow's paper. It never seems to end. 

						
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I've really got to get a life. This is way too many entries in one day but what are you going to do, sue me?  I was going through yet another notebook full of scribbling, news clippings, pictures and things and came across this:  These moments of solitude, with my music and mind. Life flashing in front of my eye. A pond's calm drowns me.  The vastness of the world boils inside. Passion and hope become headlights that guide me through my fear, your fear.  I'm standing in the shallows hoping the tide won't come. If it does, may I find the ability to swim.  I ranted earlier about writer's getting stuff like this published. It's all disconnected and  random. I remember writing this while driving around with friends. In the car was a girl I was madly in love with, she knew it, but we never seemed to get together. It was very complicated and confusing. Parts of the poem are about what was happening at the time and other parts are just lines that came to me that I thought sounded neat. I think the first stanza is about riding around with her and being in my own little world where nobody else knows what I'm thinking or feeling. After that I think I just wrote down a bunch of stuff that was coming to me in flashes. I like the third stanza. The idea of being knee deep in trouble and hoping there is a way to overcome it before it washes over you is a neat idea to work with. The visuals of a tide coming in while you're stuck in the mud watching the water rise above your head and not knowing if you can survive works really well. I think people can identify with that.  That is the end of the lesson for today class. Tune in tomorrow as Professor Cody talks about the use of  words to convey mood.  I found a quote I copied into my notebook from Arthur Kent, a Canadian foreign correspondent. I wish it were true today.   All journalists have a special mission, whether they're working in life-threatening situations or explaining events at city hall. It's called accuracy: putting the truth on public record, no matter who that truth might offend. It's about having enough courage to earn profits without distorting or dressing up the facts. Ethics do not constitute a handicap, as too many media owners seem to believe. They're assets, and when nurtured with care, they become vital ingredients to success.  

						
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I have just spent 40 minutes chasing a pronghorn antelope around the sunbeaten prairie in the middle of nowhere. I was on my way back from taking pictures of 4-H kids giving their cattle a haircut (yes, it does seem rather ridiculous) when I spotted this elusive pronghorn standing about 70 yards off the highway. I came to screeching halt and pulled the truck off into the ditch, swung the door open, grabbing the camera off the passenger seat, and made my way to the barbwire fence.  Having stalked animals since I was a little kid I knew it was important to move slow and not to look at the pronghorn who was now fully alert there was a crazy walking ape attempting to sneak through the prairie grass. I got within 50 yards and took a couple pictures. I was still too far away to fill the frame with the pronghorn so I attempted to get closer. Man would starve if we didn't have a thumb. Because of that extra appendage we are able to hold onto weapons of every shape and size. This pronghorn was no fool and began moving slowly away from me in a zigzag pattern. I began thinking about how a U-Boat commander would try to cut down the angles on a convoy ship zigzagging across the North Atlantic. It's not as easy as it looks. This pronghorn must have studied a few naval books because he did a good job of putting distance between himself and me without appearing to move at all.   Meanwhile, people have been passing by on the highway giving me queer looks. I could just imagine what it must have looked like from the road. Here's a guy decked out in cargo pants and multi-pocketed vest with flaming red hair creeping through parched prairie grass like some great predator. I'm pretty sure the pronghorn was no longer visible from the road. He was hard enough to spot 50 yards away.  Today has confirmed two things (1) I need to get a longer lens (2) photographers are crazy. We are willing to stand for hours in one spot or get covered in mud or pig shit or soaked by rain just to get one picture. We will crawl, run, dangle and hang upside down if that's what's going to get us the shot.  While you're working you don't realize how stupid you look to eveyone else but when I get a chance to watch other photographers work I can't help thinking we all need help. We hover like insects buzzing here and there. We snap pictures, adjust equipment, snap a few more then move around to the other side and do it again. We look around frantically for a better spot to shoot from. We look for an elevated position, we look for a lower position, we look for something to frame the scene, we look for the position of the sun and with all of that going on we try to anticipate what will happen next to put ourself in the right spot at the right time. Doing all of this in a matter of seconds tends to make one look crazy to everyone else.  Currently playing: Nelly Furtado-Powerless Mood- Slightly depressed. Calgary is losing the hockey game 4-1 with two minutes left. Series is now tied 2-2. 

						
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Currently playing: Four Non-blondes- What's Up Mood: Giddy  I have to thank Sheri for making my day today. She emailed me and told me a little tidbit of info about D that made me smile. It seems Sheri can make us both smile easily and I know she's having fun doing it (admit it).  Those bastards were back again last night trying to go through my truck. The doors were locked but the tool chest was unlocked so they popped the lid again. Still nothing taken. I've locked it so they'll get a surprise tonight those little shits.  I'm now 24 but I feel like I'm 18. It might be all the graduations I've had to attend in the past week. The constant message of  being in control of your destiny and having a world of opportunity in front of you if you just seize it has got me thinking like I did when I graduated. It's amazing how quickly you become pessimistic once you've left high school. I listened to the principal tell the graduating class not to see the obstacles but the goal at the end. I remember being told the same thing at my graduation but all I can see now are the obstacles. They're bigger than anyone tells you they are.   I will not see the obstacles but the goal. I remember a time when I could do that and it seemed to work. I heard so many times throughout my life from teachers, friends and my family that I could accomplish just about anything if I put my mind to it. For some people that's just not possible because they lack the skills or drive or intelligence, but I've seen it work for me. I know I'm capable of doing some really great things. I never give myself credit for being skilled or talented and tend to downplay any achievements I make. I won third best news photo in Alberta and currently up for the top prize for news photo across Canada but I don't talk about it or even think about what it means. It's just an award. My columns have been reprinted by the Canadian Community Newspaper Association's magazine, I've received dozens of thank you notes from people for stories I've written, I've been asked to speak about journalism and news photography because the organizations respect my work, but I don't focus on any of this. I still have a long way to go before I'm any good in this journalism business. I see all the mistakes I make. I see all the stories I could have made better by digging a little deeper or spending a little more time writing. I hate my writing. I read other people's stuff and wish I could write as well as they can. I'm still an amateur.  This thinking has prevented me from doing what my parents have been asking me to do for years, and that is to send my writing and photography to magazines. They keep telling me I have the talent to write for the big glossy mags and the large dailies but I don't feel I have what it takes. I see all the obstacles instead of the end result. I'm going to stop thinking like that and start sending stuff in. What have I got to lose?   

						
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I forgot to mention I was a victim of stupidity early in the morning. I went out to my truck to find the tool chest in the box open, my glove compartment wide open and tossed, my visor with the storage pouch flipped down and the armrest console flipped down and ripped open. Nothing was taken. My tool chest is full of stuff and not one thing was missing. There was nothing in the glove compartment worth taking and there was nothing in the visor. I had about $10 in change in the ashtray which wasn't taken.  I didn't even report it to the police. It's hard to steal from someone who has nothing to start with. I wish I could have caught the asshole(s) who did it. I would have called the cops then snuck outside and grabbed a photo of them in the act before beating the crap out of them.  It's my birthday today! 

						
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It's been a three-ring circus today at work. We're getting ready to host a pancake breakfast tomorrow before the town parade. I've been running around town picking things up. Never buy a truck. You end up being everyone's slave.  I got one interview done and part of the story written. Shot some photos this morning and got two other interviews schedules so it was a pretty good day. Normally I don't do anything until Monday afternoon with deadline a couple hours away.  I got paid today so I'll have money for the next couple days until I pay rent, truck payment and student loans. I love living in poverty.    

						
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Briefly: 1. Lungs are feeling much better. Coughing is under control and disappearing. 2. Busy day at work. Got a few things done. Worked much harder than last week. 3. The Flames lost, damn. We got the split in Tampa so it's not all bad. 4. Need to get more rest. 5. Happy again. Mild depression has left completely.     

						
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I'm locked in my room listening to music to muffle the sound of my roommate and his girlfriend. That's right, Greg has returned from his trip to Dallas. The house will once again look like a fucking bomb went off. I give it two days. I really want a place of my own but I can't afford it. I should ask for a raise at work so I can move out.   I've felt like crap the past two days. My lungs have been on fire and I can't stop coughing. It's not a cold or flu. I'm not stuffed up. I just have this constant aching itch in my chest and the constant coughing fits where I can't breath. If it doesn't improve by Friday I think I'll see a doctor. I'm starting to suspect I may have something. If I had to guess, I would say asthma. My dad has it and the crops have just starting germinating and I think this thing might be an allergic reaction to particles in the air as a result. If I recall, I felt like this last year around this time.   

						
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   At working thinking of my typewriter stuffed with paper sitting on my bedroom floor. I began writing at midnight last night and decided to go all night. I almost made it but settled in for a short nap for about an hour. It seems to have been enough. I arrived at work early this morning to get my stories written. I finished them up before eight. I hate that I'm so good at getting away with not writing until hours before deadine.  The writing last night went really well. I found my stride and pounded out four pages before I knew what happened. I have yet to look it over to see if any of it is any good. It's nice to produce something regardless.  I've come down with this killer cough and burning sensation in my chest and lungs. It's an aweful feeling. I couch until I can't breath and feel like throwing up. There doesn't seem to be any infection. At least none of the spittle is tainted with infection. It's probably something I picked up while cleaning the apartment. God knows there was enough mold, mildew and bacteria to kill most living things.  I've only got about nine more hours before I can go home. I've got town council tonight to cover. I'm not sure if I'll be able to keep my eyes open that long. It should be interesting. 

						
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink     urlLink Which Colossal Death Robot Are You?    urlLink Brought to you by Rum and Monkey   

						
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink     urlLink What Kind of Drunk Are You?    urlLink Brought to you by Rum and Monkey    I found this to amuse myself late at night. 

						
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    My World  The sun has come out after three days of rain. Once again God has played a cruel trick. This weekend was a long weekend with everyone wanting to get away to the mountains for some camping and the big man upstairs decided to send rain until the day everyone has to come home. It will be a beautiful week weatherwise because everyone has to go back to work.   My Heart  My sleep patterns have been off this weekend. I'm doing a lot more tossing and turning and waking at odd hours of the night. It's a good sign I'm changing some hardwiring in my head. My brain is changing things around so I can move on from the apparent disaster with D and get on with my life without crashing and burning. I spent Friday night and part of Saturday thinking about the utter failure I've been romantically but I was able to recover fairly quickly. My body is taking care of my fragile heart and the fathomless well of dispair I carry around inside of me. My mind is applying the bandages and putting a lid on the well so I don't fall in.  When the wounds heal (and they're coming along nicely) I'll be stronger and wiser. They will be just another group scars on this war-torn heart. They will be another reminder of my resilience and ability to fight on against great adversity. The fight will continue.   My Creativity  I dusted off my cameras last night and cleaned all my lenses and equipment. For those who knew me four years ago this is very alarming. I would never have let dust collect on my cameras. Dust wouldn't have time to settle. I have fallen away from my first love and I realize now that is partly why I feel so miserable all the time. A large part of who I am has been missing. I've been denying myself. I vow not to let that happen again. I need to create pictures. It's at the core of who I am. I am going out later today to shoot just to get back out shooting.  I've only ever made one real wish to God in my life. I stood at the Wailing Wall in Jerusalem and asked God to make me a great photojournalist. I asked Him to guide me and show me the way. I'm not sure if He hasn't been showing the way or if I have been ignoring His directions. I have the talent and skill. I have no doubts about that. I need to find the drive and motivation to get my work known and seen by editors and those who are important in the photographic world.  I've never been good at selling myself (see disaster with D above). I've had so many comment on how talented I am both as a writer and photographer. Lots of people say I can do great things and wish they had the talents I have. It's nice to hear but I don't really buy into it. I can't say those things about myself. I downplay my abilities. I've got to stop doing that all the time. I should be telling people how good I am and what I can do that few other people can do. I will not doubt my skills. I won't, I won't, I won't. I WON'T. I feel much better.  Currently playing- Internet radio station Analog Voyager- they play downbeat and trip-hop stuff but I'm about to switch it to For Non-blondes' What's Up. Current Mood- Hard to say. A little sad, a little happy but mostly on a creative edge. 

						
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I took a much needed afternoon trip to Lethbridge to go shopping. It was a day of therapy. I headed to my favourite place, Chapters. When I need time to unwind and think about things I head to the bookstore. I bought a couple books and had a pleasant drive back into Taber. It was exactly what I needed. A long chat with Heather and I'm good as new.  In fact, better than new.   I submitted an essay to the Globe and Mail. I'm hoping to hear back from them in the next couple days. I've got my fingers crossed they accept it for publication. It's nice to be submitting work. It means I'm writing.  My trip to Chapters has yielded three books I can't wait to get into. The most promising is  about the Author  by John Colapinto. The bastard has stolen my idea and gotten it published already. The book is about an author writing about being an author and the struggles of getting a book written and published.  It's a book about a book.  I also picked up a new translation of Dante's  Inferno  and a copy of Sir Walter Scott's  Rob Roy . I'm a nerd and I know it and I love it. I don't think there is anything worse than being an idiot. 

						
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Currently playing: Missed Me- Dresden Dolls Mood: Fantastic  I just got back from competing in a 4-H steer competition. I was a celebrity contestant who had to show one of the 4-H member's steers in the showring. I got to handle the 1,300 pound reserve champion. The bugger was scared of the crowd sitting in the stands so each time we made our way around the ring he'd stop dead as we approached the stands. Try moving 1,300 pounds that doesn't want to move, it's tough. I  had fun and only got stepped on once.  Found out it's going to cost me $500 to get my neighbour's car repainted. I was a little depressed at first but figure it's out of my control and stopped worrying about it. I've stopped worry about a lot of things and it makes a big difference.   I said things were going to change and they have already. I'm watching my spending a lot closer and it's not as tough as I thought. I've only spent about $15 this week and I'm not starving and actually cooked (as opposed to throwing something into a pot and heating it up) and it felt good to actually create something in the kitchen. It tasted better than anything coming out of a takeout bag.  I forgot to write about running into D last weekend. We passed each other four or five times downtown as we were both driving around in the rain. She completely ignored me and even slipped down a sidestreet at one point when I came up behind her (and no I wasn't following her around). I thought it was funny. I felt like Richard Dryfus in American Graffitti chasing the girl in the white T-Bird (it was Susan Sommers for those who don't know).  Two highly recommended movies: Dummy with Adrien Brody and Pieces of April with Katie Holmes. Watched them both this weekend and loved them. Both are very well written and perfectly acted. They are low-key, thoughtful movies which is unusual to see coming out of Hollywood.  Now playing: Good Day- Dresden Dolls. You've got to check this  urlLink band  out. I've never heard anything quite like this. They have restored my faith there are true musicians in the world.    

						
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This is the worse day I've had in a very long time. It started off by dropping a two hundred pound grill on my left shin crushing my leg and leaving a two inch wide gash. I then spent the afternoon talking to a guy about restoring old cars. His place was a dive and he would not shut up so I spent two hours in Grassy Lake. By the time I drove back to Taber it was past 4. I had half a dozen interviews yet to do. I got one done because everyone else had left their offices.  I get home and decide to head out on my bike after supper. I get about two miles away when the back tire goes flat. I make it back to the house, load up the bike in the truck and back out and run into the neighbour's car. I check to see if there is any damage and don't see any and the neighbour doesn't come out right away so I take off to inflate the bike tire. I get back five minutes later and there's a cop car sitting out front. The neighbour reported a hit and run, which technically is what I did. Luckily, I know all the cops in town and he wasn't going to write it up as a hit and run because there was very little damage. However, I did chip some paint which had been done only a week before. So the guy is getting a quote tomorrow and what it will cost to get it touched up. It'll be no less than $200.  On top of all of this, I still have all my fucking stories to write for the paper tomorrow because I'm the only one who knows how to take fucking pictures. I spent almost all week away from the office taking a zillion photos. Meanwhile, my story list, longer than the others put together sits nearly untouched.  And Garrett goes on holidays at the end of this week which means I'm doing the paper alone. I get to do layout of Coaldale, Taber and Vauxhall and will still be expected to fill the newspaper with stories as well for the following week. With Colleen gone, I am it when it comes to editorial decisions. I'll be acting as editor and publisher on a pathetic reporter's salary. I am so fucking asking for a raise when she gets back from collecting my awards at the CCNA conference next week.  While I'm bitching about work let me mention that Jen, the waif who can't write, not only got to take Friday off for not working on her weekend (we rotate weekends between the four editorial staff) that I did work but she also got the afternoon off today.  So she got a short week of three days, two of which she does nothing because we're laying out the paper and she never does anything, and a second long weekend. And she goes on holidays next month. Shall I mention I have not taken holidays since I began at the paper two years ago. I can't because I don't make enough money to go anywhere and I'm not wasting four weeks of holidays to sit around this fucking pathetic town.  I get to starve myself for the next two weeks until I get paid again. I'm almost out of food and I've got no money until next friday. I'm going to live on Itchban, pasta and baked potatoes. It'll be great for the figure, I figure. But I really shouldn't be btiching about my financial problems. I'd rather spend money on booze than food. That is until now. This shit has got to stop. Not only am I killing my liver but I'm wasting Friday and Saturday nights where I could be writing and I'm spending a lot of money to come home drunk, alone and miserable with disappointment.   Things are going to change. 

						
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Currently playing: Good Day- Dresden Dolls Mood: Fantastic  That's right, two fantastic days in a row. I woke up late this morning and felt completely refreshed and ready to face the day. It's been awhile since I felt like that. I got a lot of work done. Did some wash (even helped a neighbour by drying and folding his clothes that were left in the washing machine), got some writing done, watched the rain come down outside my bedroom window. It was a very good day.  The writing has gone well this weekend. I've got some new ideas and a clear direction mapped out now and things are coming along nicely. The work should be progressing well over the next couple months. It will be really nice to see pages start to pile up. The story is controversial to say the least and it's a very big risk but I think it's worth taking because if I can achieve what I've got trapped in my head, on paper, then it will be a great piece of writing. I've set myself a great challenge of not copying Nabokov's novel (which I must really read before I get too far ahead in my own novel) yet try to cover the same general topic with the same taste and style he was able to pull off. I'm not writing pornography but the story is about sexuality and sexual identity of men and women. There's nothing like aiming for the top of Mount Everest on your very first climb. Here's a sample:   She was twelve, maybe thirteen but small for her age. She could probably pass for a girl a few years younger. She was sitting on the top step, bare knees pulled up to her chest. She was watching the gathering storm like me.  I didn't notice her at firstt. I simply stuck my head out the window, arms folded across the sill, staring up at the darkened sky. It was the screech of the screen door being opened by her mother that caused me to look over at the townhouse.  Her mother was dressed in a stained yellow tank top revealing the shape of her sagging, bra-less breasts through the material. She wore a pair of threadbare  Hawaiian flower-print shorts. The shorts showed off the skinny, scared legs leading down to bare feet.  The girl looked up at her mother, cocked her head to one side, and said something. Her mother nodded, said something back, stood silent for a moment, then went back inside. That's when the girl glanced over at me catching my eye. We held each other for a moment longer than what could be defined as comfortable between strangers. I broke first returning my eyes to the sky but I tried to look at her out of the corner of my eye and got caught in her gaze again. Had she been staring at me or had she looked away, too? This time she turned away but moments later she got caught looking over. She looked away and then back again. I was still watching this small creature curled up against the world. The scene not only held my attention but my imagination and heart. The girl looked so alone and fragile, yet I knew she was strong inside. The idea excited me.  She buried her face into her knees then glanced over at me with one eye. I could see her smile as she turned her face back toward her knees. She turned once more, smiled, then darted inside.   As you can see there is a lot of work ahead of me and many rewrites in the future but the basic framework of the scene is there. I'm looking forward to fleshing out (pardon the pun) the story and see where it takes me. It's going to be an interesting and I think at times frightening journey.    

						
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Just to put everyone's mind at ease, I am going to tell Greg on Monday. I wasn't going to hide it until the day I moved. It would be a little hard to hide the fact I'm packing things into boxes. Besides, I haven't actually signed the rental agreement yet. I'm meeting with the landlord probably Monday or Tuesday so I don't feel too bad because nothing is official yet.  Anyway, I'm in Calgary right now writing on my brother's girlfriend's computer. It's nice to be home and catch up on everything my family has been doing. I'm glad to see my brother and his girlfriend are doing all right. She seems able to handle my brother's prickish nature.  My parents have gone into nurture mode again. My mom has already got double sized mattress and boxspring lined up for my new place and a pair of wingback chairs if I want them. I love the gesture but she can go overboard at times. I'm sure she'll buy a whole bunch of stuff I'll hardly use but thinks I need. I love her anyway.  I'll catch you all on the flipside of the weekend. 

						
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I feel really bad but I can't bring myself to tell Greg I'm moving. There's no way of going about it without coming across as a complete asshole. He did suggest it in his note but I think he was just looking for sympathy. I don't think he ever thought I would ever do it and especially not this quickly.  I should be able to start moving my stuff over to the new place sometime next week if I feel like it. I said I'd offically move in July 1 so I've still got a couple weeks of living with Greg. It's been hard already. I keep thinking about all the possibilities the new place will give me. I can decorate the way I want, have my stuff wherever I want and be able to do whatever I want.  I was told yesterday by my boss to take some holidays. It wasn't a request but an order. She didn't realize I have yet to take any in the two years I've been at the paper. I guess I'll take a couple weeks in July and bum around the house writing and maybe checking out some of the museums in southern Alberta.  Currently playing: Sneaker Pimps- 6 Underground Current Mood: Antsy. Can't stop thinking about my new place. 

						
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   JOY! SWEET JOY! I've found a place of my own. It's wonderful. It's a cute little one bedroom basement suite. The landlord also happens to be someone I talk to on a fairly regular basis at work. He's the facility director for the local school board. I know he'll take good care of the building and is easy to get along with. He's painting the place right now and I will be able to start moving in late next week if I feel like it and you can bet I will. WAHOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!!!!!  I'm going to have a problem wiping this shit-eating grin off my face. I can't believe how easy it was to find a new place. I called to look at this suite and it turned out to be perfect. Everything is going to happen so quickly that Greg won't know what happened. I kind of feel bad for leaving him in the lurch but at the same time I think of all the crap I've had to put up with and the feeling goes away.  Greg still hasn't come home. I think he's staying somewhere else in town but I'm not sure. I saw a weird set of keys on his desk. They sort of looked like a set of motel keys. He has yet to mention anything about the computer incident or the note.   Anyway, I'm going for a walk down by the river to celebrate my wonderful news (got I'm such an introvert).  P.S.- I'll bring my column with me to Calgary. You'll love it Heather. 

						
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I have yet to speak with Greg as he's avoided me all weekend and we hardly spoke at work today. He's still at the office trying to postpone coming home. He carried on at work like nothing was wrong. Although he was careful to keep conversation brief.  I called about the basement suite and will be viewing it tomorrow evening and if it has any promise at all I'm going to take it. I want to be out of here by the end of the month. I was thinking about it today and I could hardly contain myself. The thought of having my own place is almost too much to bear. All my own stuff and my own mess, splendid.  Anyway, I've got to get back to finishing off my stories for the paper tomorrow. 

						
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Hello everybody, I'm back. I've spent the last two days rebuilding my hard drive after my roommate fried my computer. I lost everything this time. I had to re-initialize my hard drive wiping out anything and everything which may have been locked away inside.  I still haven't spoken to Greg. He left a 12-page note on my desk when I came home yesterday after spending the day getting soaked in a downpour shooting pictures. In it he explained he felt sorry for essentially destroying my life and he went to talk about how he did it. Apparently, he was upset over what had happened during the night with his girlfriend. Something about not having sex, talking about it, her getting defensive, Greg not understanding/freaking out about how evil he is for trying to sleep with a single mom. He logged onto the internet to check baseball scores but ended up surfing for porn and a video clip froze the computer and he did something to try and reboot the computer and instead destroyed it.  I've actually been very calm about it. I've lost two years of writing, all my website stuff, resumes and other career related documents (business card designs etc). He offered to move out if I wanted him to because he's invaded my space again and destroyed something of mine. He's staying and I'm going. I've been thinking of getting my own place for awhile now and this is the catalyst. I looked at a couple places earlier this week and I'm going to call and see about a basement suite.  Here's the note (hardly legible, in fact I'm probably one of the only people on the planet able to decipher his chicken stratches):   I think I screwed your computer again. Was logging on to cbssportsline.com at first and saw a few bookmarks in the section to my liking as last night was a tad frustrating sexually with Jen. Not that big of a deal as we were getting a little closer she talked of her fears in the last time she had sex she had a kid and the father killed himself. I said I was a little hesitant to myself, her being a single mother etc. Long story short, nothing really happened and saw a couple hardball markers, went to log on to a clip and it loaded 1.3 of 1.4 mb and then just froze- tried hitting apple to force shutdown quit, nothing happened, just tried shutting off screen, nothing, tried control, apple, delete, nothing. Things like your email starting popping up. Hearing about not disrupting power source for a short ????, made a long one instead thinking it would be fine, I was wrong.  This is the second time I've fucked up your computer and if you don't want me for a roommate I'll understand. Maybe this is God telling me something like perhaps I should be viewing relationships a tad differently then I have in the past. I'm learning as Jen was telling me she could just go home if I was disappointed we werent' having sex. That was absolutely ludicrous I told her as we could go at the pace she was comfortable with. Needless to say thoug, after viewing hardball scores, I go to the sex clips that were labeled hardball. Maybe it has been my views of sex that have been screwing up my previous relationships. Maybe someone upstairs is telling me something. To have the computer freeze like that and then not be able to apple force quit or shut down. Anyway, I've taken stalk in my hour of panic trying to unfreeze the computer and subsquently get the question mark like I did as I ripped out the power source last time tripping over it. All I can say is how sorry I am. If it takes a tech man to fix it, I'll pay for it. If it takes countless hours for you to fix it, I guess I'll pay you either through beer or straight money. While the last time I fried your computer I can claim an accident tripping over wires in the dark, this time it was completely just me. If I had just stayed to reading sports articles on cbssportsline and reading baseball scores this wouldn't have happened. I'll be in Lethbridge attending a friend's birthday for a while and will probably return tonight. I'll discuss this face to face with you then. Again, I'm truly sorry. I know the words don't mean much or the anger builds in having to redo your computer (again) but I really am. If you can still see a roommate and/or friend.  I've already made a couple pledges to myself. One is to never, ever touch your computer again (which means not even asking you to check out some sports websites even when you are present). And two, I think it's swearing off the porn. Yeah, I know every guy watches it and it's not like it's that big of a deal, but if I'm telling my girlfriend it's OK to wait etc and then I'm logging on the next morning just because of a little pent up sexual frustration from the night before because this is the longest I've even dated someone (1 1/2 months) without having sex with them, then maybe I'm looking at the relationship thing all wrong. We all have sex drives, it's not like I'm ashamed of it, if we didn't the species would find it harder to survive. But it is the way society has come to handle that sex drive that has become all fucked up. I love spending time with Jen, she makes me laugh and I make her laugh. We both like movies, her parents seem to like me, her daughter is cute as a button. We have all these things working for us and here I was worried that I hadn't had sex with her yet. I find Jen very attractive to me but did not make any real overtures until last night. I enjoyed holding her, kissing her, holding her hand, calling her beautiful, all that stuff. I was almost mortified to even make any more advances because she is a mom. It's like I had this fear come over me that since she became a mom, she longer was a sexual being, it's like I thought she was untouchable. That is not a healthy view of sex either. I have to find the middle ground where sex is not what you find in downloaded porn clips and it's not like it's this prude thing either when it's like you are waiting for marriage. It's just something you can share with someone you really care about. As fucked up as my previous views of sexuality have been, I can say one thing is that I have been faithful to the girls I've dated, I guess there's some honour in that.  Anyway, I've already chucked out my two porn DVDs, that's a start. I guess. It's like I shared this wonderful night with Jen last night and what am I doing the next morning after getting my sports fix. Just because we weren't intimate, I have the sexual frustration and watch other people in clips getting intimate. That can be seen as cheating in a round-about-way. I know it sounds stupid and I've already probably sounded like a raving lunatic to you already in this note but maybe this computer freeze in a situation where I shouldn't have been on your computer in the first place and compounded by looking at a porn clip (when it locked the computer) after a nice night with Jen, perhaps someone is telling me something upstairs. Don't invade another man's space no matter how trivial that need (my sports fix) and try and get something deeper in your relationships (which I've been trying to do but obviously not hard enough). So I guess I have to end this note this way and say once again how truly sorry I am for fucking up your computer. If you like me to find another rommate and I move out, I'll understand. I've invaded your space twice now and done major damage to your computer. I'll try and make amends in what way you want me to.  Just writing this not with my thoughts, I haven't even told Jen that I love her. I've shown her at times but I haven't said the actual wors. It sort of scares me to because it past relationships I've always put my heart on my sleeve, expressed emotions freely and all it got me is hurt. But here I was going to have sex with Jen without telling her I loved her. That is cowardly. I think I'm going to have a talk with her.  I hope that not too much was erased off your computer and again, I'll understand whatever decision you make with me.  P.S- If you could, could this incident be kept to ourselves. Getting several clarity of thoughts rom simply freezing a computer downloading a porn clip, people may think I've gone off my rocker.   Well, I'm not keeping it to myself. Nobody at work will learn anything about this but the greater world and the loyal readers of this blog will know the whole story. And you can be the judge at just how fucked up Greg has become over the past two days. He's a good guy but he definitely has a lot of issues to work out. 

						
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Greg took the news of me moving out pretty well. He didn't rant or rave. I think he's still in shock. He's talking about getting the ad sales guy from the office as a roommate. I don't think he'll go for it. I think the full impact of me moving out won't hit until he sees the place empty because he owns nothing.  The fire in my chest has returned. It's been here a week now and at least once a day I have to fight the urge to throw up after coughing so hard I can't breath. My mom bugged me all weekend to see a doctor. I think I might take that advice and get it checked out tomorrow after work. It's hard to interview someone when you're holding your breath trying not to cough in their face. I'll keep everyone posted.  I spent all day Saturday in a farmer's field becoming a lethal killing machine. My brother, his girlfriend and I spent the afternoon hunting gophers. Hunting may not be the right term, we slaughtered them. I was killiing them as fast as I could load the .22. By the end of the day I was the meanest shot. I could hit a gopher at over a 100 yards without much of a thought. Sure some people may call me barbaric and a murderer but those little bastards can destroy a crop in a matter of days and shatter the legs of cattle like nobody's business with all their holes. It's also a great way of relieving stress. Just superimpose the image of someone you hate over the gophers cute little mug and blast away.  Currently playing: Twist- Goldfrapp Current mood: gleefully exhausted (moved the entire football program from old building to new building after work) 

						
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I must apologize to Jen. It's Garrett who screwed up. He thought she wasn't going to make it to the market so he called me. I had talked her just before leaving work and told her that I didn't want to do it. We both ended up at the market but it wasn't all bad, Meg came along.  I bought the most awesome desk today. On my way home from work I stopped off at a garage sale down the alley and discovered a little writing desk which is perfect for my typewriter and writing junk. The desk is two-tiered (very much unlike Alberta's health care system) and the typewriter sits on the lower with the upper part reserved for a lamp and all my papers. The raised part has drawers in it with a large file draw at the bottom. It looks like it's a 100 years old with scratches and marks all over it. I love it to death.  My plan for the next two weeks is to write every day, exercise every day and drink. Well, the drinking part only counts for tonight. In fact, I'm sipping a pina colada right now.  Special note to D. It might be lonely in Laval but it's got to be an amazing place to live. Must tell about the local scene!  Some scribbles I found in my notebook:  Heaven must be in the presence of eternal beauty as defined by our soul.  Beauty is the recognition of something it its purity, its ability to evolk more emotions and thoughts than we are capable of understanding rationally. We become overwhelmed by our senses.  Because we took from the tree of Good and Evil we are condemned to search for knowledge eternally. Knowledge will set us free from Good and Evil.  When you come to understand the animal kingdom, killing becomes neither Good nor Evil but a necessity of life. There is no judgement among other animals because they do not possess the capacity to understand Good or Evil. There just Is. They exist in a state of grace man will continue to search for throughout our existence and never find.  Thoughts, comments, questions, additions???   

						
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Telus has admitted to its mistake and fixed my phone line. They never hooked it up. The guy came today and spent two minutes reconnecting the line at the control panel and it was done.  I'm all happy now because I've got the Internet back. I'm also happy because Meg got approval to stay in Canada. She's got a some paperwork to sort out but it looks like everything is going to work out.  I'm unhappy because Jen pulled a bullshit stunt. She was assigned to cover a Farmer's Market opening tonight. She asked if I wanted to do it and I said I had things to do. She called Garrett, the editor, and told him she couldn't make it to the market. He called me and said he needed me to shoot the opening. Holidays is only a day away. I'm hoping the world collapses while I'm away.   

						
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I have returned briefly to say I hate Telus. My absence is not of my doing but that of circumstance and idiotic corporate greed. Circumstance- I have been overwhelmed at work having to produce three newspapers in two days. Mixed into that is my move into the new place. Idiotic corporate greed- Telus has yet to hook up my phone or Internet because they are too greedy to hire staff in order to keep up with the demands in rural Alberta. I am planning on making my fourth phone call to those corporate pigs today to complain once again that I am unable to phone them from home to complain. I have already ranted publicly this week vis a vis my column. That will teach the bastards to fuck with me.  Those of you curious to know how the move went, it went fine. My new place is fantastic. It's been a week and the place continues to look spotless. I no longer have to lisen to the whining of Greg about his hapless romance which is faltering more and more each day. I no longer have to pick up after somebody else and have complete control of the t.v. and stereo. I am in heaven.  The change has produced a new me. I am more relaxed and willing to take on new challenges. I have been eager to experience new things and I have. I have met someone who excites my imagination and has created a hunger inside of me for more time with her. I never expected it but have welcomed it (Sheri if you're wondering who it is you've already met her. She's very short and very Asian). We are perfectly matched, however, there are obstacles for us to overcome. I'm not sure if it will work but I've got to try. Besides everything is a learning experience.  Currently playing: Greg blabbing on the phone Current mood: Can't wait to get home 

						
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well ladies and germs, I broke my own rule and went out Friday night. In my own defense, I needed to get rid of a bottle of rum I had and didn't feel like drinking alone over the next couple weeks so I decided to teach myself a lesson and got very, very drunk with friends. The plan worked. I was so drunk I could hardly stand, think or see. I ended up at a house party with a bunch of people I didn't know. I threw up in the bathroom, layed on the cold tile floor for a little while as the world spun out of control, broke into a cold sweat, then rejoined the party. The house party was only a few blocks from my place but it took me a good two hours to get home as I stumbled around or stopped to regain my balance as the sun came up.  I woke up today at 2:30 with a headache and sore legs (I'm not sure why). I've been dragging my ass around the house. I went out at about 3:30 to collect my truck from Greg's. It was a great effort and I needed to have a nap when I got back. I had a late supper and am now snacking on smoked salmon and it tastes exceptionally good now that I can stomach food again.  The experience of the past 24 hours has effectively turned me off of touching alcohol for a very long time. Last weekend ended on a whimper and this weekend ended with a bang. My bar star life has run the gamut and will now be laid to rest peacefully with little fanfair.  Taps playing in the background   R.I.P Cody "Mr. Right" Todd 2003-2004 He partied hard, danced harder and drank his weight in booze every weekend. May his ghost never haunt the living.  I am going to pick up Ernest tomorrow morning. I'm very excited to meet my new roommate and get aquainted with him. I'm sure we will grow very close. His new home will allow him to watch me at work crafting the next great American novel.  I am going to attempt to listen to every CD I own during the next week. If I was more capable and less lazy, I could probably figure out if there are enough hours in a week to accomplish this lofty goal. I prefer to find out by trial and error.  Currently playing: Moist- Picture Elvis Current mood: recovering  

						
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I found this while snooping around the Internet. I am the rare few who support Bush but there has to be some changes made in his administration after this.  urlLink Check this out!  

						
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I have been successful in putting paint to canvas. "Ice Cube #2" still needs a little bit of work but my other painting has come off brilliantly. I have titled it "Feeling Blue". As I have feared, I enjoyed myself too much. I already have plans for two other paintings but will need to buy more canvases and gather a larger collection of paint.  It feels good to be creating. 

						
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Let me set the scene: It is 3 a.m., I have Ani DiFranco playing in my headphones, a can of Mug rootbeer in front of me and unrest in my heart.  I have felt restless all day today. I think a major player is the large amounts of sugar I've consumed in the past two days via Pepsi, rootbeer and sour candies. But another part comes from sitting around and doing practically nothing for the past three days. I'm not use to doing so little. I feel like I'm wasting precious time.  I'm trying to stick to my vacation schedule but I'm not sure if I can waste tomorrow doing nothing. I had planned on not getting to work on any of the projects I have planned for my two weeks off until Thursday but I know I will begin some of them tomorrow. I am tired of playing the XBox and getting frustrated at my inability to do what 10-year-olds find very natural and easy to do.  I have to keep reminding myself being proficient at playing video games means nothing. Most kids today can't string a sentence together or create something uniquely their own. I remember their imaginations are being quickly destroyed by the video games they feed on and parents rely on to keep their kids sedated and under control. My mind is free from the idiot box.  Yes, my mind is free. My body may still be stuck in this less-than-ideal world I find myself living in. I am still in Taber, in a small apartment, broke as usual and trying to find a way out but my mind is free. I must find a way to get my body out of this prison so it can rejoin the mind.   I used the word retreat in my post about existing in my own little universe. I would like to strike the word retreat from that post. I am not retreating back into a smaller world but rather coming home.  The past year I have been living two lives. The first was contained inside my head. It was kept locked away to make way for my second life; that of an outgoing, social butterfly. This second life required me to wear a mask. I stepped on stage and took part in the pantomime. I was never me. I was a bit player on the comic stage of a 20-something "normal" life. I almost began believing I was what I was playing. However, I was able to strip the mask away and see what was underneath and what I found was not a hideous face, rather a true and honest one which I will never be ashamed of hiding again. I'm not going to apologize for who I am or what I am.  Some may say spending all this time for myself and this focus on myself is selfish. I would say to them there is no other person more important than yourself. Others may come and go but I will have to live with myself until the day I die. I could imagine nothing worse than living my entire life being uncomfortable with myself. I will spend as much time as it takes in fully understanding who I am.  And with that thought I will need to get some rest if I am to start out on my journey of self-discovery. Goodnight.  

						
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Day Two  Well, I've done nothing but lay around the apartment eating junk food, sipping Pepsi and Rootbeer and playing the rented XBox. I haven't gotten up before noon on both days (also haven't gone to bed until 4 a.m. or later). Today is my last day for doing nothing. Tomorrow I start painting.  

						
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   A quick update before going back to killing Iraqis and Nazis(only in that world known as XBox). I have bought myself some brushes, canvas and paint and I will finally put to canvas what I've carried around in my sketch book for several years now. I will begin with "Ice Cube #2" and see how it goes. I'm using acrylic. I'm still not confident enough nor competent enough to use oil yet and I think acrylic is more to the feel of my vision anyway. If all goes well, I will then paint "Flame #1".  I also checked out the pet store looking for a Siamese fighting fish but will have to wait until next weekend when a new shipment arrives. Ernest (in homage to Papa Hemingway) will live in a nice glass vase found in the large drawer of the desk I bought. It already has gravel and a little fake plant. I thoroughly cleaned everything and have prepared a home atop my television for Ernest when he arrives next week.  Heather pointed out my wonderful typing skills in a previous post. I wrote: Heaven must be in the presence of eternal beauty as defined by our soul. It should have read: Heaven is to be in the presence of eternal beauty as defined by our soul. (Hence heaven is different from every soul as no two people define beauty quite the same)    

						
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Extra! Extra! Read all about it. Cody has sworn off ever stepping into a Taber bar again. Initial reports indicate he's sick of the complete bullshit which is the Taber scene and for that matter any scene.   According to inside reports, Cody spent a night out alone after being abandoned by Jen and Meg at midnight. It was at that point it occured to Cody that the whole business of getting dressed up, drawing out cash he can't really afford to spend and trying to have a good time is pathetic and absolutely unnecessary.  Added to the general depression of the whole night life he had been leading, Cody discovered that the apparent attempt to hook him up with one of Jen's friend was not to be. He met this friend and quickly said goodbye as she headed back to Lethbridge. Still hopeful that something would materialize with Meg, Cody pressed on but he was quickly put in his place when she continued to talk about Anthony and how important he is to her. Adding to further insult, Jen and Meg left early into the evening when things were beginning to get interesting.  Determined to make an example of the night, Cody came home, got out of his GQ get-up and dressed more to his personality and liking, and headed out to the the Heritage. He consumed one beer while watching all the pathetic people try to maintain an air of happiness and sexuality which in reality doesn't exist.  His distaste for anything remotely resembling a drinking establishment will likely result in Cody not attending this year's Cornfest as previously planned. He has vowed to stop the stupidity which has consumed the past two years of his life.  A decision has been made to retreat back into a world which is much smaller. Contact with the outside world will be kept to a minimum. The protective walls will be rebuilt, the bubble will encapsulate Cody once more. He will live within his own personal universe.  When asked what he will do within this limited existence, he replyed, "I will create and accomplish the things which I've only up till now dreamed of doing. I will become an artist in every sense of the word." 

						
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Just a quick update a few hours after the last post. It appears that I am unhappy (was at the time of the post) but really I am quite happy. I have taken this event, learned from it, and have discarded it. I no longer have an attachment to the moment. It happened in the past and I am living in the now. What else can a person do?  And to clarify, I don't blame Billy for what happened. Meg and I were not dating and noboby knew about our budding relationship. I understand why Billy focused in on her. She's very attractive on many levels. At least she was. In the end, she turned out to be like every other woman in the bar. It's the disappointment of finding out this apparently unique and fascinating individual is nothing of the sort and not the actual fact she's not interested in me which hurts the most.  As much as I find faults with Greg, I have to count him among my close friends. He called me this morning to see how I was doing. I left early last night and rather abruptly and it had him concerned. He didn't see the incident and was drunk himself and didn't catch the undercurrents within the group at the end of the night.   "Happiness depends upon ourselves" — Aristotle 

						
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Fuck women. The vile, lying, manipulative, cunt whores they are. If you want to see evil in its pure form, looking no further than something with tits and an ass.   This is not a late night, drunken rage thing. It started out as that but I have sobered and continue to feel the same way. In fact, I've felt this feeling growing inside of me for some time now.  What set this off, you ask?  Meg called me tonight needing to get out away from Jen for a few hours. She needed to talk about things. She needed someone to listen to her. I, of course, agreed thinking this might lead to something. It did but not what I expected. By the middle of the night she was dancing with Billy and progressed to making out with him on the dance floor at the Heritage (it's a bar in Taber). I nearly went insane for a moment.  I left the bar and got some air and returned thinking I could manage to make it the last fifteen minutes before last call. I lasted two and had to leave again. I sat alone for almost an hour thinking, cursing and crying.  A voice inside of me had said before the night began that I was getting myself into nothing but a world of hurt. It was my gut instinct and I'll never doubt it again.  I only went out tonight because I thought Meg needed me. I thought the fact she looked up my number and called me to talk about her problems meant something. It meant nothing. Like so many others before her and so many others I've heard of, she used me, a man, like women are only capable of doing.   I am so angry at women, the world, nature for making men so dependent on women. I could easily kill tonight. The anger boils just below the surface. I am having a hard time controlling it. I want to destroy something in rage.  I will say this with no doubt in my heart or my mind that I will never allow a woman into my heart again. This is no idle threat. I am through with allowing women to hold their sexual power over me. I am not in need of comfort, caring, or love.  I will go as far as to say I will destroy any woman who tries to put her devices on me.  I have been very zen like in my thinking of life these past two weeks but I can not bring myself to abandon the hate, contempt and rage I hold for women in general. I detest the species as a whole. There are a very, very select few who I do not reject and they will know who they are. As for the rest, they can go fuck themselves to eternity. I have no use for them whatsoever. 

						
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I've done some intense downloading of songs the past two days. I've been trying to rebuild my very extensive collection of MP3 files lost when Greggie (who is currently replacing the food in his refridgerator after the old one quite on the weekend) destroyed my hard drive. To give everyone an idea of my very diverse and completely incoherent listening tastes here is a small list of artists I've downloaded (because I'm arrogant enough to believe my musical selections mean a great deal to people).  1.  urlLink  Ani Difranco   - feminist folk/jazz/blues/rock singer/songwriter 2.  urlLink  Rasputina   - Cello group blasting out very original music 3.  urlLink Annie Lennox  - One time leader of the Eurythmics 4.  urlLink Anastasia  - Greek group who did the soundtrack to "Before the Rain" 5.  urlLink Dresden Dolls  - Cabaret/gothic duo introduced to me by Heather 6.  urlLink Broadcast - Trip-hop group from Burmingham, England. 7.  urlLink Lamb  - another trip-hop group. 8.  urlLink  Emliana Torrini  - An Icelandic vocalist. She's best known for singing Gollum's Song for LOTR. 9. Hans Zimmer score for   Blackhawk Down   10.Prince- At least the stuff he created while going under that moniker. 11. urlLink Goldfrapp  - One of the best trip-hop bands out there.  A great site to check out for those interested in knowing where I've discovered the greater world of trip-hop can check out  urlLink  Triphop-music.com    

						
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I have just finished Timothy Findley's  Pilgrim  and continue to remain speechless. It took only two days of non-stop reading (534 pages) to reach the amazing conclusion of this wonderful book. I won't even attempt to explain it but advise anyone who has any taste for great literature and a thought-provoking read to get their hands on a copy.  Spellbound as I am over Findley's book, I feel a slight despair at his talent. This is his third book which I've devoured, and devoured is the right word. I fear I will never be able to spin words into the magic Findley is capable of doing so effectively. He goes from elegant to barbaric, insightful to comical and always with a style all his own.  It's not that I want to write exactly as he does but I want to have the same, what am I looking for, essence in my writing. I feel as if my words clatter and bang together on the written page. I question if my word choice is lacking. Does my pacing leave a reader breathless as it races along or does it start and stop? Above all, I am worried I don't have the ability to bring to life real, living characters which will engage readers and capture their hearts.  Perhaps I am fretting too much about nothing. I am still in the early stages of my writing career. A novel has yet to appear in my desk drawer. I have yet to see my stories printed in a literary journal.  I am encouraged, however, at my progress as a writer. I have been compelled at odd times during the day or night to record thoughts and observations about a story I am working on. The puzzle that is the story of a man and his fateful relationship with a young girl is beginning to take a tangible form. An outline of its form is taking shape. I have begun to live with my characters.  Currently playing: Savage Garden's Affirmation album (don't ask) Current mood: Tired 

						
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Today has been food, Timothy Findley's  Pilgrim , laundry, more food, book, laundry, Internet, cooking food/beginning of Life of David Gale, eating, back to movie and now blogging. It's been a very good day. I will probably wrap it up with an hour or two of writing, more  Pilgrim , light workout, food (in the form of protein-packed oysters, YUM!) then shower and bed. God, if only every day could be like this.  There was an interesting arguement at the beginning of Life of David Gale which I found very profound. It went something like fantasies must not be achievable because fantasies facility a desire which drives us and makes us hungry for life. If we achieve our desires, we are unfulfilled once we've reached our goal because we no longer desire it. The only reason we desire something is because we do not or can not have it. Once we do, we must look for other desires.  This explains why rich people want to get richer. This explains why so many artists who have struggled for so long with success and fame fall apart once they achieve it. They do not know how to continue. There is no goal, desire or fantasy any longer. Living without a fantasy, without something to desire, must be unbearable. There is no direction to follow. Life would turn into a void in which nothing would matter. I guess the saying "reach for the sky" is a pretty good piece of advice. THe loftier the goals, the more rewarding life will be as you struggle along trying to reach it.  I just thought of another which would apply: "Happiness is the journey not the destination."  By the way, faithful readers of this blog will notice the name has changed. This blog is no longer known as Cody's Corner. I have found a much more enlightened and philisophical name. If a person is seeking their paradise, they are said to be kissing the sky because it means they have found their heaven.  I also like the idea of always reaching up and out toward something bigger than myself. The sky is vast and constantly changing yet always the same.   

						
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Today has been very zen-like. It's truly amazing the amount of thinking a person can do in one day when spending it alone. I believe every person should spend at least a week by themselves once a year.  I am finding my centre for the first time. I am beginning to understand what I must do in the coming year to make myself happy. I am beginning to see a path I must take in all aspects of my life in order to achieve what I hold inside. I am not going to share what that direction is going to be nor am I going to describe what the path looks like. I must become fully aware and comfortable with those facts for myself, internalize them and make them a part of me before I may release them to the judgement of others.   I must make right with myself and not right with the world. I have been waging a war with the world because things have not been right for me. Things have not turned out as I had planned or desired. Each failure was an injustice done to me I thought.  It has not been right that I face financial difficulties every day. It has not been right that I am alone and have no one to share my life with. It has not been right that others less deserving have got things better than I do. These are all untrue. These are not wrongs but merely workings of the world of consequence and circumstance.  I need to be right with myself and consequence and circumstance will align themselves to be right with me. I will create the balance I seek. I will find what I am looking for because I will know what it is I seek.  I expect every day to be a monumental struggle to keep myself on this path I am beginning to see emerge from the fog before me. I anticipate many obstacles, entanglements, and temptations to step from the path. If I can hold my centre, my guiding compass, I will be able to stay on the path or if I do wander from it be able to find it again and continue on my journey.   

						
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Ernest is busy exploring his new home. He's very energetic for a fighting fish and has the largest set of fins I've ever seen. He's a magnificent red and mauve mixture. He must be fairly comfortable because he already ate today. Normally it takes a couple days for a fighting fish to accept new food. Ernest hesitate for about two seconds before gobbling up the two pellets. 

						
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Early Sunday morning and I've been kicking around the Internet and had an idea strike my brain. It might be luck or the guiding genius of Heather via her links on her blog (see links at left) but I've discovered there are a lot of very intelligent people lurking in the shadows. I asked myself why our culture continues to turn out things like Survivor, Britney Spears and MTV or why it is idiots seem to be everywhere. That's when it occured to me the idiots of the world, although they seem to be in control, will not ultimately survive. Taking the Bible for what it's worth, says the meek shall inherit the earth. I believe the intelligent, creative and wonderfully diverse underground of meekers will one day be able to rise up and make this world a better place. We are gathering our forces and saving our strength for the day to come. In the meantime, we will continue to chip away at the foundation of the palace of idiots. We will educate the uneducated; continue to introduce thoughful art, music and literature; and carry the torch of human intelligence through this dark age of mindless idiot-box, video-gamed, pre-programmed zombies.  But now I must retire and slumber awhile before departing on my big day to the city to pick up Ernest. 

						
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I'm glad I'm the only one in the office at the moment as I had to chuckle after reading D's comment about asking someone for a raise. Heather, you'll appreciate the humor. I was going to ask for a raise yesterday but unfortunately I was busy doing my job. Today much the same thing. I did a major interview this morning and have been working on getting past the politicians all afternoon. I just found out Colleen has left for two weeks of vacation. It appears my request for a raise, which is futile in itself, will have to wait until mid-August. So it will remain Kraftdinner, generic variety of course, and water for this intrepid reporter.  On a professional note, I finally got to FOIP a government organization today. I'm so happy. I've been wanting to try my hand at getting past the censorship in this country but have never had a good excuse until now. It will be interesting to see what come of the request. The office staff at the Taber and District Housing looked confused when I presented them with the completed request form. The secretary tried to explain that they couldn't give out the information I'm requesting because of FOIP at which point I pointed out that was the reason for the request is for them to go through the formal process of supplying me with the FOIPed info.   It's been two years but I've finally found a scandal which I am not going to let slip away. I'm excited for the first time at the prospect of doing some real investigative, high impact reporting. I'm planning on camping out in front of the low cost housing complex to see if the neighbours are doing what my source says they're doing to her.  Look out Woodward and Berstein, I've got my own Watergate.  "And on behalf of the little people working in little towns I accept this Pulitzer and hope I'm an inspiration for the countless other journalists struggling away in the middle of nowhere and dream of making it big."  A standing ovation, how wonderful. 

						
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Currently playing: Long Cool Woman in a Black Dress- The Hollies Current mood: Tired but satisfied (get your mind out of the gutter. I just got back from a walk)  I don't have a lot to say tonight. I've settled back into work with the appreciation of Taberites. All week people have been telling me how glad they are I'm back from holidays because the paper was so bad. Before I went on holidays nobody ever told me what they thought of my writing and my journalistic skills. I guess the feeling from most is I'm a great journalist. One person even said they think I'll be the next Michael Moore (it would be nice to have the money).   

						
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It's early Wednesday morning and I felt like making a quick comment on perhaps my favourite movie of all time. I've been going through my video collection watching one movie a night until I've watched my entire collection. I came to  An American In Paris  with Gene Kelly and Leslie Caron.  I have seen this movie hundreds of times and I never get tired of it. This movie works on every level. Great choreography from Kelly. Great direction from Vincente Minnelli. And great score by the Gershwin brothers.  Those who are not aquainted with this 1951 best picture winner, the story is about an American painter (Kelly) struggling in Paris after WWII. He meets a girl (Caron) while out with a new friend (Nina Foch) who wants to sponsor his painting ambitions. This sponsor is in love with Kelly. The girl and Kelly fall in love. But this girl is also in love with a French singer (Georges Guetary) who happens to be a friend of Kelly's. Of course none of the lovers know any of this until the end. There are wonderful dream sequences showing the ambitions of Kelly and his pianist friend (Oscar Levant). The pianist is privy to the information that Kelly and the French singer are in love with the same girl in one of the funniest scenes ever to be put on film.  If you want to be introduced to musicals, I suggest  An American In Paris . It proves musicals are anything but dull. I guarantee you'll be looking for more Gene Kelly movies after seeing him in this movie. I can say with great conviction he was the greatest entertainer ever to enter Hollywood and the best dancer ever to make a movie.  From movie appreciation to writing appreciation. I have picked up a rather large volume from the library containing 65 of the best short stories from the master short story writer W. Somerset Maugham. I plan to write short stories and sell them to magazines I figure I should study only the best. I've read a couple stories tonight and have thoroughly enjoyed them. I like Maugham's writing style. He's a cross between the very succinct and punchy prose of Hemingway and the content and plot development of a Graham Greene or Edgar Allen Poe. It's a very nice combination. 

						
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   First day back at work and I already pulled through with three stories (four if the president of the new seniors organization would have called). I dug a story out of last week's issue. A woman had wrote a letter to the editor about a serious problem with the house next door being a complete wreck. Weeds infested the front and back yard. Two old junker cars had sat on the front lawn for years and the town has done nothing about any of it. This woman has complained to the bylaw officer, health officer and anyone else she can talk to at the town and nothing has been done. Nobody was going to follow up so I did. It's going to be a great story.  I also did a wrap up story on the town manager leaving. He announced it last week but the manager told me Garrett had told him he was swamped and I would do the story when I got back from holidays. I loved hearing it from the town manager. I said something about how I noticed the paper was a bit skimpy on news while I was away. The manager said, "yeah, skimpy is the right word." You've got to like it when the most powerful guy in town can clearly see who's responsible for the paper's success.  Garrett also didn't talk to Monte Solberg who was renamed the finance critic for the Conservatives. He didn't talk to the councillors in town to see if they are running again in the fall election. Didn't call the mayor to see if he's running again or to get the official announcement by one of the councillors for his bid for mayor.  Nothing has been done on the hot weather and how that has helped crop development during the past two weeks. Nothing done on the outbreak of grasshoppers because of the heat.  No update on West Nile now that the heat has come.  Nothing done on what the town is going to do without the town manager while they look for a replacement.   Nothing done on the latest development with the border issue (the U.S. has almost got Japan convinced to back off the testing of every cow).  The Vauxhall Advance (a very small weekly the Times staff also writes for) was eight pages with only four stories and two photos. A half page ad ran on the "Your Town" page. We've never done that as far as I know. I've looked through almost 10 years of papers and not one ad has ever appeared on the feature page.  The best news is the digital camera is out of commission. The thing will have to be sent to Fuji and will take at least eight weeks before anything is heard from them. From what I can tell the entire CPU inside is fried. I don't think there's anything that can be done. Meanwhile, we get to go back to shooting film. Joy, sweet Joy! The next couple months are going to be fantastic. I've got back my 24mm lens, fast focus and motordrive. What more can a guy ask for?   

						
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   In less than 12 hours I go back to being a journalist for a small town newspaper. I don't expect I should have a lot to do my first day back. The paper goes to press Tuesday and I've got a lot of catching up to do but then I am the workhorse in the office and may find half a dozen story assignments waiting for me. I'm prepared for both. What I would really like to do tomorrow is get my new computer set up. It'll take a better part of a day to transfer all my files from the laptop to the new desktop (an old G3 from the back but new to me). There are a million preferences to reset in the various programs and small personalized touches needed. I'll have to re-enter all my contacts in my address book for e-mailing.  I'm actually looking forward to going back. The two weeks off really helped with my angst toward the paper. I'm not going to blame the paper for my current career situation. I'm going to work harder at doing what I need to do to advance myself. I need to focus on becoming better at my job. I know there are larger media outlets who do see my work. Their are editors and managers who do notice those who stand out. I need to stand out more than I have. I've got to stop pretending I'm a good journalist and concentrate on being one.  We'll see how long I can keep up the current enthusiasm. Small town papers have a great way of destroying eager, young journalists.  My CD experiment has failed miserably. I am no where near finished listening to all the albums. I should have the CD rack empty by the end of the week. I recommend my experiment. It's amazing the music you forget you have and love. Currently playing is Moby's Play album. I listened to this nonstop during college. The 16 of us in the photo lab would have this album blaring while we rushed around developing film and printed pictures. I wish I could relive those days just once more.     

						
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Currently playing: Jimi Hendrix Live at the Filmore East Current mood: Proud of myself  Curiosity got the better of me tonight. I went out to buy a bottle of pop and noticed Jen's car parked outside the Palace. I couldn't resist. I went in and had a beer. Jen and Meg were just leaving when I came in. They hung around for a couple minutes while I waited to order my drink. I was polite but very brief with my answers to their questions.   I met them over at the Oilmen's a bit later. I sipped my ice water and watched the Ultimate Fighting Championship on the big screen while they sat in silence.  Jen wanted to go dancing so we went to the Heritage. I drank more ice water, watched some show about university pledges called Pledge Life. Meg and Jen danced a bit and then left when they couldn't find me. I had taking up a spot by the bar.  Meg tried to make an excuse about her behaviour Friday night. A song was playing that she knew was played Friday and she went on about she likes the song and hadn't heard it in a long time but she thinks she might have danced to it on Friday but she can't remember because she was drunk. A complete lie of course. It's what I expected her to do.  The interesting part of the night though was my reaction to everyone else. There were a lot of women out tonight and there was even a group of three trying to attract my attention. I felt nothing. It felt fantastic. I feel liberated. I wasn't sure if I could really live up to my bantering earlier about not caring and changing my attitude toward women. I passed with flying colours.   No, I'm not gay. I'm also not pissed off at women because I'm not getting it. That is always a popular response by people when someone says they don't have any need for a relationship or even sex. I mean in all honesty it's been so long since I've had sex I don't even remember what I'm missing.  So now I will be labelled a loser who keeps to himself and can't get any with the ladies. I'm frigid, a fag. I'm an angry loner who spends his nights jacking off to porn dreaming of being a stud who women want to sleep with all the time. What other labels are there? Some will pity me. Others will reject me. Some will fear me.  Now, my loyal readers, I swear this will be the last post discussing anything to do with Meg. I just thought because my previous posts have attracted so much attention I would keep everyone updated. It ends here.  On a lighter note, it seems Ernest is a huge Jimi Hendrix fan. When I put on the disc he started swimming around displaying his fins. Normally he's very lethargic at night but Jimi can get him moving.  "Hear my train a comin'...hear my train a comin'.....hear my train a comin'......" And Jimi takes over on guitar.  Rock out and have a good night, everybody! 

						
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I walked home through the rain tonight and it was the most spiritual thing I've been a part of for a long time. I was left alone with my thoughts and the gentle tapping of the rain. It was like God was washing away all the worries and doubts.  I would like to write more about this wonderful night but will save it until tomorrow. I must get some sleep after a very long and confusing week sleep-wise. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I broke off surveilence early tonight. The housing story has turned into a very difficult story. The neighbours talked to me tonight and told a very different story of what was going on. I've got to confirm certain things with the police, talk to more people tomorrow and begin watching the neighbourhood to catch some of the activities that have been going on of late.   I felt just like a cop in the movies tonight. I found a dark corner to park my truck (after turning off the lights down the block so as not to attract attention). I sat for two and a half hours watching the street. I could see people moving about their living rooms and a few people moving back and forth between houses. All very interesting but not what I am waiting to happen.  Tomorrow morning I'm going to cruise by the street again as the neighbours tell me the boyfriend, who isn't living their according to this woman getting evicted, is always in the backyard in the mornings sitting on the back step smoking. I'm going to try and get a photo of him at the house.   

						
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Currently playing: Left Outside Alone- Anastacia Current mood: Depressed  It's that time of the month again folks. I've been wallowing in career envy at recent SAIT graduates who have portfolios which blow me away. They have more work experience than I do. They're going places quickly while I sit here in small town Alberta ready to slit my wrists. It's all so depressing it's almost funny.  Now I know I shouldn't begrudge these people because they're working hard for what they get. I understand that but circumstance has so much to do with how far they've gotten so quickly. It seems timing is not my thing. I graduated in the middle of a mini recession and just when papers where starting the complete conversion to digital. I was part of the last class to be taught using film. Basically I'm a dinosaur in the pj business.  I'd like to go digital but have no money in which to switch over. It's the classic catch-22 situation. I need a digital to compete in the freelance market where I can make more money but I need money to get the digital to make money. And around I go on the merry-go-round. The trick is getting off the merry-go-round standing up.    

						
</post>


</Blog>