<Blog>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Cingulars is buying out AT&T wireless, which quite frankly is surprising, because although I understand the concept of AT&T Wireless being a sub and seperate company from AT&T, you would think AT&T was making enough cash to keep it.  They are a damned phone company after all, but Cingular is buying them, so all I have to say is that I am proud that a business can swoop in when a new craze is started (cell phones) and become so large.  They plan to add wireless hi-speed internet, too.  I know, I should link to things.  I will starting next time, I promise.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ice cream does not phase me so much, but I do love cake.  Even if it's out of one of those $2.99 cake mix boxes.  I reported a bug to Google about Gmail.  I feel justified in having an account now, considering this is beta and as it is, it is my duty to help better the application.  My summer plans have gone well today, as I feel my plans are going into process, such as the damned Honors work I must do.  I have discovered that when I listen to a song with a beat I like, I tend to thrust my fist towards my monitor and bang on my desk and underneath my monitor.  I've actually produced some pretty nice sounding and complicated drum beats.  Anyways, back to subject.  I've been working on the Reviuss logo.  Everyone knows it's a damn V.  But it is a very nice looking V, it doesn't look exactly like a V.  Why can't people assume it's just a neat arrow-looking object.  Accept that!  There is a good discussion going on in my forums about psychology and philosophy, finally the boards are running with . . well, some sort of intelligence.  http://rev.shadonet.com/forums
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Reviuss is getting worked on.  I want my development site, and it will be artsy, yay for that.  I am still thinking about it and contemplating things in my mind, but I am excited.  I have a new logo / image.  And when I say image, I mean image, not graphic.  I have a Gmail account now.  Extremely fast load times and VERY good use of DHTML, it makes me not hate JavaScript, in fact I will be incorporating some DHTML into Reviuss now because of it's inspiration along with Blogger.  I may be moving to Movable Type.  They have a pretty website, and it's written in Perl.  Although, since I am working on the new site, there would be no point, so never mind.  Firefox .9 is out.  I love the Mozilla Foundation to death and hope one day to start or be involved in an operation like that.  I'm pretty sure that is my dream and that is my goal and that is what I am going for, and why I started in software development in the first place.  I love software architecture and technology.  I am definitely back into the game, CS major for me!  I hope I get into MIT.  The things my mother told me were a bit depressiong and put me down.  I think that is my first goal in life, leading to my second goal.  I can only hope and pray to the Lord that he helps me accomplish this.  I really am worried.  I am going to revamp the forum.  I want talk of technology.  I realize this means I will be left with possibly approximately 4 users for the time being, but it opens the door for me inviting others without being worried they will find it immature and petty.  I think that is all for now.  Travis was right, a blog is theraputic.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There's about to be an external server error if you don't tell me what the hell is wrong.  Yeah, don't think that fragile metal and flexiglass case will protect you.  I have a baseball bat . . .  and power tools.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Is it just me, or do Ford and Chevy love America now-a-days?  I think their new slogans are "For every mile to the gallon, you kill that many terrorists!"  Ford is advertising with "The Great American Ford Sales Event"  And Chevy with "Chevy.  An American Revolution."  I don't get it.  Why?  What's going on with the patriotism?  I better get a damn American flag paint job when I go in.  ..I think they're losing business to the Japs.  Well, hell.  Every car company will be losing business if we don't lower the damn gas price soon!
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "you lazy ass..make the links clickable...im blogging your lazyness.."  - Travis  He's caught the craze.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I like the word tidal, don't ask me why.  The line is from a Tool song, I don't remember the name but it's about Armagedon.  It should be my theme song.  I'll find the name.  The title of this post is for my mind.  I wish a tidal wave would come and wash it all away, a lot of stress has come lately from the programming thing.  I love programming, and I've been burning myself out making something that isn't needed or useful or innovative, so I'll go back to coding things I love.  I'll tell you whenever I have ideas.  A blog is just what I need, something to write.  I like journalism, and I love psychology, so soon enough I'll move this blog over to rev.shadonet.com and I'll make my own design, figure out how to add my shoutbox (which I did code, muaha, bow to my 10 lines of text input Perl script), and also add a special section for "Life Unnamed."  For now I'll just put it on rev.shadonet.com.  A lot of people like to see it.  It will be nice.  Relaxation puts me in a pretty happy mood, and I can count pretty far up who has tried to put me in a happy mood.  Finally, one person did.  Not sure how, but thank you Kaptain.  Really.  :)  Anyways people, Life Unnamed, coming soon.  Until I have a chance to get organized, visit:  http://traviswalters.sytes.net/ - Travis' site.  We are just so cool because we blog after the craze started months ago.  http://rev.shadonet.com/life.gif - A picture of me.  http://rev.shadonet.com/Miracle.html and http://rev.shadonet.com/rl.html - Two articles out of about 5-6 currently written ones for Life Unnamed.  More soon.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've been very into the hybrid bands.  I love Soundgarden, so of course I jumped at the chance to get the first Audioslave album (Lead singer of Soundgarden, band of Rage Against the Machine).  Good band, but they need to come into their own.  I'm sure the next album will be  very  nice.  Also, I loved the song Slither from Velvet Revolver, which is a pretty recent band, they've been together for a while touring but they FINALLY released their CD yesterday, entitled Contraband, featuring Set Me Free (theme song from the movie The Hulk) and Slither.  The lead singer is that from Stone Temple Pilots, and the band of Guns n' Roses.  Let me say, after touring these guys really have found their own.  Great band, great CD, they just sound great and have a good style of music.  Give it a listen.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm neurotic about design.  So, blah.  Comment, damn you people.  I have a few ideas for the design of Life Unnamed.  What do you like?  Tidal - White, watery ish, Hawaiinish. The Map - Torn paper look, old, brown. Simple - Well, simple.  Nice use of browns, light greens, blues, and oranges.  Pretty much just text, no images.  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is the first of a few posts that will be here, in this blog, for explanation to myself and others why Reviuss did not work, where I will be taking "Epoch", and to introduce Life Unnamed.  This blog won't be here forever, because essentially Life Unnamed is where I will be posting.  So here we go.  With the design of things, I've realized I am thinking too much like an application designer, and not like a web designer.  I want things to be too complicated when they shouldn't be, content management should be easy.  However, the application side of things, for instance the administration part, can be complicated, filled with DHTML and curvey images.  I've just recently realized this.  Also, Reviuss was a little bigger than I wanted.  I suppose I didn't really want an entire community for a development team.  Sure, I like my development team (only ONE person ever helps though, so Thank You Carlos for always being there for me, don't think that because Reviuss has changed that the concept has changed, we're still a dev. team :) )  But a community and a dev team site together--no.  Doesn't work.  And all of the time from the dev team would be being put into Reviuss and Epoch.  I want to design rich applications, using new tools like XML.  I don't want to mindlessly drone over the details of usability and then write what has been written over and over again, just a few scripts snatching articles from a database.  So, from now on, the development team (when I have my time) will be working on this.  If I want to make a community, then I should make a damned COMMUNITY, not a place to post articles.  I don't know, and I'm not getting into it right now since it's taken me over 24 hours of non-stop thought to figure out what I have so far.  I swear I'm a neurotic nutcase.  So, in a sense this is still Epoch.  I am still making a site for me to post day-to-day gruff, articles, and keep it all in tact.  Of course, I will work on this little by little not to burn myself out.  I'll be going for my look here, I'll be going for a stylesheet template here, my pretty, simple, XML.  My nice features.  And I'll make the admin part as pretty and Javascripty as I want!  Like Blogger, I like Blogger's DHTML.  Life Unnamed, well that is basically the name of the site.  Anyone remember Subject to Ruin?  I write a lot of articles, you've seen them probably, and I know many at my school love them, they want them in a book.  So I've decided to organize them and put them into collections, Life Unnamed is that collection, along with every day blog stuff, and probably eventually other things.  But while I make this, this...this is my home.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>