<Blog>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       No, Rob, see the note to the right--this is your blog.    
    
    
</post>

<date>29,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       i just realized, i'm in the wrong blog. i should be in the weaveryuleblog. my bad. 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       On audio cassette or in book form: The Ultimate Weight Solution: The 7 Keys to Weight Loss Freedom, by Dr. Phil ($15.60 at amazon.com)                                                                                                       Plain, pastel pink, women's crew-style socks (no design on them)            Movie gift certificates (yes, I copied Rob's idea) --- Regal, Edwards  World peace (or whirled  urlLink peas ) 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Did someone say something about a cat? That sounds delicious. Be sure to keep our water bowl filled. We might choke on the fur.  We also like Old Mother Hubbard's P-Nuttier Extra Tasty, Natural, Basted Dog Biscuits, available at Petco at the Quad.   And, those pigs ears that someone gets us at Christmas are tasty too.  
    
    
</post>

<date>29,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Soundtrack CD for the movie "Pirates of the Caribbean"  Gift certificate to: * Pier I Imports * Borders *                  * Crate & Barrel  From  urlLink William-Sonoma  (with catalog # --- some items only available on internet or catalog, but I'm not sure which ones): * Olive Wood Grater, #86-4759445, $29 * Slanted Dish Drainer, #86-4739553, $18 * Peppermint Hot Chocolate Set, #88-4821526, $29 * Peppermint Bark, #88-3491297, $20 * Toffee Trio, #88-1263680, $22  Stamp Stuff for a hobby... Contact Helen Homet:  E-mail: hmhomet@aol.com    Phone: (562) 945-4636 Stampin' Up Consultant (free shipping if ordered by 12/10 --- saves additional 10%) Hobby Supplies: * Stamp Set: "Snow Angels" (#102692), $14.95 * Stamp Set: "Best Borders" (#102019), $21.95 * Paper Crimper (#101618), $19.95 * Stamp: "Hand Stamped By" (#103516), $19.95 --- add name: "Cindi" * Stamp Set: "Good Times," (#100116), $28.95 * Gift Certificate in any amount  Thanks.   
    
    
</post>

<date>29,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       1.  Hat(s)   2. Gift certificate to  urlLink hat store  3. Gift certificate to a store that may not specialize in the sale of             hats, but has some hats in inventory 4.  urlLink Menoxidyl  5. Gift certificate for  urlLink greyhound bus lines   
    
    
</post>

<date>29,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Ok, so my wish list might not be as funny as Rob's has been. But, it has live links:                                                                                                                                                                    
    
    
</post>

<date>29,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Audrey--                                                                                blender, 9X9" baking dish, 11x8" baking dish, blue kitchen towels, leaf blower   Timothy--[a] vice, thread seal tape, Home Depot gift card, Battel's Hardware gift certificate    Daniel--  2001 Tour de Suisse video,                                   2000 Tour de France video, 1998 Tour de France video, 2000 Giro d'Italia video, 1997 Tour de France video, 1999 Vuelta a Espana video, 2003 Vuelta a Espana DVD, 2003 Giro d'Italia DVD, Crash DVD, 2003 Year in Review book, money, WCP (World Cycling Productions) gift card ( you can find all of these at  urlLink worldcycling.com ) 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Here are the gift-giving pairing for Christmas Eve gift-sharing fun 2003: Doris gives to Steve Glen gives to Dave Cindi gives to Audrey Beth gives to Cindi Steve gives to Doris David gives to Glen Rob gives to Beth Kyle gives to Richard Audrey gives to Jane Richard gives to Rob Jane gives to Kyle  Please post your wish list on this blog to help the person who is shopping for you. Thanks. 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Here is the first sample posting. I will send everyone an invitation to join the blog. You may then sign in and post your wish list stuff for Christmas, post Christmas greetings for everyone to read. Please enjoy the first Peterson Yule Blog!  Blog is a contracted word--a combination of the word "web" and "log" --"blog." 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       What a crazy place this is!   I have tried to post some of the pictures but the JobStarts server is not responding. I will have to get that working when we get home.   I had a great time with everyone. Hope we can do it again next year. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Dear Family,  I hope all are getting rested after the big day.  I want you all to know that I had a very nice time this Christmas.  I thought that it would be hard to see you all disperse on Christmas day but since we don't know the exact day that Christ was born we just can celebrate His birthday when the family can be together.  Missed Andrew and hope that he can come to warm So. Calif. sometime this year to visit.  God bless you everyone.  Mom, Doris, Gram 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I love Sam but have never known him to be so articulate.  Also, while in PetSmart yesterday, my favorite checker said that whichever dogs I was buying for must be pretty spoiled.  Have Samson and Ashley ever had Pupcorn?  Samson may want to rethink his version of the "Pool Story" if he ever wants to try some...  Love, Auntie Beth 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       It seems that Glen is the only one who can post pictures.  Bummer.  I have a picture of the cat under the tree wishing us all a Merry Christmas (or that we would all disappear and leave her alone in HER house, can't tell the difference), but only the administrator person has those rights.  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Now Louise sounds like a level-headed cat.  D.C., of course, is nowhere near level-headed.  At this moment she is lying atop a pile of unfinished work on my desk.  I have thrown her off numerous times, but she will not be deterred.  When I was scanning something using Steve's computer, she was all over his desk like a rash.  I believe she is anxious for us to leave so she can sleep on the bed without being thrown off.  Please do not get her anything for Christmas.  She wouldn"t appreciate it.  She is a spoiled cat and reminds me way too much of myself at times...  Beth  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       This is a test. This will now show up on the blog. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I told Sam about the pool story on the blog from Beth. He asked that I give his version of the story--he can type, he just didn't want to hog my computer.  Sam seems to remember that Rob fell into the pool when he was chasing a squirel. Sam then remembers that he jumped in the pool which had a cover on it at the time and pushed Rob out, saving him from exhaustion and eventual drowning under the cover.  Thanks to Sam, Rob is with us today. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       thought of some other useful things:  9v, and aa batteries  socks-any color, or type.  stereo headphones-for guitar amp  phone cards  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
        meoooooowwwww!   I'd rather not be dog stew for Christmas, something I just noticed that was published on the blog.  I do like all sorts of kitty treats you find at almost any store. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       my fave christmas story was last year when my little brother came to visit, and i was able to hang out with him after being out of contact for three years. hope i can see both of my brothers this year. 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       One of my favorite Christmas stories happened when Glen, Cindi, Samson, Dick, and Jane came to P'Ville for Christmas.  We were all around the table making merry when Rob appeared, much like Santa Claus, to annonce that Sam had gone for a dip in the swimming pool.  We all laughed and went back to our merry making, confident that Rob was just joking (Rob?  Joke?!  Who'd 'a' thunk?)  A few minutes later Rob and Sam both appeared soaking wet at the door...and we all felt a little guilty for not having believed Rob.  But we got over it.  Thanks to Rob and Sam for a great Christmas memory.  Love, Mom or Auntie Beth 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Hello,  I believe I have already told the person who is an official gift giver to me, but just in case, here is the Official List:  Beth only wants things that can be use up like candles or coffee (check her closets and the rest of her house to know why...)  OR  things that are beautiful and useful like dishes, plates, etc. in shades of blue, gold, or yellow...  ALSO  Donations to worthy causes such as the Muscular Dystrophy Association, churches, or the Society for the Prevention of Reproduction in the Poor White Trash Community (SPRPWTC).  Yes, I made the last one up, but I couldn't help it after another day as a public school teacher in El Dorado County.  ACTUALLY  I am most looking forward to Christmas with all, or close to all, of my family.  Feliz Navidad, Beth 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       It would be a good idea for everyone to check and see what other people are getting other people to avoid duplicate gifts. For example: Rob has already recieved a clock radio CD player device. He in fact already has it so this won't spoil to surprise.  
    
    
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       And, here are some images from tonight:     Dinner at the  urlLink Chicago famous Berghoffs .     The street near my hotel.     The lobby of the famous Palmer House Hilton--brought to you by priceline.com for $74 a night! WOW! 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Hi,  I'm hoping that Timothy's REAL wish is for a vise, not vice.  Makes a big difference...I'm just bringing it up because I have not come up with my own list yet and I'm stalling for time.  Congratulations to Audrey for starting us out!  Beth 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       It involves all of us meeting at a home on a warm ocean, with plenty of room and activities for all the different ages. It would help if a maid and cook were part of the deal. More importantly, it would be away from the daily routines and distractions of everyday life. Now if it was a home I owned and lived at that might be even better, but I don't buy a Lottery Ticket any more.  urlLink I am sure Glen could find a link for this one.   Santa note: Glen might like this link-- urlLink Mayan Palace . 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
                   These images are from Miami from the window of my hotel overlooking Biscayne Bay. [I'll check on that spelling later.] The forcast high today was 80.   Tomorrow I am back up to Chicagoland. When I was there on yesterday, it was 26.  
    
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Indiana Jones DVD Set James Bond DVD Set One or Three                                                                                                      
    
    
</post>

<date>08,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
                                        adapter to play game boy games on the game cube Lord of the Rings Two Towers DVD Special Edition Metal of Honor Rising Sun Playstation 2 version Soul Calibur II for Playstation 2 Version Castlevania Lament of Innocence Playstaion 2 version 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Beth Peterson 	* bethepete@hotmail.com 	 	  Cindi Peterson 	* mrspeterson@earthlink.net 	 	  Doris Peterson 	* dordorpete@earthlink.net 	 	  Audrey Wilson 	* engr@drecomm.com 	 	  kyle curtin 	* kylecurtin@comcast.net 	 	  rob weaver 	* toastgeek7@hotmail.com 	 	  Timothy Wilson 	* tgwilson@prolife.net 	 	  Glen Peterson 	* glenjpeterson@earthlink.net 	 	  Steve Curtin 	* s.curtin@comcast.net  Dick and Jane Remington * dicnjane263@earthlink.net 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Richard and Jane Remington are also having trouble accessing the family yule blog. We will coach them once they arrive on the 17th. Then their lives will be complete. If you are getting a gift for them, contact me. Audrey should already have my mom's wish list on e-mail. Kyle needs my dad's, so I can help, if needed. 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       you guys are having too much fun. but that's not a bad thing... here's a better list than the one including minoxadyl:           a radiator-for a 1988 toyota corolla, if you have one lying around  gift cards/certificates for: target, tower books/records, mervyns, anywhere that sells food, guitar center, amazon.com, interpunk.com, cdnow.com, eastbay.com, amc theaters, blockbuster video, frys electronics, best buy, greyhound bus lines                   lakers/dodgers shirts  tickets for  urlLink lakers /dodgers games   urlLink manchester united soccer jersey-looks like this   since the cat idea was a bust, how about a pet rock?  pez dispensers-i already have c3po, batman, boba fett, and speedy gonzalez   urlLink a large, black or green one of these-    dvd-                                                                                                                          fletch, fletch lives, european vacation, anything with chevy chase, midnight cowboy  guayabera shirt(s)  cd-elliott smith:        , MIRV:                    , simon and garfunkel, santana: best of  pants-levis 501 preshrunk, dickies: tan, black or grey work pants without the cell-phone pocket, 34w 30L  cheese-mild cheddar, jack  
    
    
</post>

<date>03,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
          I had to come all the way to Lancaster, PA for this image. I am sure that there are people who appreciate this kind of weather at this time of year. I liked how the sun was shining on this field, backlighting the trees and the fence. I am looking forward to being home the rest of December. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       HELLO,  I am now posting as myself not as Steve on his computer while he is not at home.  More later.  Beth 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Hello,  This will probably post as Steve, since I am using his computer (without permission, of course...) and I have attempted to sign in to Blogger but it will not let me.   I can access it as my user name and password as originally set up, but I cannot access the Peterson Yule Blog.  And, yes, Glen, these difficulties are NOT part of the Beth Plan as we all know and love.   If you could send be another invitation, I will attempt to gain access to the Holy of Holies, the inner sanctum, and share with the rest of the group.    Love to all, except Blogger... Beth, Mom, et al... 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Santa Claus now has administrative previleges to correct and add html and links ;~)  And, now we can all add a title or headline. [You should be able to edit your own entries already if you need to change it after you have published. Just edit, preview, and publish again.] 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       subscription to   urlLink Wine Spectator                                    bookstore gift certificate:  Amazon Gift Certificates    music store gift certificate  urlLink Trader Joe's  gift certificate  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Dear Santa: Trend Warning: personal items for women (sweaters, purses, etc.) are now featured with a monogram initial on them. (insert gagging noise)  Please be aware that I do not like this kind of thing. This trend can pass me by. And fast. Don't be tricked into thinking...oh, look, it's popular...I bet she'll like it. You'd lose the bet.  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       This is my Christmas list for 2003  1.  urlLink Staples  Organizer desk lamp  $ 9.99   2.  A jigsaw puzzle made from one of the vacation pictures from Steve and Beth's      2003 Paris vacation.     3.  I can't remember the exact title but it's the biography of George W. Bush just      out.  [Claus note: this might be it:                      ]  4.  Time at the computer from those who exell and know how to cut and paste         etc.  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       i don't really want minoxadyl. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Wow!  Those Peterson girls look almost like sisters in the Formal Family Christmas Photo...(FFCP)  Beth (The Elder Peterson Girl, EPG) 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
          Sorry for the size of this image.  I will work on that next, but it was a large and very beautiful tree picked out and brought home by David and Steve.  Beth 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
          Here we are standing in front of wallpaper that looks like the Space Needle in Seattle. The real Space Needle (where this wall paper is located] has been painted 4 times since 1961. It now costs more to paint it [the real Space Needle] each time than it did to build it. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>28,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Beth and I saw Mystic River today. I am still feeling the tension created toward the end of the movie. That feeling that we can foresee something tragic about to happen and sit helplessly while it unfolds. That violence can't be rethought, retracted, or undone. That often in hindsight perspective is altered in ways that cause regret; intractable, irrepairable harm.  I am sorry to hear that Sam is struggling.  He is a "good dog" in ways that only a dog can be. My best wishes to Sam's recovery. Rob that struck me also about Spellbound. Those things said without question. Those "truths" that go unexamined.  "The absolute value of love makes life worth while, and so makes Man's strange and difficult situation acceptable." - Arnold Toynbee  
    
    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       the contraversy, and fanaticism that has been brought out in americans by this movie is...interesting. i hear that it is indeed very graphic, and bloody. but there are at least three or four films at the blockbuster i work at which tell the story of jesus' crucifixion. i wonder why this one warrants such strong (often fallacious) arguments on both sides of the issue, while these others, some made in the last five years, have slipped under the radar. i'll probably not see the new one, at least not on the big screen. i don't think there are any new discoveries revealed in the film, are there?  i was really sad to see sam struggling this afternoon. i fed the dogs, and he really didn't seem comfortable. he's the best dog ever, and he and i have many fond memories shared.  tomorrow is my twin cousins' birthday bash. just kidding. but that is so cool how they have the same birthday, even though three (i think) years apart.  going back a few posts, i thought the diversity was the star of the movie spellbound. listening to the rancher who employed angela's father say that "not all mexicans are reliable, but i guess there are a few mixed up in there," was really striking to me, and hearing the indian kid and his father who lived in san clemente rip through that list of words for hours was amazing. i cried when the boy from (i think it was missouri) was eliminated, and his younger brother proclaimed without irony "he's still a champ in my eyes." my brothers are both champs.  Before God we are all equally wise - and equally foolish. -Albert Einstein  
    
    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I saw the Passion on Wednesday in the afternoon.  I was really moved by the LOVE that Jesus had for each one of us that kept HIM on track with the plan for our redemption.  It was only His great PASSION for us, even before we were born, that gave HIM the power to tolerate that treatment without just calling it all off.  Thank you JESUS for your great love.  Doris 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Our plan for gifts for Timothy and Daniel includes taking them to the  urlLink Emerald Nuts Quality of Life Expo  that is part of the  urlLink XIX Los Angeles Marathon  and the  urlLink Acura LA Bike Tour  and allowing them to purchase something within a pre-determined price range. The  urlLink Emerald Nuts Quality of Life Expo  has vendors from bicycling shops, athletic shoe manufacturers and lots of cool stuff. I think American Honda will have cars there--and if they want to apply our $20 to the purchase of a car, I will help them drive it home.  
    
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Maybe it's those photos of the Weber Grill Restaurant, but now I'm hungry. Anyway, thought I'd check in before I break for lunch here in the home office suites of Peterson & Peterson. Samson is improving. I'm impressed and encouraged. Thanks for all your expressed empathy. The picture of Briana excavating her nose is CUTE. Beth - had to laugh at the "psycho parents" comment. A universal truth in education. I'm going to see "The Passion of the Christ" tomorrow night. Peer pressure from the grass roots publicity efforts finds me swimming along with the church crowd. Curious to hear public response and to see if ticket sales keep up with opening day results. Nervous about the brutality. May have to come home and watch Sound of Music before falling asleep to calm down. Looking forward to a low-key Academy Awards party on Sunday night (not at our house, though, since Glen will be gone). Won't get to see Mystic River by then, I don't think. So my sentimental selections are: Best Movie - Lord of the Rings, Best Actor - Johnny Depp, Best Actress - Diane Keaton, and that's it so far. Don't know if they are worthy...just picked what I like. Happy Billy Crystal is hosting. That and playing fashion critic are my favorite parts. I laugh everytime someone says in pre-game interviews--- "...and who are you wearing?" I think that's the line. Maybe it's what are you wearing? Whatever --- it's meaningless and fun. 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       A lot has happened since I last visited the Blog.  I've been spending the night aboard ship in San Francisco Bay with a bunch of 10 year olds and their psycho parents and in between doing about 3 full-time jobs.....  I'm sorry to hear about Sam, and I want to reassure his parents that it is NOT the Pupcorn.  I can emphathize with the changes that age brings to health and bodily functions.   Yes, Rob is indeed an nice guy.  Beth 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Does Timothy have a list? 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Just watched Spellbound. Noticed the wide variety of families that these eight kids came from. How the different kids where invested for different reasons. Will watch it again. I would love to have the time to interview all of those kids now. Maybe there is a documentary in that.  
    
    
</post>

<date>21,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Would he like J. S. Bach "The French Suites" Keith Jarrett on the Harpsicord or Deitri Shostakovich "24 Preludes and Fugues op. 87" Keith Jarrett on the Piano??? 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Money because I am saving for a pair of aerobars.  Cycle Sport issues: 	_ Sept ‘03 (TdF) 	_ Sept ‘01 (TdF) 	_ Mar ‘04 (Current) urlLink    A couple of CDs of composers' work, preferably from the Baroque or Classical time period like Corelli or Bach that no one in my family has already on a CD. It can just be something based around a musical instrument like a violin or harpsichord, or just a piece or pieces of music that I would like (interesting operas are fine, but I think drawn out opera is boring, and I guess I like music to be in there besides singing a large portion of the time)  "2003 Year in Review" book of pictures of the ‘03 race season  urlLink   
    
    
</post>

<date>21,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Posting a picture of a kid with her finger in her nose is taking the risk of offending others. If this picture is offensive please let me know and i will change it to one of her with her head on Beth's shoulder. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Glen your point was well taken. Here is a picture of Brianna picking her nose, not thumbing her nose at the rules, but digging away.    
    
    
</post>

<date>21,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       What could be better than a restaurant that cooks meat on giant Weber Grills indoors in the middle of Chicago? I can't think of anything better than  urlLink Weber Grill Restaurant  in Chicago.      These images are from their website and are hosted there. Therefore, when they change it, the images will disappear.  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Editing of posts should be minimal. Restricted only to the cleaning up of typos and clarifying a few things. But to reduce the whole post from 3 paragraphs to one is so sad. It will be more fun if people take some risks here. So long as it isn't me! [Steve knows who I'm talking about.]  I spent a couple of hours trying to figure out how to upload an image or two using the 10 mgs of "free" space that earthlink provides for my monthly subscription fee.   Ok, maybe it was only a few minutes. I will try again soon.  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Glad to hear that there are treatments for Samson. Here's to his improved health and vitality. Looks like Beth and I are in for the Mexico weekend. Working out the pragmatics. Cindi makes Colonial Williamsburg sound enticing even in "winter",,, burrrrr. You know Beth and I, it doesn't take much to entice us to travel. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I made a trip to the vet yesterday. Samson had a scary wheezy breathing spell in the night, and I was concerned. It sounded like human asthma. He honked/coughed/gagged/breathed hard off and on all day. If you've been around him in the last year, you've probably noticed how he sounds when he is excited. Well, it seems worse, so we went to the Dr.  $202 later, we had a bunch of interesting information, several beautiful pictures of Sam on the inside (X-rays), and a bottle of magic juice, 4 oz. of which have to be squirted in his mouth three times of day. (Are you kidding?! Getting ear drops in Ashley's ear was bad enough! I have resorted to soaking a couple dog biscuits with the potion, having had no success with the doggy rodeo wrestling to wedge a squirt tube thing in his mouth!). Anyway, you'll be interested in knowing that in addition to airway disease (bronchitis) and allergies, he has a collapsing trachea. Who knew?! Yes, his air way is constricted halfway down...behind his chest bone. And it's very wide below that from the lungs trying to get the air out --- blowing. It's a genetic thing. He'll be 13 in August, so life is getting more complicated. I started the juice last night. He is doing better and is resting/sleeping easier when he needs to, so that is comforting. And Ashley scores a biscuit, too, everytime she's around for medicine time. I would have been a pushover as a parent.   Poor Sammy. But alas, he's his lovable self. Quite a trooper. The science of it all fascinated me. I enjoyed looking at the x-rays. I saw his bones (of course)...neck, head, and ribs. His very healthy heart. His narrowing trachea with pupcorn stuck in it (just kidding, Aunt Beth). And his lungs. No mass. No cancer. Thankfully. And if the medicine (it's new medicine --- just developed) doesn't work, he can get a stint put in (just like for heart problems). We'll be keeping our jobs to pay for his pharmaceutical habits. Because we love him. His head is on my lap as I write. Bless his paws. These dogs are great company with Glen traveling more. It's great to have Rob around, too. He's a "nice guy." (Just had to throw that in to prove I read past blogs, too.) 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I just caught up on my blog reading. It's enjoyable to read everyone's comments. Glen, I'm in for the Mexico weekend. I know you know that, but I just wanted to confirm. Sounds fun.   Is anyone interested in Colonial Williamsburg some Christmas? I'd really like to do that. I know it's not everyone's thing, but I love the time period and the area. I noticed that our timeshare exchange group has availablity there in December. This may or may not be the year, but with the timeshare, we could get housing for a group. Ahhhh. Christmas dinner at Kings Arms Tavern.   Valentine's Day was fun here. We celebrated at home, as is our tradition, on Friday night. We cooked dinner, as is our tradition. I took care of appetizer, bread, and made a salad...greens, feta cheese, dried cranberries, glazed walnuts, and rasberry vinagrette dressing --- one of my favorite salads (and homemade dressing...adapted the recipe from Houston Chronicle), and dessert (which had to wait). Glen made delicious salmon and filet mignon, plus a pile of broccoli. We didn't have dessert until Monday night! Too full on Friday.  I'm working on a well-informed position with conscience and compassion about the whole gay-marriage issue. Want more than a shallow opinion, since I think it is complicated. Preparing an articulate response to the contraversy. I'm digging in the Bible, too, to see what's true. I here some Bible comments made out of context to defend both sides, so I want to look for myself.  And hooray --- it's the weekend. Glen returns tonight from Chicago. That's a great thing.  
    
    
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Glen,  i saw your thoughts on the bike ride in Mexico.  I'm with Steve about the ride but would enjoy a family get together in some nice place.  Mom 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Beth and I had a great time in SF, the City by the Bay. Saw Noises Off and had dinner in Fishermans' Wharf. Had time to roam the streets both by the Wharf and Union Square. Saw some wonderful art. I wouldn't recommend the Hilton as we could hear the conversations of our neighbors and the foot stomps of those above us. I didn't take many pictures. Was to busy having fun.     An electic streetcar in the Wharf area. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Steve, I guess that puts you in the: "For those who like to see the sites and and just hang out--you can do just that" category. That sounds great.   We can also do the birthday cake thing there!!!   For those who want to ride, more information is at the  urlLink Ensenda Rosarito web site . 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I have clients who will not come to my office on a Friday the Thriteenth. I had one client who post-poned his surgery because of that date.  I only notice the date because Kyle was born on a Friday the Thirteenth.  Hope all enjoy their valentine's weekend. The September trip sounds fun Glen. There are a couple of people that have birthdays in that month. We will look at the pragmatics and get back to you. I don't think I could sit on a bike let alone ride one more than a few feet. I am already more than middle-aged and balding.   
    
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i also saw that this morning on the bbc website. i was under the impression that i'd be a middle-aged bald guy by the time they released that. conveniently enough, it comes out a week before my birthday... 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Did someone mention  urlLink this ? 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       In cleaning out my office at JSi if found so many interesting things. This quote was on a scrap of paper in my desk:  "Success comes from experience; experience comes from failure. Eleanor Roosevelt said: 'We need to learn from the mistakes of others because we don't have time to make them all ourselves.'"   urlLink greatfailure.com  
    
    
</post>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Here is an idea: September 25 is a 50 mile "fun ride" from Rosarito Beach to Ensenada in Baja Califonia Norte, Mexico. How about if we all meet there for the weekend. For those who like to ride bicycles--bring your bikes and ride. For those who like to see the sites and and just hang out--you can do just that. We could get a couple of hotel rooms or a suite somewhere. If anyone expresses an interest, I would be happy to make the arrangements. There is plenty of bottled water and other pure beverages and safe food there!  Note: Some of us are going on the April 17 ride and it is looks like some kind of guys thing. So the September date might be better for a family outing.  
    
    
</post>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       These are my next travel dates:  Chicago: February 17-20 Pennsylvania: February 27-March 3 Miami: the week of March 22 (exact dates not yet determined) 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       south america, europe, england, what a traveling bunch. that means pictures!!! everyone bring those cameras and remember you can post to the blog from internet cafes. beth and i will be in san francisco for valentines day, then in early april will travel to new orleans. six years ago i had no interest in traveling anywhere. i was more interested in having a home large enough to house anyone who wanted to visit. very much like the home in tuscany, from a movie i can't remember the title to, that that had multiple visitors. it may be that i want both now. i enjoy the long dinner, with interesting conversations, and the feelings that come with being immersed in conversations that make you forget time. i am learning from each trip what it is like to travel again. when to look through the lenses of a camera and when to just be with out working at being some place. i am glad that beth and i both like to wander, discovering as we go along what is there rather than looking for what should be there. i appreciate that when we can do that. to all of the travelers and travelers to be, please share your experiences here, it will be appreciated. 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I also prefer calling you a nice guy.  In fact, that is what I do call you.  That is obviously what you are!  I was carried away by the fact that I actually stayed awake for a whole movie.  I rarely do that at home or in the theatre.  I think I was struck by the fact that I did not find any character in lit that I identified with, but the situation they were in, alone, in a strange placed that "should" have been exciting, all expectation with no payoff...I don't know.  I really like Secondhand Lions which we watched last night.  I cried when one of the old guys was threatening suicide, too close to home right now.  After all, as they say in the movie, "What do you want me to do, die of old age?" and my answer is yes.  We should all be able to do that...   
    
    
</post>

<date>08,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
        
    
    
</post>

<date>08,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       besides, what's so good about having a complicated mind? our president doesn't even say "nuclear" right. anyways, i'm going to carolina in my mind this summer. it's gonna be awesome. while i'm there i'll probably watch the tour de france zoom by, and run with the bulls...in jacksonville. i'm hoping i can afford this trip. actually, i saw a flyer at school for a three day trip to costa rica in july to study spanish. three days sounds brief, but that's just how i'd prefer it. in rebuttle to beth's attack of my l i t opinion, i'd like to reiterate that i thought it was "nice," (see below) just that the climax at the end wouldn't be worth it to most. personally, i liked sofia coppola's film "the virgin suicides" better. there's some tweaked out relationships in that movie too, just like the uncommon one in l i t. the assertion that i am simple minded is quite falacious and irrelevant. er....irrelevent. irelevent. whatever. ah, forget all the fiction nonsense, spellbound was the best movie. ever. in the history of...my life. wait, that disney movie about v.d. i saw in my sociology class was pretty good. but that wasn't maid during my lifetime. i digress. keep it real everybody.  anyonebutbush '04 ------------------------------------------------------------------------   
    
    
</post>

<date>08,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Glen & I are planning a trip to Europe this July, pending frequent flyer miles. A friend of ours is returning to the Netherlands for her sister's wedding, so we can bunk there and tour a little with a native. That's what pushed us forward, beyond just expressing interest in a visit somewhere other than Mexico. Although, I am grieving the fact that I may not snorkel in tropical water this summer.   We are thinking about visiting London (and a shire around Oxford and a literary quest to where J.R.R. Tolkein and C.S. Lewis hung out), Paris (working at being in a town as the Tour de France zooms by...it begins on July 3rd in a small town, Liege, northeast of Paris...closer to the Netherlands, actually), and zipping by train for a day trip to Prague, as well. I want to get backpacks (for ease of travel and mobility...not for trekking Everest) and train from place to place, taking city busy tours. Then we'll come home to rest. I'm excited, but holding my breath because costs seem prohibitive at this point in the planning. Just gotta sell a few more photo albums and stickers!  [Note to Glen...OK, now I've blogged again. Can I return to the bedroom to sleep? Just kidding.] 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       We are also on a quest to see the "Best Picture" nominees. We still need to see "Mystic River." I think we've seen the rest. I think the Golden Globes have it right by splitting up genres. It's tough to critically evaluate comedy against drama, and same with the acting roles. I think Johnny Depp made that "Pirates" role so much more than it was, as opposed to Bill Murray's portrayal of LIT (since everyone refers to "Lord of the Rings"...LOTR). Evidently Sean Penn is the favored winner.  "Master & Commander" was a good story and I thought it was well crafted and a fascinating portrayal of the time period and military life at sea. Of course, Russell Crowe did well in the lead, but his character was not compelling to me. It did not engage me emotionally. I would see it again just to see the Galapogos Islands again. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       In an effort to keep Ashley from having an "accident" where she sleeps in the laundry room, Cindi has been taking both Sam and Ashley out to the back yard just before bed where they respond to the command: "potty."  Then they all crash back into the house for their reward biscuits. It is fun to watch. They just finished while I blogged about it from the couch. 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Daniel Wilson told me this morning that he will ride in the  urlLink 10th Annual LA Bike Tour  with me on Sunday, March 7, 2004 at 6 AM.   Rob and I went on a nice 26 mile ride on Saturday and was asking me how severe the hills are in the  urlLink Rosarito to Ensenada Ride . So, I wonder if he is thinking of riding with us next time. That ride is on April 17 and is 50 miles. The hills, by-the-way, are steep and long. As steep as going up Turnbull Canyon Rd. and at least twice, maybe 3 times, as long. If you check out their website they give some details on the route and the steepness.   So far Rob is planning to go for the trip [hey Rob--ride too!] and David said he'd like to go and ride. Also my friend  urlLink Ken Brown  is going--he is already registered. And, Bob Mendoza from church is thinking about it.  
    
    
</post>

<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I would like to add Kevin Costner to the list of actors who, if not playing himself, every role is the same character.   Gods Must be Crazy I is also one of my all time favorites. I don't know that the actors had a lot of depth or could play any other parts, but that was not the point with this very orignal film. GMBC II did not take the story any further, just an ill fated attempt to build a franchise from the success of #1.  Lost in Translation lost me, not because of its complex plot, but because it failed to move me emotionally to empathize with the characters. I was  thinking that a better title for that film would be "Jet Lag."   Note to printers of images: the resolution of the posted version of the picture must be rather low. I hope that there were other forms of the picture from all those cameras in play that evening. If someone wants a higher resolution version of that, or any, photo let me know so I can email it to you.   Note to Cindi: Try to remember your user name and password so you can blog some of those great thoughts.  
    
    
</post>

<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I also wondered about the nomination for Bill Murray for his part in "Lost in Translation."  He is one of those actors, like Clint Eastwood, who play himself in every role.  Wish I could get a nomination for being authentic in my own life...  Beth 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hi, Mom,  I will send you the picture.  I have two copies sitting on my desk right now.  Love, Beth 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I still have not seen all the Academy Awards nominees.  That is my goal betwen now and February 29.  I will pass on "Cold Mountain" which was not nominated.  Anyone else out there who has seen that movie?  is it worth it?  I am not a Nicole Kidman fan, so if it has to do with liking to see her, forget it...  Beth 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Just wait until you are middle-aged.  "Lost in Translation" will not be so "fuzzy."    Love, Mom  P.S. Maybe what I am trying to say is lost in the translation... 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I haven't seen a cute button either, but Brianna is cute. And, "the gods must be crazy" is one of my all time favorites. I am looking forward to seeing American Splendor, my catholic irish roots may be showing. look out when Weber is back. 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       How could you possibly get lost in "Lost in Translation?"  I used to think so highly of you and your intellect...It was, actually, a very slow starting movie.  I myself wondered if I could stay awake during the slow unfolding of the story.  (It is a well known fact that once the sun goes down, Beth is asleep.)  I was fascinated with the characters in the movie and was very satisfied with some of the choices they made.  Maybe being in the throes of my own midlife crisis made me sympathetic...  Signed, Love my brother anyway... 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am assuming that this is the way to leave a message.  I really like the family picture  that euther Glen or Cindi put or here.  I would like a copy but didn't know how to  print it from here.  Could someone let me know.  Thanks,  Mom, Gram, Doris 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       lost in translation was...nice, but ultimately, a lot to sit through for the fuzzy pay-off at the end. i still think american splendor was awesome, so nanner nanner glen. mystic river is my vote for most awesome movie last year. without lord of the rings money, and cgi, it tells a good story. it could be cited in an argument against capital punishment. it's my personal opinion that everyone should watch "the gods must be crazy" at least once a week. that way, if you are human, there's no way you'd consider hurting another human. perhaps that's a little dreaming. oh well, "we are the music makers and we are the dreamers of dreams." that brianna's cute as a button. can't say i've seen any cute buttons in my life, so let's say she's cuter than one. look out when we get kobe back.  
    
    
</post>

<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       We saw Seabiscuit last night. It is a good story with solid character development. Special effects, gratuitious violence and chase scenes has to be cut for a lack of time.   I got lost in Lost in Translation. People wondering around looking confused. Can someone explain why Bill Murray is nominated for an award on this one? Maybe if I had just seen it in the original language, I wouldn't have been so lost.  
    
    
</post>

<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Beth, Kyle and I watched Lost in Translation last night. Beth and I both liked it, but for different reasons. I thought it captured what happens when people drift spiritually and emotionally. The characters were using this vague relationship to give direction or substance to their experience. Beth wants to see Mystic River next. We rented Jet Lag a couple of weeks ago. A movie similar in someways to Lost in Translation. A french movie focused on chance meeting and relationship confusion.  
    
    
</post>

<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       hey everyone. i think that just includes steve and glen right now, but hi if you're not one of them and you are reading this. this is more or less just a test to see how this is going to work. so far, so good. so....um.....seen any good movies lately........anyone? i will now attempt to upload a picture. 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Way to go Steve! 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
         This is Brianna eating her dinner. 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am not using my web space at this time. I can set up that site so that anyone could ftp to it with the password. I will look up the address and find the password.  
    
    
</post>

<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       To remove the Christmas limitation to the blog. I have changed the url for our family blog.   Now I have to figure out how to let everyone know the new address.  
    
    
</post>

<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Since I no longer work at the same place, we may loose access to the server where I have the photographic images stored. Does anyone else have access to a server for that purpose? I think, if we are really clever, we could also ftp all of the content to another place so we would not have Blogger advertising at the top of the blog. Any suggestions?  hmm, one other thought is that I think we could pay a fee to blogger.com to upgrade the service to remove advertising and have storage space from images.   I will look into these. Let me know if any of you computer geeks have any ideas.  
    
    
</post>

<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I have taken the word "Yule" out of the title. This may help people know they can blog outside of the Christmas season. I will try to change the URL to be more season inclusive. I don't know it that kind of change is allowed. I will try to figure that out. 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I think there should be more uses for this family blog. But that means people will have to blog!  A friend of mine who just went to work in Bangledesh has started  urlLink this blog . I'd like to say that I got him started and coached him through his first posting of the images. --because I did do that!  I think we should keep up the postings. Especailly when something interesting happens. Like my work with MEDA was mentioned by some of our clients on KCET's "Life and Times" program last night. I don't know how long they leave it up there but today you can listen to the program on their web site:  urlLink here . 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       just checking to see if anyone else checks the blog. is there more purpose than just at christmas? take care steve 
    
    
</post>

<date>31,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Brianna was here for two days. Beth and I took her for a walk both mornings. She is a lot of fun. The "Sacramento" Kings have several games on TV this week so I will watch unless they play badly. Kyle is applying for his first job this week. He wants to work at Boys and Girls Club. Help with computers, homework and video games. Pretty "normal". 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       . . . Is allowing me to access the Interent from the OCS conference at the Westin Bonaventure in Los Angeles. If anything good happens I will be right on top of it and blogging live.    
    
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am working in Los Angeles this week. Today and tomorrow I am attending the DHHS funding conference at the Westin Bonaventure in downtown. Part of my work is to help younger organizations access larger funding sources. So, MEDA is providing technical assistance to some of our groups through a consultant. I had our consultant meet with 4 of our organizational clients in Los Angeles. Three out of the 4 showed up. So that is progress for them.  Cindi went with me as we took the MetroLink train and the Metro Red Line subway to the event. Cindi spent most of the day at the Los Angeles library--a very nice building worth a visit. If we are all really nice to Cindi, maybe she will blog about her day.   
    
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       My co-worker's mom vanished on Tuesday...not like a trick in some Vegas magic show, but a tragic event to rip your world in two. My co-worker is 30. She had lunch with her mom that day, and no one has seen her since. Her car and her purse are still at home. She is 57 and lives in a very nice part of Pasadena. I am troubled because my friend/co-worker has to survive this ordeal. I'm also troubled because her dad will be questioned thoroughly, since husbands are often involved in situations like this. I'm troubled by the way the news stories stacked up on Channel 4 --- missing Pasadena woman, followed by sentencing of a man who was found guilty of murdering his wife, followed by the story of the search for a man exposing himself to teenage girls in the So-Cal area.  And I'm sad that I have second thoughts about going places alone in this crazy world. Time will make me bold and brave soon, but for now I'm quite distracted. I pray for a happy ending for my co-worker's family. It's all so curious to turn on the evening news in a major metropolitan area and find out you know the family in the lead story.  I saw the intellectually challenging and deeply moving epic movie "50 First  Dates" (Drew Barrymore and Adam Sandler) on Thursday. [tongue-in-cheek] To keep a marriage healthy, I let Glen opt out of these types of films. I did enjoy it, though I grew tired of the typical crass comments forced into the dialogue --- mostly from the other actor...I think his name is Rob Schneider. My expectations were low, but I was pleasantly surprised. No need to own it, but it was a pleasant distraction from a rough week.  We got our third set of photos of our new puppy and his brothers and sisters. This week they are walking and starting to eat solid food. They are beyond cute - chubby little balls of cute with stubby legs. Our puppy and Brianna in the same picture --- now that would be CUTE. 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Here I sit in a Starbucks in South Miami, Florida. It is so boring here. There are students sitting around in large chairs and small tables studying, working on laptops, and studying for the MCAT. After my last meeting this afternoon I drove down to Key Largo. I think that would be a nice place to visit when I have more time and someone with me to do it. Actually, I'd like to drive all the way to Key West and see where Ernst Hemingway used to hang out.   Starbucks has T-Mobile wireless access--wi-fi. So I am sure that I will be back here a few times before I head home.  [The MCAT studiers just left--one of them is the tutor of the other. The tutor was telling here about getting a physics tutor--not his specialty.]  My colleague from MEDA arrives tonight from Canada. He will write about some of the groups with whom we work here in Miami for the MEDA official publications. I don't know what time he arrives.  I am trying to decide where or whether or not I will eat dinner tonight. I am sure I will be hungry later on. It is after 7 east coast time as I write this.    
    
    
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I built a sandbox and Beth bought a swing. Here are pictures of Brianna enjoying both.    Brianna on the swing.   Brianna and mom in sandbox. 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Brianna discovered dirt and plants on the deck tonight. Here she is putting dirt in a candle holder and eating fresh chives that she picked from the planter.    Tasting the chives.    We have the dirt in the little container. 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Once again we are blessed with a visit from Brianna. Shawntea and her are spending the night. Kyle and grandpa are holding fort in the Curtin/Peterson/Weaver household. She is so busy I can't take a picture. For the record her hair has more curl and she is very busy. Beth is off seeing 21 grams. If you talk to her ask her about being stuck in the mud in a remote area and how she got rescued. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       while the early morning loonies were out running/cycling, i was home sleeping. it was a blast. if i was at the event, i'd have been one of the kids eating pancakes in front of the eager masses. (who knows how long they were to be there handing out food to the thousands of participants). perhaps it's still my instinct to defend those poor souls in the food service biz.   i went to santa cruz a few days ago for a concert. i've been making that trip periodically throughout my stay here at the peterson residence, but this time, that drive seemed unbearably lengthy. i sensed that this last trip would be the last of it's kind for me, as i'm an adult now, and perhaps i should be applying myself to other more ambitious goals.  dude, it's like 80 something degrees here! nanny na na, nor-cal!  still haven't seen "the passion...," but i think i'll see it later, as the hype dies down a bit. i saw 21 grams last night, that was...unsettling i guess. good overall though.  this time of year is always my favorite as the weather changes, and baseball season nears. father's day weekend is sold out at dodger stadium already, since they will be playing the new york yankees. i'll have to watch the blue crew beat a-rod and co. on tv then.   okay, that's all.  wait......no, that's all. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Daniel Wilson and I rode our bicycles in the  urlLink LA Bike Tour  that is connected to the Los Angeles Marathon on Sunday, March 7. 15,000 plus riders assemble on Exposition Boulevard between USC and the Coliseum before 6 AM to ride along most of the Marathon route. At the end of the ride, my odometer read that we had gone 22.8 miles. That is not a long ride at all.     As the ride starts at 6 AM, as the sky starts a pre-dawn glow that announces that the sun will rise soon, riders are packed in tightly and it take 20 minutes or so before you really start to move. It takes longer than that until you can safely assume you can stay clipped into your pedals as cyclists with varying degrees of skill are weaving all over the road. The announcer on the loudspeaker system is cheering us on as county and city elected officials take turns making comments on the wonderfulness of their work in the community that made the event possible. Randy Newman&#8217;s &#8220;I Love LA&#8221; is blaring through the speakers too. It is a cute song that mentions a bunch of the Boulevards that we will be riding on-- Olympic , Pico, Venice, etc.     Some fun things: &nbsp;Cindi and my mom, Daniel&#8217;s Grandma, AKA Doris, found a spot along the route near a Starbucks to watch us ride by and cheer their little hearts out. It is fun that all the streets are closed down and without any car and truck traffic we can ride down some usually very busy streets as the sun rises above Los Angeles. There were a lot of funny looking people&#8212;including Santa Claus&#8212;riding their bikes. I didn&#8217;t see anyone crash this year. We finished our ride before it got hot! (the runners had a different experience with unseasonably warm weather exceeding 80 degrees F.)     Some less than fun things: Did see some ambulances coming and going from the route. It is hard to find people at the end of the ride with 15,000 plus people wondering around in the quad area at USC. Kids serving a pancake breakfast at USC to support a charitable cause, hung out eating pancakes in the cooking area while people who had paid for breakfast stood in a line watching them eat pancakes and sausages while the line just barely moved.     The whole Marathon phenomenon in LA for the weekend is energizing and is an experience to behold. I remember feeling this last year too&#8212;and haven&#8217;t acted on it yet&#8212;but I imagine the glory of training as a runner and completing the running Marathon. There are 20,000 plus runners, in addition to the elite athlete runners. A couple of people I know have run in this event&#8212;Lalo Diaz and Brad Peters for example. One woman from our church ran yesterday. I don&#8217;t know who she is but someone else told me about her. David Diaz and Lalo told me they would like to run. Maybe this year is the year to get those slow twitch endurance muscles ready to go.    Cindi and Doris got interviewed by an LA Times reporter whose article appeared in today&#8217;s paper. No mention of us though. The news coverage really only went as deep as the running event. Another reason to think about running I guess.    
    
    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
         A fox on our deck. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Brianna was dropped off this afternoon with a runny nose. Steve did pretty well for a couple hours. Then Brianna got very cranky. Beth arrived in a nick of time. We will not post the a picture of the drainage. Just use your imagination.  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
           Friday and Saturday of last week I was in an international training event hosted by USAID and my employer, MEDA. The training covered something called &#8220;Business Design Services&#8221; that is the preferred method of international community economic development used by the US and Canada. The trainees were mostly MEDA staff working in Peru: Lima, Maputo, and Tarapoto; Managua, Nicaragua; Dar Es Salaam, Tanzania; Mozambique;Khajand, Tazjikstan [former Soviet Union republic]; Lancaster, Pennsylvania; Waterloo, Canada; Haiti; and Los Angeles, California. Some staff from Haiti were unable to come to the training because of the threat of civil unrest in Haiti that escalated to Haiti&#8217;s President Arristide fleeing the country on Sunday, February 29. This two-day training event was held in a hotel in Manheim, Pennsylvania (near Lancaster).    Sunday, the group moved to a retreat center outside Lebanon, PA for an all MEDA staff retreat that occurs about every three years. The group is double the size of the training that I just came from and consists of approximately one third of the 150 or so people working on staff for MEDA world-wide. This event ends mid-day Wednesday. So far the agenda has focused on team building kinds of group exercises. The experience is somewhat less goofy that the AmeriCorps*VISTA supervisor training that I was coerced to attend in 2000. The group overall is an eclectic, multi-national, multilingual mix of youthful, energetic, intelligent, overachieving folks that make this an energizing experience that will be memorable. &nbsp;    MEDA&#8217;s international headquarters is in Canada. I will guess that over half of the staff here is Canadian. Hockey anyone? The big deal for everyone is that it is so unseasonably warm here at 15 degrees C. [That&#8217;s almost 60 F for us Americans.]    
    
    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, I know everyone thought I was younger than my older brother, but, if he is watching a movie that has not even arrived at his home until after 8:00 P.M., I must be older.  Mom, when were you planning on telling us the truth.  It is now 8:48 P.M. and I have been admiring my own stamina at remaining awake as Kyle and I have been discussing the origin of the universe and the need for everyone to find a place in it when what i really want/need to do is get some sleep.  After all, tomorrow is another day.  My favorite movie line..... 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Every review has been excellent. It was one of the movies on my list to see on DVD. Let me know what you think.  
    
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Does anyone know about this movie?                                    It comes out on DVD next week. I plan to watch a preview when Rob brings it home tonight. Don't tell anyone.  
    
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Doris, thanks for your questions. The map shows the different stages of the "le tour de france" bicycle race. It starts on July 3rd this year. A cable channel has a series of shows on Thursday that give background and detail leading up to this race. While watching it last week I saw bicycle racers on a section of cobblestones. Motorcycles that were filming the race fell in the way of some of the racers and disrupted the race. That is the picture that Glen posted.  The only trip Beth and I have planned is the one to Hawaii from July 26 to Aug 2. The American Psychological Association convention is from July 28 to Aug 1. One of my friends Kirk Schneider is getting an award for outstanding achievement as an independent psychologist. He also is talking about his new book on Awe and it's importance to our sense of well-being. I also want to talk to publishers about the two book projects that are important to me. One on the "art" of psychotherapy with children and the second on my understanding of Jim Bugental's teaching and writings. Jim is/was my mentor for two decades and I feel very strongly that his work has heavily influenced my work with all of my clients. I am hopeful that you will find someone who will say "yes" and join us in Hawaii. Thanks again for your questions.   
    
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Finally took time to check on the Bloog site.  Guess I shouldn't take so much time off again as so much has changed.  The Wilson "boys" and all the new pictures of all the young in the family, Sam and Brianna.  I do have a question about the map that Steve put on.  Are you going to be traveling on that map this summer?    I am so excited about the possible apportunity to go to Hawaii.  I just didn't think it would happen so soon as Mary and Bill are definitely not able to go this year.  Am still trusting that someone will say yes.  Did enjoy the updated pictures of Sam.  I didn't really understand the conversation about cobblestone vs ather types of roads but then I don't understand a lot of things and it doesn't really bother me.  
    
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Finally took time to check on the Bloog site.  Guess I shouldn't take so much time off again as so much has changed.  The Wilson "boys" and all the new pictures of all the young in the family, Sam and Brianna.  I do have a question about the map that Steve put on.  Are you going to be traveling on that map this summer?    I am so excited about the possible apportunity to go to Hawaii.  I just didn't think it would happen so soon as Mary and Bill are definitely not able to go this year.  Am still trusting that someone will say yes about being my traveling companion.  Did enjoy the updated pictures of Sam.  I didn't really understand the conversation about cobblestone vs ather types of roads but then I don't understand a lot of things and it doesn't really bother me. I didn"t realize motorcycles were running while the bicycles were. 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I was at the Kings - Dallas game last night. I am firmly convinced that the Kings want to give their fans heart attacks. What a roller coaster of emotion. It is so loud in Arco. I have no voice left and I can hardly hear. Will make me a better therapist today. 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well. I thought I was hiding my anxiety pretty well with not being able to reach David via cell phone between April 11 and April 22, but he did call me to tell me everyhting with him was great, it was his cell phone that was having problems.  I can now sleep through the night, well almost, and he wanted me to pass on that his mailing address remains:  David Weaver P.O. Box 928 Kings Canyon National Park, CA   93633  
    
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well. having lost my head myself, I have empathy for the llama...Samson is too cute and should be outlawed in some way.  He is the desktop picture on m computer at school and has been very distracting during STAR testing this week.  I think I need to notify the state that I have administered the STAR in a non-standard way with students who need to look at and swoon over the Samson picture between questions..... 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Samson and I are getting along OK without the one with the biggest shoes in the house. He makes so many sounds. (Sam, not Glen) I never knew puppies got the hiccups and burp. He even has a sound that mimmicks Donald Duck. Of course, the wimper-chirp noise is too sweet. But I practice tough love and don't run to him at those times --- unless I suspect it's bathroom time! He spends his outside time biting off flowers and other green and not so green plants. And every now and then I pull a piece of bark out of his tiny mouth. It's fun to watch him grow. Sometimes I have to carry him outside to do the business. That's just my excuse to cuddle him while I can. We call that strategy the "swoop and poop." We swoop him up and get him outside just in the nick of time...or that's the plan, anyway. It's fun. And an adjustment. Having some little life to care for keeps us childless folks from becoming quite so self-centered. I like Samson a bunch. And yes, the llama had a seam split and suddenly poly-stuffing filled the room (almost) like a marine inversion (clouds). So llama is retired until he gets stitches. 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am glad that I am not the only posting "cute" pictures anymore.  
    
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It takes some persuasion for Sam to convince Ashley that she should play. This all seems to be related to which dog will become the "alpha dog."     The tug-of-war game has become a favorite. I hear from Cindi today (I am in Chicago posting this) that the stuffed Llama has lost its head, so to speak.      At least Sam is the "Alpha dog" over the stuffed toy.     
    
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am in Chicago again. I will be here until Friday visiting my CCF clients.  
    
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       thanks for your impression of the song. it does have that quality.  when i was in vietnam we would sit on a ship off the coast, in the heat, and i often would find a place to sit and watch the ocean. it was one of those times im my life that i could physically experience something larger and more enduring than myself. float on reminds me of those times and the comfort of being part of something so much larger than ones self.  i hope you get to the beach. take pictures, post them on the blog for those of us who pine for the ocean. 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       so steve, you downloaded float on? it's a great song, isn't it? it has the sort of melancholy, and optimisim i feel like i'd want people to leave my funeral feeling. i won't say any more, except that i love baseball. it gives me an escape that allows me to succeed at something vicariously on a daily basis. when things in baseball aren't going well, then my own endevours seem successful. it's great to pour your hopes into something other than my own tired routine sometimes. record high temperatures in the southland today. 99 in long beach. there was also 15 foot waves at newport beach today. wish i had a chance to see that. welcome wilsons.  
    
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Welcome Daniel. 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Welcome to the Wilson guys.  
    
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Daniel's on thanks to Timothy (and Glen) 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Welcome Timothy. Looking forward to your contributions.  
    
    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, Timothy is now on with a working acct.! I beat Daniel  :+) 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       We are still trying to get Daniel signed up properly. We have tried a second or third invitation, let's see if that does the trick. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hi, Daniel,  In order to post under your own name, you need to ask Uncle Glen to "invite" you to the Blog via your Mom's (or Dad's) e-mail address.  After you accept the invitation by creating a User Name and Password, you can log on to the Blog under that name from anyone's computer and be viewed as the "poster."  I am posting from Steve's computer right now, and had to click on LogOut before I could log on as myself as his computer "sees" him as the default.. Let me know how it works out.  Aunt Beth 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Brianna at Easter.   
    
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       As long as I don’t have to ride on the cobblestones, it is fine if other people do it. Even the rough sections on concrete or gravely areas of the bike path make my weary bones talk.  I am amazed at the way the TV reporters and camera folks are able to stay out of trouble on these races. I am glad they do such a careful job of it. I did see a picture somewhere on the internet of the motorcycle/scooters lying on the ground with the bicyclists riding around them. I was trying to find it to post here. I will look some more and post it if I find it.   I bet Mr. Liggett had a few comments on this if he was covering the race.   UPDATE:     
    
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It looks like the next tele coverage of bicycling on OLN is Thursday, tomorrow.   Sometimes I type my messages in a word processing program so I can get some spell check help—especially now that I know the word police are watching.  Speaking of word processing, my Microsoft Word stopped working sometime this week and I ended up having to call Microsoft’s customer service. After the very efficient person on the line got all of my customer information, including my time zone—Pacific Daylight Time, I asked him what time zone he was in. The answer: India Standard Time. Interesting.  After I had waited on hold for 45 minutes, my problem with Word was resolved in about 10 minutes. Thank you very much! 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Just checked the schedule and it was a replay of the Paris-Roubaix race from the weekend of the 11th. 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Your right, banned was the correct word.  Very good answer.  I will have to look at the tv guide and see which race it was that I watched this am. Will let you know. It was painful to watch the leaders fall because a motorcycle rider fell in front of them. Having a cycle rider fall and disrupt the race seems different than have one of the motorcycles disrupt the race. Not fair some how, but Lance Armstrong might say the same thing about people with bags clogging the route. Thanks again Daniel and for letting me know who answered my post. 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       First of all, I am asuming that Steve meant "banned," not "band" when he was talking about the motorcycles on cobblestone roads. For the bikes on cobblestones issue, I will tell about both points of view. The Belgians (or maybe just the ones from Flanders) really like them because it can allow a skilled rider to pull ahead by the path he takes through them.  On the other hand, my dad and brother (and probably most Americans, for that matter) disagree because they are really hard on the riders because they are so worn from hundreds of years' use, are narrow, and therefore dangerous, etc.  Only two Classics, or World Cup races have them as far as I know (the Ronde van Vlaanderen aka Tour of Flanders, and Paris-Roubaix), which can be avoided even if you want to win the World Cup.  What a non-cycling addict might not know about is the UCI (pro cycling's governing body) will have what they call the "ProTour" in 2005, which states that if you want to participate in any event, you will probably have to ride them all (there's another long story behing that), which means that you will have to ride those races with cobblestones, which are major events on the calendar.  Now for the question about motocycles riding them at the same time, I also state two sides.  It would be good to clear the road more for the riders.  However, without the motorcycles, there would be no one to give us the live coverage, which the sponsers want because of all the ads on the riders and their bikes.  That means all the coverage we get is from the journalists that are right there with the riders to clog up the sides of the roads, which the spectators want.  Basically, I think the motorcycles should stay, and you should only have to ride the cobbled roads if you want to, however, I probably have not seen the races the others have because of a lack of OLN. (Posted by Daniel, who is still puzzled on how to get his own name on the blog under an article.) 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Should bicycle races involve cobblestones and if they do, should motorcycles be band from those sections? After watching on OLN this am I wondered what Glen, Daniel and Timothy thought about that. 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I believe now is the time to have a PWWCR Team Musette Bags.  If bicycle teams can have them, so can we. I even found a site to order them from. They would look like this except they could have "PWWCR" on them.  There is only oen drawback. The smallest order is one hundred bags. Not sure there are that many pople in this family. We might have to recruit more people.    
    
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       All this talk about musette made me go to good old Webster and find out exactly what it was.  Low and behold it is either a bellows-blown bagpipe popular in France in the 17th or 18th century (Daniel could have used it for his report) or a small knapsack with one shoulder strap.  Glad I looked it up. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Beth, Kyle and I want to offically welcome Sam 2 to the family. He looks like he could steal all of our hearts. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Here is Sam 2.     He sleeps, romps around for a few minutes, eats, drinks. And, in between all of that he poops and pees. So far, mostly outdoors.  
    
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       An interesting discussion at lunch today led to the idea of a school report on the  urlLink history of pizza . But I think the  urlLink history of bicycling  might be an interesting choice as well. But either of these two projects would do much to enhance Daniel Wilson's academic experience and that of all of his 7th grade colleagues.   By-the-way, Daniel may be joining the blogosphere soon. And hopefully we can get Timothy involved too. 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am so excited. Tomorrow is the Grand Day of the Puppy. Starting with a trip to the spa for Ashley, so she can be smelling fine and all clean to meet little itchy brother.Then will be off with Rob for the breakfast celebration of the Grand Day of the Puppy --- waffles, for sure. And off to Chino to meet our 3rd dog and bring him home. We may take turns driving home so that Rob and Glen can hold him, and not just me the WHOLE way home. I'm sure Glen will explain to him about the Tour de France on the way home. Maybe we'll really name him Musette. Is that too girly?  I hope I'll be able to sleep tonight. Can we do it? Can we raise a social, well-behaved lab? Upon relfection, I'd have to say we kinda spoiled our M.C. (Magnificent Creature, a.k.a. Samson #1). I've been studying how to housebreak a pup --- quite a diverse topic come to find out.   I just can't wait to see which one we will bring home. And how little will he be at 6.5 weeks? We couldn't even pick out a collar yet because we aren't sure what size his neck is. We only bought him three toys. A rope (pup-size), and "puppy starter kit" of Nylabones, and a miniature tennis ball. We don't want to over indulge him. :-) The book said...one chew toy and one play toy. We must say we were slightly manipulated by the marketers...if the packaging says "puppy", maybe we need one. But we used great restraint.  We will be all consumed with cute, so please be patient with us. We are warmed up to that condition thanks to the arrival of Miss Brianna. She has taught us how to appreciate cute and find more love in our hearts.  I'm lunching with Doris and Audrey today. Audrey's on Spring Break, so out we go for some girl talk and crepes.  Great to see the photos of New Orleans! Good for Steve & Beth for taking time to get-away and play as a couple. High priority. I have favorite parts...Preservation Hall Jazz Band, coffee and beignets at Cafe du Monde, and the food! And definitely people watching. Glad you had a great time.  And I'll be watching the OLN on Thursdays now. I'll check for a musette at Crate & Barrel (Steve, that made me smile). I think it is really a sweet young woman, but Glen must not know that. OK, probably not. 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey I had no idea that  urlLink Phil and the postie boys are on Thursdays . Now that "The Donald's" show is over, maybe Cindi will let me check that out.    
    
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       We are watching OLN's Road to the Tour every Thurs. night. Phil Ligget is in fine form and I wish I was in Georgia next week to see the "Tour of Georgia". Lance will be riding in that race. You noticed I said "Lance" like Beth says "Bernie". We are so familiar here in Placerville. We don't own a musette, can you buy one at Crate and Barrel, and what does it look like? 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Only 79 days until the  urlLink Tour de France  begins from Liege, Belgium on July 3, 2004. Will you stay at home, order cable TV configured to receive OLN? Or will you head to France on an organized tour taking you daily to the various race venues with your lunch packed in your musette?  Cindi and I have decided to stay at home this year. There will be a new puppy who would be just too lonely if we were gone that long. So, warm up those golden vocal cords, Phil Ligget. We will be listening live in the morning and remixed for prime time. Who knows, maybe Uncle Glen and Aunt Cindi will invite people over to watch--especially if they bring food, gifts or even just go cycling with Uncle Glen once in a while.    urlLink Lance Armstrong's web site  has more information that you could possibly know what to do with.    
    
    
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So the  urlLink International Policy Governance Association  is putting on a conference--on what else but Policy Governance. The conference is titled  urlLink "The Future of Boards: Realizing the Promise of Owner-Accountability"  and will be held in Chicago, June 10-12, 2004. I am really looking forward to this learning experience from some of the experienced practitioners and consultants in the field today. I have been to several recent seminars on this topic and the approach is to talk about "best practices" in response to the obviously broken parts of the board governance system. They usually tell some stories about a board of director's dysfunctionality, make the audience laugh because everyone has faced some similar dysfunctionality and they the propose some fix for that particular problem.   In the Policy Governance model, the whole system is addressed and a new paradigm is built around some real or perceived value added that the board of directors brings to an organization. This is described as linkage between the ownership and the organization. The values brought by the board then are reduced to an explicit, written form of policies in four categories: ends, limitations or means, board-staff partnership, and board process.   Because I have had the opportunity to serve on several boards and work for one over the years I understand the need for addressing these issues with great clarity. I hope that my experience at this conference proves valuable for my work with MEDA providing technical assistance to community-based and faith-based organizations and for use with other organizations in the future. I will let you know how it progresses.  
    
    
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       In the past, we would have some down time on the blog server and we just had to wait for it to start working again. I haven't noticed that for a long time now. I know that Blogger is a lot more capitalized now that Google bought them. So I would expect less trouble.  Let's see if it continues to work ok.   
    
    
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am posting this because when I tried to go to the page with pwwcrfamily web name I get an error message. 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Beth and I had a wonderful time in New Orleans. We listened to live music every night, walked down every street in the French Quarter at least twice and ate well!!!!! Even the rain and lightening was an event. What a place to people watch. What a delightful place to spend a couple of days. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Beth and I just returned from New Orleans. We found a house for sale, looks pretty inviting. Good Colleges nearby.     A nice little home in the garden section of New Orleans. $840,000.00      A great place to people watch until it rains. 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       this morning: there is talk that Mr. Parks may be running for Mayor of Los Angeles.  
    
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The kind folks at JobStarts put on an event Saturday at the home of one of the board members. It was nice to have mom, Beth and Rob show up. I think Beth had fun chatting it up with Bernard Parks, Eighth District Los Angeles City Council.     
    
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today was their first day outside in the sunshine! Two weeks to go until we meet them and pick one to be Sam 2.     
    
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I think waffles would be a great idea!    
    
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Here as a picture I told last weekend. A beautiful spring day. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I have always like Calvin. If he could only join the Kings and stir them up.  Isn't there supposed to be "chevy" or "ford" under him. Oh, by the way Rob, we are expecting you to answer all the questions Kyle has about college. No pressure there but if he struggle's it will not be our fault. Besides there is not forgiveness for turning my son into a Dodger's hat wearing guy. E-mail any pictures you want on this site. I will post them for you. There has a be a way to post music so if you have a sound clip in the form of a wave file I would like to hear the song you mentioned. My funeral song is "Time to Say Goodbye" sung by Sarah Brightman. With all the trades I don't have a clue about who is on the Giants, except for that player who never used an illegal performance enhancing substance. The way the Kings are playing I will probably have more time to watch the RiverCats. And there is no giving up on anyone. ever. never. nada. though in those times I gave up on myself I was always greatful that others believed in me more than I believed in myself.  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I saw this little guy on another blog and stole him. He is now dancing in our template for the time being. Any comments? 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Bono received an honorary Doctor of Laws from UPenn. I like what he says about being a fan of America. I did not know that Ben Franklin went to Ireland for some months to study what a colonial relationship with Great Brintain looked like. There, he found poverty, mud and grass huts. He did not find anything good with the Great Britian-colony thing--so the rest is history. You can click on the title above to read the whole thing.  
    
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It was a good lunch at Glen and Cindi's for Glen, Cindi, David, Steve, and Kyle's b-day party. We called Steve on the phone to  wish him and Kyle a happy birthday.  I saw some of the Giro d'Italia today.  Cunego, Gilberto Simoni's young teammate won it.      (Cunego is the one in pink.)  Glen says I am responsible to get him and Steve caught up with the cycling world, but I get all my news from velonews.com (below), and my  Cycle Sport  magazines.   urlLink For the most up-to-date news, click this line   For his Tour de France preparation, Lance is doing well, and Jan Ullrich (his main challenger) is behind schedule with too much winter fat still. Perhaps this could really help Lance win. Beloki, another challenger for Lance, is not recovering from his nasty fall last year which broke 3 bones. 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Michael, my sister Cindy, Jamie visit.   Beth and Steve with Michael.  Michael is scheduled to leave for the Iraq in August. We had a nice BBQ with him and my parents. Beth got to talk to her brother, David and Rob. Made her day. 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       David Weaver arrived after 10 PM on Friday. He is now sitting here with Rob and I watching the puppy do his puppy thing. When asked for his best thoughts for inclusion in this post he says: "huh." 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Beth's fifth grade class spent the evening. Only one was pushed into the pool.      
    
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It is a loooooooooong direct flight from Philadelphia to Los Angeles. I was supposed to be on a connecting flight that went through Washington, DC, but that flight was delayed bcause of weather or crew delay so I was put on fight 99, direct to LA. That was better, but still long. (Did I mention that it was a long 5 hours plus flight?) 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Thanks to Cindi for the faxed birthday greeting that said: " Happy 25th Birthday! (May 25th--that is)." All of my colleagues have enjoyed that as I have shared it with them.  Thanks to Beth and Steve who sent an electronic brithday card. I tried to use their system to reply, but I lost my concentration somewhere along the way and never finished it--so thank you here on the blog.   Jane Remington gave me a call on my cell phone---what a nice surprise!  Our group of MEDA staff and affiliated programs, about 20 of us, had a dinner together on Monday evening and they made me stand up in the middle of the restaurant and sang to me.   So, I think the frenzy of birthday celebration has slowed down a little bit.   Note to Daniel: I have tried to respond to your email, but for some reason it did not work yet. I would be happy to show you how to make hypertext linkages using HTML. Maybe we could look at it together on Sunday if you guys are coming over.  
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       it won't be as humid here today as it was yesterday, but still warm. Yesterday was VERY humid and reached to 90! I am seeing may old friends here at the AEO conference and the MEDA related ASSETS program folks had dinner together last night. They made me standup and sang happy birthday. More later, or not. I need to make sure and get a lot of work done while I am here in addition to all the networking and activities of the conference.  
    
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Sat. we are having a BBQ for Michael (Steve's nephew). He is scheduled to leave for the Middle East in the next four weeks. Sun. we are attending a BBQ for Shannon Barger's son who is on leave from the Marine Corp. and will be here with his wife and stepson. Then Kyle returns on Sunday night. Beth is co-prinicpal of summer school and will be back to work on Tuesday. Flexibility is hard to come by these days. With planning we can be available for that phone call.  Beth, Kyle and I are looking forward to meeting Sam 2, visiting more colleges, and a Dodger's game. With schedules in hand we will plan a trip down to So. Cal.  Here is the best to the party goers. Happy Birthday to all. 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Everyone in the family is invited this weekend to our Summer Kick-off & Birthday BBQ. David Weaver is rumored to be coming this weekend, too. We will be celebrating the summer birthdays...Glen, Steve, Kyle, & Cindi...our May & June birthdays. We will celebrate with or without you, but it's richer if you can all stop in. I just wish I could tell you a time and day, but you know how this goes sometimes. Depending on when David gets here and when he leaves...it may be Saturday night or Sunday night or even Monday afternoon (Memorial Day). As Gumby says, "Stay flexible." Watch the blog for details. Glen and I will discuss a menu and cake priorities. Steve & Kyle - you can put in your vote on dessert preferences. Hope you can come! If not, maybe we can call you during the event, just to connect. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       By the way, Sam-2 has been with us for a little over a month. We got him at 6.5 weeks and 7 pounds. He is now 11.5 weeks and 19 pounds. And much bolder and bounces higher. A delight in my life. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Wow! Sam #2 does look big in that photo. He is so fun and cute. He has a 10 minute lesson practicing "come" and "sit" every morning about 6:30. Not sure what I'm doing, but he seems to be catching on. Next week, we'll work more on leash walking and progress into "heel." As opposed to, "heal." He, as of last week, wags his tail and runs to us. So I know he likes us now. I wasn't sure before. Maybe he even admires us, too. Isn't that why people get dogs? To project what positive feelings the dogs are having?  School ends 6/3. Teachers check-out 6/10. It's uphill right now. Lots of electronic reports to file and hours of proofreading for errors. I'll meet with all 31 students in the next eight days for the final Learning Record.   Glen grilled that Copper River Salmon yesterday. I'm not a salmon fan, but this was better than most. With salt, pepper, and lemon, I almost enjoyed it. I'd still prefer lasagna or a hamburger or beef wellington --- now we are talking! I so want to share Glen's passion for the pink fish, but alas, I cannot. If it's an acquired taste, I'll keep trying. Give me blackened mahi-mahi or just a tunafish salad sandwich like my Mom makes --- with chopped hard-boiled egg added (Glen taught me that). Must be lunchtime.   
    
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Sam 2 is looking great. Sounds from your posts that you've taken him into your hearts. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
          Samson 2 with his favorite domestique.  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       . . . about bicycling competition on OLN.   Samson gladly wakes me up during the 5 o’clock hour so that I can get my coffee and oatmeal out of the way in time to watch the coverage of the Giro d’Italia with Paul Sherwen and  urlLink Phil Liggett  commentating. (BTW, Bob Roll and Paul Sherwen do a nice job with the Tour de Romandie in the evenings. What does Phil Liggett do on his free evenings?)  I am about to write a note to NPR to suggest that Phil Liggett do a regular sports essay on bicycling—at least through the summer months. I think he could make the whole thing “very NPR.” And, it would rank up there with the old conversations that Bob Edwards used to have with Red Barber.      I really think that there would be more universal interest in the sport of bicycling than there is in horse racing, with all due respect to the horse named Smarty Jones. But, I don’t know anyone who knows anything about the Kentucky Derby or the Preakness. And NPR covers those. Are horseraces an east coast thing? Or, just something for old gamblers? Maybe I just don’t know the right people.  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       "Doug Christie covered his bald head in his hands and fell to the floor in frustration. The image told it all" according to Canadian Press (AP) writer, Janie McCauley. Our hearts go out to the sports fans of Placerville who were cheering their guts out for a chance to be defeated by the Los Angeles Lakers. But it was not to be.  I am sure that our Ploog friends of the land of 10,000 lakes will be tickled pink that their Timberwolves have now progressed to this glorious point in history.  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I will travel to Philadelphia, PA for the  urlLink Association of Enterprise Opportunity (AEO)  annual conference and membership meeting. This year the event is in Philadelphia.    urlLink      In the recent past this conference has been in Wahsington, DC; Denver, CO; Oakland, CA; Ft. Lauderdale, FL; and Chicago, IL. I have gone to this event for the last several years and enjoy seeing friends from the microenterprise industrly. My friend Andres Martinez will be there--Cindi and I stayed at his flat in Mexico City a couple of years ago when our summer vacation took us through that city. He has moved since then.   Andres also stayed at our place in Whittier when he came through Los Angeles visiting the ASSETS related microenterprise programs that MEDA promotes. At JobStarts we started the BusinesStarts program on this model.  
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       According to the sign at Ralph's, the Wild  urlLink Copper River Salmon  starts tomorrow. Last year I missed it all together our of just plain ignorance. My plan is to go down early to the store and buy some for lunch. I remember this salmon to have excellent flavor and texture. It is not farm raised so it has more of those omega fatty acids that are good for you.     
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I have decided that I no longer am interested in blog posts about blogging. I know that I invited such posts a while back. I know I have no way of enforcing the ban. Nevertheless, I hope that people will now be posting about the fascinating things in their fascinating lives.   
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am having trouble with knowing when new comments are posted. I find myself reviewing every post that has a comment section and trying to remember if the number of comments has changed or not. Often I look at the comments because I can not remember how many comments were there before. I now realize that I have missed comments on some posts and reread comments from other posts. I find this feature very time consuming to use. I realize I have the option to not use it and just continue to post all my input as posts rather than comments. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I would like to know who taught a lttle yellow labrador retreiver puppy that the area by the stove in the kitchen is a cool place to deposit a yellow puddle. Hmmn. 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I agree with Rob that the Bloog site seems less user friendly but maybe I'll get used to it soon.  I was finally able to print up a receipt for the trip.  (This not on the bloog ) They kept dumping me out saying I could try later.  I kept putting my pass word in and my secret code and also put a new one in, then when I would click on that they said I was already a member.  I finally admitted that I forgot my secret code and they sent it to me via e-mail and I realized how it got there.  Thanks Steve.  I've been collecting names of places that we just must see from different groups of friends.  The Willows has come up from every group.  It's a restaurant and has been there since before the 50's.  Will sent things on as they become clear or any of you can send suggestions of places to visit.  The most important place is the Pearl Harbor Memorial then the Polynesian Cultural Center. 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The company that is Cindi's  urlLink Creative Memories  business is running a  urlLink special promotion with Disney . It is a contest that will send some lucky customer and the consultant who sells the wining album to Disney World.   Cindi bought 15 of these special albums. 11 are already sold. So hurry in and buy your album to see if you win! The contest ends June 30. I think she will buy more if she needs to-- hurry! 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It seems like whenever I turn on the  urlLink OLN , hoping for a tidbit of news about cycling anywhere in the world, all I find are bullriders  and fishing competition.   I have read that Lance has won the  urlLink Tour de Georgia . I believe he will be competing in some other races before  urlLink TdF . I am wondering what else is happening. Can anyone help us out a little bit here? What is the state of the  urlLink pro cycling  world? Post here to let us know.   (If anyone wants to, I can teach you how to make a hyperlink like the one above--that means you can click on it and it takes you to more information at another site.) 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       A Google search tool is now located in the right side column for your convenience. Many people use Google to search the web and now you can do it from this site.   This feature was requested by Beth of Placerville.   BTW--when you enter your own name into Google to search, it is called ego surfing. Have fun! 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Rob, it didn't take another miricle shot for the Laker's to move on. They won with confidence.  
    
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       this new format for the blog seems to be less user-friendly for the "casual blogger." i don't like how you have to select a topic to read, instead of just reading it as a sort of running list of the blog entries. the lakers are going for the series tonight against the san antonio spurs. the shot derek fisher made the other night to win the game was like none that will ever be seen again. there was .4 seconds on the clock, where .3 is considered not enough time to catch the ball and shoot. sports fanatics get a little out of hand with this stuff. i saw a guy who painted "(explitive) spurs" on the back window of his truck. i wanna go watch the game at his house! sam #2 is increasing in size at an incredible rate. i just paid for my summer school CLASS, not CLASSES, and the cost was 96 dollars. that doesn't include the cost of the book, which thankfully, i'd already purchased for the bargain price of $86.50. i'm learning a lesson in math before i even take this stupid course. a collumnist who contributes to the los angeles times shared that it cost him 57 dollars for a full load to attend uc san jose for one semester. i'm considering going back to polly's, or getting a different second job. does anyone know of any openings? i have experience in dealing with customers, food service, and i'm a pretty good ticket-taker guy. don't worry about dangling participles glen... "From now on, ending a sentence with a preposition is something up with which I will not put." -Sir Winston Churchill 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am impressed by the knowledge of some members of this family group regarding specific teams or sports. I am sure that the more knowledge you have about a sport the more you can appreciate participating or observing. I am more of a dabbler. Here to the more knowledgeble among us. 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I had wanted to make a comment about subjective ness of sports in a post by Steve a while back.  However, time has slipped by and I am just now posting. As the readers of this blog are likely aware, I have not been much of a fan of watching sports. My thought on this is that if the subjective, emotional part was not a big deal, there would not be many fans. If the objective discipline and rules that set an immovable infrastructure against which to play, there would be nothing to be fanatic about [sorry this sentence ended in a preposition but it is too late to change this dangling participle].  Lakers are leading San Antonio by 10 in the fourth quarter as I type this. This may be the first time they have led in this game--an important one in a series that determines progress in playoffs. I am the only person left in the room watching this game. I think the true fans have been so affected by the pressure of the game and whether their preferred team will win that they have been driven from the room. My friend Lalo told me tonight that he has a hard time watching the Lakers--especially this season because of this whole passion issue.   Previously I had mentioned that I would comment further on the animated feature length French film Triplets of Bellville. So here it is:  1. It is extremely odd--exemplified by unusual lines and proportions on faces, buildings, streets, contrasting tall and short people, etc. and a topless dancer in some sort of cabaret and on and on it goes. 2. There is no real dialogue, the story is told entirely with visuals. 3. Interesting sonically--recurring sound devices like the dogs toenails against tile, the sound of a passing train, a whistle blowing, music, all seemed to serve to draw attention to a certain scene for a purpose. Much like the use of lighting a sound in a live theatrical production.  4. Visually interesting--combination of hand sketched 2 dimensional animations and computer generated 3 dimensional animations contrasted in the same scenes to make varying impressions on the viewer.   It may have been easier to use the comments function for part of this post, but it doesn't work on older posts.  
    
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Thankfully, Cindi is home documenting most every motion of two dogs with her camera. Anyone want to make a bet on how many CM albums will result from this new puppy? 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, this is it!  We take Cynthia to the airport for a direct flight back to sunny California and the group.  Sad to see her go, but had a perfect time!  Welcome to anyone else who comes this way. Looking forward to this great Blogging idea of Glen's.  Lots of fun!!! Love ALL the pictures, and Beth you have me in stitches.  I look forward to your postings.   
    
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       We started our Mother's day celebration on Saturday, Mother's Day Eve, with a brunch at the California Grill in Whitter.   Then, Sunday, we barbequed at the Peterson's Milton Mansion. Doris brought macaroni salad, Audrey brought a green salad with "lime" dressing that was a lot like guacamole.   Included in our celebrations: Doris, Audrey, Garth, Timothy, Daniel, Rob, and me. Hope the rest of you can join us next time.  
    
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Tonight Dick, Cynthia and I went to a Dog Training Class. There were between nine and eleven dogs with their owners learning what is expected in "Competitions".  Our eyes were opened to new fields of adventure and excellence.  There are dogs, and then there are dogs !!!  Our Sam 2 will certainly be a star!!  We are all excited again !    
    
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I was so shocked to sign into this and see a whole new program.  It doesn't take much to get me confused on the computer but after remaining calm and reading through the options I was able to fing out how to read the entries and also to make an entry.  I do like the temperature  
    
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Blogger has launched a lot of new features and a new look to the user interface section.  I have also, in a completely seperate act, inspired by the other changes, made some changes to the look of our site. I am not satisfied with several things yet; so I will keep trying.  Once I get a look that I like better, I will add those weather reporting links back in.   Your comments are weicome.   UPDATE: I have tried a couple of template changes that get the stuff I wanted to work--I kept getting various errors and formatting problems. Steve--I took you post of the steamboat off by making it a "draft." The problem is that the picture is wide and was pushing everything on the page off of the side. If you can shrink the photo, upload it with the same name, and republish that post, everything should work. Let me know what you think. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Dick 'n Jane & Cynthia drove about 60 miles in the gorgeous weather (which we always have here in Ohio) to the lovely "INN AT HONEY RUN" near Millersburg, OH in the heart of Amish country. We had delightful brunch by the windows overlooking the woods. I had bananas foster with carmelized croutons and vanilla bean ice cream.  It was very delicious!  I had never had it before. I know it would have tasted even better in a 'ramekin'.  Dick had a piece of most elegant chocolate cake with a strawberry that measured at least a 'cubit'. Cynthia's choice was a fabulous sour-cream pound cake with berries and Chantilly-cream. On the way home we stopped at one of Cynthia's favorite places in Ohio - The Pine Tree Barn where she found some very unusual sun-catchers.  Hope the day was as pleasant for all of you. [written by Jane] 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       To all of the moms have a happy mother's day. According to the weather information you will all have a bright and warm day to enjoy it. Best wishs to all. Beth and I had lunch with my mother yesterday. I got caught up on all of the "family" news. My father enjoyed our company and was glad we took time "from our busy schedules". I think anyone younger than 86 would look busy to him. It was a plesant afternoon. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Audrey and Doris are meeting Steve and Beth in Hawaii. We will all have to learn the Hula. We will also have some interesting words to add to Glen's list. 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       . . . or should we just grunt and point? Here is a word that came up at lunch today:  ram·e·kin or ram·e·quin n 1.	a small ovenproof dish with vertical fluted sides designed to hold a single serving of a prepared food, especially one that is baked 2.	a portion of food cooked and served in a ramekin  Rob said he was curious about the etymology of the word ramekin, I think he was right about the Dutch: [French ramequin, perhaps from Dutch dialectal rammeken, toasted bread, or from Low German ramken, diminutive of ram, cream (from Middle Low German).]  Maybe you were wondering what a ramekin looks like?     I recently started a list of new words for myself. When I hear or read a word with which I am not familiar, I write it down, look it up and add the definition to the list.   After watching a movie that Rob loaned me recently, I added this to my list:   rumpus (n) an outcry or noisy disturbance   --and this--  obsequious (adj) Excessively eager to please or to obey all instructions  I might of added this one after going to the theater:   scrim n 1.	a drop curtain in a theater that appears opaque to the audience when lit from the front but transparent when lit from behind 2.	a durable open-weave cotton or linen fabric used for curtains, clothing, upholstery lining, and in industry   
    
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Cynthia is sitting beside me in Akron, OH - so we are breaking our silence and joining in the "Family Blog".  Sam 2 did not come.  We all miss him, but Glen and Rob are taking excellent care of him, so not to worry!  Picked Cynthia up at Cleve-Hopkins airport Friday  10:58 PM.  Lovely day here, have already been to the new STARBUCKS at the corner of our street - How sweet it is !!!!   
    
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Cindi went to Akron, Ohio this weekend for Mother's Day. That is because her mother is there.   Audrey and I will take our mother to lunch today, Saturday, to celebrate motherhood. We expect that Rob and Timothy will join us.   My friend Pedro, the owner of Uptown Mexican Cafe, told me this week that he expects to be busy from Friday dinner through Monday dinner with Mother's day revelers. Buddy at California Grill expects that they will be busy for Saturday breakfast and dinner and Sunday for lunch.   [Little Sam is snoring away on the floor behind the rocking chair right now--it made me laugh, and reminded me of Cindi.] 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Something I started when I was working for JobStarts is a  urlLink one-day seminar with John Carver on Policy Governance  that will take place on June 5 Carver at the BP Amoco building in Los Angeles. It is now possible to register by credit card for the seminar through the Los Angeles Jr. Chamber of Commerce's website. Thas is really cool.   I am still acting as a consultant on this project. We have room for 90+ people. There are currently 19 paying customers signed up, all of whom I have personally signed up. We are a long way from breaking even at this point. I am nervous. 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       After a steady diet of sports news the last couple of months I want to change sports to a purely subjective endeavor. Teams would show up, demonstrate their skills for a set number of minutes, and then there would be no score or other objective criteria remembered. Spectators would only remember the event for is subjective "emotional" value. Sports would then be delegated to just another of those "emotional" moments that do not require any logical or critical thinking. Wait, sports writers and many fans only think emotionally about sports, they forget the scores or use the data from events for their own emotional reasons. Not much evidence of logic or critical thinking now. Forget I said anything.  
    
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well Steve, I tried. I am sure that if I read more instructions, I'd find out why the HTML is working in the right column field and not in the post message field.   Which one do you like?  The second "sticker" is identical to the one posted in the right.  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink   alt="Click for Honolulu, Hawaii Forecast" height=108 width=144>  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am impressed Glen. Value added. All the weather sites show up. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It was really hot again today in Whittier. I think that the high was 110 degrees or more! Right now in Whittier this is the time and temperature:   urlLink      UPDATE: So as a value added, you can easily check out the weather for several of the places represented by those who read and post to the PWWCR Family Blog. Did I miss anyone?  UPDATE [an hour later]: Ok, after about 3 tries with varying degrees of sucess, failure, sucess, failure, (repeat ad naseum). I think this weather listing is going to work. I was putting the HTML in the wrong place and blogger was producing errors. I have now moved it all to where I think they wanted me to put it in the first place. It seems to have responded correctly now for a few repetitions. We'll see how it goes. If it works--there should be several boxes with weather for various places on the right. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Especially after an afternoon in the hands of the lovely people at United Airlines. I will have to watch the last part of the film to see how it ends. The film is unusual and interesting both visually and sonically. After I watch the rest of it I will try to post again with more. 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       A couple of weeks ago, when Dave was here, we had breakfast outdoors. In fact, I took the skillet out there and made the pancakes out there too.  Then, I captured this image.      
    
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
          When he finds something valuable, he will carry it around the yard, chew on it, and eventually put someplace safe, like the family room near the TV or his pillow. 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       If I recall correctly, and if it will be the same as last year, I think that the local Pacific Daylight Time start of the coverage will be at 6:30 AM with the Pre-Race Show and then actual race coverage starting at 6:30 AM--that's 9:30 AM Eastern US time. Then they repeat stuff during the morning, afternoon and evening. Thats got to be better than most professional sports! I will be up at the earliest show time. (At least on Saturday, we'll see how it goes for the rest of the race.)     Be sure to notice the time zone listed. 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am sure you are wondering what the weather will be like at the start of the race. I was looking for weather for Liege, Belgium. Weather Underground returned Bierset. I don't know how close that is to Liege.    urlLink       I haven't given up yet. But, I did find the weather station for the city of Charleroi, Belgium. That is the ending point of the July 4 day of racing.   urlLink     
    
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       My work was mentioned in a MEDA Publication called  urlLink The Marketplace , a glossy magazine that goes to MEDA's membership. You can read the article by cliking on the links above.  
    
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Peets can be found at  urlLink www.peets.com  
    
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Who's next? Lance Armstrong's rivals are decreasing all the time.  First Beloki, and now Vinokourov.  T-Mobile anounced who will be in the Tour de France on their team, and Alexandre Vinokourov isn't on the list.  He crashed on a traffic island in a race and suffered a concussion, facial scrapes, and ligament damage to his shoulder. The shoulder injury required surgery, which will keep him off the bike for 3 weeks — the 3 weeks leading up to the Tour (unless he's like Lance and doesn't do anything his doctors tell him to).  He would have been helping Jan Ullrich in the battle to win his second Tour de France, so Ullrich wouldn't be called the 'Eternal Second'.  I haven't heard about the wonderclimber Roberto Heras in a while.  Maybe he wants to just train instead of race so this won't happen.  See y'all next Saturday!    (Vinokourov) 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Enjoyed the unexpected visit from Beth and Steve this last weekend and enjoyed meeting Brianna.  What a sweetheart.  Doesn't really know a stranger.  Also thanks to Glen, Cindi and Rob for the impromptu event at their home on Saturday eve. Hope Sam 2 has recovered from the invasion of his kennel.  Steve, I thought we would see a picture of Brianna in the kennel.  Our lips are sealed as far as the child protective agency.  Doris 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It was nice to see everyone. Here is a picture of Beth and Brianna at the beach. Brianna arrived safely and Jonah is out of the hospital. Thanks for the warm welcomes.   
    
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       In case you don't think you will get enough of the Tour with OLN and a possibility of another book from Lance, you can pre-order a book that will tell all about what will happen at  urlLink velogear.com .  This might be what it will look like, because the riders on the cover are favorites--the German  urlLink Jan Ullrich , winner in '97, and 5-time runner-up to the Tour, who won the Tour de Suisse (a one-week long race) by one second recently; the Texan  urlLink Lance Armstrong , 5-time winner and 3-time beater of Ullrich; and the "Man From Marblehead, Massachussets"  urlLink Tyler Hamilton , the one who got fouth place last year despite having a broken collerbone to deal with for almost the whole race, and who won the Tour de Romandie (in Switzerland) in May.   Perhaps this is what the podium will look like in Paris.    
    
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       There are only 16 days left until the Tour de France, and the Spanish rider Joseba Beloki, Lance's main rival in 2002, and crashed out last year, announced he will not be racing in this year's Tour de France due to lack of fitness.  At the end of 2003, he signed to Brioches La Boulangere (a French team) for until the end of 2005, but then he decided to cut it short and end at the end of this year, then he decided to quit in June.  He is now training for the Vuelta a Espana (a major stage race in September).  Here is a picture of the coffee table book about Lance Armstrong's carreer that I mentioned in a previous post.   I never like to look at Lance struggling in a time trial like that and don't like to see him in that jersey design because I always think about that.  I hope you don't have that problem. Lance's team (United States Postal Service Presented by Berry Floor) will quit for 2005, but it will be replaced by the Discovery Chanel Team until the end of 2007 I guess.  At the end of this year, the team will have the Discovery Chanel logo on it prominately.  Read more at  urlLink Lance's web site .  Maybe this means we will have to watch lance and bike races on the Discovery Chanel instead of the current OLN.  Lance announced he will ride the 2005 Tour de France, but just to make the change go more smoothly. You can also read the entire first chapter of Lance's new book, " Every Second   Counts ",  urlLink here .  There is a book called the  urlLink Tour de France Centennial Book  and is a coffee table book about the Tour de France with 360 pages of images and stories about the race in both black and white and color. It only costs $24.  A limited edition. 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Here is a picture of Brianna eating a piece of Kyle's birthday cake. Don't tell me there isn't entertainment at our house.   
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       We are back. Fell into bed last night around midnight. Flight went well, though a bit choppy at times. Weird thing...no window in our row. I was bummed. When I flew to Chi-town, as we Chicago residents say (pronounced shy-town), everyone pulled down the window shades so the movie screen could be better viewed in a darker plane. What is the point in flying when you can't see the view and the weather and the sky? Ugh. The movie eastbound was Starsky & Hutch. I opted to read and nap.  I'm still doing piles of final reports. I check out of my day job tomorrow, and officially begin summer vacation. Audrey, Doris, and I will go to lunch at this cute spot in Los Alamitos called Shenandoah. Wish Beth and Mom-Jane could join us. I can't wait to be done with the school year, even though I do like my job. Next year will be year three!  Poor Lakers. But do I really care? I'm planning the French toast family breakfast for the start of the Tour de France! Moving on to sporting events that really have some excitement for me.  FYI - the Remington computer is in the repair bay for a week. If you need to share news with the Ohio folks, do it the old fashioned way...by phone.  We had a nice time in Chicago. Hotel 71 is a contempo place --- kinda weird, but nice room and cool view. Maybe Glen will blog a picture. I got to meet with 10 good friends from the old days when I lived in Wheaton. So great to catch up. Sam looked HUGE to us upon our return. Wow! It's so nice to leave him in good hands with Rob when we travel.  Still so concerned for Jonah. Hope each day is a better one. And happy birthday to Kyle! How old now?  
    
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Jonah is surgery went well. No leaks into his abdomen. They resectioned his colon where it was ruptured. Beth, Brianna and I are off to see him now that he is off the ventilator. Beth is bringing Shawntea home while I stay with Jonah. That will give her a chance to spend time with Brianna and get a shower etc.  Thanks for your prayers and thoughts.  
    
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Jonah is off to surgery. The did a CT scan and he has a ruptured bowel. I will be off in a couple of minutes after singing happy birthday to Kyle. 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Just a quick note. Jonah is having some problems with his abdomen. The medication he is on now requires that he is back in Intensive Care. I saw him late last night. Today he is hoping to go back to a regular room. Several of the firefighters are there to visit him when I called. The nurses are very good at letting people visit one at a time. Shawntea is going home for a while today and spend some time with Brianna. We will have again overnight. Here is a picture of the difficult life she leads at our house.   
    
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Beth, Kyle and I saw Jonah this afternoon. He is struggling with concentration and memory. Looking at the truck this am it is amazing to me that he survived. There is still part of the tree he hit embedded in the engine block. The tree is about three feet into the engine compartment. Quess where the engine is? No wonder his leg was shattered. He now has a metal rod from his knee to his ankle. The bone is strapped and screwed to together.  His head trainer arrived as did the chief of the largest fire department in the area. They were both supportive and made the point that firefighters stick help each other out. The chief of his department will be by tonight to talk to him as well. We will see him tomorrow. Shawntea stays at the hospital with him and we have Brianna again.  thanks for your prayers.   
    
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Jonah is in Sutter Roseville Hospital. He had surgery on his leg and will be in the hospital until atleast Sunday. Kyle and I will visit him this afternoon after getting his glasses from his truck. Not looking forward to seeing his truck, heard it is in much worse shape than he is. Thanks for air bags and seatbelts. Beth returned to work this am. She had Brianna overnight. We got to wake up to a little girl calling out for her grandma. Not like a puppy sniffing your nose, but nice.  
    
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Jonah was in an auto accident today. He was life-flighted to Sutter Hospital in Roseville. Kyle and I visited him tonight. He has a concussion and both bones in his right leg were fractured. He is supposed to have surgery to repair his leg sometime during the night. His girlfriend Shawntea is spending the night at the hospital. Kyle and I will try and find what is left of Jonah's truck tomorrow and also contact the fire academy. He will be in the hospital for about four days. Will post more as we know more. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Tonight in Chicagoland the lead news story is a tornado watch and flood warnings. One tornado has been sighted south of here. I am in the town of Boomingdale, Illinois. Just gentle rain out my window.  Regarding email. I have set up a new service on my email. In order to reduce the number of unsolicited emails (SPAM) that I receive, I am trying out a system that onlyl allows those who I proactively allow to send. I think I have allowed everyone who regularly read this blog. Thanks Steve for your patience, you are now allowed to send to my account. It is not uncommon that I have to hit the delete button 50 or more times in a day for emails that I do not want. Please let me know if I have inadvertantly not allowed your eagerly anticipated and appreciated emails.  
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Beth was to ill to go to work today. Sore throat, fever, and aches. Slept most of the day with Kyle keeping watch. Well when not focusing on his video game he did listen to guess whether she was asleep or not. She is hoping that she will feel better and be at work tomorrow.  
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I will be in Chicago through next Tuesday.   urlLink      The weather looks warm and humid tonight.   I will be at the  urlLink IPGA conference  and visiting my CCF clients. 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ask to see Beth's DFish tattoo next time you see her. I thought I got carried away by basketball. I am just glad the Lakers won tonight. 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today I visited Rudy Carrasco of the  urlLink Harambee Christian Family Center . The first time I heard of a blog was from Rudy and I have been reading  urlLink his blog  with some regularity ever since. Today, in his office, he captured an image of the two of us and posted it on his blog. He included a link to us, so If you are visiting from Rudy's blog, say hello with the comment feature here.  
    
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i too, have had to drop out of a lot of races this year due to lack of fitness. this year also holds a pretty important political race, one that ted kennedy has called the "most important" election of his lifetime. hopefully both candidates will get in better shape for that race. sad to hear about president reagan. jon stewart on "the daily show" wondered out loud if reagan's death was a conspiracy started by jennifer lopez to take focus off of her third (who cares?) marriage. peace to everyone.  
    
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Will Joseba Beloki, Lance's greatest rival in last year's Tour until he crashed out, not even start this year's Tour?  He has had problems of not being able to have as much fitness as he should for having the Tour start in just four weeks.  He has had to drop out of a lot of races this year because of his lack of fitness. Perhaps it will be Tyler Hamilton that will challenge Lance the most in this year's Tour.  He won the Tour de Romandie and is showing a lot of fitness.  You can get the  urlLink Official 2004 Tour de France Poster by clicking this line.  It's only 10 dollars.     
    
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       In my last post I mentioned two books, but I forgot about another one that looks interesting.  It's called  urlLink The Noblest Invention , and has a forward by Lance Armstrong.  It's about how the bicycle chaned from its weird beginnings to what it is now.  There are over 250 pictures and essays about it.  Read more by clicking on the link above. 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       There is a new book out called   urlLink Lance Armstrong--Images of a Champion  . It's about Lance's life and has 239 photos of him by Graham Watson and was started several years ago. It will probably be outdated by Christmas because I think you can get it now, so this year's Tour de France won't be in it, but it looks like something I'd put on my Christmas list.  There is also a new book out on the Tour de France by Bob Roll [You know, in the Tour de France days you a greeted by the commentators PhilLigget, the guy with one name and that TourDay France guy, Bob Roll (and Paul Sherwan)]. It's 192 pages at $11.  Here's what Bobchi's book looks like:    Happy shopping! 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The word that a kid spelled to win the national spelling bee.  au·toch·tho·nous adj 1.	used to describe a rock, mineral deposit, or geologic feature that was formed in the area where it is found 2.	descended from the original flora, fauna, or inhabitants of the region in which it is found 3.	produced or originating as a physical function or disorder in the place where it is found  Encarta® World English Dictionary © 1999 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved. Developed for Microsoft by Bloomsbury Publishing Plc.  Click  urlLink here  for more news in the online edition of an Indianapolis news paper.  
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Any suggestions for the awards for the caption contest. I was more interested in the dinner that accompanies the presentations. Beth and I have stuff for a garage sale that might work. Easier to give away then sell. Still looking for more entries. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am having fun with the captions. Liked the others as well. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm wrapping up hours and hours of paper work for the next week or so. Students end their homeschool year tomorrow. I am swamped with work. Rumor has it Beth is back at it with summer school administration. I'm looking forward to things winding down and reading a good book for fun again. Samson II went to the vet today for his next shot in the puppy shot series. He weighed in at 24.5 American pounds and was found to have dirty ears. I lost the lottery and so I will be putting drops in while he bites me for ten days...wrestle mania with a wagging tail.  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I think this could be fun. Use the comment function to submit a caption for this photo.    
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Valueable prizes and lavish praise to the winners.    
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Beth and I had a nice dinner out. New Italian place in El Dorado Hills. Great food and lovely setting. Thanks for the pictures Rob. Wished we could have been there to enjoy the day with all of you. We are working on a schedule for this summer with Kyle. I am trying to set up a trip that includes college visits, a dodgers game and time with family. After looking at what already is scheduled, not sure when that can be.... Again thanks to Rob for the photos. I just picked a few, but let me know if you want others, I have saved them all to my website. Take care to all of you. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i started summer school today. for six weeks, i will take four hours of math a day monday-thursday. it's going to be a challenging course. i feel kind of guilty that today i witnessed sam and ashley's gleeful play session in their new (and already punctured) kiddie pool, while glen and cindi were away, missing the priceless laugh riot. sadly, no photos were taken of the event, but i was able to capture several candid shots from the combined birthday celebration that took place on sunday. it should be viewable  urlLink here  . *note to blog administrator: i give permission for you to post any or all of these pictures on the actual blog site if desired. it may make for easier access.* the celebration was a lot of fun, although i had to cut out a bit early to go to work on time. sorry not all the birthday boys and (or) girls were not all able to attend, although they were acknowledged by their names on the cake. 
    
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I was lonely this week. Glen was in Miami. OLN no longer offered any company to me. Daniel only stopped by briefly once. The Democratic Convention held only mild interest. And Sam II did not learn his "down" command, even though we practiced every day over and over.  Thankfully, Rob was here, awaiting the start of school and helping me hunt down the mysterious, evasive bad smell in the refrigerator.  So, I worked a lot on getting photos in albums. I had a very good time. It is fun to get photos organized to retell the great stories, big and little of the year. Very fun for me. I've been leaving off most of the design to speed things up. The photos and words/writing tell the story, so nothing else is really needed. And it's been a good month for my Creative Memories business.  I will be traveling next week to Minneapolis, Minnesota to attend the annual national convention for Creative Memories. It is always a top-notch experience. This year, I will be taking the "plant tour" --- traveling to St. Cloud, MN to tour the headquarters. Should be interesting. I'll be home on Sunday morning with many of the new products introduced in hand. That fact is very exciting to some of my eager clients.  Does anyone want to go to the next local Sheryl Crow concert with me? Not just to see if Lance rides through. I do like her as a musician, too.  I got bicycle shoes and gloves. Now I hope to get the training wheels off my bike by the end of the summer. I was really inspired by LA.   
    
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Glen posted something about me being in the race at Heritage Park, and that I beat the kids my age.  One of them is the State Champion.  We saw them riding on the trail yesterday, and apparently they turned around not long after to chase us down.  We were going pretty fast, like 24 mph for a while (with a tail wind), then Dad got a flat and they passed us.  We could have stayed with them if that didn't happen, and we could have stayed ahead of them if we knew we were racing (being chased).  He's going to do the US National Championships, which are in Utah, but I don't know when.  But the  urlLink national track championships  are happenning right now in maybe Carson.  For the pros, the Autumn Classics are happening, and on August 1st, the  urlLink HEW Cyclassics Cup  will happen.  Don't expect to see Lance in it because he has a press conference that day. 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Asian News Channel International  reports: "Belgian Christophe Brandt was the only cyclist to return a positive drug tests during the Tour de France, the International Cycling Union (IUC) said."  That means that the Postie boys, including Lance tested clean, as promised. Armstrong claims that he is tested more than any of the other competitors in the Tour de France. 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       yeah dude, where's the muumu's?! anywho, last night i was watching sportscenter on espn as i often do to find out about the outcome of the dodger game that day. one of the funny commercials that espn plays is where sportscenter analyst dan patrick is working in his office, when the power apparently fails. so there is a long shot of patrick walking down the hallway, down the stairs, and into the basement of the building, all the way to a door that would apparently be where generator might be, and there's lance armstrong on a stationary bicycle.  lance: "oh sorry dan, i thought everyone had left for the night." dan: "you okay? you want an energy bar or something." lance: "no, i'm good." (resumes pedaling) i thought the commercial funny.   three cheers glen! we know you were stressing the test, but we all secretly knew that it was in the bag. i bribed mr. carver with rentals from blockbuster. always looking out for you i am.   the daily show w/ jon stewart has been hilarious coming from the democratic national convention this week. one of their field reporters said he filmed all of his reports ahead of time and left early since the convention was so scripted and boring. he made sure to do reports on a few possible exciting scenarios just in case, including a polar bear attacking the delegates from kansas, and hazardous quicksand discovered on the floor of the fleet center.  
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Lance Armstrong says he is fully capable of winning the Tour de France for a 7th time.  "Time is limited but I think I could win the Tour de France one more time," he said.  George HIncapie says he is as motivated as he ever was and needs to win.  "It's [winning] something he needs in his life.  I've known the guy for a long time and that desire to win is as strong as ever.  It's part of him, what motivaties him and keeps him going.  It could be a World Cup race, whatever, Lance is just like that."  Lance hasn't said when he'll give it another go, but he's not getting any younger. 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       If everything goes as planned, this will be my last day in South Florida. I will drive south to visit a client in Florida City--about half way to the Florida Keys from Miami. If things don’t go as planned, I don’t know what I’ll do. Find a Starbucks and order a venti!   Someday I will take the opportunity to keep on driving until I get to Key West. I will save that trip for a time when Cindi travels here with me.   Some of you know that I was taking a test last week that would qualify me for participation in the Policy Governance Academy with John and Miriam Carver. I received word yesterday that I have been accepted--I passed the test!   The weather here has been steamy. This is the low season for tourism because it is warm, humid and wet--lot's of rain. I am looking forward to a trip here in February 2005 with the board of directors. I will help facilitate a tour, along with the Vice President of North American Operations for the board members and their spouses. That should be fun. I have invited Cindi to come along with me on this trip.   I am looking forward to watching OLN on Sunday with Daniel--there is a Lance interview. Should be good.  P. S. I am looking for the promised matching muumuu images from the land of Hawaii.   
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Daniel just got a velonews magazine for free for having a racing license-- sent to him with hopes that he would subscribe.  Here's what the cover lookes about like (not this grainy):    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       in 2006. Matt Damon says he wants to play the part of Lance.  
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       sometimes i pretend i'm jan. and i'm not talking brady, i'm talking ullrich. maybe that's why i feel like an underachiever.... 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       There have been at least 3 ads on OLN for powerbar.com with a guy pretending he's Lance and imagining how a commentator would commentate it.  But the pros also pretend they're Lance.  Here's a quote from one:  "When I'm taining I imagine I'm Lance Armstrong and I go up the climbs at full speed pretending I'm unbeatable" --Fabian Jeker, who lost the Tour of Switzerland by one second to Jan Ullrich, so his strategy almost paid off, too.  I definitely do not want school to start anytime soon, Rob. 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       the administrator ought to know that i tried voting in his cute little poll for best oln staff member, and it told me that i had already voted, although i have no recollection of doing so. i tried voting for kirsten gum, cause i hear she is a babe, and she must be a lot better looking than al troutwhatever. so let's see...my mom, my step-dad, my grandmother, my aunt, and my uncle are all in the tropics right now. how exciting for them! judging by the enormous insects i often encounter on my bedroom walls, i would've sworn that i too was in the tropics. so far, summer vacation is really lame. i find that i have way too much time on my hands. i just want school to begin again, so that i have a reason to get out of bed before noon. it finally feels like i'm getting things done on my own terms, because I want to, and that is a nice feeling. i feel momentum. but not at the moment, since it's summer vacation. i can't believe that i even went to summer school already, that seems like a long time ago. last night i watched a movie called "napoleon dynamite." it was super funny, and a really clean movie. (ie: no swearing, adult humor or violence.) i'd heard of the movie a while back, and later read that it was made by some graduates of brigham young university. that had put me off initially, because i've been conditioned to think anything mormon is either really weird, or really wrong. i'm proud of myself for overcoming my own prejudices, and allowing myself to enjoy something that could be enjoyable to any subculture. just for clarity's sake, there was no mention of religion in the actual film other than a mexican character who had a lot of traditional catholic symbols in his house. i'm starting to realize that i'm not taking advantage of my surroundings enough this summer. it's almost august, and i haven't been to one dodger game or visited the beach this summer! something must be done about these things. not at the moment however, since it's probably really cold at the beach at 12:13 am. songs of the moment on my very own ipod: "ocean breathes salty" by modest mouse, "over it" by onelinedrawing, and "goodmorning aztlan" by los lobos. download away... 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Some of you are wondering what iPods are.  I'm sure Glen can give you a better answer, but it is a device that can store memory to back up your hard disc, or you can download music onto it for listening with ease.  In a magazine I got today, someone said, "I've put many of my 1000 CDs onto my iPod  so that I can have all my best music with me wherever I go."    
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       In stage 3 in the Tour de France, the riders had to go over cobblestones that are usually saved for the spring classics Paris-Roubaix and Ronde van Vlaanderen (Tour of Flanders).  The riders were not too happy about this, and an overall contender, Iban Mayo, crashed and lost almost 4 minutes to Lance because of that.  Here are some quotes pertaining to them:  "Cobbles are for Paris-Roubaix, not the Tour de France.  They're not going to put any mountains in Paris-Roubaix next year are they [Paris-Roubaix is always flat]?" --Tyler Hamilton  "We're bike riders, we should ride on the road and not be gladiators.  If someone loses it [crashes] in front of you, you run over him and you crash." --Jens Voight  Source:  VeloNews (velonews.com). 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Lance Armstrong won an unprecedented sixth Tour victory this year while beating the crapes out of all his rivals (remember that add, OLN watchers?).  Today was a very easy day around the Champs-Elysees, with Lance in a special yellow uniform.  Tom Boonen won the stage, and Robbie McEwen got the green jersey for the best and most consistent sprinter.  Read more  urlLink here .  Lance in his different uniform.    Lance celebrates #6.    Tom Boonen celebrates his second stage win this year.    Winners of jerseys, left to right:  Robbie McEwen, sprinter; Lance, overall classification; Richard Virenque, King of the Mountains (for a record 7th time); Vladimir Karpets, Best Young Rider.   
    
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I really enjoyed the little bio about the Mennonite racer.  Hope he does well in the years to come 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Lance Armstrong showed he is the king of the Tour today when he won the Time Trial to Besançon.  His teamates went out with marvelous times, then when "Yawn" Ullrich came around, he set the best times, with his teamate Andreas Kloden not far away from him.  Ivan Basso was next, but he didn't do too well (as expected).  Lance Armstrong came out of the starting gate with the fastest times at all of the check points, and beat Ullrich (2nd place) by 61 seconds!  This was his 5th victory in this year's Tour, and 21st victory total in the Tour de France.  Tomorrow is an easy 100-mile day ending on the Champs Elysees. The final standings are Lance Armstrong, first, Andreas Kloden, 2nd, Ivan Basso, 3rd.  (Ullrich, a five-time runner-up, was 4th).  Jose Azevedo was 5th, 14:30 behind his team leader.  American Levi Leipheimer (Rabobank) was 9th.  Thomas Voeckler, who was in the yellow jersey for 10 days, started in the white jersey today as the best young rider.  However, he lost that lead when he lost way more than the 45 seconds he was leadings the Russian Vladimir Karpets (Illes-Ballears).  Richard Virenque (Quick Step-Davitamon) won the King of the Mountains competition with 226 points, and Lance was 2nd, with 172 points.  T-Mobile won the team competition, with the Posties 2nd.  The Sprinting competition is led by Robbie McEwen (Lotto-Domo), but the Norwegian Thor Hushovd could beat him, because the competion continues on the Champs-Elysees, and he is not far off.  For the overall contenders, tomorrow should be a fun ride around Paris with smiles all over, and some Champagne for Lance, which apparently hard his easiest Tour ever, with 5 stage wins and the team time trial in his palmares.  "I'm happy, because it's finished," he added. "I'm tired mentally, have tired legs."     
    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Beth is sitting here next to me chatting with Rob while I am watching the expanded coverage of T de F.  That's a nice surprise.  
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I friend and colleague of mine, Rudy Carrasco, has learned this week that his 4 year old son Samuel, has leukemia. Rudy is an avid blogger and has set up a blog for  urlLink Sam Sam here . I told Rudy about Lance Armstrong, who is a cancer survivor (leukemia is a kind of cancer). Rudy is now posting about the bicycle race, Armstrong's Foundation, and cancer survivorship on his regular blog called  urlLink Urban Onramps . So now I wear my yellow wristband for Rudy's Sam Sam also.  
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Don't forget to vote for who you think is Lance's best domestique.  The winner receives $10,000! Currently, George Hincapie has 55% of the votes, Floyd Landis has 24%, and Jose Azevedo has 12%.  To vote, click  urlLink here .    
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I have enjoyed Floyd Landis and his role on the USPS team to help Lance. A few months ago on a tour in Lancaster County, Pennsylvania, Floyd's family's farm was pointed out to us by out tour guide. His description was that Floyd's family is Amish. Had Floyd grown up on the south side of Hwy 30, he would not have been permitted to use a bicylce, the Amish are only allowed scooters on that side of the road.   So, I was curious when I read in Every Second Counts, Armstrongs autobiography that Floyd is Mennonite. Then, Robin William described the family as Mennonite. If you'd like to know more, read  urlLink this . I guess this interests me because I work for MEDA (Mennonite Economic Development Associates). This link, thanks to Hugo Swyzer, a Mennonite in Pasadena whose blog I read ocassionally.   You can also read Floyd's  urlLink online journal here . I think Daniel may have already linked us to that one.  
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
                   
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The riders in the Tour de France do not like the heat and even though they drink a lot, they can still get dehydrated.  Read about it in a journal entry by American Christian Vande Velde  urlLink here . 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Juan Miguel Mercado (Quick Step-Davitamon) won Friday's stage of the Tour de France while Lance Armstrong retained his overall lead safetly in the bunch.  Jaun Miguel Mercado was in a breakway, and attacked with 12 km to go, and Garcia-Acosta followed.  Garcia-Acosta was expected to win because he was stronger and more experienced, but the Quick Step drafted him to the line and outsprinted him. This is the third stage victory for the Belgian Quick Step-Davitamon team.  Earlier in the race, Italian Filippo Simeoni (Domina Vacanze) bridged the gap to the breakway and Armstrong followed because of personal tension between the two.  T-Mobile or CSC (Lance's main challenger's teams) would definitely not let Lance go, and the break knew that, so they asked him to leave, but he said he would only leave if Simeoni left, so he did.     Not the easiest route, but nothing serious.    Tomorrow is the Final TT, which Lance has always won in the past except for last year.  Jan Ullrich could also make a splash. 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The US Postal team aero bars (by Bontrager) are now available to the general public.  630 grams, $600.     The team's helmet, however, is not available yet to normal people.     Nor is the Trek Madone SL, the bike the Posties ride in races with cobblestones.    
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       In  urlLink his last diary entry ,Tyler Hamilton paid tribute to his dog (and best friend, I suppose) Tugboat.  Tyler and Tugboat.    Yes, the riders have the same idea that you do on the crowds of the Tour de France.  In a recent entry of Christian Vandevelde's diary, he says, The crowds were insane from the start of the climb all the way to the top. At times it was scary, as I didn't really know if I would make it through the crazy screaming fans. By the time we started racing the fans had finished their lunches, finished their bottles of red, cans of beer and topped it all off with shots of grappa. When people are drunk, reaction times are slow and the noise is deafening-good and bad when you're racing up a hill with sweat in your eyes."  Here, you see the crazy fans.   
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
          Lance Armstrong showed he deserves a sixth Tour victory today when he won the 17th stage of the Tour de France (making it 4 stages this year).  US Postal set a fast pace, and the only ones that could keep up were Jan Ullrich, his teamate Andréas Klöden, Ivan Basso, currently in 2nd place behind Lance, and Lance himself led by Floyd Landis.  The stage ended with Andréas Klöden sprinting away at 1 km to go, and everyone followed, and Lance sprinted out and came out right ahead of him.  Jan Ullrich probably wasn't too happy about Klöden because he took the 2nd place time bonus (12 second), leaving Jan with just the 3rd place bonus (8 seconds), putting him at 8:08 back, in 4th place, with Klöden in 3rd, at 5:11.  Ullrich has never been worse in the Tour than 2nd place.  There were some early breakaways for the King of the Mountains competition and to be the first person to be at the highest point of the Tour, the 2000-meter Col de la Madeleine, which is rewarded with a 5000-Euro bonus (6000 dollars), which Gilbeto Simoni got, just edging out Richard Virenque, with the Armstrong group behind.         
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Lance Armstrong distroyed his rivals' Tour hopes when he beat his normal challenger, a great time trialist, Jan Ullrich, by 61 seconds in just 15.5 km (about 9 miles), putting the German 7:44 back, and Ivan Basso, Lance's closest challenger this year, who is not a good time trialist, is now 3:38 behind Lance.  The time trial was up the legendary Alpe d'Huez, which turned out to be a bad idea because of the 900,000 screeming and crazy fans lining the 15.5 km route.  "I don't know that that is such a good thing for the Tour de France. I don't think it is safe. I think you'd agree. I'm sure the organizers agree," Lance said, and the organizers did agree.  Lance's time up the Alpe was the 2nd fastest in history, just one second off Marco Pantani's record.  Robbie McEwen, the sprinter's competition leader, did a wheelie when he crossed the finish line, which was a strange sight.  Lance goes hard.    Ullrich goes all out, but it wasn't enough.    Basso loses a lot of time.    It does look like Lance has the Tour in the bag, but he says the deciding day is tomorrow, a tough mountain stage.   
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
          This is from  urlLink Discovery Magazine . This is what they say about it:  --Today, Space Imaging's IKONOS satellite took a new image of the area covering Stage 16 of the Tour de France in the French Alps. The image of the 9.6-mile (15.5 km) race course from Bourg d'Oisans to L'Alpe d'Huez was collected at 11:52 a.m. (local time) from 423 miles in space. American Lance Armstrong won this individual time trial stage in 39 minutes, 41 seconds - the only rider under 40 minutes.   The image shows the winding switchback road to the town of L'Alpe d'Huez lined with cars, RVs and hundreds of thousands of cycling fans. The town itself is also packed with tents, vehicles and people.  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Did you know if you mix Daniel's name and Lance's name you get that! Cindi made up the Dance part. I added the Wilstrong part. (Daniel, has anyone ever said that before?)  Anyway, speaking of my nephew Dance, he was telling me about a  urlLink bicycle race  at  urlLink Heritage Park  last night. He rode faster than anyone else in his age group in a 20 mile ctriteirum. Hurray for Dance!  This post marks the 300th post to the PWWCR family blog! Huray for us! 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       First, I was shocked to find out this morning that Lance Armstrong's mom is my age. What?  Second, I am in awe of Lance's and the team's performances in each stage of this bike ride. They just seem to plan the work and work the plan. That is an inspiration for me with various personal goals. I'd like to be there watching in France during the third week, but not with that kind of crowd.  What is up with the announcers starting to proclaim victory with Lance? Doesn't anyone else get a little nervous with that? What if he falls? Or what if a silly spectator interferes? Aren't there still some variables out there? And there doesn't seem to be any kind of big time gap between the leaders that make me relax. Am I crazy or should I start the Lance dance now?!  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Squirt, I mean --- Sam did fine at puppy training. He performed to the "Let's Go!" command fairly confidently. He also embarrassed me with a new greeting. When the male instructor petted and talked to him at the start of class, he squirted a quick stream of liquid, let's just say, into the air. He did not hit any one. He was seated and leaning back a little, so the fluid just arched through the air with the greatest of ease. This happened one or two more times when various men in class petted him. No one was in the way.   Sam seemed oblivious to this new reaction. I'm guessing his male dog "marking" ability kicked into gear without the control factor as a natural part of puppy development. Again, never heard of that before, but it must be typical.   The command for this week is "Sit" and "Stay" with hand motions to communicate what we want --- that's the tricky part. And practicing in the heat is no fun, especially on little paws touching the pavement.  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Dick and Jane Remington will be traveling to Whittier and spending the week of August 17 - 24 to play with the granddog. A summer visit will permit some different activities. I am looking forward to introducing them to the wonder dog. I'm sure a family BBQ will be planned at our house. Hopefully, Daniel will give them an orientation to the Tour de France via video highlights.  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I think that I could stay awake easier in those early hours if Robin Williams was a regular with Phil and Bob. What a hoot this morning.  Can we put his name on the vote to the right?  
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, really? Lance Armstrong won today's stage of the Tour de France (making it 18 stage wins for the Texan) after beating Ivan Basso to the line as he did on Saturday's stage to Plateau de Beille.   This time, however, he took the yellow jersey from France's Thomas Voeckler because he lost more than nine minutes to Lance, and going from first place to 8th.  Jan Ullrich attacked on the 4th climb of the day (with six climbs total), a first catagory Col de l'Echarassson.  The German gained more than a minute on Lance, but CSC and USPS (Basso's and Lance's team) reeled him back in and he lost three more seconds in the end, putting him 6:54 behind Lance.  "Basso is riding so good that there is a chance I can lose time tomorrow," Lance said about the very difficult TT to Alpe d'Huez.  Other news:  Iban Mayo did not even start today's stage.  This was the kind of terrain the riders did.    Armstrong celebrates his stage win.    Tyler's back trouble (the spots). Read his journal entry about it  urlLink here .   
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Basso says he will only attack Lance if Lance shows any signs of weakness, which the Texan has not shown so far. "It's possible to win the Tour de France in one attack," Basso said. "Last year at Luz Ardiden, Armstrong won the race in one attack. I don't know if Armstrong will have a bad day. If he does, we will be ready. It's not worth it to attack just to gain 10 to 20 seconds."  However, Basso's teammates got injuries recently from crashes etc, so that's a disadvantage to Lance with his strong team always there for him.  Domitilla, Ivan's daughter, sits in a happy father's arms.    A new name, Andreas Kloden of Ullrich's T-Mobile team, is expected to be pretty high up in the overall standings in Paris ahead of Jan Ullrch, the team leader, if he keeps up his climbing abilities and doesn't fall behind in the TTs (time trials). 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Gravity Files, Outside Magazine--re-airing of stage 13 and a few of the Lance Chronicles. What will I do with myself today?  The Today Show seems sooooooooo unimportant [really when is it anything else].  Meanwhile in the real world--France--where the Postie Boys and their wannabe assumptive competitors are having a "rest" day.   urlLink      Looks pretty warm there. I am intrigued by the individual time trial coming on Wednesday--straight up a hill, 7.9% grade for 15 kilometers. Isn't Turnball Canyon about 6%?   Well, I think I still have a job. I'll go check. Rob wants to go for a bike ride sometime today.  
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Aitor Gonzalez (Fassa Bortolo) won Sunday's 14th stage of the Tour de France today after getting in a 10-man break and attacked 6 km from the finish (about 4 miles).&nbsp; Voeckler retained the overall lead, and Lance is still 22 seconds behind, with no major moves by any of the overall threats.&nbsp; Tomorrow (Monday) is a rest day.   As for Ivan Basso being on the podium in Paris, I was thinking of him being second (or third), but not first (because of Lance in the way).&nbsp; It would be nice to be in the leader's jersey, but we'll see where my life takes me.   Why does blogger change so much? It's hard to figure out how to do things another way so much. I think I figured everything out, though.  &nbsp;        
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I will be surprised if Basso wins. He has a history of miscalculations and mishaps. He also is not as good on the flats as Lance and is not expected to do well on the time trial. Yet many individuals in this race have not lived up to expectations and there is a lot of racing still ahead. We will see if Daniel's prediction is fulfilled. I do expect Daniel to be the Voeckler of the "le tour de france 2014".   
    
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I have really enjoyed the progress of Sam 2 in his school.  Keep it up Cindi ! !  Also enjoying the reports on the race, not that I can understand it all, Daniel,  Will be nice to see if your thoughts on the winners will be true.  Keep the information coming.   
    
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       You can get a Lance poster by Giro  urlLink here .    
    
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Lance won very difficult stage 13 to Plateau de Beille with Basso, the last stage's winner, took second right behind.  It was a very dramatic day with Jan Ullrich losing another 2:42 to Lance Armstrong, putting him 6:39 behind Lance.  Tyler Hamilton quit because of severe back pain, with others quiting also.  Iban Mayo almost quit today after being dropped on a lesser hill, but he was persuaded to keep going by his teammates, other riders, his manager, and Basque fans, but he lost almost 38 minutes to Lance.  Stage 9 winner, Tom Boonen, crashed on a descent, when some part of his bike broke apparently, and overall threat, Roberto Heras, also crashed on another descent, and he also finished, but his overall hopes are history.  Be prepared to see Ivan Basso on the podium in Paris.  Lance takes the stage ahead of Basso.    Jan Ullrcih loses more time.    The yellow jersey is still on a very hard-working Voeckler.    Tyler Hamilton quits with back pain.    Mayo almost quits.   
    
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Samson #2 did really well today on his training task of "Let's go." He stayed on my left side with slack in his leash...Not pulling nor dragging behind and a minimum of puppy play. I was very encouraged and he almost seemed proud, too. We got a "training collar" (formerly known as a choke chain), which seems to help the process. We practice with him each day, so it was a thrill to see such progress today.  &nbsp;  Sam marched around in his new pool yesterday. Just a molded plastic shell thing that cost hardly anything and can't be bitten and deflated. Glen went in, too, to demonstrate how to splash and enjoy the water. It's deep enough for Sam to be in to his chest, but shallow enough for him to step/climb in and out. The fun increased with the addition of pool toys: a little floaty ball and a piece of wood from somewhere in the garden. He pawed and chased those around and seemed to have fun. Soon he'll be ready for an actual swim somewhere. I had fun, too, watching him cool off.  &nbsp;  The Tour de France was good again today. I enjoyed the ending very much. The rain is something else! Can't imagine riding that fast, downhill, in the rain. I'd be tortured. It's fun having Daniel here some days to watch, too.    
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Lance Armstrong showed just why he is a five-time Tour de France champion when he took second on today's stage, gaining two minutes and thirty seconds on his closest rival, Jan Ullrich, and 3:27 behind Tyler Hamilton, and 2:57 over super-climber and ex-teammate, Roberto Heras, now on the Spanish team Liberty Seguros.  In the overall standings, Thomas Voeckler (Brioches la Boulangere) made a huge effort and kept his yellow jersey for another day.  It was a day of much rain, making the descent dangerous, but luckily, no one crashed, and at the end the roads were dry.  The posties (in the rain) made the pack go in many groups  because of their hard pace.  Lance kept that pace and even sped up when his last teammate was through and made many suffer more.  Ullrich was just having his day in the first day of the mountains in his huge gear.  Lance could have won the stage, but he is trying to help Italian Ivan Basso's mother fight cancer. "We've been friends for a long time, and off the bike we're trying to work a little bit on his mom's situation, to try and see if she can win the fight against cancer," Armstrong said.  Basso wins the stage ahead of Lance.    Ullrich has trouble.    Hamilton also struggles.   
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       What an exciting morning of racing. What an effort by team postal. Another example of how important working as a team is in cycling. 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The Tour started out with 55-degree weather with rain causing many crashes, but now it is up to 100 degrees, "But I don't think anyone is complaining after the [cold and rain-sodden] first week," said Lance Armstrong, defending Tour champ.  Because of this (and on-and-off back pain), Paris-Roubaix (a "Classic" with many cobblestones) winner Swede Magnus "Maggy" Bäckstedt, and also the heaviest rider in the peloton, had to call it quits.  As for the good things of the stage, there was a three-man breakaway that turned into a chase group when one the the three attacked (Frenchman David Moncoutié) and won the stage.  The overall standings remained the same with the Texan ahead of all his rivals.  As for Saturday's extremely hard stage, he said, "It's very nasty. I think they should take it out. It's a violation of our human rights. I love it," showing his Texan behaivor all around.  But for tomorrow, Iban Mayo is expected to attack because it is in front of his home crowd (the Basque).         
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Tyler Hamilton, #11 in overall standings in the Tour after Stage 10 is pictured here with his 9 year-old golden retriever Tugboat.      Tugboat has been sick for some time,  diagnosed with cancer this week, passed away in France.  
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It looks like 3 guys withdrew from the Tour today. Watched Sébastien HINAULT get taken away on a stretcher and ambulance. Yesterday a guy just ran out of juice, stopped, and handed-off his bike to a mechanic and got into the team car. Not to indulge in too much schadenfreude!  I am looking forward to seeing LA pull out of his #6 position. He was in good spirits yesterday, joking with the press.  
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Richard Virenque won the first mountain stage (and also the longest stage) of this year's Tour de France, while the overall standings have not changed much because Lance's main rivals finished not long after him. Thomas Voeckler retained the overall lead, but only because of his teammates' help.  The Frenchamn Richard Virenque wanted to win on this day because it is  Bastille Day in France (July 14). He was in a two-man breakaway with Axel Merckx (Lotto Domo), but the Belgian could not hold Virenque when he upped the pace.  He says that he will really pay for the effort in the days to come like he did in last year's Tour when he took the yellow jersey and the King of the Mountains (KOM) jersey. He only took the KOM jersey this time.       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Beth has Brianna for the whole day tomorrow. Watch for non-tour pictures coming to this blog. I would expect that they involve swimming or playing with water. You can see the temp on the side bar to the right. hot, hot, hot. 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This is Robbie McEwen's second sprint victory this year.  There was a two-man breakway that lasted most of the ride, and unlike most of the breakways so far this year, they were certain of a victory, but the peloton reeled them in just in time for the sprinters to take over.  This is a little sad to watch, but at the same time, it's one of the best things in bike racing.     McEwen sprints to the finish line.     The General Classification (GC) remained the same.  Answer to Cindi's Question: A person that you've never heard of can take the leader's jersey because of a smart breakaway like the guy on Brioches la Bolangere did.  The favorites are not scared because they know they will get the time back in the mountains, which start tomorrow.  Lance says there should be an individual time trial (ITT) so that this won't happen, and only real contenders will get the jerey, but Jean Marie Leblanc (the guy in charge of the Tour) likes to have it the way it is.  In order to have a exciting finish, he makes the real action  (the mountains, not the crashes) at the end of the Tour with a sprinter's first part of the race.  So anyway, it's because of a breakway with the times so close together already. 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, we took Sam to the first day of dog training last night. And of course he napped in the mud to cool off prior to class and dirtied his new school fur. Off we went, helping him into the back seat (he doesn't quite get the jumping in part), and wondering what the evening would be like.   He is riding in the car well, now --- staying seated most of the time. It helps that he is big enough to see out the window, I'm sure. The evening went well. He was very timid...tail between his legs, ears low, and body slouching down, when we arrived. He stayed very near to us and sat and looked around. To others, he seemed well-behaved, but we know the truth.   He was nervous about the first day of school. Would the others like him? Soon enough, he was sniff-greeted by a few others...the 9-week old rotweiler (how do you spell that?)and another BIG lab. The rot puppy was the only dog smaller than him, and her name is ---of all things---Delilah! Ha. Samson and...well, you get the picture. Sam stayed calm, sitting/or laying/lying/lieing (grammar patrol --- help!)and watching...often facing the wrong way for the instruction.   Then came the first walking on a leash practice with Glen. Well, he made great improvement by the end of the evening. Enough said. The end of class is "free play." All the owners let go of the leashes and the dogs are allowed to interact. It's fun to see.   Sam seemed to get along OK, though he seemed uncertain at first. Then he romped gleefully with a...Great Dane! A sight to see. Quite the size contrast. The Dane got so tickled he started to prance/pounce on/at/around Sam. Sam just flattened out on his belly on the ground...like a pancake or like someone about to be arrested after a car chase. No one was hurt. I was nervous, but laughing.   And home we came. Sam got a big drink of water and fell sound asleep. 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       In order to keep harmony in our home, I am compelled to blog now and then. I do enjoy reading the family blog, though it seems to have a single focus these days. I've been safely coasting along in the family blog peloton, but now I'm breaking away to post again. My Mac cannot support the posting, and I'm now using the PC. So I'm back from the silent period of reading and not responding.  I am enjoying the Tour de France. Yesterday was a day off, and I was glad to catch up on other responsibilities. I found myself anxious last night, though, to watch the next stage. To me, it's been like reading a good book...a real page turner. The kind where I can't put the book down because I want to know what will happen in the next chapter, er -- stage. I enjoyed the stage today. The countryside and towns, the blue sky with puffy clouds, and the crash! What? Again. Yes, and this time the cameras seemed to capture the whole thing. A guy hit a thing in the middle of the road and some one hit him and tumbled hard. The second guy already had a BIG bandage on his forearm. I'd be thinking..."I could be on a swim team. This is crazy! Neosporin and an Advil please. And airlift me to the nearest...hot tub! But no, not the mighty cyclism warriors. Back on the mighty steel (or some speedy alloy?)steed with wheels and charge forth. Just for the chance to wear polka dots? Or some other color shirt. Just go to the closet and pick one! What's the big deal? [I'm kidding. Of course, I get it and know it is not just to wear a new shirt!]. Can someone, however, explain to me how a guy who's name I never hear mentioned day-to-day during the race ends up keeping the yellow jersey? How does that work exactly? I am clearly missing something simple and obvious to the family experts, no doubt.   
    
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Monday is a day off for Lance and the TdeF riders as they will fly to the next starting point. The schedule says they will be in Limoges for their rest day.   urlLink      Now, according to Daniel, the interesting thing about Monday's coverage is that they will show footage of the race and the the significant events to this point. This will include a re-showing of the crashes up to this point. They will likely show these several times over. And, Daniel will come over early to see it all! 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Thor Hushovd won Sunday's stage 8 of the Tour de France, after the field caught multiple breakaways (in the second picture you can see one of them), and Thomas Voeckler retained the overall lead.  There was a crash at the back of the peloton, due to a dog crossing the road at the wrong time, but no one expected to have any affect on the race was hurt.  The overall was not affected much at all.  Read more  urlLink here .          The riders traveled by plane to the next stop for tomorrow's rest day. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Get your 2005 cycling calendars now with  urlLink World Cycling Productions !  Only $15 each.  History of Tour de France or current cycling.         
    
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Stage seven of the Tour de France was won by Italian Filippo Pozzato, who was in a breakway that broke away at 2 km to go and opened up a 15-second gap.  He is a Tour first-timer and the youngest rider in the race.       There was another breakway that was caught well before the finish line with just two riders, Dutchman Erik Dekker and Belgian Thierry Marichal.       The overall standings remained the same with Voeckler retaining the overall lead 9:35 ahead of Lance, 10:11 over Tyler, and 10:30 ahead of Jan Ullrich.   There were more crashes, but the main contenders were not hurt. 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, Tyler Hamilton crashed again, but at least he hasn't broken any bones yet.  He landed on his back and got "significant bruising", as a Phonak team spokesman put it.  Lance Armstrong did crash in an earlier pile up (just 14 km from the start), but is fine except for a few burns from a tire.       As Glen said, Robbie McEwen, the guy leading in the sprinter's competition, crashed, has bad abrasions on both hips and arms, and is out of the Tour.   Tom Boonen won the stage in a crash-marred uphill finish.     Voeckler is still the yellow jersey.     Read more  urlLink here . 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I found this easy to understand  urlLink FAQ section  at  urlLink cycling news.com  wtih some of the basics for us who are new to the T de F.  
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       After the massive pile-up at the 1 KM mark, I saw Robbie McEwen's leg and thought--"hamburger". The creative writing staff on the official T de F web site put it this way: ". . .Robbie McEwen who slid along the tarmac long enough for him to tear a big hole in his green knicks and make his powerful quadriceps look more like a pizza cooked up with the dangerous combination of speed and gravel."  It was amazing to see Juan Antonio Flecha so far in the lead for such a long time. What happened demonstrated how this is so much a team sport and not an individual thing. When the peloton swarmed down on him and passed him--I think it was at 8 KM before the finish--it looked like he had all of his energy drawn out of him. PL said it looked something like predatory birds swooping down on him as they approached. It was dramatic.  I hope we get the real commentary from Daniel today. Even though he didn't come over today to watch, he will have the inside track. Daniel--you might want to come over to watch the expanded coverage later today!  
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Wear Yellow--  The yellow wrist bands have arrived. I orderd 10, so come by to get yours soon.   The  urlLink Lance Armstrong Foundation  is raising money through the sale of yellow wrist bands and its  urlLink WearYellow, LiveStrong  compaign. I have bought 10 of them for anyone who want to wear them.  The cancer connection in our familiy is in our own grandma Pete who is a two time cancer survivor.  
    
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       There was a five-man breakaway that gained 16:30 over the field, but the field got back four and a half minutes by the time the break crossed the finish line because there were strong winds keeping the peloton from going too hard. Stuart O'Grady won the stage, but it was Thomas Voeckler (Brioches La Boulangere) that took the yellow jersey, who was fourth in the breakaway, and started the stage three minutes down on Lance, by more than nine and a half minutes.   (Armstrong is not concerned about him, and will not fight to get the jersey back too soon.)  It was another raining day, and there was a mass pile-up half-way through the stage, which took down three of Lance's teamates, two sprinters, Alessandro Pettachi and Robbie McEwen,  Bradley McGee, and Roberto Heras, a rival of Lance, but Lance himself was not hurt.    Top: you can see that the wind was quite fierce in the picture here because of how the riders are all single-file across the road; bottom right:  Portugal's Jose Acevedo, and the Spanish trio of Jose Luis Rubiera, Manuel Beltran and Benjamin Noval go down in a crash, bottom left: the new yellow jersey.                             
    
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Someone was asking about women in professional cylcing on Sunday. There is a  urlLink Women's Giro 'd Italia  that you can read about at the link.   Yes, Steve: I left a really good comment on your post. It didn't show up, so I tried it again. Didn't work a second time either. Just know that they were really smart! 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       my last blog states there are two comments, but when I check there are none there????  
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today was the Team Time Trial that USPS won last year and moved Jan Ullrich 43 seconds farther away from Lance.  Today?  Well, because of a new rule, Ullrich only got 40 seconds farther from the yellow jersey! What I mean is, US Postal won, and Ullrich's T-Mobile team took third. Good news, and another one of Lance's rivals, Tyler Hamilton, his team took second, more than one minute down from USPS.  I guess the new rule says that you can only lose 20 seconds from next team up, so Tyler just lost 20 seconds to Lance.  Lance now leads the Tour de France, although he doesn't want to defend it yet because it would strain the team too much for the mountains in front of them.  It was a rainy day with a tail wind, which made it very difficult to stay upright on the paint on the road.  Tyler Hamilton's team, Phonak, lost 3 or 4 guys due to this (and puntures), so they only finished with 5 guys, the bare minimum.  Here you can see how wet it was for US Postal, which had the worst weather.  Lance seems like a really happy guy!          
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       neither rain nor snow nor fallen comrade will deter lance from winning today. not bad for a postal rider. 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This likely is what those cobble stones look like up close:     They are available from  urlLink Belgain Block Co.  
    
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, someone did lose their Tour hopes on stage three's cobbles. Thankfully, it wasn't Lance, but a Basque threat, Iban Mayo, lost almost four minutes due to a crash on the cobblestones of Belgium and France (and Jan Ullrich's T-Mobile Team putting a lot of effort in at the front to make sure he wouldn't reach the pack).  Jean Patrick Nazon took the stage in a sprint, while Robbie McEwen took the leader's jersey.  He is no threat to Lance when the race hits the mountains.  Tomorrow's stage is a team time trial which US Postal won last year and is expected to win again this year. 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       "I think everybody is worried about the cobbles - even the riders who are good on them are worried," Armstrong said.   "You could be involved in a crash and that would mean the end of your Tour. Somebody's Tour will be over on Tuesday and I could be one of those people."   Are you nervous yet? 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       on July 6. 16 kilometers from Brussels, Belgium. The race is 210 kilometers to Wasquehal.     urlLink     
    
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       To blog users:  I am finding that almost none of you have made yourselves known on the "Contributors" section on the right side of the blog.  In order for us to know you better, I think this would be a great way to do it.  To blog administrator:  When looking for the word "comentary" at dictionary.com, it says, "No entry found for Comentary" and says below, "Did you mean Commentary?" And yet this "word" appears on the side of the blog.  Another thing:  I notice on google.com that the "Googe" thing on top of the page is changing a lot.  Today for Independence Day, for instance, has a red, white, and blue Google icon with an eagle, but on the blog it is always the same.  Is there any way to change that?  Just curious. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today AG2R's Jaan Kirsipuu won the first stage of the Tour de France.  Fassa Bortolo's Fabian Cancellara retained the overall lead, while Lance takes third place overall.  It was a cold and wet day, normal for Belgian racing, and had numerous crashes like I had predicted, but at least no overall contenders were seriously hurt (or was that a bad thing?).  Yes, Tyler Hamilton crashed again, but he got back on his bike immediately.  OLN advertises its race coverage as "The Cyclism", and after watching a day's worth of racing, I really want to go out and do something like what the pros just did.  Yesterday I sort of did a short time trial, and after I was finished riding, I was still thinking about it and completely forgot about what I was doing (and wanted to either keep riding or blog something.  Oh, the Cyclism! 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I posted news about the Tour de France.  However, I forgot to write about an important aspect of it--I saw it at Glen and Cindi's house with wonderful hospitality.  It was a wonderful time breakfast at their house with Mom, Dad, Beth, Steve, Kyle, Rob and Grandma.  Too bad Dick and Jane couldn't be there.  Thanks again! 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Lance took second place in the prologue while his biggest rival, Jan Ullrich, took 16th!  Good news so far.  Here's lance on his TT bike.  The most critical stage, a time trial, is on l'Alpe d'Huez, and lance rode it at least ten times in May to "learn every centimeter of it."  There was one crash on the course when the rider started pedaling while he was on a corner (no one worth mentioning).  Actually somenone had a worse crash before the Tour even started when he was riding the course to know the corners as well as possible.      Eddy Merckx was the best rider that ever lived and won a third of the races he participated in.  He is also a good friend of Lance Armstrong and says he should try the to break a record for going as fast as possible in an hour around a track (Eddy did that).   All the pro cycling magazines have Lance on them because he is the favorite and he can break a record (and tradition).  Here are a few  of them:                   
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Graham Watson is making a book of his photographs called "The Landscapes of Cycling"  and can be learned more about  urlLink  here .         For another book photographed by Graham, click  urlLink here .        Graham Watson also has made coasters with his pictures on them.      
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The 2004 Tour de France is meant to be an on-the-edge-of-your-seat route.  It does not favor our Lance Armstrong, but is meant more for an all-climber type. It does not have a long time trial (TT) prior to the mountains, which Lance has in the past dominated, and in the team time trial (TTT), the maxium a team can lose is 2:30, no matter how bad they are so that they are able to get the yellow jersey.  Lance has a good team for the TTT and is the favorite to win as they won last year, and ONCE (now Liberty Seguros), their greatest rival, in it isn't as good as they used to be (they finished third in 2003).  In 1999 or 2000, Lance gained 4 minutes with the TTT on his greatest rival.  So for the overall classification, we have Lance Armstrong, the five-time Tour winner; Jan Ullrich, the five-time Tour runner-up (and won in '97); Tyler Hamilton, who placed fourth last year with a broken collarbone, and Iban Mayo, the Basque that won on Alpe d'Huez last year and has made life difficult for Lance in pre-Tour races both this year and last year.  Some other possibilities for podium places are Haimar Zubeldia, which came in fifth in front of Mayo last year, and is on his team, and Roberto Heras, which was on Lance's team starting in 2001.  From right to left, that's Iban Mayo, Lance Armstrong, Jan Ullrich, Jose Luis Rubiera, and Haimar Zubeldia.     Key stages are: the stage to La Mongie, the Alpe d'Huez TT, Plateau de Beille, and the final TT in Besancon.  For the King of the Mountains competition (KOM), the favorite is Richard Virenque that won 6 times already and is aiming for a record-breaking 7th title.  Allesandro Petacchi should be a good rider in the sprinter's competition, which he won in the Giro d'Italia along with a record-breaking eight stage wins. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Do you want to be able to watch the 2004 Vuelta a España like you watched the Tour de France?   urlLink Sign this petition  and hope to make an influence on those fishers at OLN. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Steve had a great time in Hawaii. There was time for play and time for psychological stuff.  My friend Kirk Schneider invited me to fill in for an ill speaker. That allowed me to talk about my work with children. I was able to attend two workshops, one on psychotherapy with males and one on psychotherapy with couples. Both were helpful and validating. It is nice to be reminded that you know something and that others are interested in your sharing. I value these experiences very much. I enjoyed the time in the ocean and at the beach. Audrey asked what was my favorite part of the trip? I first thought of all the things we did and tried to decide what I enjoyed the most. What I realized later was that it was having time for such a trip. Having time for myself, Beth and I, or with family feels like it is in such short supply. Much less than I like. So having the time for myself, Beth and family was the best part.   
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Hilton Village from the Beach.   Dancers at the Polynesian Cultural Center.   Wind swept ladies at Pali Point overlook.   Visiting the Battleship Missouri.   Visiting the Dole Pineapple Plantation. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Here are a couple of pictures from our trip.   The ladies on arrival.   A view of a rainbow from Beth's and Steve's room.   Hunauma Bay where all four of us got wet and Steve, Beth, and Audrey snorkled.  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       oh yeah, i tried to put my picture in my profile, but failed. am i allowed to do this blog masters? and if so, how can i make that happen? 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       today, after work, i spied a three day old piece of meat in the fridge that was begging to be cut up, and joined with a tortilla to become a burrito. i gladly, guiltlessly obliged, and it was pleasing to the lord. however, later in the evening, glen and cindi (my landlords) returned home from puppy bootcamp with the apparent goal to consume leftover foods from the refridgerating unit. in a sad turn of events, it turns out that i had eaten glen's intended supper! the guiltless glee that had filled my tummy quickly turned to shameful sorrow. glen had to settle for a nasty frozen pizza instead of a steak dinner. for this, i am eternally sorry, from the bottom of my cold, black heart. i'd like to buy you another london broil glen, if i may.  i like telling sam "down" after he's already decided to lay down. it makes me feel accomplished, and fulfilled.   i got a postcard today from my pen pal in hawaii. it was beautiful, and made me jealous, and proud all in the same instant. can't wait to hear more stories.  looks like you can download speeches from the d.n.c. for free at itunes music store. i'm thinking of downloading them, and playing them when i've already tried counting sheep at night, in order to induce sleep. (yawn)  peace 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Sam II goes to his fourth puppy class tonight. I have been doing "down" with him all week with little to no success. Sniff, sniff. I tell him down and wave my hand appropriately and all that. He looks at me and doesn't move. So, I go to level two...pull his paw out and roll him gently to that same side. Then I get big results. He resists, pulls back, and nibbles my hand. I wrestle him to the ground and say "Good dog." What?!! Yes, I've battled him to the ground everyday this week for the sake of "down."  Is Sam testing me? Am I doing something confusing to him? Does it normally take more than a week to "get down?" And dear, sweet Ashley. She's come on the scene a few times. Sits promptly next to me when I tell Sam to sit. Goes down with grace and beauty in perfect Olympic form when I tell Sam to do the "down." Ugh. So he figures if she's got it, he's off the hook.  Glen, oddly enough, observes from a distance and just laughs. With me of course. Well, I leave for Minnesota on Wednesday. He'll have the bulk of the training time this week. We'll see how it goes. This week's command will probably be something easy like "leap on the sofa" or "chomp on an avocado" or "look sincere" or "beg for an ice cube" (his new treat of choice).  Livestrong. Laughstrong. Downstrong, please. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yaroslav Popovych signed for the Discovery Channel team (US Postal next year) for 2005-2008.  "I'm really excited to get Yaroslav on the team," said team director Johan Bruyneel. "He's a young rider who has shown his talent on numerous occasions. ... I'm sure he still has a great margin of progression (to make), and I see him as a future contender for the Tour de France in a few years. It's great to have a big talent like him joining us. He really believes in our program."   "Riding for the Discovery team in 2005 has been my ultimate dream," Popovych said. "It's a team in which I believe in and a team where I'm sure to receive the proper education from directors such as Johan Bruyneel and Dirk Demol to become a three-week stage racer."   The team is also trying to get American Levi Leipheimer to sign, but no results yet.     No OLN? OLN won't be showing the Vuelta a España as much as usual.  They said, "Our current plan is to air a one-hour highlight show of the Vuelta on October 27 at noon Eastern time."  Bummer.  At least we shouldn't miss Lance because of it because he has never ridden the Tour and the Vuelta the same year.  Lance's fan club website,  urlLink thepaceline.com , says that the interview continues today on OLN. I was wondering if the OLN people (Glen and Cindi) know about this at all and when it is. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The PWWCR blog welcomes Jeff Barneson who has responded to the invitation I sent for him to join our blog. I hope that he will weigh in on the Lance mania and other bicycling chatter here. AND, I hope he is inspired to produce his own brilliant blog.   I told another friend about the blog, he got inspired and  urlLink blogged about his recent trip to Cancun .   BlogStrong; LiveStrong  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Stuart O'Grady won the   urlLink HEW Cyclassics Cup race in Germany  and just beat last year's winner Paolo Bettini.    
    
    
</post>


</Blog>