<Blog>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       At work we were just notified that once the contract ends we would be put immediatly into OEM (hardware) and customer service skills...  Basically the severence that we were offered because we were being laid off is horseshit.  The whole point of that fucking package was so that we could have a comfort zone while we looked for new work.  How exactly im going to look for work while working a full fucking shift all day.  I really hate how theyve jerked us all around for the last three years.  just totally lying, and fucking us around.   -- Jax, signing off. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, there are some new, almost confirmed rumours floating around work today.   First, a friend of a friend is coming back from pregnancy leave,  she is due to start training (OEM) this monday at 11am...  this is from her lips.  Secondly a supervisor told an agent that around thursday or wednesday of this week an email would go to the floor telling of the status of future contract...  Thirdly A source that shall remain nameless.. the workers in the building have been begging for two weeks alone in the building to replace the decrepit elevators...  Fourthly... a local political figure said in "confidence" that stream employees had a 99% chance of having a small amount of time off as opposed to the paid lovefest we were expecting.  its also an election year...  what does this lead to?  Well, the OEM option, coupled with the Sirius radio option comes to mind.  not one, but two full contracts... sigh.  Im not sure how i would deal with that.  I hope that i get a contract where i can make some bonus again,  i need the dollarz.  but there is definatly something coming down the pipeline.   I hope we get some time off.  -- Jax, signing off. 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, There is a new rumour from a reliable source.  Apparently We arent even going to have any time off once msn expires, we are supposed to go directly into training for the next contract... I hope this isnt true. i really want the summer off.  I wouldnt be totally adverse to a new contract, but why cant it be at end of the summer?   
    
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, the rumours are getting hot and heavy at work. The main ones inolve the new contract supposadly coming in...  its supposadly an sattelite radio called sirius radio.  which wouldnt be bad.  of course id rather it would wait until the summer was over.  There is a confirmation that they are going to tour the building on june 10, 11.  Add to that the fact that the building is getting a make over in our absence, and the elevators are being replaced.... well I think that the gig isnt totally up.. Darn.  Well, i kinda hope things get better, but i kinda wanted out at the same time.  Im having mixed feelings. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       well lowell is the new acting leader.  oh fearless leader!   kathryn is leaving today, the usual email went out about how she loved us all and what not.  nothing really to report today. 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, another day down in the salt mines.  The news announcement hit.  no big deal, it wsa just about the name change.  phew!  people were scared it had something to do with a new contract, of which there is none in sight.     Still 40 calls in que...  which sucks.  they caught that sassar worm writer.  which is ok, but i feel kinda sorry for him.  even tho im shoveling his shit he did it for his mom.  so what ya gonna do? 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, today was another lovely day.   we had que (which means lots of people waiting) all day long.  the damn sasser worm has the nuts coming out of the woodwork...  There was cake, and a few spatterings of baloons.  Basically they announced the new corporate name and logo.  Since stream was sold by solectron to ECE we have been waiting for this.  the name is still stream, but the logo changed.  its sort of a mod 60s look.  very bubbly and colourful on a white background.  the cake was cheap, and it had the logo on it.  there were rumours about some sort of annoucnement on the news.  god i hope its about the name change. if i have to spend one more hellish summer in this hellhole ill kill someone. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well. this blog is basically going to be a day to log of what happens here at work.  Now the reason this is of interest is that work is gonna be gone as of may 28th, (thank god)    
    
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, we have an update loyal listeners.  Allans going to be working MSN again...  groan.  Basically MSN's india offices "cant handle" the call flow and we are going to be working msn for the foreseeable future.  now what this has to do with Indias recent elections, leading to a coalition communist government have to do with this is a mystery to all but the most astute of my loyal listeners.  apparently call centres are fleeing from India like its the mutiny all over again. oh well, hi ho, hi ho, its off to work i go.  -- Jax, signing off. 
    
    
</post>


<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      well, I baught a pair of shorts last night.  cute little baby blue board shorts.  they look damn good.  :-)  Im so surprised and delighted they fit!  i went to wallmart, tried them on, and then baught them.  it wasnt a hunt for something that fit....  I didnt have to shop around, find a store that sells the "big" clothes, nor did i have to shop around these precious few stores for the best prices or what looks moderatly fashionable.    Its been such a pain, all the "big" clothes are like something farmer fred would wear. and the colours are bland, and well they are just horrible.  the freedom of just going to a great big store (and honestly, im anti mega store for ethical reasons)  but going to that store and just buying a pair of nice cute shorts was just the coolest thing!  ;-)  Well, this is jax signing off
     
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ok, so, i weighed in, and I'm now 423pds!  thats a further ten pounds!  exellent!  also I was trying on walmart pants (previously far too small for me to wear) and they were fitting!  woo hoo, im like a former porn star, dropping X's from my title every day!
     
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, ok.  I guess my stats are good to have on this.  Im Male, 26 years old (born nov 15 1977) I am 5'11' and i weight somewhere around 433pds. This is a bit excessive, i know, thats why the atkins.   I'm going to take this diet and get down to a svelt 200pds of lean mean fucking machine!  ;-)  so far I have actually lost around abouts 30 pds on Atkins, I started out at 456 or 460... and in the month or so since ive been on atkins I've lost quite a bit.    Some of the effects of Atkins on me:  I've lost 30 pds, about 10 pds a week.  I'm not hungry.  I have much more energy  My heart doesnt pound in my ears when i climb stairs  My penis has grown an inch longer (I thought this was a myth, but apparently for every 30 pds you lose you gain an inch in length)  I dont get depressed like i was getting   daily highs and lows in energy dont happen, i dont get the midday sleepies anymore  I dont get the headaches I used to get  my mind isnt as cloudy in the morning as it used to be.  Now, there are some "negative" effects...  Im always thirsty  (dont mind it)  My bowels arent as regular as they were, but im not constipated.  there are eating limits (i want to drink ice cold pepsi.)  te cravings were bad at first, the sugar, and the caffeine were bad for the first week or so.  Luckily I had been trying to cut caffeine out of my diet for the last few months anyway (it makes me jittery) so when i cut cold turkey at the begining of the diet it wasnt too big a shock to the system.  the sweets however were another thing.  i was a big baker, i loved making and eating sweets. the cravings for sweet went away (not all the way) the first week.  so there we have it, my experience thus far.  thus endeth the lesson. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      well, this is my first post.    Basically im going to keep this updated with my life, and  effects of going on the atkins diet. 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, Ive been feeling so good that ive started to consider working out...  the problem is I do not want to go back to the gym... not yet at any rate.  I want to start there when i actually look a helleva lot better.  for now I want to get going at home.  Doing stuff with weights and resistance.. Now of course I have no idea what im doing, so im going to have to research.    Oh, my father is also feeling a lot better on the new WOL.  Which is good. when he gets down farther on the scale im going to get him working out too.   Hmm low impact cardio... -- Jax, signing off.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      well, ive finally talked my father into going Atkins.  He had been doing the dieticion "eat a leaf of lettuce" diet for the last little bit.  We started to diet at the exact same time...  he on his dietician enabled horror diet, and me on atkins.   Well, he was immensly skeptical about it from the begining.  he read the book, and he wasnt sure. he watched the tv shows, and wasnt sure.  he saw me lose about 50pds in a month and a half. he started to consider it  I baught a bunch of wal mart clothes (they dont make clothes to fit us usually) he started to consider it more.  Finally I talked him into it.  Hes already starting to feel the effects.  Hes in induction, and had his first energy burst the other day.   He cleaned the yard out for the spring, loaded the junk onto his truck, and hauled it away.  somethinghe would not have done a week ago.  Which is excellent.  Hes also had a positive result by way of his gas production (which had always been a problem)  Once he sees how positive this is for him it will totally win him over.  -- This is jax, signing off.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, i did my weigh in.   I went down another 6pds.   I thought because of my earlier indescretions I wouldnt lose so much as an ounce.  Well, I lucked out and lost 6 which is excellent!  -- This is jax, signing off.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, i doubt ive lost anything this week.  after my little pie adventure earlier in the week (mothers day)  i just started getting back into ketosis.  which is ok, but i have to be more careful about carb loading.     but ive been very good since, eating the things i usually eat. so i wont have to worry too much.  its a slow down, not a stop  -- This is jax, signing off.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, last night aside from the cake i was a good boy.  had some stir fry my grandmother made, heavy on the steak.  made plans for a carb free beef and broccoli.  which rocks.  im still a little hungry today, which is to be expected after the carb loading yesterday.  Luckily the plan says to carb load if you notice that your slowing down or stalled, and then go back into induction.  which is my plan.  The new shoes i got rock. sort of suede and no laces, very ncie, and when i wear my jeans they look vaguely like suede boots.  :-)  -- This is jax, signing off.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, I have good news and bad news.  Im down the 417pds.  Thats the good news.  the bad news is that i had some cake today, and chocolate yesterday.  Now this isnt a major setback or anything... it just means im slowed down a bit. prolly have to go into induction again.  but thats no problem what so ever. the only thing is i didnt enjoy the cake.  makes me feel like i ate a bowl of flour.  yuck... i dont know why i ate it, my will power is usually much higher than that.  oh well :-)  At this rate getting to 200 by my birthday will be easy.  this diet is absoutely tailored to me.  -- This is jax, signing off.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      You know, growing an inch in penis length in a month is a good thing.  :-D  -- This is jax, signing off.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      well another fine atkins day.  People are still snarky about dr atkins being dead.  sigh, people just suck.   -- This is jax, signing off.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ok, i did another weigh in...  I now weight 420pds!  woo hoo. lost 3 pds in 5 days.  which rocks  Also, im wearing my walmart pants.  they fit nice.  -- This is jax, signing off.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, im down to 395 pds. yay!!! yippee!!  now, the bad news, things are slowing down a tad. not really slowing down. but getting more difficult.  ive reached a spot that people dread.  the spot where my body likes to be weight wise.  now its well below what my goal is, and its not a good aesthetic weight.  SO I have to work a tad harder.  Right now whats typifying whats happening is a series of stalls.  Luckily Ive been responding well to carb loading when this happens.  The proces is to take a day and load up with carbs, and then go on induction the following week.  this usually gets the loss going again.  which is good.  After this hump things will go back to normal, but until then its carb loading/induction.  which i dont mind at all.  although a lot of the old food i used to eat I kinda find gross now. im going to have to see what i can do. -- Jax, signing off.
     
    
</post>


<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You know, over my boring summer Im thinking of doing something unique..  I want to either convert a car to run on vegetable oil, or I want to make a biodiesal maker.  It might be an opportunity to enhance my car technical abilities (currently a first level know nothing when it comes to cars.)  It would be a pretty neat project, and have real life effects on my community, and what not...  Hmm I think i shall research this more.    -- Jax, signing off.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You know, I've been thinking for awhile.  One of the things that is thrown in the faces of gays from the religious people is the ole nugget. Thou shalt not lie with mankind, as with womankind: it is abomination.  Now, what I've been thinking is that maybe its not so much to do with homophobia, but mysogany...  My train of thought comes from the fact that women were quite a bit less than men at that time.  It was almost as bad as women being livestock.  So basically if you look at the quote, especially since its surrounded with admonishments agains sleeping with the livestock..  Perhaps they meant not to lie with a man as woman, as in women are lesser, dont treat men as lesser?  Or something to that effect?   -- Jax, signing off.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Have any of you been reading metafilter lately?  yowza!   the things in there are just orwellian nightmares... students being expelled for "unpatriotic" poems?  Teachers being fired for not pulling down anti patriotic posters or art?  What the hell is going on down south?  -- Jax, signing off.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, have any of you heard of this Matrix thing?  No, im not talking Neo, the one.  Im talking about that new anti terrorist sorting device...  How close to thoughcrime is some of this stuff?  they had a component that would analyze the data and affix a terrorist quotiant to each person.  Now this would of course scan for non criminal activity, and criminal activity alike.  So theoretically if you read mein kampf (for isntance) and had a parking ticket on the same block as a KKK meeting place it would raise your TQ (terrorist quotiant)  All of this info would be put togeather and you would be judged.    Now, in theory this ability has been removed, but seriously, when ever has a genie been put back into a bottle?  Now this type of technology while beinign in and of itself. randomly coalating data, all of it thats already had, and putting it togeather.   The thing that makes me want to go out and buy a tinfoil hat is simple.  It fosters a paranoid reaction  "should i read this book?  how would it look on my report?"   It doesnt actively prevent freedom, it just makes you less likely to act in a free manner.  If i had to come up with an anaology, id call it pre emptive mcarhtyism.  The all seeing eye affixing a value and measurement on the individuals daily activies...  "Sir!  you are a communist!"  "I have not now, nor have I ever been a communist!"  "Ahh, but we have records that state otherwise, here on october fourth, your car was given a parking ticket two blocks from communist headquarters, and here, you obtained a russian english dictionary at the library, and here you were viewing the webblog of a notorious communist! and that sir, that marks you in our books!"  So knowing that everything we said, everything we did, no matter how random would be watched, sifted through and compared to "patterns" and your eventual behavior was judged, regardless of your activities or even actual affiliates.  Well what typeof atmosphere does that promote?  You may be free to read books shunned by the governmen, or visit websites unpopular with the particular regime.  But when you do each and every time its marked down against you, and so many hits, and bam, your out of the ballgame.  -- Jax, signing off.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, apparently Sonia ghandi is not going to become the prime minister of India... She is citing security concerns of her children, i wonder if the stock market crash had anything to do with it?  -- Jax, signing off.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, so apparently the Indian people have elected Sonia Ghandi and her party into power.  Revitalizing the Ghandi "dynasty"  This is accomplished by her alliance with the Indian Communist party...  Of course this crashed the Indian economy, Foreign investors who have recently been flocking to India because of its financial reforms and general cheap labour force are leaving India in droves, taking their money with them.  India had the largest stock market crash in its history.  so, we have a communist backed Congress party is close to ruling India, how communist do you think they can get India?  whats this going to do with all the recent hullabaloo about outsourcing?  How much does this effect the probability of an Indo Pakistani nuclear war in the near future?
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I saw the trailer for farnheit 911...  and all i can say is astounding.  I cannot wait to see the full film.  it looks like it makes a lot of connections. which the average man on the street isnt aware of.  its going to be good when this stuff hits the pop culture fan.  -- Jax, signing off.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>