<Blog>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, the workout yesterday was definitely not my best ever.&nbsp; We biked right after work, and everything was great until the last few minutes of the biking.&nbsp; I was suddenly exhausted for no reason (it's possibly time to re-evaluate my diet).&nbsp; Luckily we had the wind pushing us home!&nbsp; Then we had our swim class at the Y again, which is still going great!&nbsp; It would've been even better had I felt "tip top" yesterday.&nbsp; Our instructor is a very large man, name Dida (pretty sure I'm not spelling that right), from Germany.&nbsp; He definitely knows more about swimming than either of us, so I'm all ears!&nbsp; He wants Mike to try and swim without his wet suit and nose clip...Mike isn't&nbsp;a fan of the water, so he not too fond of these suggestions.&nbsp; I personally enjoy him wearing the nose clip, its fun for me to plug my nose and talk back to him.&nbsp; Although, now that we're swimming at the Y, the water is much deeper, so spontaneous laughter doesn't work so well anymore.&nbsp; I'd rather not drown myself for the sake of humor!&nbsp; Now that I've blabbed all kinds of senseless stuff today...&nbsp; I'll be out of town the next few days (headed to Dallas), so I'm not sure whether or not I'll get the chance to update.&nbsp; I'm sure I'll have plenty to say by the time I get back!
     
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, so I'm wishing I had started this several weeks ago, but here goes anyway.  First of all, for anyone who doesn't know me.  My name is Kristi, I am 24 years old, and live in Abilene, TX.  My friends and family all know that I'm training for a triathlon right now, and I figured this is the best way to update everyone regularly.  Therefore, if you want to know about it--great, if not--that's great too!    As for my "journey", it began about 5 weeks ago.  My friend, and now training partner, mentioned he was about to begin training for a sprint triathlon.  I'm not really sure when it was that I began to lose my mind, but next thing I know, I'm searching for triathlons on the internet.  I came up with the Danskin Triathlon in Austin.  The estimated training time you should allow yourself is approx. 12 weeks, and the Danskin was exactly 12 weeks away the day I found it!  This must be fate!  So, here I am, 5 weeks down, 7 to go...  Here are the basic details of my tri:  First of all, its a "Sprint" Triathlon, which is a much shorter distance than say, an Ironman.  It starts with a 1/2 mile swim, then there's a 12 mile bike, and it finishes with a 5K run.  Sounds easy enough, right?  You bet!    Mike (my training partner), is competing in the Capital of Texas Sprint Triathlon in Austin on Memorial Day (2 weeks prior to mine).  He went to Austin two weekends ago and checked out both of our courses.  He also brought back photos of my course so I could get an idea of what it was going to be like.  It looks much more difficult that I had anticipated!  I've actually decided to go to Austin in a few weeks to try out the course.    We usually switch out our running and biking throughout the week, but I've had problems with one of my legs the past week and a half, so we've been biking and swimming alot lately.  I planning to try and run again tomorrow, so we'll see how that goes.  We started a swim program at the YMCA yesterday, and I feel really good about this.  It may be all in my head, but I felt like I was swimming more smoothly by the end of our first workout there.  I plan to stay in this program until the tri.    
     
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Mike had his triathlon today.  He is now an official Triathlete.  He text messaged me earlier and simply stated "Mission Accomplished".  We talked for a few minutes, but I won't get all the good details until I get back to Abilene.  He said it was really tough.  I am personally proud of him for completing his swim.  As I've said several times, that has been his primary struggle.  It would be so easy to quit during the race too.  There are people right there with you offering to help you out, get you out of the water, give you a floating device, you name it.  He also said the humidity was a killer.  More details to come on his...  Speaking of humidity, I've had my share of training in humidity lately.  I'm in Wills Point right now--this is "home".  I love home.  I've been home for a few days now and I've decided that this is the life.  Abilene is still paying me, but I'm hanging out at "home" doing a lot of nothing.  We had a Memorial Day family get together today...I did a lot of prep work etc...but other than that, all I did was get a nice tan (actually sunburn, but it'll be a tan by the morning).  I took off working out on Saturday, I mentioned it was time for a "rest day", this always helps me out.    Yesterday (Sunday) I got up fairly early (9 o'clock) and decided it would be best to work out before it got any hotter or any more humid.  My brother left his mountain bike at our parents' house for me to use, so I took off for a nice scenic ride in  Wills Point, TX.  I'm not a big fan of being "seen" in my hometown, but who in the world would suspect me to be riding a bike around town with pig tails in my hair (my hair is too short for a single pony tail).  I took off across town, taking back roads.  It was pretty windy out, but I didn't notice right away since it was behind me.  I was debating on a turn around point when I came across a boxer standing in the middle of the road staring me down.  This looked like a good enough spot for me.  Back to the house I go...The wind was pretty rough on the way home, but I obviously survived.  I was planning to run after the bike, but had somehow forgotten that I pulled a leg muscle on Friday--I remembered quickly once I started my bike ride.  After the ride, I went for a swim instead.  I have no clue how far or long I swam.  My dog (Daisy) cracked me up during my swim.  My dad let her outside while I was swimming laps, and she kept chasing me from one end of the pool to the other.  Every time I would come up to switch directions (I didn't bother to learn a flip-turn) she'd be there waiting on me.  It was hysterical.    Today I woke up a little later than I had planned.  I laid around debating on what to do, and goofed around for an hour or so before deciding I was going to run.  It was almost 11 by the time I headed up to the track.  Bad idea.  I feel like a broken record, but it was humid!  I decided on the track for two reasons. One, I wanted to do some speed drills and this would be the easiest place to measure my distance.  Two, it was hot and I was afraid I'd run further than I could handle (like Friday--you still have to make it home after the run).  I ran a few miles of drills which really seemed to help me out.  I suppose we'll see in the long run.    Yesterday was the "two week" mark from my tri.  My anxiety level is going up.  I'm more nervous than excited this week.  It makes me feel sick.  I really hope the excitement comes back next week.  I plan to work out really hard this week so that I can let up slowly next week.  Everything I've heard and read says to slack off on race week so that your body will be completely rested up for race day.  I'll have a hard time doing this, seeing as how I've grown up with the "practice makes perfect" motto...but I'm sure I'll survive.  
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm in Dallas now (actually Las Colinas or Irving)...I'm taking an extra long holiday weekend.  I won't return to work until next Thursday, I'm pretty excited.  I'm spending most of my weekend at my parents', but I usually stop off and stay with Jessica on my way through.  There's just something about sleeping on a couch (at my parents' house) that doesn't excite me...another month and I'll have a bed there again.  I got to Jessica's at about 6:30 today and was in dire need of a run.  I was pretty moody and running usually makes me feel better.  Jessica is fairly new to her neighborhood, but she has seen a park while driving that she really wanted to check out.  So, off we go to the park.  I'll admit, it looked really great--all nice and new.  Little did I know that this was going to be one of my more interesting runs.  We get out and walk a short distance to warm up a little and we come across a sign.  The sign explains the measuring system used at the park.  It says something about these stars along the path and how they mark every 1/4 mile, blah, blah, blah.  Great, so we can somewhat measure our run...Off we go!  We're running along, neither of us having the best start ever.  My calves are killing me today.  I think I need a "rest day".  After about 5 or so minutes, we finally pass our first star...we assume we're probably just running slowly(remember, the stars are supposed to be ever 1/4 mile--this should only take 2-3 minutes).  No surprise there.  We continue running...where are all the stars?  I seriously think we only passed 3 stars our whole run!  The track appears to make a complete circle, but it's hard to tell because it goes through trees and such.  We keep jogging along.  Every curve seems like it should be taking us to the outer edge of the park...none of them do.  It was like a never ending run.  We just kept going and going...like energizer bunnies or something.  We both wanted to know how it would end...would it circle, would it drop off?  I would guess that we ran about three miles...and we finally come to a dead end!  The stinking thing dropped us into a parking lot.  We went under two highways, through all kinds of woods, then it just dumped us!  We were just about to turn around at one point, but Jess was getting dillusional.  She saw a trashcan ahead and thought it was a water fountain, so we kept going.  Our conclusion -- the park is still under construction.  We ran all this way, we're tired, now we still have get back...We start back knowing how long we have to go, really hoping it doesn't get dark on us.  The only real excitement on the way back was us coming across a snake.  You'd think with both of us growing up in the sticks that we could handle a helpless garder snake...nope.  My instant reaction to anything that scares me--I gasp for air and point--I can't speak.  Jess sees the snake and runs behind me!  I wish the snake had chased us back...it sure was a long walk.    Here's a perk to my evening.  I felt a ton better after the psycho run.  I think all the extra walking relaxed me.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm down to 16 days actually, that would make yesterday 17...  The only work-out I got in yesterday was my swim.  At lunch yesterday I went to a local bike shop and checked out road bikes.  Mike has two bikes, a road bike and a mountain bike, we've been switching out the bikes for the past two months.  It's been great not having to buy a bike, but I think I actually want one now.  When I went to the bike shop, one of the guys that works there gave me all sorts of info on all kinds of bikes.  I know nada about bikes, much less road bikes.  We decided the first thing I should do is to come in a get sized for one.  This would require a little more time than I had, and I also needed to put tennis shoes and shorts on.  Storms hit again early in the afternoon, so I decided to go after work and get "sized" for a bike.  After a few hours, we figured out what all I needed, and I am now dying to have my own bike.  The first thing you'll notice about road bikes is that they seem ridiculously expensive.  They serve their purpose, by all means, but the price tag nearly kills me.  The second thing you'll notice is the tires.  They have these little bitty tires.  I've never been the best with balance (even on my own two feet), but with practice, I've learned to somewhat keep myself upright.  I tend to get wobbly on occasion, but that's nothing new.  Right now I'm in a dilemma of which bike to get.  There's a women specific bike that's pretty nice, and a unisex bike that has much more on it for a little more money.  I'm thinking that if I buy one, I should go ahead with the better bike.  For now, if anyone feels the need to contribute to my bike fund, feel free!
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday, the extent of my workout was biking...I felt fine on the bike ride until the end.  Suddenly my energy was gone.  I planned to run and swim after, but decided against this.  One thing I've learned, if I don't feel well, don't even attempt swimming.    I woke up early this morning and headed to the Y.  I was glad I waited until this morning because my swim we super.  I did a 200 warm-up, then a 200 kicking to start off.  After that, I did a 500 freestyle.  Rested for a few and did a 600 freestyle.  This pretty much took up my hour.  The "kid" that I previously talked about who works at the Y (and never shows in the mornings) was actually there today, but it was his last day.  He says he's moving, but I can't help but wonder if they're sending him on his way slightly early.  Anyway, he tried to get me to do some crazy dolphin kick thing on my back.  I couldn't help but look at him like he was a complete idiot.  My usual instructor (Dida) would never in a million years think of asking me to do something like that.  And he surely wouldn't try to teach me something new two weeks before my tri.  I told the kid that I didn't really want to do it.  He told me to try anyway.  He counted to three and I didn't move.  I felt kind of like a brat, but knew there way no way.  There was another guy swimming with me this morning, an older man who is also training for a tri.  He was a good student and attempted this maneuver, but couldn't do it.  I gave him an "E" for effort.  I, on the other hand, gave myself a big "F" for being a wimp and not allowing myself to look like a complete idiot.  The kid really should've known better.  Overall, this was one of my better swim days.  I didn't feel quite so winded during the distances.    I think Jessica and I decided against the 5K on Saturday, for unspoken reasons (she hasn't been running lately, she's been focusing on kicking rear in tennis).  We were trying to figure out the actual point in running the 5K anyway.  It's like, can I pay you $20 to let me run and you can give me a t-shirt.  Why don't I just go run 3 miles on my own and buy a t-shirt that I really like?  That makes more sense to me. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday afternoon storms decided to roll through town.  It was thundering and all sorts of horrible noises were coming from the sky, but no rain...that is, until I decided to walk out the door of my office.  Actually, I was shutting my computer down when I heard the rain start on the roof.  This is my luck.  It never rains until I'm ready to walk out the door.  Oh well.  I went home, hoping for a break in the storm so I could run, and luck did turn my way.  It went from a hot afternoon to a steamy one, but I didn't care.  I went to the park and got a three mile run in.  It was okay.  My times are still horrible, but my leg (the right one) is bugging me again, so I'm just glad to be able to finish.  Jessica (my old roommate) and I may do a 5K this weekend in Dallas.  The plans are still pending, but I think we'll do it.  This will give me more of an idea what my race day times will be like.  As you can see on my profile, the photo there is me, Mike, and Jessica at a 5K in April.  The adrenaline rush I get from the race atmosphere is enough to top out my race times.  I'm anxious to see how we do.  Sorry if I seem to be lacking personality today, I'm still recovering from a night of rest.  I'm attempting to get a real sleep schedule lately, but failing miserably.  After my run yesterday, I didn't feel well the rest of the evening.  So, I decided to hit the hay at 8:30 last night.  It's looking like one of those days where you don't feel bad, but you don't feel good either...hopefully you know what I mean.  My best descriptive word for this feeling is "blah", I feel "blah" today.  I think I'm going to try the sleep thing again tonight.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I forgot to mention yesterday that Mike only has one more week until his tri.  It's on Monday, Memorial Day.  He's supposed to be taking it easy this week, but I don't see him having the ability to take it too easy.  What would he do with all that extra energy?  Most days, he has more energy than should be humanly possible.    Yesterday was the best Monday ever!  We started our workout with a 10 mile bike yesterday.  The wind was pretty rough, but we survived!  Much less, we finished with our sanity.    After biking, I decided to do a bike/run transition.  This is also known as a "brick".  They say this term is used because your legs will be hard as bricks if you do this very often.  My interpretation of a "brick" is that my legs are as heavy as bricks when jumping off the bike and starting a run.  I haven't done a brick in a while, and I was planning to swim after, so I decided on a mile run.  It's crazy how hard this is!  My body seriously feels like my weight has doubled!  I somehow survived my mile.  Next we headed to swim class.  I was nervous that I had used all of my energy on my bike/run, but somehow found all kinds of extra energy for a great swim.  We swam for about an hour or more yesterday, although I can't remember how far...I've slept since then.     This was the first day I've ever actually done a swim/bike/run all in the same day (not in that order though).  My body is pretty tired today, but I need to be working super hard the next two weeks.    I also got up bright and early this morning and got my swim in for the day.  I swam for about 45 mins this morning, I must be really tired because I can't seem to remember how much I swam this morning either...  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I realize that neither of the above have much to do with swimming (my main objective for the weekend), but this is all I can think of when looking back on my weekend...Austin is a beautiful city.  I may be half crazy, but I loved it there.  The drive to and from was so great that the bad cell phone reception didn't even bother me!  This was one of the most peaceful weekends I've had in ages.    To start off, I got to Austin somewhat late Friday night.  Of course, there was plenty of time in there to get lost...you know me!  I planned to get good sleep Friday night, but I was visiting with a friend that I haven't spent much time with in years, so this didn't work out as planned.    I pop out of bed at 7:30 Saturday morning, change into my swimsuit and hit the road.  Luckily I left a with a little extra time, because I got lost (once again) in my friends neighborhood.  I love new cities.  I find it extremely exciting to explore and find out all there is to see and all the wonderful stores to shop.  My downfall is my horrible sense of direction.  You'd think with my car having a compass built in that I'd be fine...nope.  Anyway, back to my morning.  I finally find where I'm supposed to be swimming, and I'm right on time.  I had no idea there'd be so many women there.  I would estimate 200-300 women were there for the practice swim.  It could be more, as I tend to be an underestimator (not sure if that's an actual word).  I walk up, sign in, blah blah blah.  There was a time trial taking place just before my swim.  The swimmers were supposed to finish in less than 12 minutes...there's no way!  That's some pretty fast swimming (for me atleast).  When I first walked up, there were people holding three different signs to help and group us.  Basically they were going to send us in waves of "experienced", "intermediate", and "what the heck am I thinking" groups.  I put myself in the intermediate group.  I wasn't terribly worried about my ability to swim, it was more the idea of swimming in the lake that had me scared.  While they separated us into our group, we received a few transition tips, but nothing I hadn't already heard or read, although it was nice (and free).  The "experienced" swimmers were sent out first...there were only a handful of women willing to jump into this category.  Now it was time for me to strip down to my swimsuit and prepare for the water.  Here I am standing in the middle of hundreds of women all in their swimsuits, ready to jump in.  It was hard to be too scared because there were so many of us doing it.  There were buoys set up all in the water for us to take breaks holding onto.  We were told to swim to the first buoy, if we were tired take a break.  Then swim to the second, if you needed a break there, take it, but then swim back.  This would help you determine if you could complete the swim.  Okay, great, so now I have a way out.  It's finally my turn to step into the water.  The lake is springfed, so it was definitely chilly.  I let got in the water and let it come over my shoulders, within about 30 seconds, it was fine.  Here I go!  I swam to the first buoy and stopped for a second, mainly because I wasn't really sure how I felt.  I was somewhat tired, but not winded.  I rested for a second and started up again.  I passed the second one (it was pretty crowded), and rested again at the third.  This stop was similar to the first one, but I'm realizing by this time that I don't feel any different.  So, after the third buoy, I didn't stop again.  I think there were 6 or 8 total, I really don't remember for sure.  A few times during the swim, I quit concentrating on the swim and noticed how gross the water was, but mostly I only thought of my swim technique.  The swim was great!  I loved it!  Before the swim, I was talking with a girl in my wave and she compared an open water swim vs. the pool to running outside vs. the treadmill.  Afterward, I completely agree with this.  I am so excited now because I know I can do this part of the tri.  It's not nearly as intimidating now.    While I was waiting to swim I met another lady who invited me to tri course with a group early Sunday morning.  I decided this would much safer than attempting it myself.  After the swim, I decided to jog the trail around the lake so I could get a feel for my energy level.  I planned to run 1 or 2 miles, but ended up running 3, so that was nice.  It was still fairly early (maybe 10 o'clock), so it wasn't hot yet.    Saturday was a wonderful training day for me.  My energy and enthusiasm were both sky high.  After this, I took the rest of the day off of training, and decided to have a little fun in Austin.    Saturday night I was in bed by 10:45 (I probably shouldn't admit to that), this left me plenty of time to sleep before meeting at 8:30 to bike the course.  Things don't always work out as planned with me, lately sleep has become a huge factor for messing up my plans.  I woke up Sunday morning at about 10:45.  12 hours of sleep!!!!!  I couldn't tell you how long it has been since I've slept that much!  That would explain why I'm up typing after midnight, I'm nowhere near sleepy!  I decided I couldn't be completely lazy today, so I got my friend up and we decided to go for a neighborhood jog.  Today was much hotter and much more humid than yesterday.  I'm pretty sure the hills grew overnight too.  We took off in the neighborhood, neither of us knowing much about where we were (she just moved to Austin last week).  We decide to use the first hill (which begins at the driveway) as our warmup.  I think I was ready to call it quits by the time we finished the "warm up".  We start jogging and everything is good.  I'm sweating within moments, and I don't think I quit until about 2 hours later.  About 5 minutes into the run, I'm dying!  I'm such a wimp!  If I hadn't just run so great the morning before, this run would have deeply depressed me.  I'll go with my problem being a combo of too much sleep, heat, humidity, and hills.  None of which I'm used to!    Now I'm back in ugly, brown Abilene.  I think I love any city that's East of Abilene.  The drive back today almost depressed me because it began so beautiful, and it got less and less beautiful the closer I was to home.  Abilene actually isn't brown yet...give it a few weeks, it'll be there.  That's okay though, I'll be going home to East Texas this weekend.  I'm sure it'll be beautiful there too!
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm running short on time today, but thought I'd post some quick info.  Wednesday was my last time to swim, all was well...now I'm preparing for my open water swim tomorrow.  I decided to give myself a slight break before going to Austin so my body would be rested up.  Yesterday I didn't do any of my usual tri workout stuff.  I went to Lake Brownwood for the day and did some rock climbing, repelling, etc.  It was a blast and a nice change for my workout.  This was the first time I have tried any of these activities, and I think I could definitely make a hobby of it!  There was a particular place where we repelled from, they called it a "free fall" repel.  I learned to repel upside down also, which was a definite rush!    Anway, I'm headed to Austin shortly.  I have my open water swim in the morning and I'll be checking out my Danskin course while I'm there...Wish me luck!
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I keep trying to instill this idea, and it's not working this week.  I've now had two consecutively bad Mondays swimming.  I told my swim coach yesterday that they were going to have to refill the pool after I got out because I was inhaling so much water.  I only swam about 30 minutes yesterday, I wasn't getting anywhere and decided not to force it.   Before swimming yesterday we took our 10 mile bike route.  The ride was great.  The weather was nice, somewhat windy, but bearable.  All this working out outdoors has left me with a beautiful farmers' tan.  Very nice.    I took another PowerBar gel shot (or whatever they're called) yesterday between the biking and swimming.  Let me reiterate how much I love those things!  I was through the roof!    I decided I'd get up this morning and swim because I have other plans this afternoon and won't be able to make the swim class tonight.  5:30 at the Y, and the lifeguard beat me there.  So did the rest of the city. (8 people other than myself)  Who in the world gets up at 5:30 to swim just for the heck of it?  These people must be crazy!  Atleast I have a good excuse for my insanity.  I was really hoping for a better swim than yesterday.  There was improvement, but still not good.  This has me scratching my head trying to figure out the problem.  My only conclusion is the sleep factor.  I did great sleeping normal hours last week, but this week has been back to 5 hours a night again.  I plan to get to bed at a decent hour tonight and hopefully all will be well again tomorrow.  I'm thinking the late afternoon "caffeine shot" doesn't help my sleeping much.  At this rate, I'm getting slightly nerved about my upcoming swim on Saturday.  Although, I'm trying to stay positive (as much as possible).  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I can't believe I only have four more weeks to prepare!  It doesn't seem like I've already been doing this for eight weeks at all.  I'm already trying to decide what I will do next.  Right now, it's looking like a half-marathon (13.1 miles).  Although, after my run today (which does not fall into a "best ever" category) I'm rethinking this one.    I didn't actually think I would have time to workout today at all, but I'm pretty stressed at the moment and running always seems to help relieve this.  Then again, taking a stress break in the middle of the afternoon was probably my first mistake.  It was my only option (I thought), but I obviously have extra time right now...  Yeah, it was pretty toasty out today.  I'm sure that's what slowed me down.  Going into the tri training, my goal was to complete the race...I wasn't worried about times.  Well, this has changed.  I'm a pretty competitive person, and although I'm only competing with myself, I have always been my toughest competitor.  I really want to speed up my running times.  I've been horribly slow lately, so slow that I won't even tell you my time, lol.  The only thing is, I don't take the time to work in speed drills, I'm really considering this for the coming week.    Here's a positive from the past week...my hunger has finally toned down!  I haven't felt like I was starving in a few days, and I haven't been eating differently.  It's kind of nice!  It has crossed my mind to use this to my advantage and drop a few pounds, but I would hate to mess up my training by not eating enough.  I don't know whether or not my weight has fluctuated lately, I've been too scared to hop on the scale after the phase of "perpetual hunger".  I've always spoken out against scales anyway, probably because I hate them so much.  I believe that as long as you're happy with you, it doesn't matter what the numbers say.  But, I did finally break down and buy one last month, not that I've gotten any use out of it.    So, does this mean that my belief is a lie?  Hmm...    It's going to be a great week, I can feel it!  I'm ready to jump in the open water and swim away next weekend!  Hopefully I'm still this anxious by the weekend!
     
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today is a beautiful day. I'm all rested up and the weather is perfect.   First, I'll start with yesterdays workout. I left work early yesterday...I didn't feel great...probably needed sleep. Instead, I went to try for my swim again. Yesterday now wins my "best ever" award for swimming. It was excellent. I was gliding, breathing air (not water), what more could I ask for. Actually, I was timing my laps, and I had dropped an easy 5 seconds off each lap. I'm so impressed with myself. I swam for an hour and finally decided not to push it, I love ending on a good note. If I swim like this next Saturday, I'll have no problems.   Back to my wonderful day today. I'm feeling slightly high on life at the moment...no real reason (or caffeine). Maybe all the sleep I got last night did this to me. Then again, maybe it's the weather. Its not too hot, too humid, too windy, not too much of anything! I took my longest bike ride yet today. Mike is out of town and left me his road bike, so I though I should get good use of it. I made up my own route today, starting from my apartment, and making my way all over town. I rode 20 miles (1 mile further than my longest ride), and my legs don't even feel tired. I could've gone longer, but my back side was getting sore (darn bike seats). I decided on the route through town because I had a feeling I'd get bored out on the highway by myself. I love people. I love talking to people. I love watching people (no, I'm not a stalker). With the weather being so nice today, people were everywhere. I rode through and around two different parks, through neighborhoods, I was all over the city of Abilene.  I did end up in a few empty areas, and attempted my usual entertainment.  I felt a little silly singing while riding alone... I even caught a few people staring at me -- I seriously doubt it's because I'm so darn hot!  I decided to give up on singing for the day, it just wasn't working for me.  Two amazing days of training back to back...what more could I ask for? I'll be greedy -- I want more days like this!  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was slightly concerned that my afternoon nap yesterday might turn into a trip to Oz...but soon concluded that the chances of a tornado finding me were slim, so I crashed for a good hour. The weather yesterday was ugly, to say the least.  I love napping in the rain, but absolutely hate storms.  I'm not quite sure where this fear originated, but I do recall always being the first one prepared to "take cover" as a child.  I'm not much better as an "adult".   Apparently I was exhausted, because I slept like a baby right through mother nature's commotion.    Needless to say, I didn't work out yesterday.  The weather was bad, and it was probably about time to rest for a day anyhow.  However, I did get up bright and early this morning to swim at the Y.  I got there, only to find out that the lifeguard was running late.  The receptionist called him (at 5:30 am) to make sure he was coming in...he was still in bed!  Not that I could blame him, but COME ON!  I dragged myself out of bed at 5:15 and the kid wasn't even there!  I do recall my college days, and there was no way you could've bribed me to get out of bed that early.  No amount of money was worth my precious sleep time. I decided to go home and get ready for work rather than waiting around on him to get there.  There's no telling what time he would actually show.  I mentioned a few weeks ago that I was going to Austin to check out my race course this weekend.  Well, plans change.  Actually, I am now planning to go next weekend.  For one, it worked better for the friend I'm staying with. But more importantly, I found out that there's a Women's Open Water Swim Practice next Saturday at Quarry Lake in Austin.  This is somewhere on the northwest side of town (not that I know a thing about the Austin area).  The swim practice was primarily set up to help women prepare for the Danskin and other triathlons.  There's supposed to be technique training and transition tips also.  I'm very excited about attempting my first open water swim, but I really need to get all the pool time I can this next week.  Also, I'm glad to finally have a chance to jump in "not-so-clean" water and get a feel for it.  I bet I'll have my "rocking" down when I get in the lake...who wants to inhale nasty lake water?  I'm not quite sure what the rest of my day has in store.  I'm considering going  back  to the Y at lunch and getting my swim in...otherwise I'll have to wait until 5, and I'd rather get part of my workout complete before the afternoon.  It  is  Friday, you know...if I only have one after work activity, it'll feel like a huge break!
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've decided that I'm never going to get used to, much less enjoy, the West Texas wind.  For those of you from here, I realize you don't exactly consider Abilene "West Texas", please recall that I'm from Wills Point...this is West Texas!  Saying that, I'll also quit complaining about it after today (maybe), because it seems like every day is the same complaint.  I do know that yesterday reportedly had wind gusts up to 32 MPH, and I believe it held steady at about 15 MPH.  Definitely nice and breezy!  We also have a phrase we use frequently on windy days.  I thought this was my phrase until Mike used it yesterday, now it belongs to whoever feels like using it.  I know I only use it when I would love to quit and head back to my car.  It's a reference to wind and goes something like this "If the wind is still blowing against us when we head back...I quit!"  I probably overuse this one, but that's how hopeless the wind makes me!  I know this makes us sound like negative people, but we're actually far from it.  We use negative humor to make it through, and this just happens to be what works for us.  Back to our ride yesterday...  Given the weather, we decided on our 10 mile bike ride again.  About half way out, delirium set in.  All my energy is being used to pedal, even something as simple as laughing expends too much extra energy and slows me up.  Times like this, I feel like I could just lay on the side of the highway and laugh for hours.  I didn't care too much about extra energy yesterday, I was bored of the wind, and my vocal chords were becoming restless.  "Fill me up Buttercup" was back on my agenda, I had the chorus down, but the rest of it just wouldn't come to me.  I think Mike really likes my singing (lol), he did email me the rest of the lyrics today.  I assume that means he wants to hear me belt them out.  Then again, maybe it just drives him crazy to hear me make up the rest of the words.  Whatever the reasoning may be, I'll still be sure and get them down so I can sing tomorrow.   After burning up all my energy singing and biking, we still had swimming.  I swam an 800 meter warm-up and I think another 200 meters and had to go.  Mike swam a little longer than me.  We both had places to be after swimming, so it was a rushed practice yesterday.  My swimming felt pretty good again, but I think I needed some more PowerBar Gel.  I've decided I loved its affect on my energy so much that I want a whole case of it!  I kept sucking water in my mouth and/or nose yesterday.  When swimming your body is supposed to "rock" from side to side, so when you're ready to breathe, all you do is turn your head and the "rocking" should pull your face out of the water.  I think I was too lazy yesterday to "rock" as much as I should.  Therefore, my mouth wasn't coming out of the water like it should.  This, my friends, causes you to suck in water when you're trying to breathe.  It really doesn't feel great.    That's all my workout wisdom for the day.  The weather isn't looking too great for an outdoors workout today, they're calling for afternoon thunderstorms.  I surely won't be outside waiting for this. Today sounds like a good day for an afternoon nap...   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterdays workout was fantastic.  All that sleep really paid off!  I was "gliding" through the water again yesterday, rather than sinking.  I did all kinds of different drills that added up to 1600 meters or more, I'm not sure exactly.    I tried out some Power Bar products yesterday, I figured it couldn't hurt.  Before the swim I had a Pria bar, which was good.  No big deal, or big difference.  I also purchased their Gel Shots (not Jello shots) for a quick pick-me-up if I needed it.  When I finished my swim I was still bouncing off the walls (my natural high), but after my shower, my body seemed to crash. I was determined to run (since I cut my Monday workout short) so I took a quick shot of the gel.  The next thing I knew, I was bouncing off the walls again, but this time it lasted for hours.  I ran a quick mile and half, then I had to get across town for a softball game.  I was such a spazz the whole softball game.  A friend of mine pointed out that a lot of "pick-me-up" sports stuff disguises caffeine with other ingredients.  I suddenly remember reading the label and it said something about how much caffeine was in it, I don't remember the exact amount, but that's basically all the shot was.  Caffeine and my body don't mix well, especially at night time.  For one, I rarely drink anything caffeinated so I really affects me when I do.  Also, my body has never handled it well in the evenings.  I remember many nights that I have had coffee too late in the evening and wasn't able to sleep a wink.   Oh well, it was too late at this point.  My review of the gel shots...they're great, as long as I give myself plenty of time to work off the high.  Luckily I was up late on the phone last night anyway, so by the time I tried to sleep, I crashed!  Maybe it was my caffeine downer time...  Overall, yesterday was a great fitness day.  Lesson for the day:  Always read and pay attention to food labels!
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've beens so busy lately I haven't had the chance to update, so here's a quick (or possibly not so quick) recap.  Friday morning I found myself standing at the entrance of the YMCA at 5:30 am wondering once again, when exactly it was that I lost my mind.  I wasn't even working on Friday, but knew I had to be up and at 'em early if I wanted to get my workout in before leaving town.  I went in a swam an 800 warm up, and began another 10 sprints when and old arm injury (from my one rodeo experience, lol) came back to haunt me.  I had completely forgotten about this injury, my rotator on my left arm basically pops with every stroke, but it is now back.  So, after about an hour of swimming I decided I had plenty.  The park I like to run at just happens to surround the Y, so it's hard to pass up on a run also.  I actually surprised myself with my jogging.  I haven't jogged immediately after swimming before, so I expected I'd wear out quickly.  I jogged a nice (slow) 3 miles and called it a day.  The main purpose in running Friday was to make sure my leg would be hurting for my doctor's appointment.  Well, it hurt for the first half mile of the run and it went kind of numb for the rest, this is fairly normal.  By the time I got to to the doctor's office, it felt fine, of course.  He basically told me that I'm pushing my body to its limits right now, and I probably have tendinitis in my right quad.  The only thing I can do differently to fix it would be to slow up on my working out, which isn't an option right now.  So, here I go, popping Tylenol on a daily basis for the next month (that's the second solution he gave me).    I took Saturday and Sunday off of working out, I had a ton of things going and my body was needing a break anyway.  Yesterday we decided to start the week off somewhat easy.  We met after work to ride bikes, and took a shorter 10 mile route.  The wind was awfully gusty yesterday, probably 20-25 MPH gusts, this is just my guess.  We knew what to expect when we started out luckily, it was pretty obvious which way the wind was blowing.  We rode south into the wind the first half, and basically flew home the second half, so it wasn't all bad.  Although, it definitely wore me out.  Then we had swimming.  Yesterday was possibly my worst swimming day ever.  It started out by me tearing my swim cap, so my hair was all over the place.  And Mike left his goggles, luckily he was able to borrow a pair.  About the time we got to the pool I suddenly didn't feel well.  I got in the water and did a 600 warm-up.  The whole time I was swimming I felt like I was sinking, it was a struggle the whole time.  My left arm also began to bother me again, which put me in a horrible mood.  I was only at the pool about 30-45 minutes and finally decided to call it quits.  I was so upset when I left, I felt like I was losing my swimming suddenly.  But, I began to realize that my body is just exhausted right now, and I really needed to rest.  I've been averaging approximately 5 hours of sleep each night, and with the stress of training also, my body was spent.  I had already planned to go home and hit the sack after swimming, but my body decided it was ready  during  swimming.  I went home and was in bed by 9:00 last night, and I slept later than usual this morning.  I got a good 9 1/2 hours of sleep last night (can't remember the last time that happened) and I'm raring to go today!  I don't think I've mentioned that I have been getting to work at 7 for the past month so that I can leave around 4 to start my training.  We don't usually complete everything until about 8 most evenings, so there's no way I can get to bed too early.  This is obviously taking a lot of time and energy, but I really do love it.  Training for a tri is also not the easiest thing I've ever done, but as they say, if it were easy, everyone would be doing it!  
     
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Its my Friday this week.  I'll be heading to Wills Point tomorrow for the weekend, my brother graduates from nursing school Saturday morning (Yea!).    Here's my only downfall so far to this whole process.  For the past week, I have been constantly hungry!  I'll eat, be full, and ten minutes later, I'm hungry again!   I'm pretty careful about what goes in my body, so it's not as if I'm filling myself full of junk.  I'm sure it's that I'm burning more calories and my metabolism is speeding up, but I absolutely hate being hungry!  Worst of all, when I get hungry, I get moody. This couldn't possibly be fun for anyone involved!  There has got to be a way around all of this hunger!  We planned for today's workout to be somewhat simple, but the idea didn't follow through.  We were only biking today, and after yesterdays struggle with the wind we really thought we had our route figured out.  Maybe I should have referred myself to my previous entry about the wind always blowing against us, no matter what direction we're riding.  The wind was definitely tough on the way out today, but Mike planned it this way.  The thought was that if we ride against the wind one way, it'll carry you home when you switch directions.  This works when you're riding directly into the wind only, when its blowing at your side, the wind never helps you along.  We rode 17 miles today, it shouldn't have tired me so much, but factoring in the wind that's not too bad.  We all know I'm a pretty "quirky" person, and I realized a new quirk today.  When I'm tired, like exhausted-tired, I get goofy.  I prefer to call it delirious--it seems much more fitting.  Everything becomes hysterical.  I lose all sense of balance (not sure I ever really had this).  The ride back today seemed impossible.  It didn't help when Mike tried to convince me that we had 30 more minutes of our ride left when I thought we were almost finished.  (By the way, I was correct in this case, we only had about 10 minutes left)  When I'm tired and I realize I have more to do than I think, this leads to sudden exhaustion.  Which, eventually leads to goofiness.  When we finished, I was having trouble putting the bike in the bike rack--somehow this was hysterical to me.  I couldn't seem to function.  Guess that's one more quirk to add my rapidly growing list!  
     
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Have you ever noticed that the wind can blow from all directions at the same time?  How on earth can the wind be blowing from the south, but still be against you when you're heading north? No matter what direction we go on our bikes, the wind is always against us!  We try taking North/South routes...that doesn't work.  Today we went East/West...still no good!  I'm completely stumped!  Have you ever wondered what people do to restrain boredom while riding bikes?  If you're me, you sing (terribly) every song that comes to mind.  Last week it was "Little Bunny Foo Foo" (a rabbit was hopping along the side of us a one point) -- thanks to my friend Rebecca, I now remember all the words.  Today, it was "Build Me Up Buttercup" (there were cute little buttercups up and down the road today)--this one will continue tomorrow probably because I couldn't seem to remember all the words today.  Mike, on the other hand -- he enjoys talking to all the animals we see.  He makes horse, cow, donkey, and whatever other animals noises we see. It's actually very entertaining.  Oh, and I almost forgot.  I came within an inch of running over a snake today!  I'm not sure if it was deal or alive, and I sure wasn't going back to find out!  I thought it was a piece of a tire until I was looking directly down at it.  More than likely it was dead, because I don't think it moved.  All I do know, is that it was huge...and that I'm deathly afraid of rattlesnakes(which tend to be huge).   If you can't tell, in my mind, this huge (probably dead) snake was definitely a rattlesnake(my biggest fear in Abilene, TX).  That's all for my deep thoughts today...  On to the workout!  If you haven't picked up in this yet, the bike ride was a little windy.  We keep changing up the bike routes to try and catch the wind at our sides rather than straight on, but its just not working.  We got a late start today, so we cut back to 12 miles.  Then we were off to the Y.  Swimming was wonderfully hard, as usual.  We started with 800 meter drills, similar to yesterday.  Today it was swim/kick/pull/kick, 100 meters of each, until we completed 800 meters.  Then I did 10- 50 meter sprints (with 20-30 second breaks between each).  To finish, the plan was that I would pace myself and swim as long as I could.  This one didn't last long, I was already worn out.  I don't think I've given you the actual "pool distance" of our swim, but its about 800 meters, which is 16 laps in the pool.  We've been swimming almost double that distance each day, so I'm convinced I'll be prepared in 5 1/2 more weeks!  I think I'm about to go crash now, I'm so exhausted that I could sleep straight through tomorrow!
     
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today my arms feel like Hanz and Franz have been pumping me up.  I've been working at using my arms as much as possible in my swimming (this will save leg energy for the bike and run on event day).  I've also been incorporating free weights into my week, nothing hefty, just a lot of repetitions.  I always knew I had no upper body strength, but now I actually need it.  As for yesterday, I decided to give myself an easy day, and allow myself a little fun time.  Rather than going directly from work to training, I went shopping for a few hours with some friends of mine.  Those of you who know me well, know that shopping is nothing new for me.  But seriously, I haven't shopped without a specific purpose in ages!  Okay, so maybe it's only been a month or so, but that's pretty impressive for me!  I think I need to train year round from now on...it seems to be saving me money!!!  Okay, back to my workout.  I was on my own yesterday, so I went swimming.  I also had to cut my swim short (had a softball game that I couldn't miss!).  I think I probably got as much done yesterday in 45 minutes by myself as I did the day before with my friends.  Hmmm...maybe I talk too much?  I worked a lot on my distance swimming yesterday.  We always start the swim with drills.  Yesterday it was 800 meters (maybe yards, can't remember, but there's not much of a difference).  I did 200 swim, 200 pull, 200 kick, 200 swim.  This terminology may as well have been Greek to me a few weeks ago.  Basically, the 200 swim is 200 meters of freestyle.  The "pull" is where you put the buoy between your legs to float you legs and you only use your arms...hence the term "pull".  The 200 kick is using a kickboard.  Then you finish with another 200 freestyle.  The only breaks you should take are between each set of 200, and that should only be for 30-45 seconds.  The first time I tried this, I thought I was going to drown right there at the YMCA.  It's actually getting easier now, which is how I know my endurance keeps on building.  After this, I took a quick breather and did 200 freestyle at a slightly faster pace, then an easy 50.  By this time, my 45 minutes was up and that was it for the day!  Mentally, 45 minutes sounds like nothing, but physically my arms are about to fall off.  But, here's the psycho in me saying that my arms hurting like they do, feels GREAT!!!!  All I can say, is Hanz and Franz had better watch out!
     
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was definitely right, this is starting off to be a great week!  Yesterdays workout was fantastic!  Okay, I may be overdoing it a bit with "fantastic", but it really was great!  We have a few different bike routes we take, and we did what used to be my favorite one yesterday.  As of yesterday, it is no longer my favorite.  Its a pretty hilly ride on the north side of town, out towards Lake Fort Phantom (yes, there are all kinds of ghost stories that go with the lake).  The only problem with this ride is the wind.  If it's blowing directly from the south, the second half of the ride is miserable...this was the case yesterday!  Mike and I are both sure that the wind picked up sometime between 3 and 4 yesterday afternoon, but we toughed it out.  I guess I should refer myself back to yesterday's post where I talked about the windy days making it easier in the long run, but that was the last thing on my mind yesterday!  We actually figured out that the wind was blowing approx 12 MPH and we were only peddling about 12 MPH (in the tough areas)...so we were basically getting nowhere.  I realize this is bad math, but it sure seemed to make sense during the ride.  Luckily we had 45 min to an hour of down time before we were supposed to swim.  The swim was great yesterday.  We normally swim for about 45 min, sometimes an hour.  Yesterday we were there for an hour and fifteen mins.  I figured up the actual distance we swam, and I believe we swam just short of 1 mile (not without resting, of course).  I can definitely see improvement in my endurance.  As for Mike, he finally graduated from his nose clip yeseterday!  Our normal coach wasn't there yesterday, but his wife was.  She also convinced Mike to give up his wetsuit.  Although, the "flotation belt" he now wears brings new humor to the sport.  Of course, I have my flaws in swimming also, but I just don't enjoy making fun of myself nearly as much!  I watched the weather this morning and its looking like a great week ahead!  I love the heat and sunshine!
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am now over half way there!  That's actually more of a scary thought than an exciting one sometimes!  We took what has become our usual bike ride yesterday, approx. 15 miles.  The weather was beautiful, the wind was hardly noticeable, which is nice for Abilene.  I guess all the hard work on the windy days makes days like yesterday seem like a piece of cake!  It's always nice to feel the payoff!  It was a great start to the week, which leads me to believe this week will be a great one for training!  The hardest part of all of this would have to be having a bad day or worse, a bad week of training.  It's so easy to burn out and consider quitting, especially when you're just doing this for yourself.  I know I won't quit now, I've put too much time and effort into all of this.  Mike had a rough week last week, and I've had my fair share of them in the past.  The best part of training with other people is that you don't usually have bad days and/or weeks at the same time.  There's always someone there to motivate you when all your personal motivation has exhausted.  Another motivator I've found useful is reading stories of people who have completed a tri.  I get an adrenaline rush just reading about their excitement crossing the finish line!  I can't wait!  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Life has been fairly hectic the past few days.  I hate to admit this, but I've slacked on my training since I've been out of town.  My knee started bothering me again on my way to Dallas on Wednesday, so no run there.  Besides, by the time I reached Dallas, it was almost time for The Bachelor to come on, and I really can't miss that!  The weather has also been messy, but I finally got a good run in today.  Being my first day running in a few weeks, it was much better than I had expected.  I'd guess it was about 3.5 - 4 miles, I timed it at 41 minutes, but I'm sure my pace was pretty slow.  I was planning to be back home tonight so I could get be sure and fit a bike/run in tomorrow.  But, seeing that I got lazy this afternoon and didn't make the drive, I'm not sure how that will work out.  I do know that I'm ready for a tough week of working out, I feel like a slacker lately, and this is really not the time to be slacking!  I now have 6 weeks until the big day...which means I'm half way there!  I'm already excited and nervous!  I have to go and see my "leg doctor" (previously known as the "knee doctor") this coming Friday, hopefully he won't tell me to quit training!  I seriously doubt he'll say that, I'm really hoping he'll help me out on this right leg, maybe we can figure out what the problem is.  My brother brought something to my attention tonight about my leg.  Number one, being that this is obviously a problem I've not experienced before.  Number two, I've never biked much in the past.  Number three, the area that hurts is my lower quad (the muscle used most in biking).  This one really shouldn't take a rocket scientist, but this suddenly sounds like a biking problem...  For whatever reason, I was blaming it on running!  Our conclusion was that my tendons are possibly fatigued, and hopefully not stressed, pulled, or torn.  My body has never endured this much training for such a period of time before, so this all makes sense.  I'll get back later in the week with the Doctor's orders.   
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Since my last entry, Ive had to lay off again.  I got a good run in Friday morning before having my stitches removed, only to find out that this would be my last run for several days.  Im still not quite sure why the nurse took them out because they werent ready.  All weekend theyve been trying to split open.  Ive been stuck working out at the gym on the stationary bike and elliptical machines.  Talk about boring.   I did get brave last night and play softball.  I was planning to sit out, but most of my team didnt show, so I played.  My stitches were fine, but my jaw is another story.  At the expense of my own stupidity, I got knocked in the jaw with a softball.  It didnt feel so bad last night, but its really sore today.  Im betting Ill have a bruise before the end of the week.  So exciting.  Thatll teach me to talk and throw a softball at the same time.  This feels oddly familiar.  When I was younger (probably 8th or 9th grade) I was talking while playing softball and got whacked in the nose.  I ended up with a broken nose and two black eyeswe call the photos my mug shots.  Somehow I managed to get past my fear of softballs over the yearshere we go again.       
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sorry Ive been out of pocket for a few days, but Im back!  I guess I did say that I wouldnt be back until I actually had something worth talking aboutso Ill give it a shot.  The last time I mentioned working out, it was all but a disaster.  Ive actually been able to do quite a bit this week.  I went to the park the other night, Monday I think and walk just planning to walk a few miles to keep myself moving.  Just as I was finishing up my 3 miles of walking I ran into a friend who was running.  I decided to jog beside her for a few minutes to catch up and ended up get a mile and a half in.  I had convinced myself that I couldnt jog with stitchesguess I proved this theory wrong!  By all means, they were sore, but I could still do it.  Tuesday I went to the gym so I could get on a bike and use those muscles a little bit.   This was the first time on a bike (stationary or any other kind) since my tri.  Im still waiting to get my own bike, but I had some unexpected expenses last week that sucked away the funds for a few more weeks.    Yesterday I didnt think I would get anything accomplished.  I left work at lunch not feeling well.  I went home, got some rest, and was ready to go again by early evening.  I went to the park around 7:30 last nightyou cant beat this weather were having right now.  It hardly reached 80 yesterday.  Im sure the summer heat will come again soon, but Im enjoying the weather for the meantime.  I got a lot of exercise in yesterday, I ran 3 and walked 3 (miles, that is).  I'm sure my boss would love to know that I got 6 miles in after going home sick, lol!  I plan to start swimming again at the end of next week or the beginning of the following week, basically at the beginning of July.  Ill get my stitches out tomorrow, so thatll be out of the way for good (hopefully).  For now, hopefully Ill continue to keep my running up to at least 3 miles.  I may start running with a friend of mine next week who has been running 5 and 6 miles a day, Im not sure how well Ill handle that, but its worth a try!   
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here are links to a few more pictures.  I've tried figuring out why in the world I'm so intent on looking at the ground in these two...I've decided that I'm concentrating, lol.  That's the best I can figure out!  urlLink http://www.brightroom.com/view_user_photo.asp?EVENTID=4144&PWD=&ID=8210705&FROM=browser   This one isn't exactly meant to be of me, but I'm in the background!  urlLink http://www.brightroom.com/view_user_photo.asp?EVENTID=4144&PWD=&ID=8210703&FROM=browser 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I should've caught up on all my rest by now, but I'll be taking it easy again this week.  I have stitches in my side right now (literally) so the next several days will be forced rest.  All this sitting still is driving me crazy and making me more lazy.    The Danskin had an event photographer for the race and those pictures are posted now.  If you're interested in them, here's the link   urlLink http://www.brightroom.com/view_user_event.asp?EVENTID=4144&PWD=&BIB=2246    The one of me crossing the finish line cracks me up.  There's no huge smile across my face, just complete relief.    I'm a fairly boring person lately, not a lot to say.  Hopefully I'll be back soon with something exciting to talk about. 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My massage yesterday was wonderful.  However, I had no idea just how worthless I was becoming.  I crashed again immediately following the massagethis time, for 2  hours.  I knew my body was exhausted, but this is getting a bit ridiculous.  I really dont feel well today, but Im sure Ill be fine.  I plan to refuse my body a nap this afternoon.  Id really like to get started working out again.  My knee is feeling better already, Ive kept it iced for the past two days, so maybe it could handle a slow run tonight (not that my legs know any other speed).  Ill either run or swimdepending on my knee.  For now, Im just trying to keep my eyes open at work.  Im getting sick of this crash phase.  Then again, Im sure it could always be worse!  :)  
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm so glad I was able to take off work yesterday.  Other than updating this page, I don't think I did much of anything!  I didn't even leave my house until 11 last night, and that was only because I was out of milk (which I can't survive breakfast without).  I'm still pretty exhausted, but glad to see the human race again.  I did get a massage scheduled for today--I'm pretty excited about this.  My muscles are so sore still.  I'm thinking tonight might be another lazy one since the massage is immediately after work.  I plan to try and get in the pool in the next day or so to work some of the soreness out of my muscles.  Call me crazy (again)--but I really am ready to hit the training all over again.  Challenging my body to its physical limits like this has been the biggest high for me.  Yes, it sent me crashing down Sunday afternoon, but wow, nothing I've ever done before beats this! 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    I did it!  Here are a few photos for now, I'll have more later.  This is one me in deep concentration just before the start of the race!
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    I'm thinking the water was slightly frigid at this point!
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Run Kristi Run!
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Not only did I survive, but I also beat the time I was shooting for!  Yea!  It had so much fun!  I don't even know where to start.  Before I forget, I have a few more photos posted on my yahoo photos page   urlLink http://f2.pg.photos.yahoo.com/ph/kristi.c@sbcglobal.net/album?.dir=/1c9d   First of all, we got to Austin around 9:30 Saturday morning.  We stood in line for a while to get checked in, I had a course review, and then headed to check in the bike.  After all of this, Jessica and Jenni got to town, so we all went to lunch then just relaxed for the rest of the day.  We shopped, napped, and ate...that's about it.  I didn't get to bed until after midnight Saturday night and had to get up shortly after 4 Sunday, but I figured my body wouldn't even notice.    I was up and at 'em at 4:15 Sunday morning.  I took a hot shower (to get my muscles warmed up), packed my bags and headed to the race site.  We had to park at the Travis County Expo Center and they had buses shuttling us to the park from there, about a mile away.  Before getting on the bus there were volunteers standing there with markers to put your race number all over your body.  I had it on both arms and both legs--beautiful.  I was one of the first people on the buses.  I knew I needed every last second to set up my transition stuff, otherwise I'd worry too much.  Luckily Jessica's co-worker gave me a heads up on taking a flashlight race morning to help me because it was still dark when I got there.  I was one of the few to have a flashlight with me.     The first thing I attempted to do race morning was to air up my tires.  At the meeting on Saturday they warned everyone to let some air out so your tires wouldn't pop in the heat.  I figured this couldn't be too difficult, I was just airing up a few bike tires, but boy was I wrong.  I couldn't figure out the stupid pump.  Luckily, there were volunteers there to help us air up tires, so I took the bike to them.  Now it was time to set up my towel, helmet, shoes, snacks, etc.  This wasnt too big of a deal.  My biggest problem before the race was trying to decide what I was going to wear for the race.  I had a swim suit and running shorts or a tri suit (which is basically bike shorts and a top, but all one piece), and I couldnt decide which I would be more comfortable in.  At the last minute, I decided on the tri suit, which Im glad I did in the end.   Once it was time to leave transition (7 am) no one was allowed back in until they had completed their swim.  When I was leaving transition there were a bunch of ladies just getting there.  I couldnt believe they were so unprepared.   They actually ended up having to delay the race start because of all the traffic, which is why so many of the athletes were running behind.    I headed down toward the water at 7.  I was in the 20th wave, so my start time was scheduled for 8:12.  With the delay, I didnt get to start until about 8:45.  I did have one horribly embarrassing moment while I was standing with my wave waiting to start.  My tri suit that I was talking about, it zips up the front, and the zipper is supposed to lockits really difficult to zip up, but if youre unzipping it, all you have to do is barely start it and it completely unzips itself.  Yeah.  Im sure youre already getting the idea.  I think I was pulling down on the top of the suit and BAMit unzipped completely (which is about half way down my stomach).  All I could do was shriek and cover myself.  Luckily these three very sweet ladies helped me put myself back in the suit without a huge scene!  I wanted to die!    Now it was time to start the swim.  This went really well.  Each wave has about 100 women in, so if you can imagine all of us trying to start swimming at the same time.  Really the whole swim was jam packed with people.  Youre kicking some, getting kicked by others, but the nice thing was that this race isnt terribly competitive, so everyone was super apologetic.  The sun was really bright, so it was difficult to see the buoys, but there were people in kayaks helping us to stay on course.  They were also there to drag people out of the water that werent making it (there were a few).  Other than that, the swim was just a swim.  I was also pre-warned to try and pee before getting out of the lake so I wouldnt waste time in transition going to the restroom.  Okay, have you ever tried to pee while youre swimmingthis isnt the easiest thing Ive ever done, but I somehow managed it.  My final swim time was 22:04.  Not too bad, but theres plenty of room for improvement.  This also ranked me at 1215 out of 2724 on my swim.    When I got out of the lake, I had to run up this long hill to get to transition.  When I got there I dried my feet off, put my shoes and socks on, put my helmet and sunglasses on, threw on a tank top, took a GU shot (gel shot) and headed out.  Before I could get on the bike, I had to walk it out of transition (way on the other end from where my bike was located) and then walk it down a road a short way.  The transitions are also timed for us, and this first one took me 5:17.    Now I was off on the bike leg of the tri.  We drove the course the day before so I was prepared for the difficulty.  There were many rolling hills, but a few that were out of the blue killers.  To my surprise, this ended up being my strongest leg of the race.  On two separate ends of the course, there would be a downhill where you had to come to almost a complete stop, make a 90 turn, only to see a huge steep hill waiting for you.  The only way I survived these was by gearing down and not looking up!  A lot of women got of their bikes and walked up these.  This makes me thankful we trained in sometimes difficult conditions.  As I said before, the atmosphere of this race was super friendly.  The whole race everyone was talking to each other, encouraging each other, it was wonderful.  One of these difficult hills comes at the end of the bike course, while the bikers are going up the hill, you see the runners on the other side of a fence running down it.  All the runners are yelling out for the bikers the whole way.  It was great to have the encouragement.  In the end, my bike time was 46:53, which was 15.8 MPH and ranked me at 852.    Transition 2 was much quicker than the first one.  All I had to do this time was to find my transition spot (which gets difficult when there are 3,000 spots around you), rack my bike, replace my helmet with a ball cap, take a GU and hit the road.  The start of the run was directly beside my transition spot, so this transition only took me 3:26.    The run started off a lot easier than I had expected.  My legs usually have the jello feeling when I start, but they didnt for some reason.  By all means, they were tired, but I didnt feel like I was going to fall over at all.  The run was nice, but some areas were solid mudyou can just imagine how beautiful my shoes look.  There were several water stations set up along the way also.  At each station I took two cups, one to drink and one to pour over my head.  By this time, it was getting near 11:00, so the sun was really beating down.  I think I survived most of the run by talking to other ladies that were running beside me.  We were all exhausted by this point, but also knew that it was almost over.  We took our turn at encouraging the bikers while we were running down their big uphillthis was probably the easiest part of the whole run course.  The most difficult part was about the last half mile.  There was this huge uphill, but we all knew that once we reached the top we were home free.  This is the only time that I walked during the run portion.  I think I was walking as fast as I could run on this hill.  When we hit the top of the hill, we could hear the crowd yelling and the announcer in the distance.  This was our last  mile.  I think everyone was running at this point.   I only had enough energy to sprint the last 100 yards, but I made it!  My run time ended up being 34:11, which broke down to an 11:01 mile.  I really though I was jogging slower than that, and considering I walked for a minute or two, was actually okay with this time.  My run rank was 1135.    After completing the run, I was slightly disoriented.  I spotted Mike in the crowd waiting after the finish line, and the girls were nearby.  They sent us all through an area with fruits, cookies, animal crackers, etc for race recovery.  I remember stumbling through this area a bit, feeling a little confused.  When I walked out I found my friends and we celebrated!  I forgot to mention earlier that the girls made me a "Go Kristi" sign and held it up when I was passing by.  They were all over the race course.  I never saw them until they yelled at me or for me, usually after or while I was passing by.  When you look at all the women out there, we all look basically the same.    Overall, my time was 1:51:53, which put me at 57 out of 104 in my age group.  My overall rank was 1058 out of 2724.  This puts me at about mid pack with my age group and almost the top 1/3 overall, so I am very pleased at the results.    You may be wondering, what next?  Well, for now, Ill be healing my knee (which when crazy on me during the final  mile).  Hopefully this will only take a week or two.  During this time, Ill be looking for a new goal, probably a new triathlon.  Keep checking back for more photos also.  There was a photographer on site to catch action photos, and I expect those to be ready at least by the end of the week.  For now, Im going to use the rest of my day off the take a nap and be lazy!   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's almost midnight and I'm not a bit sleepy (yet).  This is a good thing since I've not yet finished packing.  I mentioned this morning that I was going to try and leave work early to run errands and take a nap.  I did leave early, but only accomplished half of my list during work hours.  I went home and decided the nap was my number one priority.  I crashed around 1 p.m. and didn't wake up until 5!  I told you I was exhausted!  Afterwards I ran some errands and went for a swim.    My final swim was nice.  I took it easy, but swam 800 (about a half mile--my race distance).  I didn't time myself exactly, but I'm fairly sure I can finish it up in 20 minutes.  That'll surely help my overall time.    Mike and I plan to leave at 6 in the morning.  I'm a little nervous about this since I'm not sleepy yet.  If I don't get tired in an hour or so, we may just hit the road tonight and probably sleep in the car in the morning.  I prefer getting tired in the next hour.    This is my last entry before the big race.  If you don't hear from me again, this means I drowned in the lake.  Otherwise, I'll probably update again Sunday night.  Until then...
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Im down to two more daysand Im slowly wearing down.  This has possibly been the fastest week of my life.  This whole race has really creeped up on me.  I still havent gotten that swim inIm planning it for this afternoon.  I think Ill try and leave work early today so I can get my bags packed and get some rest.  Were leaving at 6 a.m. tomorrow so I can be in Austin at 10 to check in my bike.  I have two meetings to make tomorrow also.  One is a first timers meeting.  Itll basically help prepare me for what Im about to do.  Theres also a course overview meeting.  This is probably where Ill find out about any course changes and get the final course map.  The weather forecast is looking good also.   urlLink http://www.weather.com/weather/local/USTX0057  Theres only a 20% chance of showers for Sunday.  Rain or shine, well do the course, but thunder and lightning could delay start times.  The way I see it, the earlier the better, so I wont be doing any rain dances this weekend  Today Ill be going back over all my reading material making sure I havent missed any details of what I need for race day.  Serious Kristi has come out for now, but Im sure my delirious side will be around tomorrow.  Ill be sure and let you know all the stages my personality goes through the next few daysFor now I'm serious and sleepy.  Or maybe that's seriously sleepy.  I'd love to crash right here at my desk (I'm writing this from work). Ive been so exhausted this week that I actually did catch some zs at work a few days ago.  I have one of those leather chairs that are sort of tall in the back.  I turned away from my door toward the back wall of my office, put a book in my lap (just in case someone walked in) and passed out for a few minutes.  It wasnt the best sleep of my life, but it worked temporarily.  This is the week I should be getting good rest, but Ive just been too busy.  You know, so much to do, so little timeFor now I should probably get some of that so much to do done.   If Im not back on here tonight, watch for me later on in the weekend.  Ill update as soon as I get back to town.  Wish me luck!
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've caught myself snapping a lot the past few days.  I assume it's the pressure I've put on myself to perform this weekend...I hope it doesn't get worse the next few days.  I can only describe the feeling as like when something is coming up and there's nothing you can do about it but just wait for it to happen.  No more preparation is going to help me this weekend.  It's just the course and methats it.  I'm wishing I had trained differently in some areas, then again this is my first tri.  I can't actually expect too much of myself never having done this before.  Dont mistake all this for lack of excitementI really am thrilled about the weekend, but nervous.    I did my last day of bike training yesterday.  It was possibly the windiest and most difficult day yet.  I forced 10 miles out of my legs.  The wind was a steady 25-30 MPH, plus the gusts.  This made for one fun ride.    I planned to go for my final swim this morning, but have been so tired this week that I didn't make it.  I planned to swim at 5:30, but didn't manage drag myself out of bed until 7:15.  I'll go swim either tomorrow morning or tomorrow after work (depending on when I get to bed tonight).  I was headed home to hit the sack around 9 last night when three of my girlfriends wanted to go to "good luck coffee" with me.  There's no way I could consider turning that down--it was so sweet and not to mention, unexpected.  It's always nice to get together with my friends, it seems like I give myself less and less social time lately.  I'm really going to work on this if I continue training after this weekend.  I'm sure there's a healthy balance somewhere, I just haven't found it yet.  Most training books actually have a chapter on balancing your personal life with training, but theres not a simple chart to follow like there is with training.  Each person has to accommodate for his or her individual lives.     
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm back to my excited phase, no so much nervous at the moment...maybe more hyperactive than anything.  I  am  slightly concerned about the weather, but Danskin mentions that the race course may change (the run may shorten) if there is too much rain.  Let's just say that I would be the last to complain!     In my week of tapering off, I feel like a complete lazy bum!  Short swims, short bike rides...you name it.  I swam yesterday for about 45 minutes, and it wasn't even a great swim at that.  I'll swim once more before the big day, so hopefully it'll go better.    In the past 24 hours, I've received tons of great advice for Sunday.  Jessica has a co-worker who is in year-round tri training that was willing to offer me tons of advice for race day.  It was so nice to have an experience triathlete helping me out.  I also have another friend who has done a tri that has given me advice also.  There are lots of minor things I would never have thought of.  For example:  Jessica's co-worker mentioned taking a trash bag and a grocery bag to the race with me.  This is in case it rains (which is looking like a possibility at this point).  The grocery bag is to put over the bike seat (to keep it dry while I'm swimming) and the trash bag is to put my transition stuff in to keep it from getting wet.  Sounds pretty ingenious, but I had no clue!  There are tons of simple details like this that will help me tremendously.   I think I'm ready!!!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Strange...I think I've calmed my tri fears for a short while.  I've barely thought of it today.  I didn't even think about posting on the site until now...this is odd.  This must be the phase where I compose myself for a short while.  I called this morning and booked our hotel rooms for Saturday night.  Mike is going with me to help me out with my preparation and to be the wonderful supportive friend he is.  Also, having someone to drive home will be nice!  I'm sure I'll be exhausted.  I also found out yesterday that two of my girlfriends (Jessica and Jenni) are coming to Austin to watch me on Sunday. I'm so excited to have all this extra support.  There's really no way that I can talk myself out of the tri now!   As I said before, I plan to take this week fairly easy.  We went out of a bike ride yesterday afternoon and the plan to was to keep is short.  It ended up being shorter than we had intended, but the wind is was more miserable than usual yesterday.  I think it ended up around a 9 mile ride.  Mike made a good point though, it's only 3 miles less than my triathlon ride, so it suddenly sounds much better.  Mike's also starting to get sick on me, but refuses to quit training with me.  I'm planning on one more bike ride this week (tomorrow) and that should do me in...and hopefully he'll get better after that.    Other than easy training, I'm just trying to prepare and make sure I have everything I need for Sunday.  I've been making a checklist of things I need to pack, and researching all over the internet to make sure I'm not missing anything.  If anyone has any great words of advice, be sure and share with me...I'm up for any help at this point!  Oh, one more thing...I hope Mike doesn't mind me doing this.  If you're interested in seeing pictures of him completing his tri, you can go to  urlLink http://www.kreutzphotography.com/  and click on the first option "America's Triathlon and Capital of Texas Triathlon", then type in his race number "5022".  The pictures are awesome!
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      6 days to be exact. I'm trying not to think about it, but of course I can't seem to think of much else lately.  I'm planning to go super easy on my training this week so that I'm completely rested up on Sunday.  One of my legs has been bothering me again, so I don't plan to run at all this week.  I want to start my race with zero aches and pains.  I'm not concerned with how I will feel after the race, all I care about it completing it.    On Friday afternoon Mike and I went for a quick bike ride.  We did a little over 12 miles, just to refresh me on the distance.  It went really well.  Saturday my mom was in town, so my workout for the day was a nice hour long walk with her and Daisy.  It was a nice break, but this is also where I noticed my leg bothering me.    Yesterday (Sunday), Mike and I planned on biking at 3:00, and I decided on a quick swim beforehand, just to get the feel again for a swim/bike.  I swam for approximately 20 minutes, then went straight to the park where we start our biking.  I did my biking in my swimsuit with a pair of shorts pulled over so that I could try out being soaking wet on a bike.  It was actually kind of nice.  Having my hair wet kept it from going all over the place, and the water also cooled me off before and during the biking (it was awfully warm in Abilene yesterday).  I decided to try out a different brand of the gel shots yesterday, hoping to figure out what I want on race weekend.  The ones I tried yesterday tasted just as awful as the rest, but I felt a different kind of energy surge.  I wasn't like I was all hyper, it was more like I had super human powers.  I've been thinking a lot about my race times lately and plan to attempt the bike portion in less than an hour, so we decided to atleast keep the pace at 12 MPH yesterday.  This becomes more difficult in the wind, but I was able to maintain this speed the whole way out (the way back is the easy part...usually about 20-25 MPH with the wind).  Today is supposed to be more windy than yesterday, so I'm anxious to see how my speed is this afternoon.    Last night I went to watch a softball game and ended up playing...this may have done more harm than good.  My right arm is killing me today.  It probably didn't help that I stayed after the game to practice throwing.  Luckily I don't plan to swim until tomorrow, maybe the worst of the pain will be gone by then.  So much for super human powers...
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm not quite sure how excited I actually am about today being Friday...My weekends always fly by which means that before I know it, my race will be less than a week away. I still have that sick feeling every time I think about it.  I'm really hoping that I don't get sick race morning from nerves.  That would be just like me...   This was supposed to be my super heavy duty work out week, but has turned out more along the lines of a lazy week.  I did go swim yesterday afternoon, but that was all.  I swam some in Wills Point last week, but probably not enough to help me much.  I had trouble getting into a breathing pattern yesterday.  I figured out that my kicking was throwing me off.  Actually, that's a lie, my coach figured this out.  I was kicking with my knees rather than my thighs which was slowing me down tremendously.  It was also causing me to use up extra energy because I was kicking furiously trying to go faster, but getting nowhere.  This probably explains all of my problems yesterday.  I stayed and swam for about an hour and fifteen minutes, and I was back in the swing of things by the end of practice.  I only wish I had figured out all of this in the beginning of practice rather than the end.  The whole practice I felt like I was drinking the pool dry.  The bright side of this is that I'll have these things to think about when I go swim again (tomorrow or Sunday) so I can improve them and definitely not make the same mistakes.    The weather appears to have cleared up (for the meantime), so we're planning to ride this afternoon.  Although Mike has finished his race, he says he'll train with me until mine is over.  Hopefully he's had enough time to rest up since his race.   One more thing--I emailed Danskin yesterday and made some changes to my race category.  This whole time my focus has been on completing the race, therefore I registered for the "Recreational" category.  I couldn't stand it anymore.  I'm too competitive.  I need to see how I rank in my age group so that I will have a starting point for improvement.  I'm not planning to base too much on this ranking, as this is my first tri, but I still need it for self-improvement.  Danskin agreed to change my category to "Competitive Age Group", so here goes nothing...
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow, I can't believe it's already Thursday!  The countdown is on--if I'm counting correctly today, I only have 10 days left!  Jessica offered to be my "official counter", so I'll have to check my math with her--I'll get back with you on that one.  I'm definitely on the downhill side of my training.  I'm finally back in Abilene and ready to have four or five days of good hard training before I have to let up next week.  Being off work the first half of the week you'd think I would have plenty of time to fit in my workout, but no, I just found more to do.  My mom and I did get up early yesterday morning (7:30--hey, I was on vacation) and go to the track.  I did sprint drills again.  I didn't do as well as Monday, but I'm convinced these will pay off in the long run.  Although it is humid in Abilene at the moment, I'm glad to get out of East Texas.  I was sure the humidity was going to kill me.  It rained almost every night I was there, then it was hot and steamy during the day.  No thank you.  I'm ready for a hot and dry summer in Abilene.  When I drove into town yesterday afternoon the thermometer in my car kept switching between 98 and 99 degrees, which probably sounds miserable to some, but not me.  
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As of Tuesday afternoon, I am the proud owner of an '04 Specialized Allez Sport Trip road bike!  I am so excited!  I wanted so badly to ride it Tuesday, but I already has plans to go to bible study.  By the time that was over, it was already dark out--so I held on until yesterday.    Wednesday after work I met up with Mike (my tri-training partner) for my first ride.  It was great!  I love my bike!  I didn't want to over do it, but still felt the need to push myself, so we rode 15 miles.  The bike rode great.  I also ran yesterday morning, 4.5 miles, which is the furthest I've run in years.  The downside to all of this is that I forgot that my body needs extra calories to burn when I'm working out this much.  Around the last five miles of the bike ride, I started getting weak and shaky...symptoms of low blood sugar for me.  Luckily Mike had a granola bar on his bike that saved the day for me.  We're riding again this afternoon, so I'll be sure to take in a snack before riding.    I've decided that my first bike race (ride) is going to be the Tour de Gap in Buffalo Gap.  It's in 2 1/2 weeks.  I'm signing up for the 25 miles ride and hoping that I work myself up to 25 in time for the ride.  I think I should be fine...2 weeks to add 10 miles...hopefully no problem!    Assuming I remember, I plan to take a few pictures of my bike this afternoon, and I'll post them tonight or tomorrow.  It's so awesome--you're gonna love it!
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Im realizing that I never followed up on my Jawbreakers post from last week.  My jaw never actually showed a bruise (no complaints there), but it was sore for the remainder of the week.    I havent posted lately because theres still nothing to really talk about.  Today is more of a gripe session for me.  Im not in the best mood.  Ive been trying to increase my running distance lately.  I ran last week with some friends who are training for a half marathon.  I didnt run quite as far as them, but I increased my distance by about a half-mile.  My plan is to increase by about a half mile each week until I work myself up a few more miles.  Ive had a million things going on lately, so I was just able to get out and run again last night.  I thought it went really well.  My knee was bothering me slightly, but I had my brace on and thought it would be fine.  Well, I got out of bed this morning only to see that I could hardly stand on my left leg.  Here I am now, hobbling around, ready to break down and cry.  The cry is more for frustration than for pain.  Also, the pain is a little different and more intense than it has been for several months.  Usually if Im having a bad knee week, it only hurts when my weight goes on to the left leg.  Now it hurts when it bends as well as when I put my weight on it.  I hate to go back to my doctor because all hes going to say is that I need to rest it.  Right now, I prefer to ice my knee, take my Tylenol, and complain to anyone wholl listen (or read).    An exciting note for the week is that Im ready to buy my bike now.  Im still trying to decide which bike I need.  I think I know, but hate to invest so much money too quickly.    I hope Im not bringing anyone down with my complaining blog here.  We all know Im usually much more upbeat than this, but hey, we all have our daysright?   
     
    
</post>


</Blog>