<Blog>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       heyhey guys. nothin is really new with me at this time, but im sure something will happen soon. and when it does, ill get on. sorry that i havent been on in a while, my computer is screwed. still is but i got it to log on.  shout outs!  EMILOO! hey lozer! u never called back and they left. i had the perfect time to talk to them, and you never called back!!! i was sad. oh i found jon's house. woo hoo~ haha ill have to tell you the story later! cya  jon! haha sorry about the unexpected visit, i have to kno where everyone one of my sibblings freinds live. and you were next on the list! haha...well im gonna go, i have to reply to ur emaiL!   haha court court~ im talkin to you on the phone right now! haha well this means that i dont have much to say to u bcuz of the phone thing...haha i am confusing myself~!  EVERYONE DONT FORGET ABOUT WHAT I SAID IN THE FIRST POST ABUT THE 4TH!
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Thursday, June 17, 2004 heyhey guys! im back! i want to give a shout out to all of my friends! Emily~ haha i so wish i werent grounded! these crazy kidds, you so need to come over! haha! well hey ill try to get my daddy to give me one day off! i have been being really good!;)~!!! love ya~!  JON & DAN~ you guys ROCK! sorry i didnt swim with you, but uhm, you guys were being a lil crazy! i didnt make you nething to eat, cuz you never told me what you wanted! i would have done it to! oh and dan, i like the goggles! haha, and jon you hair looks so cool when its wet! i love it! come back over soon! oh and while im here, jon i will join speech! love you guys~!  Courtney~ i l0ve you to death baby! haha, neways, you can laugh at me all that you want to but i still like him! you dont kno him! haha i make everything include drama dont i? haha well i am gonn abe goin~ cya lata!~!   OK NOW THIS GOES TO EVERYONE! FORTH OF JULY I AM HAVING A JAMMIN' BASH! THERE IS NO OTHER LIKE MY BASH! SO GIVE ME A CALL AND I WILL LET YOU KNO IF WE HAVE ENOUGH FOOD FOR YOU TO COME! THANX AND HAVE A WONDERFUL EVENING~ I KNO THAT I WILL! HOTT BOYS HOTT BOYS~~!~ HAHA   ~Kat  // posted by Kaitlyn @ 8:28 AM  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>