<Blog>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just did some writing. It felt so good to return to my story. Good to know the muse is still there...
     

    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey! My first blog posting! This is pretty cool. Thanks, Matt S., for pointing me to this via your site. Well, where shall I start?  The job was pretty rough today (development editor for a publishing house). I was there for about nine hours and didn't get to have lunch with Melanie. Sorry, hun. I'll make it up to you next week. I saw Justin on the T today. It seems to be the place I meet up with everyone these days. It's always nice to have someone to talk to, rather stare off into space.   Now I'm just chillin at home with my cat. Perhaps I will write tonight.  This weekend should be fun. I'm going to get a tattoo tomorrow. Eeek! I'm definitely going through with it, though. I've wanted one for too long. Its my little reward after a hard semester.  Kris and Jay are coming to visit tomorrow. Yay! I'll get to see my "niece"!! We'll have dinner with Erica and David, then head over to Melanie's for a party. Sunday I'm going to walk in the Walk for Hunger. If you're interested in sponsoring me, drop me a line! If I'm still standing, its over to Pete's for a little Texas Hold'em!  The summer is finally here! Time to relax!
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ah, the end of a long weekend. It really wasn't long enough!  I was sick for all of last week and half of this weekend, which kind of put a damper on things. This apartment seems a lot smaller when you spend two straight days in it.  Thankfully, I was better on Sunday and could join the gang for bagels and a movie on Sunday. Then, it was off to the Cape to celebrate my Mom's b-day. Check out www.gostowe.com to see a picture that her friends put up just for her! I also got the opportunity to see my grandmother, who looked rather well.  By the way, I recommend that everyone go see Shrek 2 if you haven't already. I was in tears with laughter throughout the entire movie!  I got a chance to sit in the park and read on Sunday, as well. What a great way to spend an afternoon. There was a wedding party in the Gardens getting their pictures taken. They say that it's good luck to see a wedding. We'll see if some of that good luck comes my way.  Now, I'm just relaxing in my apartment and making some dinner. I'm trying to make mashed potatoes, but I don't have any margarine. I subsituted horseradish cheddar cheese. I'll let you know how that one goes. There's nothing like culinary creativity in a pinch!  I have seen quite a bit on t.v. about the war memorial for the WWII veterans. It's about time they finished that! In fact, I'm surprised we didn't have one sooner. It's unfortunate that so many veterans, such as my late grandfather, never got to see it. I know it would have meant a lot.  P.S. I neglected to mention in my last post that I did not write that poem. Actually, I don't know who did, so if anyone does, drop me a line and let me know.  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Have you ever wondered why Hollywood insists on rehashing the same love story over and over again? And yet, we still go to watch them. I just watched one of these movies. I can't even remembered what it was called, but it was the usual girl-gets-heart-broken-but-finds-solace-and-love-with-the-unlikely-guy-type story. It was predictable, trite, and lacking in thought.   But, I was glued to it. The hopeless romantic in me couldn't be pealed away from it. Why is that?   Perhaps these movies are like comfort food. They are safe and full of hope. I don't know. It's just a thought I had.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      After a while you learn the subtle difference      between holding a hand and chaining      a soul. And you learn that love doesn't mean leaning,      and company doesn't mean security. And you begin to learn that kisses aren't      contracts, and presents aren't promises. And you begin to accept your defeats      with your head up and your eyes open,      with the grace of a woman, not the grief      of a child. And you learn to build all your roads today,      because tomorrow's ground is too uncertain      for plans, and futures have a way of falling      down in midflight. So plant your garden and decorate you own soul      instead of waiting for someone to bring you flowers And you learn that you really can endure,      that you really are strong      that you really do have worth And you learn, and you learn. With every goodbye, you learn.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's been a long time since I wrote anything. What can I say? Life has been less than boring lately.  Last weekend, my best friend from high school (Charity) and her boyfriend came to visit. We had a blast! I took them all around Boston, including my favorite museum (The Isabella Stuart Gardner Museum). I think they had a really good time.  Well, they were having a good time until we stayed at Kevin's party until 4. The party was a blast, but we are all getting a little too old to drink that much and stay out that long. We were all hurting the next morning.  Despite that little hiccup in the weekend, I truly hope that I convinced them to move here! I would love to have Charity here all the time!  I have spent most of the week trying not to get sick. It didn't work. I have missed two whole days of work this week. I am incredibly behind on my projects. Eesh! I will definitely be going into work tomorrow. I'm actually looking forward to it, because no one will be there to interrupt me.  Well, this long weekend should be fun. I'm going clamming with my uncle Billy! I haven't seen him in a very long time because he lives in Mexico.  Right now, I'm just tired. Perhaps I will just curl up with my book for a while. It's very rainy and icky outside.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Congrats to all the couples who got married today! Double congrats to all of the politicians who made gay marriages possible in the state of Massachusetts! Let's just hope that we can keep them legal! Get out and vote in 2006!
     

    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, it rained today, so there was no ultimate frisbee. I'm a little bummed about that. I really need to join the gym this week so I can get some regular excercise again.  I just came back from Kris and Jay's. It was great to see them again. I missed Kris so much when she lived out west. It's wonderful to have her back. We were the best of friends in high school. I hope we can continue to be that close.  Ah yes, and yet another strange person decided to talk to me on the T the other day. Oddly enough it was the same guy who sat down next to Kevin at Bruegger's one morning and tried to strike up a conversation with us. All he really succeeded in doing was sitting on Kevin's scarf and throwing his hat dangerously close to my sandwich.   This time he started telling me about being called into work. I tried to excuse myself as politely as I could. Why do people on the T want to talk to me? I didn't think I looked lonely or anything.  Ug, I have that dazed and tired feeling you get when you have a sunburn. I spent a little too much time out on the patio at Tealuxe yesterday. I do have to sit out there more often, though. I love people watching on Newbury Street. Next time I'll wear sunblock, however.  Oh no! The loud lady who asks for money is back! I  have  to get to sleep tonight. She can't stand under my window again. She usually stays there until about 1am. Arrgh!
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, work is crazy lately. I'm going a lot of overtime. I look forward to when we start having half-days on Fridays. God knows I'll have wracked up enough overtime to take them.  Once again, its been a while since I have written anything. I need to stop that. I have just been so tired lately.  I got my first guitar lesson from Kevin. It went very well. I'm excited to start learning some songs. I feel like once I put the chords into context I'll be able to remember them better. I have a big problem with bar chords, though. My fingers just can't do them.  Jed came out with us to Anam Cara, it was so good to see him again! I love that I've been able to reconnect with him.   I'll be going to ultimate frisbee tomorrow and then on to Kris and Jay's for a barbeque. Yay! I get to see Alanna.  Well, now that classes are over, I've actually had time to think about things and what I've been doing with my life. I know I've made some bad decisions lately. I hope I can remedy them. I've pretty much decided that I need to start living life for myself, rather than for other people. I feel like in all the chaos of the last few months that I have lost myself, if that makes sense. I definitely need some me time.  If I could take the vacation time, I would totally just get away for a week. I have no idea where I would go, just somewhere where I could be by myself for a while. That would be great.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nothing like a good book....  I bought myself treats today:  A Lost Lady , by Willa Cather and Cold Mountain. It's so good to read for myself again!
     

    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got my first edited book back from the press today! What a great feeling to see the finished product. I'm particularly proud of this one because I got to pick the cover image.  While I'm on the subject of work, I would like to take this opportunity to say that editorial assistants are angels! They get to do all the funs stuff like photocopying, numbering pages, and ordering stock. I will miss them when they are gone after the summer!  Speaking of summer, what a fabulous day! Too bad I was inside for most of it.  Well tonight should be a quiet one. A little dinner, a little 24, perhaps some practice on the guitar. Kevin is giving me a lesson on Thursday. I'm psyched! I can't wait until I'm good enough to jam with him and Guy. 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yay! Hoobastank is on the radio! I love their new song....  Anyway, its been a while since I posted, so this is going to be a long one.  I spent most of the weekend with my parents on the Cape, it being Mother's Day and all. We did some female bonding (i.e. shopping) and had a nice dinner as a family. I also visited with my grandmother and managed to get through the whole visit without her finding out about my tattoo. Whew! I also got to catch up on my sleep.  I spent most of the week visiting with friends and staying up way past my bedtime. It was worth it, though. There was much fun and guitar-playing to be had.   I went to see  Van Helsing  on Friday with Jon and Justin. What an awful movie! We spent most of it laughing out loud. Note to self, no more Vampire/Wolfman movies.  Now I'm back at my apartment cleaning out my closet and trying to organize everything that I haven't gotten to since I moved in. I finally bought a chair! Now people can come to visit and they won't have to sit on my bed. That wasn't always a selling point, especially since I have a lot of guy friends.  My novel is coming along. Hopefully, I'll have a new chapter by the end of the week. Hopefully, the writing group will meet next weekend. I'm really excited where this one is going! 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Guy is back!! I just spent the evening hanging out with him and some other friends. It was great to see him again. I missed having my big brother around.  It was also nice to get to know Lyndsae a little better and to hang out with Kevin. I feel like I haven't been able to do that in a while.  Its just nice to know that I have such good friends.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It is both amazing and humbling how your opinion of someone can change so quickly. I spent an entire semester berating this one professor who just rubbed me the wrong way. Last week, he invited the class over to his apartment for a little dinner party. As reluctant as I was to go, I decided to give it a chance. Imagine my surprise when my professor turned out to be a rather interesting and likable guy. He is totally different outside the classroom. I guess it's just life's little reminder that everything and everyone should be given at least two chances.  This little reminder will have to carry over into my job. It seems like every other day I have a small moment when I want to throw in the towel. This one is going to take several chances, I think. I just have to keep reminding myself that I can only do my best. After all, I'm beginning to live out my dream. I'm actually an editor. To say that makes it all seem worth it.  As a little side note, I got to see one of my favorite views tonight (the Boston skyline at night as you travel over the Longfellow bridge).  I also got to smell one of my favorite flowers (lilac). It brought me back to Vermont in the Spring and the lilac bushes that used to grow under my bedroom window. Waking up to that smell is a better pick-me-up than coffee.  It's the little things that keep me going.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Whew! I just finished the Walk for Hunger! Well, I didn't really finish. My feet failed me at the halfway mark. Now I am totally beat!  Its been a crazy weekend! My tattoo looks great, and it didn't hurt all that much.   I had a blast at Melanie's party last night. It was really great to just sit and talk to everybody. I probably should not have stayed as long as I did, though. Getting up for the walk was pretty rough.  Well, it's time for a nap before I head off to poker....
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My friend sent me a list of ten things she loves lately as one of those chain things. Here is my list.  1) The way the air smells now that it's summer. 2) Running 3) Macaroni and cheese with tomatoes (Thanks, R2!) 4) Spontaneous outings 5) My new air conditioner (Thanks, Justin!) 6) Chatting with friends on YM 7) My blog 8) My new bathing suit, even though I haven't worn it yet. 9) Walking through the quiet streets of Brookline 10) THE RED SOX!!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, I was walking home from the grocery store, when I noticed a sign posted on a telephone pole. It was one of those homemade deals with the tabs cut into the bottom, each one with a phone number. The sign read "Private 'math' lessons available." The math was literally in parentheses. That got me to thinking, what does this person mean by quote-unquote math lessons and why are they so private? Hmmmm.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow! It's been way too long since I have updated this!   I have been practicing my guitar and getting a whole lot better. Now that I know some songs to practice, I really feel like I'm getting somewhere. Thanks Kevin! I owe you one!  I have also decided to look into opening my own bookstore. When I think about my future, I can't imagine it inside a cubicle for the rest of my career. I would love to be an editor, but perhaps I can do that freelance. What I can see is a little book store with big soft couches for customers to sit in. It would be a focal point where the community could gather. Cross your fingers for me!  Let's see, what else has been going on? I went to see Dodgeball on Sunday. What a hilarious movie. I cried laughing! I highly recommend it if anyone is in the mood to laugh 'til it hurts and not think too much!  I can't believe it's already the end of June! Please God don't let this summer fly by before I can enjoy it! I want to do a lot of hiking/camping/hitting the beach this year. If anyone is interested in joining me, drop me a line!  Well, happy summer everyone! 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, believe it not, I've been running a whole four times now. Who would have ever thought that I would like running? It's great, though. It helps with stress.  Well, this weekend was full of the usual shenanigans. A bunch of us went out to celebrate Kinney's birthday and to send of Ben in style. I must say that my pool game is very rusty. Jon's encouragement helped, though. Thanks, pal!  I had a marguerita that tasted like barbeque sauce. Very weird!  Frisbee was rained out once again. It turned out okay, though. I went running instead and ended up seeing Jed and Chris on the street. I haven't seen them in a little while, so it was a pleasant surprise!  I must say, I was rather shocked to hear the news of Ronald Reagan's death. Despite that fact that I was born during the Carter administration, I still think of the Reagan administration as the first one I lived through. His presidency had a huge impact on the decade of my childhood. I guess because he was such a political and cultural icon, I never really thought of him dying. Although, 93 is a pretty good run. I didn't realize he was that old.  Well, I am very tired and my shoulder hurts. I think I will turn in a little early tonight. My place is a total mess, but I think I'll ignore it for now. I need a little break.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      How silly of me, I forgot to give a shout-out to Kinney. Today is his birthday. Happy birthday, sweetie!  Okay, I have to go find my cat, now. It scares me when he disappears in an apartment that's only about 400 square feet in area.  Laurie
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got this strange and overwhelming urge to run today. I hate running, but I did it anyway. Get this, it actually felt good! What has come over me? Who am I?  Anyway, so after I ran, I cleaned and did other productive stuff like catch up on my e-mail correspondence. If this continues, I may end up doing something crazy, like cleaning off my desk!  Well, today was a dreary, cold day in Beantown. I'm dying for the sun to come out again! I want to go to the beach and rollerblade. (Not at the same time. Sand and rollerblades spell disaster.)  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went to Avalon last night to see The Black-Eyed Peas.&nbsp; They really put on a good show! Josh finagled a bunch of tickets from the Rock the Vote people, who were hosting the event along with the BEP record label. Jonathan invited me to come along.   What a night! We had no idea when we got there that there would be an open bar and a spread laid out. There was dancing until midnight, when the Black-Eyed Peas finally came on. They played for about an hour and half and they were amazing! I had an absolute blast. I owe Jonathan big time!  I am paying the price today, though. My ears are still ringing and I am about to fall asleep at my desk. 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I heard on the radio today that 77 percent of people in the Boston area decided to take their vacation this week to get away from the DNC. This is all too apparent when walking around the city. It is the strangest feeling! The trains are less crowded and all of the people you usually see walking around the streets or having their lunch on the Common are gone.  They have been replaced with police officers and very serious-looking people in red, white, and blue outfits. The normal traffic on the street has been taken over by taxi cabs, police cruisers, and large black cars with tinted windows.  It's an artificial Boston that these delegates have come to. Nothing is as it usually is this week. I wonder what kind of impression they will be left with when they hop back on their planes to go home. They'll remember a sterilized Boston with flowers running down Boylston street and no garbage cans to be found.   They won't know the true heart and grit of the city because it has been covered up in embarrassment. Even the protesters have been shuffled off to a quiet corner. 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Updates:  My sister is engaged! Her girlfriend proposed last week!  I have a new job! I'm going to be a grade level editor for a small development group. I'm am beyond excited!  I won a Red Sox jersey autographed by Kurt Schilling.  Congrats to Erica for getting a new job as well!  &nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ah, life in the city....  Yet another strange person decided to talk to me on the T. This lady wanted to know what my height was, because sitting down I looked to be exactly the same height as she. I told her I was 5'4" and she declared that she was 5'7".  "Are you sure?" she asked, surprised at my answer.  "Yes," I answered and tried to go back to my book.  "That's actually a normal height, you know."  "I know." Clearly, there was no getting back to my book.  "Do you mind being 5'4"?" Now this was just getting ridiculous.  "It makes no difference to me," I said. In truth, it had made a difference, once upon a time. Being one of the shortest in your grade school class definitely has its disadvantages. But, this was an insecurity I had long since gotten over. Furthermore, I was not about to admit this to the strange lady sitting next to me, assessing my height. I just wanted to read my book!  Finally, she was distracted by a woman carrying a Nordstroms bag. She struck up a conversation about the location of the nearest store and I was left to  The Life of Pi . (As an aside, it's a very good book.) 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I learned three very important lessons today:   1) Never run after eating pizza.   2) Never sleep on your arm the wrong way and then try to do anything with it.   3) Before they were the Red Sox, the Boston baseball team was called the Pilgrims and they won the very first World Series ever played. This World Series was played on what is now the Northeastern University campus.   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I bused it down to NYC this weekend to help Rachel celebrate her 25th birthday. I had a fabulous time! I got in Friday night and after I made it to her apartment, we had one of our marathon talk sessions. Saturday, we walked all around the Times Square area and did a bit of shopping in preparation for her party.  Her friends, her sister, and I took her out to this very trendy-looking restaurant for her birthday. (Gina and I are right! That waiter wasn't gay!) Then we headed to the Village where we met up with more friends, including Emersonians I had not seen in forever! We then proceded to take over the bar. They were playing great dance music. There was no dance floor, but that's never a problem for Emersonians. We just made one of our own and had the whole place hopping!  Around 2, when I suddenly realized that things don't close that early in New York, we left the bar and went back to Rachel's with Gina, Jen, Justin, and Jared (how alliterate). We talked until about 4:30 in the morning. What a great night!  It was wonderful to see the people I knew and I loved meeting all of Rachel's amazing friends! They all want me to move to New York when I graduate. Hmmmm.....an interesting thought.  Two things I learned about New York this weekend: Every place delivers, including McDonald's. Delis and pizza shops stay open 24 hours. Amazing!  I am now thoroughly beat, having only gotten about 5 hours of sleep and braved the Greyhound bus system back here to Boston. Milo has finally settled down. (He's curled up in a Trader Joe's shopping bag.)  I think I'll go to bed super early, so I can get lots of stuff done tomorrow.  P.S. I promised I would return to NYC in August. I already can't wait!
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, tonight I got to hang out with Mike Boland, a guy I haven't seen since I left VT, eight years ago. It was wonderful to see him, again. He was my buddy during the Lamoille County Players' production of  Grease . He was Sonny and I was Patty Simcox. Jed (aka Johnny Cool) was with us as well.  We saw Spiderman 2, which I had already seen on Friday. It was such a great movie that I didn't mind seeing it again, especially if it meant hanging out with yet another Vermonter. There's something about hanging out with those guys that is comforting. I guess it's because they understand where I'm coming from.  After the movie, Jed mentioned that he thinks I look a little like Kirsten Dunst. I found that both amusing and extremely flattering. Good luck at your audition tomorrow, Jed.  Ug, work tomorrow. I dread the piles of projects that await me on my desk. Tomorrow will definitely be a long day. Well, it's off to bed for me. I am thoroughly exhausted and I feel pretty sick right now.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      All I can say is, what a strange day. I started out feeling great. I was hanging out with some of the people I cared most about in the world. I ended up watching the fireworks through tears. Why do I do this to myself?
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      On a whim, Melanie, Kinney and I went to the Esplanade to watch the Pops dress rehearsal. We had no idea David Lee Roth would be there to sing "California Girls" and best of all, "Jump"! What a great concert it turned out to be. The evening was beautiful and we just sat on the water, looking at the city lights and listening to the music. I love this city!  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>