<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Off today - hope you are as well. We'll be back tomorrow. Have a safe and happy Memorial Day. 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This morning I wanted to briefly discuss crafting a job description (needs analysis) when working with recruiters.  To help you - as a recruiter I will definitely want to know about the core competencies required for the job, experience level required, educational background etc and why the vacancy exists.  But I will also want to know who else is on the team and for how long, what are their strengths and weaknesses?  What would happen if one of them left...what is the next most critical skill set required?  A good recruiter will ask a LOT of questions.  We want to know and understand what you really need.  Sometimes you won't know and that's ok.  We work together to find out.    So the next time you have a vacancy begin to think about other members of the team, their core competencies and strengths, so the new hire is a complement to the team instead of just the new hire.  Have a safe and happy holiday weekend.  Lucia 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I spoke to a VP of Human Resources for a large company last week who had signed on 15 contingent recruiting firms to assist his in-house recruiters to fill quite frankly, a lot of new jobs.  He was becoming frustrated because of the amount of time updating all of these firms was beginning to take.  On top of that, many of the firms were overlapping with one another and beginning to submit the same candidates.  How is this helping the organization that hired on these firms?  I don't think it is. When trying to decide whether to go to a retained search firm or a contingent one...you have to think of many things - especially the value of your time.  Many firms offer a hybrid approach - we call them engagement fees.  You put a deposit down and pay the balance upon the new hire being made.  Our firm charges for example, a modest $295 down and it's applicable toward the total search fee upon placement.  Why do we do this?  We do it primarily to get your attention, to engage you in this process which goes very well provided there aren't 15 other firms involved.  I understand the need to work with more than one firm in the event we're talking about filling multiple positions. And some firms specialize in different areas as well.  But in selecting search firms, remember to work with those recruiters who work well independently - provide good updates and don't need to talk with you every day for a status update unless there is a need to do so.  By the way, as recruiters, it's our job to find out where our candidates are interviewing and where they've been submitted whether we are retained or contingent.  It wastes an awful lot of time (worth money!) when we don't do our jobs well.....and it doesn't help you, the hiring managers in the least.  If this is happening to you - it might be time to talk with your recruiters or account managers.  Have a question?  Just ask... http://www.askhireworks.com    
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Morning,   I realize it may be difficult due to volume to confirm receipt and/or acknowledge each applicant who contacts your company.  But you MUST do this.  Your IT folks should be able to set up autoresponders to work with your ATS to make your life easier.   However, please put some thought into the verbiage used in these acknowledgements.  I'm going to assemble some of the worst I've seen and publish them soon.  Remember, some of these applicants will be people you are interested in and you leave a lasting impression on people with not only your first contact/correspondence but all of them.    Those of you with access to your marketing departments should really get them involved.  Strong verbs, empathetic - caring language - personalized messages (even addressing them by first name in autoresponder thanking them for their interest) should be used here.  I'll get some examples to show you and post soon.  Thanks for reading and make it a great day!  Lucia 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I receive emails about once a week from LabSitesOnline.  They offer a $125 gift certificate usually to Walmart, Home Depot etc. if you purchase a job posting.  If you decide not to elect a gift certificate you get a discount on your posting and it's only $170 instead of the $295.    I find this interesting.  I don't think this appeals to most corporate clients, and wonder if this isn't having more success with independent recruiters (like myself).  I haven't personally posted a job and will not do so. I don't believe posting jobs on traditional or even niche boards is effective anymore.  Posting to a job board is like playing darts.  You have no idea really who will see your ad and how well the site is actually optimized. And you are dependent upon people contacting you. Most candidates who will contact you as a result of a posting will generally be those with issues.  Maybe it's a work history (lots of jobs all the time).  Maybe a license has lapsed.  Maybe they were terminated at one time.  I'm not saying this is always the case....but usually there is something.   The best way to source candidates is still in my opinion by referrals from those who are excellent, above average performers.   But if anyone out there has tried this board...please share your feedback and I'll post for the group.    Best wishes,  Lucia 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Morning!  He who interviews best gets the job? Hmmm, not sure I totally agree.  Let me explain.    I found a great site today by accident really.  A former pharma rep who became a recruiter is really offering a great value to potential candidates who want to break into the pharma sales field. I applaud Pat Riley (although I don't know him) for providing valuable information to interested candidates and putting in place a system for his business.  However, as a hiring manager, do you really want to hire someone who interviews well or who WILL DO WELL on the job?  That's not to say a good interviewer won't perform well on the job....but it can go the other way as well.  When interviewing a candidate, be sure you are asking questions that will give you an idea of future - predictable behavior.  Be sure this individual is motivated, excited and driven. Ask for specific examples of how they handled challenging situations in the past.  What happened, how did they react...if they didn't handle it well - but would have now ask why.  What did they learn as a result and what would they do differently now.  Ask them how a colleague and/or a customer would describe them.    What we are after is high performers - strong leaders.  Sometimes they may not always be the best interview...at least initially.  After a bit they will open up, relax..ask good questions and show you who they are.   Wishing you more fun and success with interviewing...  Lucia   
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         urlLink   
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I talk with candidates looking (and sometimes not looking) for new and interesting career opportunities every day.  Many of the candidates I talk with are leaving a current post because of a conflict or unhappiness with a manager they report to.  What does that mean to you Company XYZ?  Your most talented staff members may not be quitting you when they leave, but they are quitting their manager!    Of course this topic runs deep and is one we can discuss further so you can remedy it. But as turnover increases (and it will!) be sure you are conducting exit interviews to see WHY people are leaving.  You can outsource the function to make it confidential or have HR staff conduct them for you.    In the era we're in with labor shortages rapidly approaching (and worsening e.g. healthcare) you need to be able to invite former staff back into your organization.  Be sure to take the time to find out why they left in the first place and see if it's something that can be fixed. Asking questions is still the best way to learn what we do not yet know.  Feedback and comments welcome....  Lucia   
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink The Hiring Insider  
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    HireWorks...helping you make better hires faster.&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       New, Improved - Hooray!   Hot Job!  Business Development Rep - CRO Experience Required - Work from home!   I’m pleased to be working with a client who was named one of Fortune's 100 Best Companies to Work for in 2004.    We’re seeking an innovative and motivated Business Development Representative to sell the services their research division has to offer clients worldwide.  Your role?  Expand a current customer base as well as establish new business in the field of clinical research.   Qualified candidates should have a minimum of three years experience in a CRO environment selling services (Phase I-IV). Strong project management skills and proposal writing skills are a must. The team includes 4 Business Development Associates each reporting to Director of the department. For profit organization, campus/academic setting.    Would you like to join a team of professionals in clinical research where there has been very little turnover, excellent support for research to prepare bids, quotations and proposals? Interested in experienced clinical staff to travel with you to sell your services?   Please send resume and cover letter to my attention at lshaw@hire-works.com.  Tell me about the types of projects you sell and service, therapeutic areas of interest, as well as what preferences you may have.   Compensation plan includes generous base PLUS bonus and full benefits package.  Should you choose to relocate to client site, relocation assistance is provided.  If you have a friend or colleague who may be interested, please feel free to have them get in touch with me.   Lucia Apollo Shaw Recruiter lshaw@hire-works.com   Have a question? www.askhireworks.com  HireWorks, Inc. www.hire-works.com   Toll Free: (866) 960-3411  Phone:    (919) 960-3411  FAX:       (919) 960-3413        
    
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Niche Boards vs. the Big Boards  I received an email today from topusajobs.com stating niche boards hiring more than 10x the number of candidates than do the big boards (e.g. www.hotjobs.com).  Well I should hope so!  The big boards account for LESS than 6% of hires made on average.  That figure is so low it's not worth the time you take to set up an account and post the job.    This email was promotional however, it did attempt to list a diversified list of sites, among them www.latpro.com, a site focused on diversity recruiting - specifically Latino candidates.  Please submit your favorite niche sites to me at lshaw@hire-works.com.  I'd like to do a post and survey to publish and share with readers.  Make it a great day!  Lucia 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Job Posting - Do I Dare?  In today's mail I received a coupon from monster.com offering me 2 free job posts if I post 5.  The promo copy compares the value of a job posting on monster.com to a posting you might place in your local or a regional newspaper.  Monster applauds its screening tools and comments that in a newspaper ad anyone can apply and you cannot screen them out.  Well, screening tools on the internet are a far cry from screening anyone out.  I have used several job boards (in the past...I never use them now) and anyone really can still post a resume online and apply to your posting causing you HOURS of work filtering through all of the unqualified candidates.  I can almost guarantee you that within 1 hour (yes 1 hour) of posting a position to monster.com you are likely to receive over 50 resumes and that number will surely be closer to 100 by the end of the 1st 24 hour period. Ask yourself, do I have time to post a position and deal with all that comes with it?  Sites like monster definitely have their place in the search space.  I think they are great places for image advertising (good value really for that) and posts here are a great tool to see if folks really can follow directions, use email, attachment features etc.  Posts are great for retail and hospitality positions when it's also important to you that future team members are computer literate.  I welcome comments and questions from readers...email me at lshaw@hire-works.com.  Make it a great day! 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Getting "Linked In"  I'd like to invite those of you who have not checked out http://www.linkedin.com to do so.  It's an excellent way to search for candidates if you are a recruiter.  It's also a great way to network and do research for companies you think you'd like to do work for.  If you are looking for a new position, job, career, you can post a resume on-line as well so we can find you!    I'm a Spoke (http://www.spoke.com) user as well, but must admit that I much prefer the ease of use on LinkedIn.  Spoke's support however is fantastic.  I emailed with a question and got a call back the very same day from a member of the support team.   Remember, if you are looking for work - job boards are not the only vehicle.  Do research in your field.  Use boolean search strings, look for blogs like these (and others).  If you are a life sciences professional I recently discovered an exellent resource www.dnajobs.com.  Very organized list of positions by specialty and state.  If you have a great resource you'd like to share, email me at lshaw@hire-works.com so I can post it for others.  Have a great day!   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Free Webinar, The Future of Hiring, sponsored by Deploy Solutions will be held May 18th, from 2-3pm EST.  Guest host is Lou Adler, industry expert and author of "Hiring with your Head".  Lou is a great presenter, speaker with over 30 years experience in the field.  Not to be missed!  Register at www.deploysolutions.com.  Lou always has a Q&A session at the end of each call....and usually a download of the webinar...great value...!  See you on the call. 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Applicant Tracking, Talent Management - Deploy Solutions  
    
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Pharmiweb.com | The Heart of Life Sciences on the Web  
    
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Blog Search Engine - Blog Directory, Blog Search, Blog Directories - Add Link  
    
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Good morning!  After much work, the first issue of our monthly ezine is now available.  The Hiring insider, helping you make better hires faster.  To subscribe please visit http://www.hire-works-forhire.com and sign up for our newsletter.  Or, send us an email at info@hire-works.com.  We look forward to your feedback.  Make it a great day.  
    
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Pharmiweb.com | The Heart of Life Sciences on the Web  
    
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Pharmiweb.com | The Heart of Life Sciences on the Web  
    
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Google Toolbar  
    
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Hot Jobs!   We're pleased to be working with a client who was named one of Fortune's 100 Best Companies to Work for in 2004.   We’re seeking an innovative and motivated Clinical Trials Account Manager to sell the services their research division has to offer clients worldwide.  Your role?  Expand a current customer base as well as establish new business in the field of clinical research.  Qualified candidates should have a minimum of three years experience in a CRO environment selling services (Phase I-IV). Strong project management skills and proposal writing skills are a must. The team includes 4 Business Development Associates each reporting to Director of the department. For profit organization, campus/academic setting.   Would you like to join a team of professionals in clinical research where there has been very little turnover, excellent support for research to prepare bids, quotations and proposals? Interested in experienced clinical staff to travel with you to sell your services?   Please send resume and cover letter to my attention at lshaw@hire-works.com.  Tell me about the types of projects you sell and service, therapeutic areas of interest, as well as what preferences you may have.  If you have a friend or colleague who may be interested, please feel free to have them get in touch with me.   Lucia  lshaw@hire-works.com  
    
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        
    
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        INSIDER TIP 1:  LEARN HOW TO THROW A BOOMERANG   Welcome to the Hiring Insider.  Let's begin to build you a Hiring Toolkit  you can use .  We'll archive all posts and assemble tips and tools into a toolkit you can access, so don't worry if you are trying to figure out where to store these ideas!  Besides, you must admit you’re curious about the proper way to throw a boomerang?     “The boomerang effect” is a relatively new trend of inviting back talented former employees into the fold.  Surveys indicate 12% of employers cautiously admit they would re-hire ex-employees (alumni).  An additional 21% say they welcome back alumni without hesitation because of the time and dollar savings.  In fact, the Gartner Group estimated that in 2003, 60% of midsize to large companies will have routinely hired back former employees.  Here are four simple strategies you can consider to reclaim lost talent swiftly:   	Keep your alumni on your press release distribution list.  Keep them in the loop!   	Send current and former employees alike a list of your job openings!   	Invite alumni to company picnics, holiday parties, and other casual, festive events!   	Keep lines of communication OPEN.  At the very least, you want these people might to refer other talented candidates your way.    Remember, they’re going to talk either way. Why not help your own cause?    Watch for a new tip or tool each week.  To contact me directly, please email (me) Lucia at lshaw@hire-works.com.   To ask us a question, please visit our new ASK page (complete with images and sound!) http://www.askhireworks.com.   
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Part II of your search plan should be a summary or approach of the process.  Possibly the first step will be an initial review of job description (s) and maybe even the complete life cycle of the current recruitment process.  Next you will want to identify who will be involved in the interview process and why.  Map the process out on a whiteboard with targeted deadlines (or desired dates for completion). Will you need someone to start by a drop dead date for cross training (before the outgoing ee leaves)?  Or is there a manager the person must meet before going to Japan for a month? This is a time to check everyone's calendar and avert disaster whenever possible!  Be sure that you and your recruitment team are clear on who is responsible for what.  If travel arrangements and interview times need to be scheduled don't lose time figuring out who is responsible for the workflow. Likewise, who will be extending the offer to the candidate and checking references; will you need a background check, health screen, credit or licensing check?  I usually present my written search plan to clients for a sign off just after we sign a contract to proceed with the work. That way before going forward we're on the same page about what will happen next.   Part III to follow tomorrow.....make it a great day. Lucia 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This week I'd like to review the 5 elements in a solid search plan.  I thought I'd break it down and do one part each day for a series this week. On Friday I'll post a full mock plan.   When working with an executive level recruiter you will have an  initial phone consultation  which is generally followed by a written search plan so both parties are on the same footing and in agreement about the search process going forward.  The phone consultation should review why the vacancy exists, who else is on the team and what strengths are we seeking in a new addition to the team. Is the position actually approved and what will the interview process look like (who will be involved, who will make the offer and when do you need someone to start)?  In a written Search Plan HireWorks, Inc. (my company) first reviews your needs summary.   I. Needs Summary   This should summarize your information about the position, location, title, number of positions, salary range, work environment etc.   Skills and competencies required should be listed next.  I typically use adjectives and phrases listed in a series to be sure I've hit on all areas of interest to my client.  This includes  minimum  requirements such as degree required, years of experience, software knowledge etc. But it also lists for example, critical thinking skills, ability to work independently or from home.  I'll speak to motivation levels and attitude required as well.    Tomorrow I'll review Part II of the Search Plan - Suggested Work Plan (Process).  Questions and comments are welcome.   Lucia lshaw@hire-works.com 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Bear with me today - I'm reprinting an article in its entirety today...good read. Enjoy.    Make Use Of The Calm Before The Storm    By: Bill Larkin    This article originally appeared on HR.com.    The primary motivator for employee loyalty over the last three years has been fear – fear of being downsized, and fear of not being able to find another job. But as signals of an improving job market continue to flash, thousands of employees who have been rooted in their jobs are plotting to free themselves. The market tide is turning in favor of the workforce, and experts say few employers are ready for it.  If you don’t believe it, consider this: in a survey conducted by Accenture, 40 percent of U.S. workers say they plan to leave their current job within the next five years. A recent AOL survey paints an even grimmer picture; in which 58 percent of more than 5,000 participants said they “may” or “will definitely” start looking for a new job when the economy improves. Why are these numbers so high? The need for financial cutbacks forced many organizations to neglect programs that are essential to employee retention. The Accenture survey says it all: respondents cited lack of compensation (71 percent), advancement opportunities (58 percent), and professional development or training (51 percent) as the primary reasons for seeking new employment.    Despite the renewed focus on employee retention that 2004 is expected to bring, many experts say the damage has already been done. “We are entering a dynamic period for the employment market,” says Ed Jensen, a partner in Accenture’s Human Performance Service. “Employers need to protect themselves from raids on their talent in order to remain competitive.”   It stands to reason, then, that there are two main challenges looming on the horizon: acquiring only the best of the candidates you will need sooner than you think, and keeping the best of those you have. Ironically, these burdens will fall upon one of the hardest-hit departments in your organization: human resources.    Pan for gold It’s hard to believe that a short time ago, HR professionals – and the organizations they work for – were used to shelling out 30 percent search fees to agencies in the hopes of securing a high-quality candidate to fill one of their many open requisitions. Now, there is no room in many budgets for outside help in the hiring process, and there’s less time and manpower to do the legwork internally. For those HR departments that find themselves short-handed due to recent downsizing and attrition, the thought of a renewed focus on recruiting is surely a cause for concern.    Despite the popular assertion that the current market is still flooded, finding the right candidate is harder than it may seem. “The writing is on the wall,” asserts Scott Cohen, national practice leader for talent management at Watson Wyatt Worldwide. “Organizations will increasingly compete for the smartest and the best individuals.” And they’ll have to hunt pretty hard for them, like the proverbial needle in a growing haystack. A recent report issued by Challenger Gray & Christmas Inc. maintains that 92 percent of recruiters and hiring managers were inundated with irrelevant responses via the Internet, and 71 percent said a majority of the resumes they received in response to an online job posting did not match the job description. The increasing demand for resume and recruiting management is poised to overwhelm an HR department that has already been reduced by layoffs. How does the already overburdened HR professional handle and evaluate resumes to fill critical positions from a shrinking pool of contenders with less help on a tighter budget? Most major and many smaller companies have already automated their recruiting and applicant tracking processes. Those that have not need to make it a top priority.    The ideal solution should provide integrated applicant management capabilities that not only streamline the hiring cycle, but also enable hiring managers to identify the best candidates more quickly and cost-effectively. The idea is not to replace human judgment, but to support decision makers by automating repetitive tasks and increasing the efficiency of those high-touch activities that cannot be automated. Managers may even use self-service to hire applicants on the spot, an important capability in environments where demand can dictate rapid bursts of hiring, such as retail.    Do your homework In desperate times, people may take desperate measures: some people will do anything it takes to land a job, up to and including fabricating degrees, work experience, previous earnings, and qualifications. Even worse than including phony accomplishments, they may leave out negative information that would typically disqualify them. In an era that has uncovered – too late – a high-profile college football coach who exaggerated both his college and football experience and an armed robber turned board chairman of a major firearms manufacturer, it’s frightening to imagine how many covers have yet to be blown. While some of these stories are benign enough, the wrong person in the wrong job can cause real harm, and when that happens, the damage to everyone involved can be devastating. How can organizations avoid hosting the next big scandal, or worse? By understanding how to legally and accurately verify candidate credentials, and making the effort to do it consistently.    With less HR staff in place to perform extensive background checks, is it worth the time it takes? Absolutely. Even one bad hire can do some serious damage. LeRoy Robbins, CEO of recruiting specialists IIRC, claims that the hard costs are estimated at “50 percent to 200 percent of that person’s salary and benefits,” not to mention the soft costs of an increase in workload and its accompanying decrease in company morale and customer service. “As you move up the line, bad hires become more significant because of the impacts of their roles. Having to replace that person is enormous,” explains Robbins.    Beyond the responsibility to the organization itself, there are legal duties to consider, such as taking the proper steps to avoid hiring an unfit individual who causes harm. Negligent hiring processes, discrimination, and invasion of privacy can all lead to costly grievances and lawsuits. At the 21st Annual Employment Law & Legislative Conference, Wendy Bliss, J.D., SPHR discussed effective pre-employment screening practices. Depending on the requirements of the position being filled, all of these methods may be appropriate: multiple reference checks; verification of the last 5 to 7 years of work history; criminal background checks; a social security number trace, examination of education and motor vehicle records; and credit, professional license, certification, or registration checks when job-related and validated. She also recommends checking the applications over for any of the following red flags: blanks, unexplained gaps in employment, questionable reasons for leaving prior jobs, illegible writing, no signature, information that is inconsistent with the applicant’s resume, and multiple people listed who may not be contacted for a reference. Because every state’s laws differ slightly, it is vital that employers familiarize themselves with the specific requirements governing reference immunity, service letters, use of criminal history, and other related issues for any and all of their locations.    Stay ahead of the pack As the job market continues to improve, employers will find themselves once again catering to the best and brightest talent. “Employers have been less careful about how they treat their employees because they know there is a ready supply out there,” says Sharon Koss, SPHR, president of Koss Management Consulting in Seattle, WA. “They have forgotten what turnover is, how expensive it can be, and how hard it can be to find good people.”    They’ve also forgotten how much good people can cost in a competitive market. To avoid getting burned, employers need to first make sure that all current employees are fairly compensated, and when a position comes open, consider hiring from within. In many cases, the best person for the job may be lurking a few cubes down. This is another scenario in which an automated system can make a world of difference. With a comprehensive in-house talent pool just a couple of clicks away, recruitments costs are significantly slashed. This makes it easier for organizations to promote top talent, fostering higher employee engagement, and improving the retention of key employees.    Then, organizations should start putting in place a system by which they can ensure the compensation packages they offer are competitive, but also fall within the parameters of their budget requirements. For example, are you able to quickly measure the value of a candidate’s total compensation package (salary, benefits, bonuses, etc.) against your budget for the position? Can you compare packages you are offering against industry compensation data, salary surveys, and internal jobs before an offer is made to the candidate? Can you easily take into account the geographic pay differentials that exist based on the candidate’s work location?    It’s a lot of work, but a system of compensation “checks and balances” is critical to preventing your company from overpaying or under-competing for talent. Fortunately, there are applications available that can automate much of the legwork that needs to take place in order to assemble sensible but competitive compensation plans. In fact, some organizations have used applications and the accessibility of data to take a less traditional approach to compensation.    According to Edward Lawler, a professor at the University of Southern California’s Marshall School of Business, many organizations are using the availability of compensation data combined with automated employee performance management to develop competency-based compensation systems. It attracts employees who like the notion that, if they work hard, they know how and when they will be rewarded. It also prevents the loss of talent, which is perhaps even more important. “A competency-based system helps an organization achieve its goals,” explains Lawler. “When it is structured right, it rewards top performers and keeps many of them from leaving.” Companies that do not provide the right rewards and opportunities, however, wind up priming their talent for the competition.    Watch where you’re going Many organizations are blissfully unaware that they are currently suffering from a false sense of security; in fact, most organizations believe that when the employee exodus does happen, it will happen to some other company. It won’t be long before that illusion is shattered. As the pendulum begins to swing back in the opposite direction, savvy employers who anticipate its movement can survive, or even thrive, by taking preemptive actions to retain their proven performers while they attract and groom the best of those candidates who have begun to test the waters of the recovering job market. By providing the appropriate rewards and opportunities to seasoned in-house talent and offering competitive compensation plans to meticulously screened prospects, your organization can ride the wave of the impending upheaval while your competition struggles just to weather it.   About the Author:  In his role as Vice President of HRMS Solutions, Bill Larkin’s current charter is to drive Kronos’ success in the Human Resource Management System (HRMS) market. In June 2002, Kronos entered the middle tier of the HRMS market with licensed HR and payroll products, which complement Kronos’ existing suite of employee resource management solutions.    Larkin brings to Kronos extensive consulting, sales, product development and marketing skills honed during a 20-year career in human resources, in which he held positions with Automatic Data Processing (ADP) and Genesys Software Systems.    Prior to joining Kronos, Larkin founded LCS and Associates, a consulting firm specializing in HRMS end-user requirements definition and vendor selection. Larkin also has helped a number of software vendors develop and expand their HRMS strategy. Larkin was a co-founder of the eClipse Group, a consulting firm formed as a joint venture between the Human Resource Management Consultants and LCS and Associates.    Larkin is an active member of the International Human Resource Management Association and the Northeast Human Resource Association. He holds a bachelor’s degree in business administration from Iowa State University.    
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The Triangle business journal reports that a recent survey conducted by Manpower states employers are looking to hire big in the 3rd quarter.  The paper reported:  "From July to September, 47 percent of the companies interviewed plan to hire more employees while 3 percent intend to reduce their work force, the survey says. Fifty percent expect to maintain their current staffing levels.  Nationally, 30 percent of the 16,000 U.S. employers polled said they planned to add new employees, with 6 percent expecting a decline in the number of jobs."  Call your recruiting partners and prep us with projected needs and timelines.  The more we know, the better able we are to assist you.  Looking forward to hearing from you!   
    
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Good morning,   Many people want to know just what is the difference between HeadHunters, Exec Recruiters - third party recruiters and so on?   Well, typically we are all self employed and do not work for a corporation we've been hired to staff - we're a third party provider. Some recruiters don't like to be called HeadHunters, doesn't bother me in the least.  We are hired to do what companies cannot or will not do for themselves.  Research positions, the market and target candidates who will become strong achievers for that organization.    I did a quick google search this morning and many searches are being done each day for all of the above titles and keywords daily.  In fact, the daily budget google recommends for an AdWord campaign is $750/day.  So that tells you about the level of interest and the intensity of searching for recruiters to call most days of the week.  If you are looking for a recruiting partner, give us a call.  We'd be happy to do an initial 30 minute (free) consultation to see if we might be a resource for you.  Best wishes,   Lucia 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Good morning!  Is your recruiting process going well? Is your recruiter(s)responsive and do they understand what you need? Are you happy with the flow of candidates, scheduling of feedback and interviews?  What is missing from the process and what can we (recruiters) do better to serve you?  Recruiting is a  service  you pay for.  You pay us to make it go away!  I tell my clients they should feel a huge weight lifted from their shoulders once they sign my fee agreement.  At that point I own the process and update them along the way. It is no longer their primary concern or worry.  They can move on, perform other duties and know that they'll hear back from me with status updates.  We want your feedback!  Is recruiting what you think it should be? Where do we have room for improvement?   Suggestions and feedback welcome.  Look forward to hearing from all of you out there!  Make it a great day.  Best, Lucia 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I subscribe to ERE Exchange - a group/forum for recruiters.  Each day there is a feature article and while most are quite good, written by Dr. John Sullivan, Mr. Lou Adler and other professionals, today's article was awful.  For many reasons, articles like today's and recruiters like the one featured, is why I remain a recruiter.  Recruiting is tough work and some days even life insurance salespeople are treated better than we are...but articles like those found today are why!  Actually if you can get past the first paragraph of the article I do agree with most of what Mr. Adamsky says.  Sales is service...if you believe that and act that way then there is no need to be shark-like and use terms like Eat what you Kill. Just God Awful if you ask me.  People do business with those they like, know and trust.  I think the words you choose to represent yourself and those in your profession should be chosen carefully.  Tip of the day:  Be sure you LIKE, KNOW (or get to know) and TRUST the recruiter you are working with.  I promise it will be much more fun!  Best wishes,  Lucia 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So you've now got a sexy, exciting job posting written...   Where do you place the post to get your hire?   First of all, be sure that you comply with corporate policies and procedures and if required to do a 3 or 5 day internal posting for existing employees that you do so.   Then you can have some fun placing the ad/post where your target population is hanging around.    Ideas include:    User groups/forums  Google AdWords or Yahoo Overture (PPC) text ads  Flyers for bulletin boards in coffee shops, wireless cafes etc.  Blogs!  Audio Postcards Niche web sites (don't forget the diversity sites to target women and minority groups).  Job Boards (depending upon the type of position).  Print job announcements on pay stubs, in company newsletters and more.   There are many more ideas of course - brainstorm and track your results.   We'll cover tracking and ROI tomorrow....     
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Writing Job Descriptions that  pull  - that folks  want to read ... That's today's topic.   Job postings, position descriptions, ads whatever you'd like to call them should be written from a sales or branding perspective. What are you trying to accomplish with these posts? We want folks to call or email us a resume right? Well then STOP posting job requirements that top candidates will never respond to.      Job posts should be interesting and lead the reader like a good title does a news story.&nbsp;&nbsp; Your post should be full of action verbs and questions...   Example:   Seeking energetic multi-tasker who likes to interact with others! Does this sound like you?  Issue a challenge in the post:  Would you get excited to be charged with the task of decreasing downtime by 10% in 60 days? Would you get even more excited charged with increasing productivity by 20% in 30 days?  Top candidates, those who have the competency to do the work and the motivation to do it better than it's been done before WANT you to challenge them! Why not start with a challenge in your ad or posts and distinguish your brand or work culture?  Have a story you'd like to share? We want to hear about it!   More tomorrow.....   
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Good morning!   I'm back after 10 beautiful days of vacationing on Cape Cod. It's the longest vacation I've ever taken and I highly recommend it to anyone who needs a good break.  I'm going to cover a 5 part series this week on how to hire. We'll begin at the beginning...  So you have a vacancy to fill. Why? Where? What's the work to be done, how and when?!  Take this as an opportunity instead of looking upon it as a burden.&nbsp;   What work needs to be done and with who?&nbsp; Who will supervise the effort and why? How can you measure good work? What skills are required or can be learned on the job?  Take a good look around the team make-up and "re-engineer" if it's time to do so.&nbsp; Become friends with your compensation department and help them to understand what you need and why.  Begin to make a good list of action verbs for the position description...which we'll tackle tomorrow.  Make it a great day. lucia  
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       We'll be on vacation the 16th returning on the 26th....."see" you again soon.   p.s. if anyone has posts they'd like to share for future time off we'd love to review your ideas.  Lucia/HireWorks 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Good morning,  CareerXroads just reported that only 1.8% of hires were made as a result of posts to www.hotjobs.com.  Last year they reported that less than 10% of all hires made came from the big 3 (monster.com, hotjobs.com and caereerbuilder.com)... Feel free to click on the link above and read the full article.  They've got a ton of information on their site - really a must read!  These are not great numbers folks.  As I've said in the past, I do believe job boards have their place.  However, if you are reading this entry - they probably aren't going to be the best tool for you based on your needs.  Corporate sites (if maintained and working well) outperform boards by almost 40% on average...and of course working with recruiters really increases your success rate.   Remember customized search plans are 20% off (regular price $297) through July 31st.  Email or call us today and tell us "I want to save 20% today!"   
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Usually after receiving a signed fee agreement and completing a customized search plan for a client I email the a Work Environment Questionnaire to complete.  I can email the PDF file to you - just email at lshaw@hire-works.com  It's just 2 pages but gets right to the heart of the matter.  We're trying to find out if there is turnover, what can we do? Is it a fun place to work? Do coworkers like and trust one another? Is management open to listening to new ideas?  It's a good exercise...  Make it a great day. 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Calling All Hiring Managers! Take 20% off your initial consultation and customized, written search plan (value $297).  Simply subscribe to our e-zine, The Hiring Insider by July 31st.  The Hiring Insider, a monthly e-zine, provides hot tips and tools to help you make better hires faster.   Email us at info@hire-works.com and in the subject line type “I want to save 20% today!”.    We look forward to serving you.  Lucia 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Part IV and V  Part IV of the search plan is usually where we include a bit of information about us (and I include my Bio).  I do this since the person with signature authority might not know much about the process to date and we want them to have a clear document with an articulated path that is easy to understand and sign off on.    Part V.  Proposal of Services and Terms.  1.  Planning 2. Execution 3. Working Status 4. Expenses 5. Rate or Fee (depending upon the type of work or project engaged in). 6. Termination Notice  7.  Related and on-going services   I'll put this all together and publish a live search plan to illustrate these points below:   Example of Live Search Plan (some information omitted to protect client confidentiality)   Recruiting Plan for "client"   HireWorks has prepared a proposed Recruiting Plan to serve as the blueprint to meet client's recruitment and retention goals.    I. Needs Summary:   Company name:	 Title of positions:	Customer Service Representatives Location:	 Number of employees:	40 + (high-volume recruiting needs) Orientation:	Nine-week training program Salary:	 Bonus:	 Benefits:	 Environment:	    Skills and competencies:	Strong multi-task abilities 	Flexibility in work scheduling (The facility will be open from 8:00 am to 8:00 PM Monday – Friday) 	Clear communication skills 	Problem solving orientation 	Critical thinking skills 	Previous experience working in a call center environment preferred 	College degree preferred 	Works well independently as well as interdependently (in a team environment) 	PC literate (ability to type minimum 35-40 WPM) and possibly other minimum requirements as determined by client. 	Positive attitude, patience, strong commitment to excellence with fortitude to see a case through to completion.     II. Suggested Process   An initial review of both job descriptions and the complete life cycle of the current recruitment process (including metrics and related hiring and retention statistics) shall be conducted.  As part of this process, input from key managers and call center reps (staff) should be solicited.  All comments and suggestions should be considered.    The existing process should be mapped out so that process improvements can be introduced and rolled out.  For example, is client conducting exit interviews?  If so, why are people leaving?  Can any imrovements be made to increase retention?  Finally, a timeline for current hiring needs shall be defined, as well as a master plan for overall hiring needs as of January 1, 2005.  Note:  Be sure to secure buy-in from the management team as part of this process!   Projected timing and planning:  Since this call center is a benefits call center for client base, and open enrollment is July through October, all new hires must begin their nine-week training program by the last week of April.  Therefore, offers must be extended to determine the actual level of staffing by late March or early April.  Of course additional flexibility will be built into the plan in the event additional contracts are accepted, and staffing levels need to increase or decrease accordingly.     III. Sourcing   I would suggest the engagement of  multiple, simultaneous sourcing activities to keep the center staffed properly.  While I have not listed all possible methods, below are a few ideas to get started:  1.	Boomerang campaign (“We want you back!”):  Who left the center that you’d like to return?  2.	Sourcing from competitors (locally and regionally). 3.	Sourcing from like industries, based on specific skill sets required (i.e. hospitality, airlines etc.)   4.	Campus recruiting (two and four year schools).  Sell the management as well as the global opportunity with client, and promotional opportunities therein.  Does client assist with college education for staff  as an incentive?  5.	Diversity Recruitment (on-line, career fairs etc.).  Is there a need for bilingual phone reps? 6.	Job Boards:  Monster, HotJobs, local boards (e.g. trianglejobs.com and use of MetaPosts.) 7.	Internet Sourcing (AIRS Oxygen, Boolean Search, etc). 8.	Open Houses (to be held at call center) followed by an Ambassador Program. 9.	Career fairs (locally and nationally). 10.	Online communities (e.g. Topica, AOL etc.) 11.	Media outlets: Print advertising, billboards, possible use of radio and internet radio shows in to reach the appropriate target market.  12.	Employee referral program (ERP).     IV.  Lucia’s Bio   Lucia Apollo Shaw is President and CEO of HireWorks, Inc.    She has been helping her customers for nearly nine years, working both as a third-party recruiter for CDI Corp. (staffing customers like IBM), Trilogy Consulting (now Venturi Partners), staffing the Biotech and Pharmaceutical industry, and in places like Duke University where she was a corporate recruiter and Team Leader for recruitment for Duke University Hospital.   Prior to her recruiting career, Lucia was among the first group of trainees hired when Phoenix and Home Life (PHL) Insurance merged and created a new call center in New York.  Lucia was promoted to Team Leader, responsible for hiring, training and managing a group of 12 staff members.  At that time, the reps averaged approximately 100 incoming calls per day (in a four-hour time frame).  Lucia was employed by PHL for a period of four years before relocating to North Carolina.  Lucia earned a B.A. from the State University of New York (University Center at Albany) and pursued Graduate Studies in Public Administration at the Sage Graduate School in Albany, NY.   V.  Proposal of Services and Terms   Per our conversation on, I understand that the current need is for a senior recruiter to work for a period of  three to six months.  I am incorporated, and currently have an office, equipment, etc. in Chapel Hill.    I propose the following (and welcome further discussion):  1.	Planning:  I will create a specific recruitment and hiring plan as outlined in this document (which will include feedback and input from client) for implementation.  2.	Execution:  I will work from my office in Chapel Hill three days per week, and report to client site two days per week (with the understanding that there may be occasions where additional on-site time is required).  When off-site, I will be available via telephone, fax and e-mail.  3.	Working status:  The contract that both parties (client and HireWorks) will sign will recognize that neither HireWorks, nor Lucia Apollo Shaw, will be an employee of client.  4.	Expenses:  HireWorks will not seek reimbursement for costs of operation relating to phone, internet charges, or travel expenses to and from the client Site.   5.	Rate:  $35.00 per hour, on 40 hours per week, for a period of three to six months.  Invoice remuneration to be submitted to HireWorks on net 30-day terms, which shall be inclusive of  actual hours of service performed.    6.	Termination notice:  Minimum 30-day notice required to HireWorks.  Regardless of the timing of the termination notice, all billable time for services rendered, but not yet paid, to HireWorks, Inc. shall be recognized as the final payment to Hireworks.    7.	Related and on-going services:  HireWorks welcomes any future discussion of on-going  contract services beyond the anticipated three to six month initial requirement.  Additional recruiting services and searches for specific positions can be initiated upon request.   
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Customized, written search plans continued...  My favorite part - sourcing candidates!  Most recruiters will suggest the engagement of MULTIPLE, simultaneous sourcing activities to keep the flow of candidates moving for both the short and long term.  Remember, you are also always seeking profile candidates for positions you don't even have vacant now as well!  Here is an example from a live search plan I'm currently working for a client:  1.	Boomerang campaign (“We want you back!”):  Who left that you’d like to return?  2.	Sourcing from competitors (locally and regionally). 3.	Sourcing from like industries, based on specific skill sets required (i.e. hospitality, airlines etc.)   4.	Campus recruiting (two and four year schools).  Sell the management as well as the global opportunity, and promotional opportunities therein.  Do you assist with college education for staff  as an incentive?  5.	Diversity Recruitment (on-line, career fairs etc.).  Is there a need for bilingual staff? 6.	Job Boards:  Monster, HotJobs, local boards (e.g. trianglejobs.com and use of MetaPosts.) 7.	Internet Sourcing (AIRS Oxygen, Boolean Search, etc). 8.	Open Houses (to be held at call center) followed by an Ambassador Program. 9.	Career fairs (locally and nationally). 10.	Online communities (e.g. Topica, AOL etc.) 11.	Media outlets: Print advertising, billboards, possible use of radio and internet radio shows in to reach the appropriate target market.  12.	Employee referral program (ERP). Does it need a refresher? Do staff members know all there is to know?   Tomorrow we'll close this up and put it all together.  Questions/comments??? email lucia at lshaw@hire-works.com or post a comment on the site right here.    
    
    
</post>


<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have a question for all of you candidates out there.  How are you finding/locating recruiters to send your resumes to?  Are you doing searches on the internet or using on-line recruiter directories?  I am receiving a LOT of unsolicited resumes lately (which is fine!) but do not use any of the job boards for position advertisements.  So we're in the office getting all of these resumes from people in our space (relevant resumes) wondering how it is happening!  Email me and tell me how you heard about HireWorks, Inc and we'll post our results.  P.S. Keep the resumes coming - we look forward to serving YOU in your search.  Best wishes,  Lucia lshaw@hire-works.com  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Calling all PT's, OT's PTA's and Speech Pathologists!  We are staffing rehab facilities throughout NC and VA and need your help to spread the word.  Excellent multi-disciplinary team environment, great benefits and continuing education program.  Please call Lucia directly at 919-960-3411 or email resume to lshaw@hire-works.com.  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Senior Sales Professional - Online Patient Recruitment Services   This position requires  significant experience in selling patient recruitment services  to biopharmaceutical clients.  We require an energetic, motivated individual who can sell an array of patient recruitment services, is agile/flexible and adept at thinking creatively and can communicate effectively with a variety of audiences.    Our client provides solutions through three distinct product lines: clinical trial listing service on the Company’s industry-wide clinical trial information exchange (veritasmedicine.com); clinical trial specific online recruitment campaigns with screening websites; and client specific web-based recruitment systems.  Base salary plus commission, Medical, dental, 401K, and stock options.   Please send resumes to Lucia at lshaw@hire-works.com.  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm working with a new client with multiple locations in the SouthEast and we're seeking Therapists to join our team. We'd prefer direct hires, however will consider per diem hours and contract staff.  Feel free to send resumes to Lucia at lshaw@hire-works.com or give me a call at 866-960-3411 for a chat.  Have a great day!
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We have multiple openings nationally for cytotechnologists...certification desired but not required.  Experience preferred, but new grads are welcome to apply.  Please contact Lucia directly for additional information:  toll free 866-960-3411 or lshaw@hire-works.com  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Most recruiters will be happy to help you revise and customize your resume for jobs we're helping you interview for.   I must admit though, I cannot stand writing and updating my own resume, must less anyone elses.  Remember to lead with strong action verbs, list major accomplishments and please be sure to spell check your resume (including getting rid of extra spaces).  You would not believe the typos I see that I would rather not.    Also, there is no need to list your date of birth, marital status and names of children.  Even hobbies are questionable in my mind on a professional CV.    There are good resume writers - no question...but they cannot invent the content and experience..you've got to have it!  Questions and comments are welcome.  Look forward to hearing from you.    Lucia
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Morning!   I need some feedback from those of you paying to have your resume "Blasted" to recruiters.  Are you getting phone calls and job offers as a result?   I've recently subscribed to all 3 services as a recruiter and am getting some good looking resumes on paper.  But I'm curious to know from you, the users (and payors) how is this working? What is its biggest strength and weakness? Do you have to pay multiple times to get through all of the "noise" on the internet?  Do you feel like you hear from more experienced recruiters than you do if you just post free on hotjobs.com or monster.com?  ...inquiring minds want to know!  we look forward to hearing from you.  Lucia
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I receive hundreds of unsolicited resumes via email each month.  It never fails - several per week come to me "To whom it may concern".   Please do not continue to do this.  If you have taken the time to research recruiters and send your resume to them unsolicited why don't you address it to them personally?  I must tell you that this is such an irritant to me that going forward - any resume I receive in my inbox "To Whom it May Concern" will be deleted immediately.  Tip: take the time to research your contact, spellcheck your email and resume before sending to anyone.  Have a great weekend.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Like many professional recruiters, I like to work with candidates and set up phone appointments for pre-screens.  I let my candidates know we'll need 20-30 minutes together for them to share with me their background, likes, dislikes etc.    The purpose of this call is not typically to discuss a particular job.  Candidates I talk with often are not looking for a new job the first time I talk with them.  They make become a client first and sometimes I may never place them at all.  There have been times where the placement did in fact occur sooner than both of us thought it would and I've often refrerred candidates I speak with to colleagues who have helped them if I could not.  But my tip today is to KEEP that initial phone appointment with the recruiter.  If something comes up and you need to change the appointment, email and/or call the recruiter.  But do not blow it off.  We'll probably never call you again and I for one will be sure to make a note of it in my database where it will forever remain.   Keeping appointments is professional courtesy and an indicator of future behavior.  Many recruiters ask themselves, if they blew me off, will they blow off the interview with a hiring manager  I introduce them to ? Remember, we're doing our homework for our clients.  Keep those appointments and follow up with your recruiter.  Have a great day!  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      To all of you sending out resumes via email......please do not email PDF files of your resume or CV.  Most of need and want an MS Word file we can import into our database to search and parse data later on.....  Just a tip!  best, Lucia
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I’m pleased to be working with a client who was named one of Fortune's 100 Best Companies to Work for in 2004.    We’re seeking an innovative and motivated  Business Development Rep  to sell the services their research division has to offer clients worldwide.  Your role?  Expand a current customer base as well as establish new business in the field of clinical research.    Qualified candidates must have a minimum of three years experience in a CRO environment selling services (Phase I-IV).  Strong project management skills and proposal writing skills are a must. The team includes 4 Business Development Associates each reporting to Director of the department. For profit organization, campus/academic setting.    Would you like to join a team of professionals in clinical research where there has been very little turnover, excellent support for research to prepare bids, quotations and proposals? Interested in experienced clinical staff to travel with you to sell your services?   Please send resume and cover letter to my attention at lshaw@hire-works.com.  Tell me about the types of projects you sell and service, therapeutic areas of interest, as well as what preferences you may have.   If you have a friend or colleague who may be interested, please feel free to have them get in touch with me.   Lucia Apollo Shaw Recruiter  lshaw@hire-works.com  Have a question? www.askhireworks.com  HireWorks, Inc. Chapel Hill, NC  www.hire-works.com  Phone:    (919) 960-3411 FAX:       (919) 960-3413   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Welcome to the first entry of The Job Blog.  I am a life sciences recruiter (just over 9 years now). What does that mean? I've been recruiting for Health Care Institutions (clinics, research centers, hospitals) and for small to mid pharma/biotechs and CROs.   Hope that helps....we recruit for all disciplines as long as they are in the spaces mentioned below.  So if you are an IT professional, RN, Pharmacist, MD, Rad Tech etc. we are looking for you if you are looking for a new career.  Be sure to read daily and post your comments. If you are ready to send me a resume feel free to email it to me at lshaw@hire-works.com.  But if you want to lurk around and read and get to know me - feel free to do that as well.  Best wishes,  Lucia Apollo Shaw www.askhireworks.com/healthcare.html www.askhireworks.com  www.hire-works-forhire.com  919.960.3411 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Cover letters should be short, strong, and interesting so the reader moves on and reads your resume.  Cover letters should not be a recap of your resume.  Keep the cover letter to 3 or 4 short paragraphs.    Paragraph I.  Let the reader know what you are applying for and how you heard about it.  Paragraph II. Use 3 or 4 bullet points with strong action verbs demonstrating how what you've done elsewhere could be done at the job you are applying for.  Talk about how much above goal you are if you are in sales or how far below budget you came in at if you are a project manager or how quickly you accomplished XYZ etc.  Paragraph III.  Invite the reader to contact you for more information about how you can help them.  Paragraph IV is optional...if you need more room.  Folks reading resumes get a LOT of them.  Readers will really appreciate your ability to get to the point quickly and highlighting what they need to know.  And be sure to SPELLCHECK your document!   Good luck!   
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      HireWorks is expanding.  We recruit healthcare and clinical research professionals nationally and need more help.    We are seeking Recruiters and Researchers who will work from their own home.  You should have access to high speed internet and a dedicated phone (biz) line.  Part-time/Flexible hours are ok.   Please send resume and letter of interest to Lucia at lshaw@hire-works.com  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Afternoon!  Today I read a stat which was very interesting.  According to the Cornell University Career Services Department research show that up to  80 percent  of all job openings are  unadvertised .  As a recruiter I know that many jobs are never advertised for many reasons.  But I'll be honest, I did not think the number was that high...50% or more maybe..but 80%.  Wow!  My advice:  Find a recruiter you  like, know and trust  and they'll help you find the best job for YOU.  Make it a great day. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>