<Blog>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This is the coolest thing!  I just figured out how to get the blogger shortcut on my google toolbar!  Now I can blog at the touch of a button!  O' the joys of technology!
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well it was Brents going away bash this past weekend!  It was great fun!  The padres kicked in for food and beer...they got not only 1 keg of the glorious C-, but 2!!  It was awesome!  And you would think that 2 kegs would be too much, but not for this group of partiers!  We pretty much finished both!  I couldn't believe it!  And I have to say that Jay and I kicked ass at Beirut!  We were the first team to take Brent and Matt to sudden death overtime!  O' yeah baby!  We didn't quite get the big W, but we gave them a run for their money!  The night came to a close with, of course.....the hot tub!  Its amazing how we always end up in th hot tub at 3 in the morning and why we think that is normal, I don't know! LOL!   The next morning we were all feeling pretty chipper.  I think we attributed that to the second round of sausage that the grill master cooked up at 2 in the morning!  Thanks Cory!   Well now Brent is off to Sea for 4 months, and he will be missed but it was great that we got to send him off with a bash! 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well I think its time to go home.  Im still at work, which sucks ass.  I bought LOTR:Return of the King today and I want to go home and watch it.  This week is pretty much going to suck I think.  Im looking forward to the weekend though!  We are going to have a bar-b-que at our casa on Sunday.  Everyone is invited!    On to some good news.  Brian told us today that we should never work both days on a weekend from here on out.  That was pretty comforting to hear after having to work a couple weekends both days.  He also said that he would not ask anyone to come in and work on Memorial Day weekend.  But of course that is a load of crap, we have to come in for at least one day.  Im going to just work Saturday and get it out of the way so I have the rest of the weekend free!  Well I've been here long enough, it time to head home!  See ya all on Sunday hopefully!
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    See, now this guy has a good job.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Did I mention that work sucks?  Just in case I did'nt.........work sucks.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So i rode my hog, a la GT I-Drive style, on over to the old Mackay house to see what the fellers were up to. Lundberg had the THQ MX Unleashed game for XBox - so sick. Maybe honey pants would like an Xbox for her birthday!? The graphics and the sounds effects escpecially of the monster truck were awesome. Reminds me of riding my two stroke dirt bike in the hills of hungry valley, speaking of which we should plan a date for the peeps to go rent some dirt bikes and create a little havic!
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, E3 is over and it was awesome.  It seemed to come and go so fast.  I got to see all my friends from back up in the bay area.  We basicly got drunk every night and then went to the Sony party and saw Black Eyed Peas, Missy Elliot and The Crysal Method.  All in all, I would say a great E3!  As far as going back to work goes....it sucks.  We are crazy busy around here and look to stay that way for a while.  We get a break somewhere towards the middle of July, but other then that we are crammed.  This is really putting a stress on all of my Summer plans!  Hopefully I can work though it though.  Jay is back in town and we hung out with her and the peeps this weekend down in the RB.  It was sweet.  Got drunk on Saturday out at the pier at this new place called Underground.  It was actully a pretty cool place, and I think I will be going back there for sure.  After that we hit up the beach on Sunday and chilled all afternoon to wind down.  Im not sure what the etiqutte is on how long these blog posts are supposed to be so im going to cut it short...until next time...
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ok so I have checked out the Redondo police report and the Beach Reporter crime watch report and no such arrest of an irate man that was rear-ended and arrested on Saturday, May 8.....This is not complete proof that it did not happen.....But I am smelling a big hunk of bullshit!  If Cory can actually find an arrest record I might be convinced, but otherwise the smell continues to permeate!
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      All I have to say is that I   HATE   Windows XP!  My employer (and IT department whom I've spoken with about 30 times over the past 3 days) for some reason thinks that this "operating platform" is God's gift or something.  I hate to break it to them but... IT SUCKS ROYALLY!  I can't do anything in it.  And the best thing is that the software I use to actually DO my job doesn't run on this freaking system.  What is up with that?
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So we have plans to go to the beach on Saturday afternoon with the infamous k-dog...I am thinking.....he is really making efforts to redeem himself..this is a good thing.  Its 2pm and Cory has talked to him at least 4 times that day working out the details.  Cory and I get to Hermosa, hanging out eating sandos and waiting for K to show up with the beer. Cory really wants a beer so the minutes are like hours...lol...So K calls and says he has to pick up ice, and then he will be there....well another hour goes by and no beer!!  We have been there for two maybe three hours at this point, so  we take off and don't hear from him for the rest of the day/rest of the weekend!  I guess its par for the course and solidfies the "flakester" nickname he has earned!  But wait, I get a message this morning that he was rear-ended on the way to get ice and ended up getting in a fight with the guy that rear-ended him......it gets better....the cops showed up and he got arrested and his car was impounded!!  He said he spent the last two days in jail and just got his car back!! Is this story for real?!?!?!  I dont know what I believe anymore....... 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Whew, almost an hour later and I finally can post up to this blog. I had to scour the net to find a web hosting space to stash my cool avatar pic. Come on, Carl is the coolest F'n character evar. Anyway, I just want these next 2 days to pass as fast as possible because the coolest nerd convention of all time is occuring here in sunny so-cal. Much like Cory, I can't wait to geek out and play all these damn games that I have been reading about this past year. Ok, I think I could write here all day, even though this is my first time writing to a blog. I feel like a young virgin breaking her cherry for the first time.... oops, I think the fcc might come down on this place already. Gotta go!  One last thing, don't you hate it when the bathroom stall is outta TP when you sit down?
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      E3 is coming up this week and I cant wait!  There are going to be tons of new games and things to see.  All my friends are going to be coming down from the bay area too, so there is going to be some serious partying going on as well!  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well its been pretty hard ot keep up with the blogger lately.  There has been so much going on here at work that I barley have time for anything anymore!    Last weekend was really dope.  We hung out with Larry and Colette down in the South Bay and surprise, surprise, we got wasted!  Nothing like a little dip in the hot tub/pool at 3am!  The fatty neighbors were not so happy about it, but thats OK.  =)  On to this week.  Basicly this week has been all about work.  We are trying to get our Focus disc and Public Beta disc done this week, so I have not been home much at all.  I hope that next week tones it down a bit.  All this work time is getting to just be too much!  This weekend.  Its going to be sweet.  We are going to the KROQ Weenie Roast on Saturday!  We being Christi, Paul and I.  Im really stoked to see the Beastie Boys and the Yeah Yeah Yeahs.  We have lawn seats so we are going to have to get there early and its going to be a long day.  Im looking forward to those $7 beers!  Well better get back to work....
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Christi and Cory's amazing new futon in living color!
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So we just got back from a weekend of motorcycle mania.  It was quite fun I must say.  Not so excited to be back at work though.  My first full week in about a month.  Pretty much sucks even though I'm doing more of the emailing than the working...but whatever...I still have to be here which pretty much blows.  Why can't I have a sweet job that gives me the summer off and pays me for it.  Or shoot...why not the whole year!  What I wouldn't do for that job.  Anyhow, here are some highlights of the weekend: 1. Cory and 8ball on the walkie talkies.  I think their next occupation should be truck drivers.  They've aced the most important part of the job - CB radio kings.  2. Fixing Christi's car hood on the side of the 46 at 2am.  8ball mcguivered it with a license plate screw, strap, and duct tape.  The key to the job was definitely the duct tape.  What a sweet ride that was after its makeover.  The green machine definitely would have made the Top 10 list of Best Hoopdies.  3. Wine tasting.  Enough said on that subject.  I mean really...we all know I'm the wine queen!  4. Riding on a motorcycle with 8ball.  I was pretty much scared shitless and swore that I would never get on one of those death machines.  But 8ball finally wore me down.  I had a great time and am looking forward to riding with him again.  I just need the proper equipment.  My sister has pretty much stated that I will be murdered if I do not get proper footwear.  So I'm going out this weekend and getting some steel-toed boots that will save my little footsies from serious damage.  (And I'm definitely of the mindset that I don't really ever want to have to put them to the test!  So you better be safe with me Mr. 8ball!)  5. Motorcycle races at Laguna Seca (the whole reason for the trip).  8ball brought them up a couple of months ago and stated that he didn't want to miss THE races at Laguna Seca.  I was thinking that 2 days of watching motorcycle races was pretty much going to be the death of me.  But thankfully...they rocked!  I had a great time.  We sat in awesome seats, right on the track, in the Aprilia tent. Those guys ride SOOO fast!  It's pretty cool watching them on the turns and hauling ass down the straight-a-ways.  Very fun.  On the whole, the weekend rocked.  The Laguna Seca Race Weekend will definitely make it into the "annual vacation" register on the ol' calendar.  :-)  On a side note...can everybody say Kern River in one week's time?  WOO HOO!!!! 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>