<Blog>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm moving in with Brads dad in July.  I'm alittle concerned with where my place is going to be in this new setting. I have a feeling I'm going to be left sitting on the couch while Brad and his dad work on cars all night. FUN! The only thing I can think about is how much money Brad and I will be saving.   So I have been eating dinner with Morrie on Wednesdays. Bonding. It's real fun.   I go to work at the ob-gyn office everyday to listen to women and their female problems. The best one I heard this week was from an OB patient who asked if she broke her water at home, would her dog get sick if it licked up the amnionic fluid. YUMMY!  I guess since Rosie used to lick my old pads and Coz is on a Cicada diet, it's not such a bizarre question.  I saw some movies this week end. Nothing new. Paycheck was alright if you can watch Ben Affleck anymore without thinking of J.Lo .  Do not rent Torque unless you are a guy. 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        So I started softball again 3 weeks ago hoping to get in shape before the wedding. Its terrible. Im so out of shape that when I run around the bases I hear my thighs slapping together. At least I can still hit homers, I must hit it pretty far because I feel like a Turtle running around the bases. When I wake up the next morning after a game I can barely move. Its awful.    So Im packing up my apartment after living here with Brad for three years. Im a little sad but happy at the same time.  No more Phil Collins blaring in the window at 2:00AM on Saturday night from the single guy living across the way. I just don't see how anyone can listen to that when they are "getting down". I know thats what he is doing because a large part of my apartment experience has been smoking cigarettes, observing the habits of others on my balcony. I feel a bit like Jimmy Stewart in Rear Window. I know what everyone drives and who are their significant others. I have never spoken to any of them. So I say Good Bye to all the freaks on the other side of Dartmouth Way. I will not miss you. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have been so depressed today. This should be the happiest time in my life. I am getting married to the most wonderful man in four months. He is everything I could possibly ask for in a mate for life.  He is my everything. My best friend, my sole mate. I couldn't be more lucky.  Yet here I am so depressed I feel I could cry forever. I have no mother. The closest thing I could get to a mother, died almost 6 months ago. I think it is all settling in for me. Things are changing in Brads family and I don't really like it. Brads mom was a wonderful women and I can honestly say that one day I would have called her Mom. I always said that people who called their In-Laws " Mom & Dad" are the cheesiest but I can bet my life after Brad and I got married I would have gladly called her as such. Mom.  It makes me miss my Mom all over again. I feel so selfish in my misery because I am blessed in so many ways.  I have a wonderful family. My God! I do. So many people out there are going through worse than I. I don't say this to get people to feel sorry for me, I say it to wallow in my own self pity. I guess I'm on my period and things always look darker than they appear.  I will someday be a mom and have my own family. I look forward to the day I am married so I can begin my family with my husband. My sweetest Brad. Oh, only our Mothers know how much we love one another.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>