<Blog>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When I originally began this journal, I wanted to report on daily events and chronicle them in an objective manner for you as well as myself.  What has transpired since appears to be a stream of consciousness filled with some of my deepest desires and sobering fears.  One day I hope to look back and see how foolish and immature I was, and how far I have grown since then, and dispel all my childhood hopes and fantasies.  Is that not what journals are for?  Well, I guess it's time for me to get to the heart of the matter: love and relationships.  My current love interest happens to be a fellow co-worker who possesses many of the qualities I find incredibly attractive in a woman.  She is intelligent, affluent, well coiffured, personable, mature, healthy, fit, and above all else, beautiful.  Many students find her cute and attractive.  So what is the problem?  She is already involved with another person.  In fact, we are on good enough speaking terms that we share details about each other's relationships (up until the point where I broke up with my girlfriend).  Communication is a little strained these days, because in the past I made overtures about how beautiful she was; some in private, others in public.  My compliments were not a problem, because I would slip them in during friendly conversation as to not embarrass her.  In fact, I believe she liked them, a lot.  Most of the time it was like a tease; one that she could easily laugh off if it became too personal.  Having a girlfriend at the time made it easier to chat without adding any sexual tension.  Nowadays I have to ignore her and pretend she is not in the room.  I seldom reach out to talk to her.  The sexual politics can be difficult to navigate, especially when your workplace is 90% female and gossip is all the rage.  So why am I still struggling with my feelings over this co-worker?  I guess I am having difficulties coming to terms with the fact that she is unavailable in more ways that I can comment on.  Still, I find her completely intriguing.  One log entry is not enough to explain the depths or complexity of her character, from her upbringing to her educational background... from her worldly experiences to her relationships.  I have to admit that I am more than a little star-struck.  The funny thing is that it has been like this for months, and it does not seem to want to stop.  She may be older and considerably wiser than me, but she also has a youthful exuberance that I find very endearing.  Through careful observation in the workplace and careful questioning, I was able to develop a picture of a person below the surface, with real problems and real feelings.  Is it possible to know someone completely?  To my surprise, many of my predictions about her were confirmed over time.  So, before my behaviour becomes unhealthy and obsessive, I am going to find different ways to attain the closure I need.  Most people I have cared for in the past simply drifted away while others left on bitter terms.  It is especially difficult in the workplace because whatever happens, you end up seeing the person day in and day out.  So how will I accomplish this task you ask?  More to come...
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This weekend has been, and continues to be, an exceptionally festive one.  I had a wonderful "Stone Pot Bibimbap" at the Korean Barbecue Restaurant with some International students, celebrated my good friend's birthday at the  urlLink Sticky Wicket Pub , and attended a wedding and reception at the beautiful  urlLink Crystal Gardens .  It's only Sunday, and there is still more fun to be had.  As much as I try to pull myself and others up, there is a sharp pain that resides deep within me; perhaps somewhere in my soul.  The prospect of visiting Korea excites me, but the idea of going there and never coming back excites me even more.  Am I running away from something?  Am I just trying to feel alive?  I cannot help but believe that part of me is dead to the world... it has been that way for quite some time.  Even before I broke up with my girlfriend, that nagging feeling that I am not where I am supposed to be in life rang truer than ever.  Self inflicted paranoia perhaps, but observing the people and events around me stir up strong, pent up feelings of doubt and despair.  When faced with apathy and sometimes narcissism, I find myself in a more positive and reassuring state.  That is a difficult state for me to maintain.  More often than not, I am the one friends and family are tending to.  I joke to  urlLink Lola  that I am a "lightning rod" for schizophrenics or other disturbed individuals, drawing them to me.  I thought I was dealing with it well, but now I find myself surrounded by sickness in all my social spheres: family, friends, lovers, coworkers, & even strangers.  Despite their misgivings, some of those individuals seem to be on the rebound and moving on with their seemingly miserable existences.  However, I now find myself slipping into their ranks.  This has been difficult transition for my close friends who have not seen me this depressed or subdued before.  I may be a bit over melodramatic, but the craziness has indelibly scarred me, leaving me in this frail condition.  Further to that, other people's joy and happiness bring about feelings of profound sadness.   I am not where I want to be in life .  I know these feelings are irrational and unhealthy, so I have dedicated even more time to self care.  My girlfriend at the time said I liked the gym more than seeing her.  I nearly stopped going in part due to her complaints, but now that we have broken up, I am back to my usual exercise routine.  Planning this trip to Korea has also kept me occupied.  The past 8 months have been a time of considerable physical change.  On my Atkin's diet, I managed to shed over 60lbs and draw many complements about my new fit, healthy appearance.  My challenge now is to match that growth beneath the surface, emotionally and spiritually.  I hope a change of scenery will do the trick, and help recapture some of the "steam" I have lost of lately.  Carpe Diem!  (Seize the day) 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Korea, here I come!!!   I can hardly contain the excitement I am feeling.  My uncle in San Diego agreed to purchase me plane ticket to Korea this summer!  If things work out as planned, I can bunk with my sister in Sokcho.  I haven't seen my sister in almost a year and a half.  This is my chance to make up for lost time.  Eventhough financing this trip weighs heavily on my mind, I cannot help but feel this is a once in a lifetime opportunity.  When I was younger, I passed up many opportunities  sometimes just out of plain fear.  I often convinced myself it was my innate desire to be the 'responsible' son and pay my own tuition while I went to college.  On a deeper level, I was just trying to differentiate myself from my sister.  Why did I feel the need to do this?  The only way I can explain it is that in the chinese culture, being the first-born son carries great importance.  This meant that as a career, I had to become a respected professional.  This included, but was not limited to, being a doctor, lawyer, or engineer.  That was not to be.  How did I become the "black sheep" in the eyes of my family?  My high school years were wrought with what I deemed to be pain and hardship.  My lack of friends and adequate social skills did me in right away.  I cut school, and often displayed a lack of commitment to my studies.  As for my sister, she didn't have an easy time either at first.  She carried some resentment towards me for being more well-liked by my mother's extended family.  In junior high, she befriended some really shady characters that could have potentially lead her down a path of drugs and reckless abandon.  She was fortunate enough to switch schools by grade 10, and recognize her own potential.  By grade 12 she was a yearbook editor, a lieutenant governor of her youth group chapter, was well-liked by her peers, and attended many life-changing conferences.  By graduation, she accomplished more than most would ever hope.  She made an even bigger splash in University, running for student office and working part-time in a print shop.  Despite what others think, I was not at all jealous of her success; in fact, I was, and still am, very proud of her.  What made things difficult was that her success overshadowed any of my achievements in the eyes of my parents.  Parents can be cruel by using favouritism as a form of reward and punishment; often times it just reinforced entrenched views and values.  A comment my father once made gave me the greatest insight into the chinese culture.  He said to me "your sister can do whatever she wants, because in the end, she will marry into wealth".  Hearing that made my heart stop.  The realization for me was that I had fallen short of their expectations.  What hurt even more was that my father and I never communicated very well.  I perceived his comments as attacks, and I responded by defending myself or sometimes by withdrawing which further frustrated him.  It has taken me years to overcome the bitterness of that realization, and somehow make peace with that utter disappointment.  It was not so much disappointment in them but a greater disappointment in myself.  I was in denial about seeking help because it was still very much taboo in chinese culture to talk about your problems outside of your family.  Instead, the problem internalized within me, and it slowly ate away at my confidence.  How did I let all this fester within me for so long still haunts me to this day.  I sometimes sit up and wonder how I let so many wasted years go by with a total lack of ambition or sense of direction.  Despite this track record, the human spirit is resilient and in the end I simply find myself choosing to move on with my life.  I am quickly regaining the steam I thought I had all but lost, and looking more positively toward the future.  Things I once abandoned long ago I am revisiting, including my desire to be more healthy in body and soul.  Travelling was always something I easily talked myself out of.  This time I hope to go with a sense of purpose.  I want so desperately to see the world from a whole new perspective, and to see my little sister whom I miss dearly.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello Friends and Onlookers,  Nothing too special to report today other than I have updated my profile with a picture of myself and my fearless dog.  I guess you can put a face on "faceless" from now on.  The picture is not the best picture of the lot, but it is a good picture of me and my dog, Nihanni.  We call him "Honey" for short.  He is an American Eskimo Miniature (Miniature Spitz is the more politically correct term).  He is a veritable ball of white fur, and I have often thought of making a sweater out of him.  Believe it or not, we managed to find him at the local SPCA animal shelter.  I know what your thinking; who in there right mind would give up such a beautiful dog?  Well, it was not from a lack of love.  The previous owners left explicit instructions about how to care for him, from how to play with him to what snacks he likes.  We spoiled him pretty badly.  At first he chewed everything.  I lost a watch, a shirt, a very expensive goretex jacket, and more.  We literally had to barricade all the rooms.  Did I mention he could open doors, drawers, and even closets?  It was quite a transition that first year.  On the bright side, Honey is a beautiful dog.  He draws complements from complete strangers, creating opportunities to meet new people.  A weekly tradition of mine is to walk along the waterfront and enjoy the weather.  On another note, my friend  urlLink Lola  was trying to post a comment.  Her blog is titled  Can you dig it?   I have hopefully fixed the error so you can begin posting comments.  It's after midnight, and I have to get up early for work.  More interesting stuff to come...  Regards,  Faceless Butcher
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Welcome Friends and Onlookers,  After months about hearing about these "BLOG" journals, I have finally decided to give into peer pressure and begin my own, documenting the weird, the interesting, the delusional, and seemingly surreal, parts of my life.  I hope it is an interesting journey for you as it is for me.  I am a 26 year old college student living at home with his parents but pretending not to.  I somehow managed to drag out what should have been a 2-year diploma into an 8-year adventure.  It's a long story that I hope to share with you sometime.  My only crowning achievement during that time is that I found a job as an overpaid instructional assistant for the college's ESL department.  It's a great place to work that challenges my creativity (as long as you don't let the internal politics get you down).  Plus, you get to meet some interesting people.  As for the romance area, it's been rocky at best.  I will even go so far as saying that my relationships have the same effect as kryptonite on Superman.  I have recently broken up with my girlfriend; mostly because I am hopelessly in love with a coworker who is totally unavailable.  I welcome your feedback, comments, wisdom, and your plain old criticism.  If I can accomplish anything with this blog other than chronicling my daily mishaps, it would be to give you a sense that your life isn't as complicated and screwed up as you think it is.  Hell, have a laugh at my expense if you can.  ^_^  Cheers,  Faceless Butcher  
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      An ESL teacher referred a problem student to me who was in need of conversation practice.&nbsp; We arranged to meet twice a week in my office before her class.   Unbeknownst to the teacher, the student and I were acquainted long before the start of class.&nbsp; We met while walking&nbsp;along the&nbsp;beach&nbsp;on Dallas Road&nbsp;one beautiful spring evening.&nbsp; She stopped to comment on how beautiful my dog was when I turned around to&nbsp;recognize another colleague who happened to be her homestay parent.&nbsp;&nbsp;The student&nbsp;was then&nbsp;happy to learn that I worked in the ESL Department of the school she would soon be attending.&nbsp;   I was thumbing through one of the conversation books looking for an interesting&nbsp;dialogue for our first appointment.&nbsp; Food served as an excellent discussion topic.&nbsp;&nbsp;It is often the first thing we really take notice&nbsp;of in&nbsp;other cultures: the&nbsp;subtle differences in&nbsp;the ingredients used, the table etiquette, and the presentation of the dishes.  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  From that first appointment, I became starkly aware of how&nbsp;food was a driving force within our everyday lives.&nbsp; We&nbsp;derive comfort,&nbsp;love,&nbsp;reward, and sometimes&nbsp;even punishment from it.   The first incident she spoke of was over a bowl of jam.&nbsp; They had toast that morning, and used only&nbsp;a small amount of jam.&nbsp;&nbsp;Afterwards, her&nbsp;homestay sister took the remainder of it, which seemed&nbsp;perfectly good to reuse, and poured it down the garborator.  &nbsp;  The second incident was over a bowl of chili.&nbsp;&nbsp;One of the homestay sisters refused to&nbsp;eat the chili&nbsp;upon finding&nbsp;out it was made&nbsp;with beef.&nbsp; What was more disturbing was that&nbsp;she left the dinner refused to come back to the dinner table in protest.&nbsp;&nbsp;The chili was subsequently thrown out later that evening.&nbsp;   Upon delving deeper into her feelings around the subject, it appeared her shock was personal as well as cultural.&nbsp; She grew up in a poor family.&nbsp; Her parents were divorced or separated, and finding enough food to fill a meal was a daily chore.&nbsp; She&nbsp;described situations where she would hide her food because her hungry older brothers were constantly&nbsp;stealing it from her.   Seeing how plentiful food was in our culture, and then seeing it being wasted, was difficult for the student.&nbsp;&nbsp;She&nbsp;expressed her reservations about the behaviour, but&nbsp;it failed to&nbsp;yield any concern or&nbsp;validation from her homestay family.&nbsp; Her homestay father's initial&nbsp;response to&nbsp;the situation&nbsp;was "it's okay, because the fishes will eat it".&nbsp;   I pointed out how absurd that response was, and that seemed to help validate some of her feelings.  &nbsp;  In truth, I&nbsp;could easily identify with her situation.&nbsp; I grew up in a chinese family where food was never wasted.&nbsp; In fact, having leftovers at the dinner table was a cultural "faux pas".&nbsp; I spent most of my&nbsp;childhood in the back of the&nbsp;family restaurant, and we often ate around those hours.&nbsp; For my sister and I, dinner was around 9 or 10 in the evening when most kids were preparing&nbsp;for bed.&nbsp; Dinner was&nbsp;the only quality time I spent with my parents, who&nbsp;both worked two full-time jobs.  &nbsp;&nbsp;  There was much more going on for this student behind the scenes.&nbsp; She desparately sought her homestay father's&nbsp;approval, but found him somewhat&nbsp;callous and unfeeling towards her at times.&nbsp; This seemed to draw a tear or two.&nbsp; It reached a point where she began hording the leftover food that the family was sending to the garborator.&nbsp; The food that she&nbsp;once derived so much love, comfort&nbsp;and reward as a child now became her punishment as an adult.&nbsp; She now&nbsp;equated&nbsp;saving leftovers&nbsp;to "eating the family's garbage."&nbsp;  &nbsp;  My subsequent meetings with the student were more fruitful as the days went on.&nbsp; Somedays she was brought to tears; other days&nbsp;she was happy and almost giddey.&nbsp;&nbsp;Did she find a kindered spirit in this foreign land?&nbsp; Who knows?&nbsp; I just know that it is nice to be heard once in a while.     
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The Road Less Travelled   I have found it more difficult to journalize entries this past week.  Writer's block perhaps, but closer to truth, there have not been any other significant developments between my colleague and I that are worth mentioning.  Also, I am working towards abating and understanding my deeply held attraction to her.  While picking up my belongings, I unearthed an old book aptly titled "Chinese Love Signs".  Despite the book's gimmicky context, it makes interesting conversation at parties, and doubly serves as an ice breaker.  After studying books about "I Ching" and "Taoism", I find the Chinese Zodiac fascinating not only by its predictions about human behaviour, but also its simple explanations about my sometimes seemingly complex personal relationships.  My girlfriend was constantly threatening break up towards the end of our relationship.  True to her astrological sign, the Goat, she was quick to change her mind each time I suggested we work it out.  Unbeknownst to her, salvaging the relationship was not what I truly wanted.  Out of a sense of responsibility, I was quick to resolve our differences, especially when it was driven over minutia.  When it finally came time for me to suggest dissolution of our relationship, she was devastated to the point of threatening suicide.  This, unfortunately, was not the first time she cried "wolf".  This was behaviour I observed a couple times over the months, usually with other family members.  That, coupled with her flip-flopping change of heart made the decision all the much easier.  In the end, she would not stand for a even a lukewarm friendship (although her tune seems to have changed again of lately).  Irony, as it would seem, placed my co-worker and potential love interest as an equally incompatible match.  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The Christmas Card & New Year's Waltz   I subscribe to the belief that we all operate under a system of paradigms, a set of rules that guide us in all aspects of our lives; a road map if you may.  For most of us, those paradigms are so deeply instilled within us that we follow them without a second thought.  But what happens when those "road maps" do not reflect the true environment.  Do we have the courage and wisdom to redraw them?  With my last girlfriend, it took me a few weeks to figure out I was not in love with her.  It took us a few months later to decide to end it.  Unfortunately, the break up was quite bitter and draining.  I honestly thought a chinese partner would yield a more successful relationship, but we experienced all the same pitfalls as other couples do... perhaps even more.  So, how does this relate to my co-worker?  Before Christmas, a wise friend asked me if I had a choice between these two individuals, the now ex-girlfriend or co-worker, who I would choose.  My answer must be pretty obvious by now.  Days later, I made my feelings known to her in a Christmas card.  It was accompanied by a gift I carefully selected and packaged for her.  On Christmas Eve, I got an e-mail thanking me for the gift, but no mention of the card; not quite the response I was hoping for.  Things were already progressing with another love interest, so I quickly focused all my attention to her.  A weekend in Vancouver allowed us to be carefree and spontaneous.  The new experiences and unfamiliar surroundings helped bond and cement our relationship a bit more.  The rest is history.  As soon as New Year's came and went, I called up the co-worker wanting to tell her I was alright and that I was moving on.  Our communication never seemed forced, but I was frustrated each time I tried to broach the "attraction" issue. Like seasoned diplomats, we danced around the topic.  Her non-response to my card was difficult, but telling her about my new girlfriend was even more so.  So, we continued our usual "waltz" over the telephone lines, providing a summary update on eachother's holiday fun.  A couple minutes into the conversation, I brought up the Vancouver trip and my new girlfriend.  Almost as if she were in shock or disbelief, her voice fell silent.  I was overcome with a sense of guilt for even mentioning it.  To fill the silence, I began talking about how my girlfriend and I were good for eachother.  When she regained her composure, the questions to follow were a little more direct.  Before I could finish answering them all, we were interrupted by her father calling her on the other line.  She immediately had to go.  I sensed a bit of awkwardness between us over the phone call.  Unfortunately, I did not take the opportunity to confirm it.  Was I wrong to call her?  Was this news too personal to share?  I may have initially foist the issue into the spotlight, but telling her the news did not yield the relief I thought it would.  How did she really feel about this new revelation?  A friend commented that she might have perceived the news as a 'slight' for side-stepping the Christmas card topic.  Another suggested that I was "rubbing in" the fact that I was not single anymore.  A few weeks later, upon the Chinese Lunar New Year, I jokingly mentioned how our zodiological signs made us incompatible.  It was at that moment she responded with "I found someone".  As complicated as our communication was, I would not take back any kind or ill word that may have been spoken.  If anything, the our exchange had kept me thoroughly intrigued; on some days, it still does.  These days, our talks are very casual, most of the time never getting beyond "how are you?"  What other adventures are there in store?  More to come in part 3...
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is my first blog entry about my vacation since arriving here in beautiful  urlLink  Sokcho City  , South Korea.&nbsp; It is located on the northeastern coast of the country, a mere 4 hours out of Seoul and an&nbsp;even shorter distance to neighbouring North Korea.   Today the weather hit a high of 35 degrees celcius, breaking a record high for the city this time of year, and making it the hottest city in all of South Korea.&nbsp; It also seems that I arrived at the tail-end of a very short monsoon season.&nbsp; The first week, with the exception of the first couple days, was symbolically wet, warm and humid; the type of weather&nbsp;most locals are accustomed to.&nbsp; Now we've hit a spell of hot, humid weather that could last the rest of my stay.   My sleep rotation was off the first week when I arrived.&nbsp; Despite a wonderful, restful&nbsp;flight on  urlLink  Singapore Airlines  , the 16-hour time difference was a difficult transition.&nbsp; Some evenings I was lucky to get a couple hours of rest.&nbsp; On top of that, I began tutoring and teaching almost immediately as I arrived.&nbsp; With only a few Korean words in my vocabulary, I ventured out only a short distance from my place of residence, sticking to familiar streets and&nbsp;travelling&nbsp;between work and home.   South Korea is a dramatic departure from my comfortable, familiar life in Victoria.&nbsp; As soon as you step out of the airport, you are in a different world.&nbsp; English was hardly spoken everywhere I went.&nbsp; I mostly had to use hand gestures to describe what I wanted.&nbsp; It didn't help that I looked Asian, so most people identified me as a local.   The locals are fiercely proud of their language and history.&nbsp; It is rich with culture as I soon discovered.&nbsp; The language is composed of their own distinct alphabet (24 characters in total).&nbsp; It is a mis-mash of chinese characters , japanese grammar, and english words.&nbsp; Some words like "bus terminal" have been translated verbatim into Korean and virtually sound the same as English with a few minor pronunciation differences.   The Sokcho City limits remind me of a Vancouver Chinatown, with open markets and tiny little specialty shops at each corner.&nbsp; Stores go out of business overnight, and new ones crop up in their place the next day.&nbsp; You can always tell when a new store opens up because you find ballooned archways, potted plants, loud music&nbsp;and "Go-Go" girls dancing&nbsp;at the grand opening.&nbsp; Even at the grocery stores, you can here pop music blaring in the background.   The&nbsp;downtown&nbsp;encompasses an area similar to Victoria inner harbour, stretching all the way from James Bay to Esquimalt in a single land mass.&nbsp; It's a beautiful sight with its boardwalks lining the site of the recent 1999 Travel Expo (not to be confused with the World Expo), but it pales in comparison to the Inner Harbour/Causeway waterfronts of Victoria.   The locals do not consider Sokcho a wealthy city, but surprising, it has a reputation of being one of the cleanest in the country.&nbsp; The roads and sidestreets are run down, with plenty of potholes and uneven concrete.&nbsp; To the naked eye, the city looks like a slum, with high rise apartments towering over it.&nbsp; The buildings look old, run down, and in need of serious repair.&nbsp; I think I even noticed some   "leaky condos",   with buildings completely&nbsp;draped with green mesh material.&nbsp;   The real attraction of Sokcho City is the neighbouring  urlLink  Mount Seorak National Park,   or   "Seoraksan"   as the locals call it.&nbsp; The base of the mountain is riddled with luxury resort spas&nbsp;and natural, outdoor hot springs that make it a famous tourist attraction.&nbsp; You can go bungee jumping, take long hikes up and around the mountain, or take a swim in the beautiful waterways of the&nbsp;Yang Yang River.&nbsp; You can even&nbsp;ride some of the rapids like a sort of natural, outdoor waterslide.&nbsp;   Crime is virtually non existent in Sokcho&nbsp;and most of South Korea.&nbsp; The young men of the country are enlisted into the army at the age of 22.&nbsp; All over the city, you can see army men in their fatigues walking the streets.&nbsp; People even feel safe enough to leave their wallets or valuables&nbsp;on a&nbsp;park bench and not have it taken.&nbsp; I won't be testing that theory anytime soon, but I'll take their word for it.   There is much that can be said about South Korea as it slowly unravels in my mind.&nbsp; I was expecting for a totally backward experience that would send me home packing with a larger appreciation for my place of birth.&nbsp; What I am discovering is a very complex, modern society that has much to offer the world beyond its picturesque tourist sites and highly commercialized, flashy&nbsp;business culture.   The experience thus far has confirmed, and refuted, some of my personally held views about comtemporary Asian culture.&nbsp; I was once embarrassed by asian counterparts&nbsp;who appeared to me as&nbsp;striving to emulate the   eurocentric North American culture  , assimulating all its best and worst egos and icons.   I am glad I am here to see what it means to be "Asian" first hand.   
     
    
</post>


</Blog>