<Blog>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Went to Centennial park over the weekend, and i must say that it was the most enjoyable park experience i've had ever...the weather was nice and cool, birds chirping in the background, the swans and funny looking ducks waddling in the pond nearby, people walking their dogs, horses trotting round the park....lovely. Just sitting there and taking it all in made me look up in awe at their wonderful Creator...He is just so artistic...i actually felt very much at peace at that very moment, felt so proud of Him. Amazing... Never enjoyed parks back home, the heat and mosquitoes never fail to distract me from appreciating what was around me...am thankful for the experience that day... Saw so many dogs of all shapes and sizes that day too....made me desire one so much more! Just something about them that says...TAKE ME HOME!CUDDLE ME!PAT ME!TICKLE ME! Its amazing that God created a creature like the dog...wonder what was on His mind when He created it...must be thinking cuddly and warm feelings! I must remember to ask Him when i see Him face to face... Ok...enough rambling...glad that i posted this amazing experience...it would always remind me that there is more out there than life itself...
     

    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Gosh...my memory is truely failing me! Went to my blogspot and couldn't seem to find a button to click to post a new blog...when i finally found it, i forgot both my username and password! That was frustrating!! Eugene asked me...have i updated my blog? Was not very keen on posting a blog, but somehow felt compelled to keep it updated for awhile.. Have been feeling homesick for singapore on and off...there are down moments and there are up ones, but i tend to remember the down ones more vividly...sigh. Its not easy being here in Sydney, my mum told me to enjoy the place cos she thinks that Sydney is a very beautiful place to be in. I will, and actually i have, but i still find it hard to call it home! Home to me is still high rise flats, crowded shopping centres, fume infested eating places, oily and unhealthy food, humid weather...yup that is still very much home. Went to eugene's colleague's new home yesterday, it was HUGE...a really nice house with 4 cute dogs and 2 adorable children and all...started day dreaming about us having the opportunity to own such a life! But somehow couldn't fit this dream in the context of singapore...so i guess its either or....the possibility of a nice HUGE house AND dogs or a 4/5 room flat in singapore? What a choice! Enuff blabbering for now...its so amazing how easy it is to end a blog...and how hard and awkward it is to end a conversation! 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Eugene has been bugging me to set up a blogging account for ages so here i am...finally! This feels like the first time i set up my email account...strange but a proud moment for me! Thought i would start this up since i'm over here in Sydney and have lots of stuff and thots to share with anybody who would be interested to hear, oops or read. Have seen many interesting and beautiful "blog sites" (is that what you call that?) and feel so very inspired to create one too! But i am a computer virgin so it might be quite some time before i acquire those specific brain cells to even create something on the web! So strange to be sharing these thots to nobody in particular!  ok..eager to see how my blog site looks like so this first blog is dedicated to my dearest husband! (SEE I FINALLY DID IT!)
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Caught the show on DVD last night, was quite filled with.."wow..the Japanese really know what it means by loyalty". Wasn't even concentrating on Tom Cruise, the Japs in the movie really stole the show, especially the young actors! The movie portrayed slaying as such a glorified spiritual act. To me, killing another is murder, but of cos there are those that kill out of self-defense. I don't know, realised that am quite conflicted over this issue. But the bible does say, thou shall not kill...that's pretty clear to me.  Anyway, apart from the moral issues that i was pondering about, the movie did feel me with much respect for the Japs/samurais...the honour and cause that they all vow to fight to the end for. But then again, honour can also be misplaced...sigh...starting to contradict myself again! ANYWAY...had a nice time, catching up with the girls yesterday, over coffee and cakes...this is the life! So blessed to have such good company and the time to enjoy these little moments of joy! Women can really talk...dunno why we have so much to yak about and so much to let out! Gonna miss this when i start work...but i am really looking forward to starting work in the child care...a whole new experience.  This morning as i was doing my quiet time, started thinking of my dear friends back home..really miss you guys still, all of you will continue to be my thoughts and prayers. 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Went down to Chinatown to book cheap tickets back home for December...and we are set to go home on the 19th December. Seating there and waiting for the agent to confirm our flight, made me day dream about home and anticipate that blessed day! Pathetic right! After 6 months in Sydney, am still attached to Singapore. Its hard to explain or express this longing i have to go back, not that i hate the life here in Sydney, but... Was my grocery shopping day today, always feel a sense of achievement when i stock up the cupboards and fridge...the simple pleasures in life! Visited Vicki's blog site just now, and it never fails to amaze me at how God has brought our paths to cross...its so timely...and thank You God for these friends that You have provided. Another friend coming up today, Lloyd...another welcomed visitor!
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    My sis sent me a recent camp photo of the Young Adults group from my church back home. Looking at all the photos really made me miss them so so much! Sigh, all of you are still very much in both of our hearts and prayers...miss my sister so much too! Absence really really makes the heart grow fonder...Rebekah! Can't wait to see Ruth/Boaz soon!
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Charles...yup we had another friend over to visit us, and this was a picture taken  the night he was going to leave us, we were at Mrs Macquarie's chair, where you could see both the Sydney opera house and the bridge at the same time..it was freezing!! It was nice to have an old friend come to visit...made us miss home yet again...sigh
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Another amazing experience at Port Stephens! This time a total change in landscape...it was sand, sand and more sand! REally felt like we were in the deserts! It was so so cool to try our hand in sand boarding, had a mini race, and its obvious who won! I must say that it was pretty intimidating at first, cos the drop was very 90 degrees! But after doing it a few times you just want to keep going up and flying down again..Never ate so much sand before...but the scenery again left us dumb founded with awe...
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    After following them for a long time, and seeing their fins poke out of the surface..these beautiful creatures took a final bow before they left us on their way. It was stunning, a creation of an awesome God. The majesty of the creature was just jaw dropping, everybody on board just gasped in delight...the scene was priceless...
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Went to Port Stephens over the weekend to do some whale watching, and this was the beautiful view that awaited me as we took the boat out... 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    A truely beautiful experience with a treasured friend...South Head point @ manly. We wanted to capture the moment, but there was nobody who could help us out, so we attempted to do it on our own...not too bad, considering the shaky hands!
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       friends   urlLink     Friends from afar.  Had yet 2 other friends to come and visit our humble home. They demanded a home cooked meal as proof that i could cook! So i showed them! It was a nice warm fuzzy feeling spending time with friends from home. I miss home! Thanks for coming!
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It has been some time...since i've dragged myself to the computer to share my thoughts to the worldwide web. I feel God's powerful hand upon me the last week...i am now employed and also accepted to further my studies. Its funny how a particular door closes while another opens wide...i've got an inkling that God wants me in this line of work. Thanks for the big hint Lord! After the week passed, i also realised how easy it was for me to let these blessings go by without much joy...the complicancy of man... Had a really good friend over with us in our humble home too...it was refreshing catching up and hearing news from home. Today she has left for sunny Singapore and her absence is greatly felt, it always happens, but i thank God for the little reminder of home. I just hope that i would be equally joyful when trials come by again. But for now, i'm at peace....
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    I love kangaroos (not!) but I want a dog now.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yup..that was what the children called it when they saw it flying in the sky during outdoor play. It has been officially one week since i started work in childcare...and i've really grown to like what i'm doing with my time in there. The children are just so adorable in their own little ways and all of them are really uniquely themselves, i had difficulty identifying a favourite among them..love them all! Today was a good day for&nbsp;me, felt so satisfied with my day with the kids, had a few magical moments with some of them...and their adorable smiley faces made me smile too. The not-so-good moments, were changing pooey nappies and clearing the nappy bin after that! YUck yuck yuck, wonder how they stand their own smelly poo! Changing them always makes me feel pukey too. You can always tell when they have done a poo in their nappies, they suddenly become very still and quiet, they start holding their bottoms or they start pulling their pants down...they are that predictable! The joys of innocence... 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was my first day at the child care centre...am so so tired now....but my head is so full of thoughts about the day i just had, a headful of mixed emotions and feelings about my experience today. I must admit that it was better than i thought it would be, my colleagues are pretty ok, i guess i would have to get to know them better, but am still struggling to adjust to the way they communicate and just the way they are, we are just so different...sigh. And apart from that, i was in a constant blur the whole day, i think i was the only blur blur one, cos the rest were all in childcare for many years. But the day did get better when i actually got to interact with the kids and as there was an Open Day today as well.  But there is more to just playing with them, reaching out to them and having them play with you is a skill! Not easy, have to decide when and how to approach them, so that they won't run away from you!  There was this cute little girl with the same name...she was so so cute...but ignore me i'm biased! All in all, i just really thank God for being with me and arranging for things to be the way they were today...i still need time to adjust though...Lord give me strength and courage... 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Another familiar face from home...it was good to have you with us Lloyd! Got to know him a bit better too...and that guy is really crazy over his schweppes! He made both of us gain that extra KG...he can really eat!
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yup...started realising how different the aussies are to us. I guess it struck me when i was attending a First Aid course (oh ya, am a certified First aider now!). When i tried communicating with them....just had so much difficulty connecting and maintaing a conversation...why? Sigh...talking with them has made me so conscious of how i spoke and if they could understand me at all and if i was using the right grammer etc etc...why?  Rubbish!!I know i can speak good english...i shall just be myself and try again to communicate with the members of this community which i have to call home for 3-4 years more...Lord give me the courage and thick skinnedness! Back to episode 11 of The Successful Story of the Bright Girl!
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Started watching the korean drama serials that my sis sent to me...thought i should get started on it before i get back to work... Am hooked! It is so intriguing that i find myself wanting to put in one disc after another...refusing to stop and watching in anticipating to see what happens to the protagonist...now i understand why my sis says that its good...ok...back to episode 4...
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yup..that was how i felt throughout the entire show...COLD! Maybe cos its also winter now, so i could totally identify with the protagonists of the movie!  But i must say that it was beyond my expectations and it had the right elements for a catastrophe-thriller kind of film. 2 thumbs up, since i only have 2 thumbs!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was the last time i'll get to go grocery shopping with Lianne (my fellow housewife!)Cos once i start work in the childcare next friday, i won't have the luxury of going grocery shopping in the afternoons. Felt kind of sad that we won't be able to do this anymore. Was so so happy for my other fellow housewife, Vicki..SHe's got herself a job!! Could feel her excitement and joy over the phone while talking to her just now...Go girl! Lianne will be start schooling soon too... Yup...our mini homemakers' support group is slowly moving onto bigger and better things, a sign that we are all finally settling down to living out our lives over here! Really thank God for His providence for this little group of ours. Still remember the times when we were moaning and groping for some kind of direction and wondering what to do with the time on our hands. But i will make sure that we will still meet up at least twice a month, to yak and catch up with one another. Hmm...it might have to be Saturday mornings, while our husbands catch up on their sleep...we will sneak out and have a cuppa together!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My course materials and requirements for one of my modules has arrived!! And am feeling very intimidated by it...starting to realise that its a lot of work and its not going to be easy to discipline myself to set aside time to read and start on my assignments...wonder what made me think that it would be a breeze! Now am really wondering if i can cope with full time work and starting this postgrad dip? Oh well, am excited to start trying...challenging. One more to add to my list of "things to adjust to" 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>