<Blog>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      a lot of people seem to be looking for owned pics, so i thought why not make a whole site of them. well, here you go, 149 pics so far -  urlLink the owned archive 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
          Your browser does not support floating frames.  Please go to  urlLink the Punkscape newsring  for the latest punk rock news.      
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'm building a lounge downstairs so we can have parties and crap that are a whole lot cooler. If all goes well, I'll have a recording studio setup down there, and of course a skating area.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink http://www.purevolume.com  Trust me, if you like punk rock, this is your site.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      yeah, i figured since i listen to it so much, i might as well start playin it. anyway, i've got the lead guitar covered but i still need someone to play bass, a drummer, maybe a backup guitar, and someone to do vocals. you gotta live in or around gallatin, tn (town in the middle of nowhere that you've probably never heard of) and be 13-17. anyone got any suggestions for a name?
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink www.pwned.nl 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Click here for an Owned Pic of Britney Spears 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Just found this -  urlLink EDGE FM - ROCK RADIO  - station rocks
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink The Buzz Top 9 @ 9:09   urlLink The Buzz Top 20   urlLink The Buzz New Music 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Buzzfest 4 is set for September 6 at AMSOUTH Amphitheater. More Info at  urlLink http://www.buzzfest.com/index.html  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I decided I'd post some singles for you to go out and download out of boredom.  #10 - Breaking Benjamin - Simple Design #9 - Three Days Grace - Just Like You #8 - Smile Empty Soul - Your Way #7 - Taproot - Poem #6 - Shinedown - 45 #5 - Eve 6 - Hokis #4 - The Used - Maybe Memories #3 - Thrice - Silhouette #2 - MXPX - Well Adjusted #1 - Thousand Foot Krutch - Step To Me  EDIT: Just bought the HIM cd, but I'm too lazy to type all the track names in. Anyway, the entire cd rules, go buy it.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Just thought I'd share these with ya,   urlLink College Humor   urlLink Ebaums World   urlLink Neowin - Jokes and Funny Stuff   urlLink Liquid Generation   urlLink Urban Dictionary 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      yea, i finally set one of these up. not really sure what it is or what it will be yet, but who knows.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i'm not using thecowgoesmoo207@hotmail.com anymore. use thecowgoesmoo207@gmail.com instead.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      we've got bass, lead, backup, and drums. now we need someone to do the vocals, who actually can sing.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      then just visit the worst named site on the net,  urlLink the rasterbator 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      well, the dc banner turned out a lot better than i thought it would, so i decided i'd go ahead and make an element banner and an adio banner too. i'll take the pics when i have all three of them up :).
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      as i'm writing this, my printer is printing a giant 4 sheet x 3 sheet DC Shoe Co Usa logo. when i get the thing up ill take a few pics and post em.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>