<Blog>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      finally....jun hols!!! ok...so today was kinda sad 4 1/1...mdm ismi had to migrate to australia.....*sob* All of us cried( thk god did not flood classroom!!!) and she even gave us chocs! yum.. Hi ena! if u r reading this entree..thks 4 the autograph bk! Ok 1pm-2pm was most boring for us as we had a SUPER boring tok...all on stress reliev and all the crap..hu wanna listen to all that CRAP!? haha Chryz
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      blah blah.....well...exam results are kinda the best and worst stuff to noe....if u score well...u happi...if u fail....u sad and feel like the world is falling apart.. haha              Life Brought us together   Maybe the road was tough Maybe u thot life never gave us enuff. Have you ever thot abt the road ahead? the life u wud have missed if u were dead? Heaven brought me and u together.. to bring others joy.. to share the sorrows of the pple. to bring peace to all..  the journey ahead maybe be tough, forget all troubles, love and lust. for God has brought us together. Friendship maybe at the baq of out heads, but nuthing beats the love of your life.  one day, this fairy tale will end. the clock will tick its last beat, the birds will chirp no longer, the life will soon be crumbled and, realise that friends and family are the only way..                                                   to all i noe          
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hie! well today i got baq sum of my result....thk goodness...did not fail anything yet...phew! haha cant wait 4 tomolo!! Walkathon!!
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      haha...a bit lame rite.. well...i went ot c scuba too yesterday...he is a dog btw...so cute!!!Woof!
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      haha...finally...i m invading the universe....nah...it is jus slack time....ok...so maybe skool isnt over but at least we have post exam stuf for 2 wks and tan aye leng chasing us for money as if she was a legal loanshark...so irritating..always saying...girls pls hand in ur financial report now...i wan it by 2pm..but she is nowhere to be found so everyone heck care...and oso abt the $10 we owe her....hiya...she really lyk loanshark....everyday come to our class and assume that NO ONE pays her...sian already.....haha she is no. 1 on my *target* list...followed by indy....tcherz... ok...enff of the bad stuf 4 the week...went to movies to day....50 first dates...quite funny but when u r watching it with xq..it gets even funnier!  HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA *lafs hysterically* kk...gotta go werk on my plan to world domination...actually i mean PRO SLACKING haha
     

    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Harlo...well today... i went baq to wrps and guess what...todayz my last paper!!! so happy....well at least i get to slack..yay mum is comin home with spongebob sqpants stuff 4 me!!haha...i lurv spongebob!! so lame rite...but i m lovin it!! Xq and cidy...if u r reading this...i really miss u and also to the rest of the wrps gang!! maY MY DOOM FALL ON TO UR FILTHY DUNE HEADS!!
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello.....well my battery operated brain just exploded 2 the exam hall today...I was having geog in AVA rm and the aircon was lyk dammit cold.My hands were freezing and my head was bobbing away to the beats of the questions...especially the acid rain one....so sian....tomolo is another hard hitting day coz i have math!! Dunno waht has come over me....i m not crazy or wat..it is jus that math fever came and never got away...at least for a few mths...i hope it lasts....haha May my doom fall from the sky onto ur filthy dune heads...wel there is no upcoming invasion though...jus keep on reading ok? I wanna study me formulae 4 math now....aniway....thats my last paper...gotta give it my best shot..:p haha Calling u stupid wud be an insult to stupid pple...  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi!! this is the blog that i will finally hve the HEART to update...TOTALLY!
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Damn....y does SHE always tell me to do things....y does she always tell me how much to eat.....it is my appetite mind you,!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  nt refering to parents
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      HHAhAHAHA oops..gone mad..  On and On  The river flows... the grasses grow.. will they ever stop in time to come?  THe Life goes on.. speeding by. the rocky road ahead.. never seemed to end.. it just goes on and on..  maybe the Lord just wants  to give us this test? to show our true colours... to allow us to show our strength..  Life entwines round the human soul.. no one can change it for it has been planned. Mastermind..... the river of life  On and On... the road... endless as it seems.. grants ur the chance.. to live our dreams...  In denial.. i crawl up to the cliffs.. realising that the river.. entwined with our souls.. goes on and on...    
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sry ar....havent been in action for many moons...Was in HK enjoying mah..aniway, skool hols ar the mosy boring and exciting times...boring becoz u have to do hw all day long...exciting becoz u have the whole day to ur self...unless u have to go baq to skool 4 ELDDS lyk me larh..aka CCA for all of u..If u pple haf ani tournaments and competitions, Gud Luck! If u pple r on holiday, HAF FUN!! But if u pple r sick and sneezing away @ home, take care k? ok..i shall quit toking crap and tell u wad happened..NOTHING! For all 1/1 pple (IJTP) heres the HW list: English Math Chinese..... Nt alot rite..haha gud luck... *me abt to complete liaozz* haha luv chrystal
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      haha! well it has been some time sice i have written in here....heres a new poem  Dreams Untold  Confusions, in a whirl of rights and wrongs. Sholud i be dreaming or should i be gone?  The life, never-ending, the river always flows. When will the songbirds sing? When will the moon lose its glow?  Dreams aint reality, neither are they true, Why do pple evn dream, when nothing ever happens to u?  Entwined on a fence, trying to let go. For God gave us grace, to go with the flow.  Lonely, even i feel sometimes. When can't i comprehend, What i say sometimes?  So maybe time has passed too fast,  to let us live our dreams, to show ourselves, what we will really be....      
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For each day...  for maybe God has given u grace... to live it up to the next day... why not treasure it than waste it away... coz i noe heaven is never gonna stay 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>