<Blog>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Last night we caught the 10 pm showing of  The Day After Tomorrow  at the PK mall in Hilo. We both liked it despite the extra cheese and preposterous premise (global warming causes an instant ice age). Halfway through the movie, a bright, slow-blinking strobe light came on next to one of the exit doors near the front of the theater. This prompted many people to stand and head for the exits. Meanwhile, May and I sat quietly until the light stopped flashing a minute or so later. Weird.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So Fantasia wins narrowly over Diana. Just as I expected. Now what will I watch on television?
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    This picture was taken on Valentines Day this year at the park in Hilo near the hotels fronting Hilo Bay. I'm still evaluating Picasa. Posts pictures ok, but no way yet to create a caption for the blog post without editing the post later and no way to set the photo as an inline image. What's up with that?
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Two days later and I'm having none of the symptoms I had with the bladder infection. But the Cipro makes my head buzz, and not in a good way. At least I didn't wake up with a headache like I did yesterday morning.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    An Azalea bush sits at the top of our driveway.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Well, she finally got voted off American Idol, to no one's surprise, I'm sure. It's sad to see the last of three Hawaii contestants leave the show, but Jasmine was the appropriate choice. She seemed to take it well and she accepted her fate without shedding a single tear. Jasmine did Hawaii proud.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Meet Rosebud, our pet goat.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      They weren't originally slated to come to Hawaii, but with two Hawaii contestants in the top ten (and one in the top three!), thankfully someone saw to it that they book a couple of dates here, well, on Oahu (Sept. 28 & 29). Tickets go on sale this Saturday and they're sure to sell out.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Jasmine sang ok, but not great tonight. Both Fantasia and Diana sang better. Again. Still, with all the support she's gotten from her fans these past weeks, it won't surprise me if she isn't voted off the show tomorrow night. We'll see.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I can't even remember when I last saw a doctor for any reason. The number of times while living in Kona must surely be less than six. Last night I was up almost all night in extreme discomfort with what I suspect is a bladder infection. Symptoms, mild mostly, began about two weeks ago but came to a crux last night. Ouch. In the course of the visit they determined that my blood pressure is high and the doctor wants to have my blood checked for diabetes. Prostitis, thankfully, is not likely the cause of my current condition. He's prescribed Cipro, an antibiotic, for a week. May seems to think Cipro is weak and ineffective. I hope not.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
                       I'm not sure how she did it--maybe it was her tears after all--but somehow Jasmine managed not only to survive to the next round, but she wasn't even in the bottom two! For all we know, she may have received more votes than anyone. But I doubt it.       
     

    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Picasa, the photo posting software endorsed by Blogger, isn't freeware. Bummers. Guess I'll have to post pictures the conventional way.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      As a lifelong Hawaii resident, I feel torn about Hawaii's American Idol contestant, Jasmine Trias. She's a good singer without a doubt. But she's not nearly as good as any of the three other contestants. So although I love the idea of someone from Hawaii winning such a huge competition, I can't really see her moving on to another week on the show. I'll be very surprised if she survives tonight's voting. Yet stranger things have happened.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
                       So Google's recent takeover and overhauling of blogger.com lets me post to my blog by sending e-mail to a secret address.&nbsp; Cool feature if it works.    Need to get the server box up and running at work so I can take off the web server from this machine at home.      
     

    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Thought I'd give this new blog a go since my own fell to the wayside a while back. Whether I'll find time to post regularly to it is yet to be seen.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      After a week of poked fingertips it looks like my blood glucose levels are sliding downward. Started at a high of 193 on the initial test the morning after the doctor's visit and a low of 95 before dinner last night. Blood pressure is down to 113/77. Too bad no way to monitor cholesterol. Started a blood watch blog to record testings.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The good news is no urinary tract infection anymore. (Duh.)  The bad news: my blood pressure is high, my cholesterol is bad, and my blood sugar is high. Basically, the doctor told me I have type 2 diabetes and I have to monitor my blood glucose level 4 times a day. 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Fasted from 8:30 pm Sunday night to get my blood tested Monday morning at 9:30 am. No phlebotomist-in-training meant no problems drawing blood and no pain. Probably won't find out results until my doctor's appointment on the 21st. At least I hope I don't have to find out until then--the old no news is good news.   Spent rest of day shopping in Kona (again). Ran into Jill again, this time in Wal Mart. We bought green curtains and a couple of curtain rods. Got home and May wasn't happy with the mismatch in greens between the curtains and couch. I thought it was nice that the two greens were different. She wants to replace the curtains with a lighter sage green.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Spent most of Sunday working on May's project list. First, Ralph and I cleared out the left half of the garage closet. Took off the doors, removed all the shelving and nails everywhere and shot down the floor with the hose. Lots of that unknown red powder everywhere. Later, we pulled up the fencing along the wall in Rosebud's pen. The grass had grown over much of it making it a real pain to get the fencing free.   Yesterday we went to Kona to shop. Picked up a bolt cutter from Home Depot to cut the fencing we pulled up Sunday. Bought a couple of curtain rods and shower curtains to use as temporary doors for the outside closet. Bought some tile squares to cover the board over the old barbecue grill. Ran into Jill Stewart at Lowe's. Tried eating lunch at Killer Tacos but the place was closed for Memorial Day. Ended up eating at Taco Bell instead. Costco and Fite's Furniture closed too. Stopped at Foodland in Waimea on the way back home and picked up dinner from Don's.  Got a call from Kevin. He left a voice mail message.
     

    
</post>



</Blog>