<Blog>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I’ve just cancelled my ‘web’ access on my phone that Verizon so nicely charges five bones a month for. While it’s a neat idea, I used it approximately three times. When it comes down to it, is any information REALLY that important that I must have it right fucking now? Once again, I am grounded in the reality that a phone is a phone. I tend to get caught up in all the newest bells, whistles, and offerings, and forget that all the thing really needs to do is unfailingly make and obtain calls. Imagine that. Thankfully, the phone and coverage for me is fantastic, so I have no complaints there. I also get to bark various commands at it to do my every bidding, which makes me feel superior and powerful.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Let the earth tremble and the heavens pour.  I am going to the gym.  This of course is, by itself, nothing special. The special part is that it’s me. The guy who will pay his kids to get him a soda so he does not have to move. After the deal with my back, and this little thing called a mirror, I’ve finally decided to stop being a fatass and get back into shape. Not that I am some sort of huge couchcreature, but I defiantly ain’t what I used to be. Not only did I join this ‘gym’ but I am going at five in the morning. And also, gasp - watching what I eat. It’s like crashlanding on an entirely new planet. A strange, odd planet, but one that you begin to sort of like. I already feel much better, have more energy, etc. Why anybody would really want to know all of this, I’m not sure. But that is why I have a blog, so I can say shit about myself that nobody really cares about. Viva la Ego.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I hate buying software.  No, it's not the money. I have no problem supporting a developer that makes a good product. Especially smaller, independent ones that don't rhyme with RICROMOFT.   What I hate is this: there is always something better around the corner. And sometimes, it's free.  Take my current situation with Winamp5. After using older versions for quite awhile, and really liking the library feature to organize my MP3's, I thought it was time to pony up the cash. I was quite happy until I found I-tunes.  I-tunes does a fantastic job of organizing your music library. Much better than Winamp, in my opinion. I-tunes also has one other fantastic feature.  It's free.  I admit, I am always playing with new software, looking for the next great thing. The problem is that there are simply too many good products released weekly, especially the smaller utilities.   So what's the answer?   I have no idea. I am sure in two weeks, I'll move on to something else. I just won't be buying as quickly as before, and I'll do more research, I suppose.  Or not.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink CNN.com - Ronald Reagan dies at 93 - Jun 5, 2004   Rest in peace, Mr. President. You deserve it.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today's challenge is to manage  not &nbsp;to read or hear anything about  urlLink The Village  before one sees it this weekend. Which is just about damn near impossible with the media overload being shoved down our throats everyday. Turn on the radio,  urlLink  Howard Stern   is talking about it. Visit just about any website, touche. I am sure people will start talking about it at work soon, with no respect to those who have not seen it. See, I don't know much about the movie, other than the trailers, and I'd like to keep it that way. So you people who have seen it - STFU. At least for a couple weeks, ok?    urlLink Geekman . For those that don't work in the IT industry, please buy one, and abuse  it  instead of us. It may make you feel good for a minute, while you are angry, but in the end, we all know we are smarter than you. Let it go.   &nbsp;    
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       We all know what he would do. But what would he  urlLink drive?    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Microsoft has a  urlLink beta news portal  up and running.  I guess  urlLink Google  really makes them nervous, and heaven knows we  really  need yet another news portal, since good news is so hard to find. On the internet.     If cake is your thing, or the  creation of cakes,  take a look at a  urlLink Thorax Cake , created by the talented and not at all disturbed Barbara Jo.      (pssst Blogger - you might want to throw Google into your spellchecker. Since they own you, and all.)   
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        I suppose, if one desires their blog to be read on a regular basis, they must likewise  update  said log as well.        I obviously have a problem with this.        Since we decommissioned  urlLink the toast , I really have not felt like writing much. Sometimes a good break is needed.        So here I am, making an attempt to keep this thing updated on a regular basis, so those that  do  stop by won't shake their heads and move on.        I am not sure what I'll write about. Probably not games. Sure, I could tell you how fantastic  urlLink ESPN NFL Football 2K5  is, and at twenty bucks, and absolute  steal . I could type my hopes that more companies follow the brave lead taken, and re-think the pricing of their titles. I could blather on about how I feel  urlLink Riddick: Escape from Butcher Bay  is the best FPS since  urlLink Half-Life . (I could also, in the same sentence, damn the FPS label it has, and add it has a little bit of  every  genre mixed in, like a tasty soup.) But I won't. I could tell you that  urlLink City of Heroes  nearly stole two months of my life, like a perfumed harlot in the night. Nah.        I guess this space will be dedicated to whatever is on my mind at the time. Hopefully you'll stick around for the ride.        (pssst....have you tried  urlLink Firefox  yet?)    
    
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       There is a rather pleasing yet unpleasant side effect of this whole losing weight thing. When one drops a certain amount of mass from their frame, the clothes they once squeezed into begin to expand. After a couple months of this, one starts to look like a small child putting on adult clothing. Or as my co-worker so nicely put it, a ‘street person.’ I finally made the jaunt to the Land of Outside, and picked up some new threads. They fit much better, and yes, I look damn good. (The unpleasant part is that one now has to use actual currency to by said new clothes, instead of buying the important things like games, CD’s and books.)  This is not the point of this post, however. While out, I returned a CD I got for Fathers Day, and picked up the VELVET REVOLVER cd. I’d been putting this one off for a good bit, mostly because the singer really does not do much for me. The players are first rate – it’s almost Guns n’ Roses, for frigs sake. The music, as to be expected, is excellent. The vocals are passable, and I am sure I’ll be at a point where it won’t bother me, but I can’t help thinking how much better it could have been with a different singer. The vocals almost seem buried, like you really have to listen also. Maybe the producer felt the same as I.   End result – great music, so-so vocals.   Let’s talk about the copy protection that they included for a moment.  When you put the disc in your PC, you are prompted to approve to a licensing agreement. The CD then installs a device driver that seems to run as a service, which does not allow you to rip the CD. That you bought. And own.  This is all fine and dandy, the record companies are trying to protect their interests, blah blah blah. Does it matter that HOLDING DOWN THE SHIFT KEY bypasses the entire thing? Good job there. For those of you that DID install the software,  urlLink here are details  about the copy protection, and there MAY be instructions somewhere there on disabling it. They DO include the files in encrypted WMA mode on the CD, which allows you to play them with the DRM rules and regulations – check that link for the jolly details.  I am sure this policy will stop piracy in its tracks. Perhaps when they create an auto-running program that when the CD is inserted, DELETES THE ENTIRE INTERNET.    
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Last night we closed  urlLink Wickedtoast.com  for good. The end of some sort of era, I guess.  The reasons are many, but it really boiled down to one major thing - we simply didn't want to carry on with it anymore. Lost the desire. The flame went out. Pick yours.  Part of it was the site was becoming a genuine pain in the ass. It was hard to get people to do anything. A publisher sends you a game, the expect a review in short order, or at least in decent time. We started getting too many free games (a good thing!!!) that nobody wanted to review (bad!). That left the responsibilities to those of us who operated the site, and that got old really quick. Then there was the constant prompting to get people to write something, week lapses in communication, bickering with reviewers you are trying to constructively edit...the list goes on. My favorites are bringing on someone to write, and either finding out they are not very good, and having to spend hours reconstructing their reviews, or getting a primadonna who thinks his shit don't stink, and fails to see that our simple suggestions on oh say, proper sentence structure are out of line. Fortunately, our last batch of writers working with us didn't have these issues very much, but we went through some not so fun times. We did have a few that took the criticism seriously, applied it, and turned out to be damn good writers.  The other part was sheer discouragement. We were a tiny fish in a too-large pond to begin with, but hey - we were quality. We didn't bow to the pressure of game companies, since we paid for most of our own games. The companies we were close with respected us. But watching our stats rise and fall, and mostly fall was fun. We always said we were doing the site for ourselves, not the publishers or even the public, but you can only fool yourself with that for so long. You WANT people to read. You WANT to see your blurb on the cover of a game. You WANT comments about your work. When those things don't come, you do get discouraged.  The last part was simply time. We just didn't have the time anymore that was required to give the site 110%. I suppose we could have let someone else run it, but....no. We conceived the site, created it from scratch, and babied it all the way. If we can't run it, then I'd rather see it non-existent.  It's sad enough that working being in the IT industry has totally suffocated any joy out of my computer hobby, but the site was starting to do the same with my gaming hobby. And that's just not acceptable.   So we pulled the plug. Yeah, I miss it already. But on the other hand, a huge weight has been lifted, and I can either move on to other things, or just do nothing.   That last option is looking better and better. 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'd like to start out by thanking all of you humans of the male persuasion that get dressed and undressed quickly at the gym. Especially the gym I attend. You are doing the rest of us a great service.  If any of you go to the gym, or any place with public lockers-slash-showers, you've probably met The Naked Guy. He is the one that for some reason finds reasons to parade around the locker room buck ass naked. The same one who gets undressed, and manages to find a small speck on his locker that captivates his attention for 20 minutes. Also the same guy who manages to put every article of clothing on  before  his pants. Including his watch.  Changing ones clothes, or showering, by nature  requires  one to enter the naked state. That is understood, and accepted. Reveling in your nakedness, when accompanied by a Locker room full of men is just creepy and wrong. It also makes everyone uncomfortable. There is really nothing of interest on the ceiling - it's just a logical place to look when you are parading around sans pants.  Take this morning, for instance. We'll call today's offender 'Bob.' While I am doing my thing (very quickly, I might add) Bob gets undressed. I do not make eye contact with Bob, but I can tell, from the far corner of my vision, Bob has undressed, and is now naked. The blinding whiteness gives this away. Bob then stands in front of his locker, obviously admiring the blue metal that is so fashionable in the locker genre. He then begins to walk to the showers, stopping along the way to step on the scale. He then saunters into the shower area, and I am thinking that it's safe to turn around and leave the Locker room. Wrong. He must have forgotten something, and saunters back over to his locker on the other side over the room. Repeat the admiring of said locker, and back into the showers.  Why? Is it so hard to put on a towel? I am pretty sure he'd probably walk around the entire gym if it wasn't illegal.  The moral of the story is this. While you may be proud of yourself naked, there is a pretty good chance that you are CREEPING EVERYONE ELSE THE HELL OUT. Please stop. For the children, the kittens, baby Jesus and whatever other entity you are offending.  
    
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Eating an entire thing of Cinnamon Tic-Tacs in five minutes MAY make you want to puke.  Carry on.  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Spent some time with  urlLink Doom 3  last night. Overall thoughts, keeping is short - it's the same game you've played 1,000 times, just prettier. Sure, you'll be impressed by the graphics, especially if you have a nice fast system. Even at 800x600, which I have to play at, it looks damn good. But once you get over the oooh's and ahhh's, you start seeing the shortcomings. There is virtually no  urlLink physics  system. The environment allows very little interaction, if any at all. You'll spend most of your time in small, cramped spaces endlessly killing things over and over. There are no  urlLink alternative ways  to accomplish something - it's all straight ahead, into the next area. While these things certainly do not make a bad game (sometimes mass destruction is good!) they don't urlLink  compel me to keep playing  either. In my opinion, Riddick was a much better game, and looked nearly as good. And that was on the xbox. I don't think Half-Life 2 has much to be worried about.  Next.                 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Sometimes I wish I could re-open the toast just to give a game a fair review. Then quickly close it down again. With haste. This will of course never happen, but hey...  The game in question is  urlLink Sudeki  on the  urlLink Xbox . The  urlLink reviews  have not been terrible, but they have not been overly kind either. After playing for a good three hours, I can say most of the reviews are a bit too low. Maybe expectations were set too high, or people thought it was something other than delivered. I don't know. It's a fun RPG that is heavy on the action side, with lots of items to collect and cool places to explore. I really don't see much difference from games like Final Fantasy, except I actually control the battle in real time, and don't have to listen to brooding, whiny characters.  I also picked up  urlLink Dues Ex 2 , and am finally able to enjoy it. I gave the PC version a shot, but it ran like crap, and I had to lower the detail and resolution just to be able to play it. Reason 1,784 why I really dislike PC games. I'll take a console any day, kthx.  Edit: It looks like  urlLink someone got it right . Go, Avault.  
    
    
</post>


</Blog>