<Blog>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So Carole got a blogger, and I already had one (because I am oodles of blogs) so I decided that I would update this once in awhile, too.   So today I am going to Reader's Theater rehearsals for an hour, and then I was thining about just taking the bus over to Bill's from there. I was going to run over to Blockbuster and get a movie for us, but I only have 3 dollars. I hope that they have a few there already.   Spiderman 2 comes out tomorrow at midnight, and Bill and I lus Pat and Leslie (his girlfriend) will all be going. I still haven't really met or been introduced to Leslie, and I guess she told Pat that I glared at her. Eek! I didn't glare at her, and she sounds kind of interesting, so I don't want her to think that I am rude. Oh well, I guess. Back to Spiderman 2. It's going to be so awesome. I mean, it really is the best comic book movie out there. And there are going to be 3 of them. I think that they cast the movie so well, and th special effects are awesome. Bill is even more excited than I am, which is predictable. I mean, he actually reads the comics, and has been for a long time. He is like a little boy that is going to off to camp. He keeps telling me that he can't wait for it to come out, he just can't wait. And then I told him that it is soon and that he is going to have a wait a bit.   So yea, that's really the highlight of my day/week/summer so far.  Oh, except for the fact that I practically got the job as a lifeguard!! I got a call back saying that I had passed the interview process and that they wanted me to come for a swim test. And that I can definitely pass.   Ack... I just heard voices and noises... but I don't know whether it is coming from my house or from out my window...  No one is home but me... ok, I am thouroughly freaked out. Oh god. Hmm... there is probably no one in my house. God damnit. I'm in a towel though... I should probably get dressed.   More later,  VenusPanties  
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Thirteen Random Things You Like:   Swimming    Music    Bill    Reading    Excitment    Good butterflies in my stomach    Lain and Boogiepop    Peanut Butter    The 50s    Ska    Politics    Being in water (in general)    New clothes     Twelve Movies: (no order)   Elephant    Lost in Translation    Big Girls Don't Cry    Kill Bill vol. 1    Kill Bill vol. 2    Romeo and Juliet    Pleasantville    Hairspray    Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind    Detroit Rock City    Suicide Club    Fight Club     Eleven Bands and Artists (no order):   Reel Big Fish    Catch 22    Streetlight Manifesto    Planet Smashers    The Toasters    The Who    Pink Floyd    The Beatles    Buddy Holly    NOFX    Five Iron Frenzy     Ten Physical Things About You:   My lips    My gray-blue eyes    My hair    My blob of a stomach    My ever-gorwing boobies    My toned calves    My scarred hip    My ankles    My "beauty mark" above my lip    My butt     Nine Good Friends: (no order)   Christa    Carole    Bill    -    -    -    -    -    -     Eight Favorite Foods &amp; Drinks:   Peanut Butter    Water    Potatos    Sushi    Pie    Miso Soup    Edomomi    Chicken Nuggets (homemade)     Seven Things You Wear Daily:   Underoos    Bra    Pants/shorts/skirt    Socks    A shirt of some sort    Scars    An apathetic facial expression     Six Things That Annoy You:   Myself    My body    My habits    My boredom    Ignorant people    People telling my to calm down/shut up/stop yelling/etc.     Five Things You Touch Everyday:   My hair    My computer    My bed    My phone    My legs     Four Shows You Watch:   I love the 80's strikes back    Best Week Ever    Paula's Home Cooking    Iron Chef     Three Celebrities You Have A Crush On:   Leonardo DiCaprio (he's my boyfriend)    Hugh Grant (he's the sexy bastard that I cheat on Leo with)    Dominic Monaghan (I sex him when I need that little bit of excitment I don't get with anyone else)     Two People That You Have Kissed: (the last two)   Bill    ...     One Person You Could Spend The Rest Of Your Life With:   Oh god... the rest of my life?   
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Write a short paragraph involving two  children  teenagers and a dead duck.     Sadly gazing down at the innocent victim, Noel sighed. It was a disappointed sigh; a viciously disappointed one. She had, in fact, run over this duck. With her own car, started by her own key, and propelled by her own foot. This was not a good sign.     Noel didn't usually believe in omens, but she knew without a doubt that this definitely was one. A horrible omen to have come across on the day of her last AP final. Noel wasn't frustrated at this fact, nor angry. Just... very disappointed. How could she have let this happen? She was a  wonderful  driver. License obtained on her 16 birthday, 50+ hours driven beforehand with her permit. This was a very disappointing event indeed.     Biting her lower lip, Noel crossed her arms and continued to stare at this deformed animal sprawled across the roadway. Vulture food is the only thought Noel had floating in her mind. A very graphic scene indeed. And then-- what would her friends think? What would they say? After the crude questions and remarks along the lines of, "Did you smash it?!" or "Was it gross?", Noel's friends would be simply horrified by the accident. Appalled. Noel herself was appalled at what she found herself capable of-- involuntarily, yet without and urge, effort, or thought to stop what would ultimately happen to this poor, poor duck who had been wondering across the country road.     "Where is your family, little duck?" Noel wondered, a calm, puzzled expression glazing across her face. Where had this duck been off to? Down the road for a soda pop? Surely not.     The ferocious sound of a car horn whirled her back to reality.     "Get out of the road, Bitch!" yelled an obviously upset teenage boy driving a beat up Honda Civic.     Noel, composure intact, glanced down at her watch revealing a time of 7:22am, and frowned. She was now going to be late for 1st period. Looking back at the duck once more, she decided that maybe it wasn't that huge of a deal in the first place. Maybe it's not even worth telling anyone else about.    Strolling back the her immaculate Chrysler Sebring Sedan and popping the drivers door open, Noel eased herself into the seat, turned the key, shifted into drive, and lightly pressed the accelerator; not forgetting to signal the fact she was getting back onto the desolate road, of course. Driving away from the scene, Noel was left just as she had first been-- disappointed.      
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Moo?       So I told Bill that I could stay up longer than him tonight. He stays  up until like 7am... and it's 12:51 and I am already tired. Gah! How am  I going to last?    
    
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey, how do you make a bored person? You call them Kristy and smack them with a boyfriend who has become nocturnal.   GAH!!!!! 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It's oh-so-hard not to pick fun at these. She may look good when others are choosing her clothes and doing her hair and makeup, but just look at how she dresses herself!         -----  In other media gossip, it may be a cocaine problem, not an eating disorder, that both caused the 75 pound weight loss of Mary-Kate Olsen, and to check into a drug treatment center in Utah that "also deals with eating disorders". Yea, uh huh. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So I keep hearing about how Internet Exploer isn't safe and how it gets all these viruses and shit, so I decided to download a different browser.    urlLink FireFox   It really is a neato brower, but it's still kind of in it's beta version, so there are a few stupid things about it.   For one, most the blogs that I go to are fucked up in some way or another. My  urlLink greatestjournal  layout is messed up with weird borders, and the friend's page only loads about halfway down the visible screen, and then just stops... with no scroll bar or anything, and this weird border around it. And this journal won't even load at all.   I do have this thing though, where you have the option of viewing the page with IE, so that's what I do for those pages.  And it has this client for livejournal/greatestjournal that really rocks my socks.  So I think that I will stick with  urlLink FireFox , and just complain to them about my pages. They are sure to fix it if I do that!  --------------------------  In other news, it is almost one o' clock in the morning, and my ex-boyfriend just accidently called (I think he must of sat on his cellphone or something).  My mom got on the phone and thought (since I was on the line) that it was me calling from somewhere else (she was already asleep when I got home), and was all confused.  That made my night a little less boring.  
    
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Welcome to Comcast High-Speed Internet!    I swear to God I am ready to fling this fucking thing across the room!!!!!!  I have been trying to make my comcast personal webpage for awhile now, and have gotten no where with what I want.   See, I uploaded the song that I want to post on the webpage (so that I can use it for the background music on my blog), but for some goddamn reason I can't post it on my webpage. I am getting REALLY mad.  In their stupid little wizard thing, it has no options for using your uploaded files. And I can't find out what the name of the fucking source directory is to use either. So I don't know how to reach my uploaded files. I did the live chat assistance thing, and the guys told me nothing.   GAH! I am so frustrated. I have been working on this for about 2 hours now, without any results. It's really bugging the fuck out of me. I hate it I hate it I hate it. I am seriously so MAD.  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink hi5 - Who's in?   So this is cool. Another little blog thing that I am never going to update because it's more like a friend's network than a blog. And there are a whole bunch of groups that you can join too! (Of course while searching through them you have to go through the  ~!!!~~yO ppL CuM joIn mY SExY GrOup 4 TEenS!!!!~~! ) GAG.  Some of the groups that I am in are:         Virgo          Comic Books          Readers Anonymous (The Book Addicts)          George Orwell 1984 and Shooting an Elephant          Independent films/Cult films          Lost in Translation         BATTLE ROYALE!!!!!!!!!!!!!          The Film Critics          Japanese & Korean Drama Paradise          Kill Bill          Foreign Movie s         Rude Boys And Rude Girls    (this is a ska term)        Ska          Catch22          60s and 70s Rock and Roll          Beatlemania          Dim Sum and Sushi Lovers!!          BoA lovers..         History          THE DEBATE GROUP          Republicans and Conservatives           So yea, you should go to that link at the top of the page and join and come be my friend! And join some groups... because I say so.   Here is the link again  urlLink  hi5  . 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So I wrote this whole long entry, and then my computer froze the page. Goddamnit. Whatever. I'll start over with what I remember.     So I got all of my information/profile page filled out. Man, was that interests list a bitch! I have 200 intrests on my  urlLink greatestjournal , so I had to edit all of that down to get like... 15 interests. Fuck that.  But yea, now it is done. And I even made and uploaded a nice little profile icon/picture thing too. Me= pleased.     In other news, I saw the midnight showing of  Spiderman 2  on Tuesday night/Wednesday morning. IT FUCKING ROCKED MY [TUBE]SOCKS!!!! It was so awesome. You can read my excellent review of it from when I had just returned from the cinema  urlLink HERE .  It's SO worth spending your money on... so do so.      Yea, I like this blog because it is my ramble-away-about-not-really-anything-but-somethings journal. I mean, I have SO many other blogs, but this one is really nice.   I've got my  urlLink regular greatestjournal . This is for my normal posts about things that I find interesting, fun/random updates, and my  urlLink OneWord  writings. It's basicly my default blog.  Then I have my  urlLink Rants and Raves greatestjournal . That's for my opinionated posts about politics and such.    Another one is my  urlLink livejournal , my totally private journal where I am free to post my true feelings on things, situations, and people without the scare of high school drama/gossip/tattle-tale/ridicule/etc. Bill is always trying to weasel his way into this one to see things that I have said about him.   I also have my  urlLink melo (melodramatic journal)  for my more artsy and darker posts. This is where I spill my prose and poetry. The site is down half the time, and not many people know about Melo anyway, so I would never rely on this as my normal blog. I don't think you can see it unless you are a member anyway.   I rarely use my  urlLink xanga , but that's for the Columbia River IB webring with the same people from the forum, so that doesn't really count. (I think that I have just as many aquaintances from River than I do Skyview... but I have never met any of them). *shrug*   Then there are the ones that I never use, like my  myspace , and my  blurty , and my  woohu , and my  minilog , and the couple of actual free  websites  that I created and attempted to have journals on, and thousands of other blogs that I have started and never gotten back to.   Ah well.      Oh, I downloaded the little  blogthis  thing for your toolbar. That's what I am using right now. Pretty spiffy, I'm telling you.    But now I am off... it is 2:30 in the AM, and I am bored, so I think that I am going to search for people on blogger that have my same interests... or taste in books/movies/music.  See ya! 
    
    
</post>


</Blog>