<Blog>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Are you the type of person who cannot get along with your fellow employees? Is it because you feel like you do your job better than anyone else and you don't have to get along? Well, I have news for you, you can be replaced. As much as I don't want to have to terminate you, because you do a good job, I am willing to spend the training time on a team player who has a good attitude versus putting up with the crap you stir daily. Don't think this business can't run without you, because every position can be filled, even the CEO. That is what I am thinking about today.  

						
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   How much do you know about your boss? Do you have any idea what he actually does? Try looking at yourself from his position, what do you see? The next time you feel like complaining about your work load, put yourself in the owners position. Sure, he is the boss, but what kind of headaches have you given him today. What can you do to show him that you acutally care about the business and are willing to help ease his workload? That is what I am thinking about.  

						
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Alright, I better clarify that I am not in fact a virgin, just a virgin to this format.I have been trying to think of ways to express what I am thinking and it was suggested that I try a blog. As this is my first time, I am naturally a little apprehensive, but excited to see how it all works. I am the CEO of a small company with 16 employees, and aside from needing support from time to time, I just need to vent a little too. This morning starts off with a managers meeting to come up with a solution to replace a customer service rep. We want to promote from within, and have a great candidate, but he is doing a great job where he is and his manager doesn't want to lose him. Because pulling the candidate from where he is will cause more problems in the short term, we have decided to fill the csr position temporarily with someone from another dept who knows that job, and she can train our candidate as he is doing his regular duties. Now we need to find another entry level person to train so that we can promote our candidate into the csr area. I am thinking about how to get the right person in the right job with the least amount of disruption to our customers.  

						
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I looked really hard at all of my employees recently, seriously evaluating the performance of each.  As I identified those who might be performing at less than peak, the advise I received from Dr. Lawrence King at a recent meeting came into clear view. In order to have peak performers, you must stamp out mediocrity. How do you do that? I have setup 90 day reviews for some of my mediocre performers and am monitoring their performance. Can I get my employees to put out more? What is their motivation? I will have to inflict some kind of change to induce the necessary stress needed to make change. I know change is hard, but if you don't change when the company changes, you may find yourself out of a job. That is my thought.  

						
</post>


</Blog>