<Blog>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'm off to a job interview. In a few hours I could be on my way to becoming an IT consultant for the Swedish company Office IT-partner. The scary thing about this is that I'm not even sure I want the job. It's not the coolest company in the world and to top it off, I get to work in VB6 :D The job also requires me to drive around Sweden a lot (one or two hotel nights a week). We'll see. I'm probably going to another job interview in Lund next week. If I screw this one up, I can rest assured I get to try again next week :D
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      A lot of trailers and sneak peaks coming out of E3 today. I've spent the last hour or so watching as many of them as possible and I must say that the Halo 2 multiplayer movies impressed me the most. Gotta love the partially destructable vehicles. I wonder if it's still XBox exclusive for two years of whatever like it was with the first one. I sure hope not. I refuse to play games with a stupid gamepad!  The new Half-Life 2 trailer didn't really tickle my fancy. Sure, it's probably gonna be awesome, but I just get the feeling we're seeing the same scenes over and over again, just from different angles. Counter-Strike on the source engine did look kinda cool though. It's weird seeing one of those old maps, but all of a sudden it doesn't look like crap anymore :)
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Why doesn't "cool" stuff like E3 ever take place in Sweden or Denmark or whatever? No no, it has to be half way across the world. Man, first chance I get, I'm moving out of this god forsaken place. You! Headhunter for some cool up-and-coming IT business located in a warm but not too warm area of the United States, hire me!
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I figured I'd start me up one of these too! Who knows, maybe someone will read one of my posts some day (yeah, right!).
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I was at my second interview/tour this friday. This time I visited a software company in Lund (approx. 57 km/36 miles from where I live). The company is called QlikTech and they develop business intelligence software. I was interviewed for a position as a software tester. The guy who interviewed me was afraid I might be over-qualified for that particular position, but he told me to think about it and let him know if they should consider me for the position or not. I've given it some thought over the weekend and I think I'm gonna give it a shot. Even though he might be right and that I am a tad over-qualified, it still seemed like a really nice place to work. I also hear that the company is expanding at a rather rapid rate, so I guess I could always move around inside the organisation if I find it unchallenging.  Now, all I can do is cross my fingers and hope they pick me. Lets do it together! :D  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>