<Blog>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Woohoo - she'll be here tomorrow! - which probably means I need to clean the place up a bit - uh oh :(  Since Jen's going to get a car we'll be able to at least grab some furniture so she'll have somewhere to sit - and she has timed it perfectly for the pool opening on the weekend.  While I'm slaving away in work, she can lie by the pool and fight with the cicadas :)  Got my HDTV Cable hookup - unfortunately the on-demand function seems to have broken in the meantime, so I have to get out early again today so someone can come look at it.  On the brighter side of things techie I managed to blag two 1U dual PIII 866 machines for free, I'll swap the mobo's out into a more reasonable case and hook them up at home - no idea what I'll use them for yet but I'm betting that they'll munch a few SETI units in the meantime while I figure it out.....  One last thing - where the hell is the Alt Gr button on US keyboards? - it annoys me to have to type Alt+0128 for the Euro (€) symbol and then have to remember what the code is for accented e etc.  I know I could change the keymap to UK or whatever but I shouldn't have too - how about an Alt Gr option or something?  *end of rant*
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      That's right, this is the week, Jen arrives on Thursday and will be staying right through to the following Sunday - Yay! :)  Also on the good news front, I now have Cable TV, Broadband and a new mattress.  On the not-so-good-news-for-Jenny front I still don't have a bed frame, a couch, or even something besides the floor for her to sit on......  On the other hand that does mean that she will have plenty of reasons to do that favourite female pastime - shopping! And with someone else's money no less - always the best way to do it.  Should be getting a few rack mounted dual PIII's gratis from the job too - will be nice to play with them, maybe set up a beowulf cluster or something else equally difficult to configure :)  After all I'll need something to do with my spare time when Jen leaves :)
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'll be getting bot a new mattress and cable TV/Cable internet on Saturday.  The prospect of Digital Cable with HDTV and a 3MB cable connection makes me drool :)  Should be cool - though I still need some furniture - a desk, a couch, a coffee table etc.  The place looks so bare without anything - though the stacks of DVD's books and cd's help a bit - so shelves are on the list of things to buy too.....  At least the TV works as a monitor so I'll be able to actually able to use my cable connection when I get it.  Hopefully the next post will be from my G4 cube hanging of a 3MB cable connection :)
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My stuff from Ireland arrived this morning - so I now have all my CD's, DVD's, clothes etc.  Unfortunately I have nowhere to put them :(  On the bright side though, I  did  get my new  urlLink TV .  Not a bad price either.  Plan is to use that for now and them wall mount it in the bedroom when I get my bigscreen TV later.  I've been looking at some of the 50" to 60" DLP screens but I can't decide at the moment.    My phone should be hooked up tomorrow which just leaves the Cable to go, fingers crossed I'll be up and running by Monday - it's always nice to have a 3 MB internet connection :)  Got a nice aerobed to sleep on for now, my mattress has been ordered and should be here on Saturday.  No word on my bed frame yet though - can't win them all I suppose.  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've decided to document my little adventure in America.  My previous attempt at a blog ( urlLink http://adam.killingmachines.org ) has fallen by the wayside somewhat, but I think with some of Blogger's extra features, I should be able to rectify that situation. Besides all that - it will give me somewhere to moan about the red tape infested wold you end up in when you immigrate into the US these days.  Anyways, on with the blogging - after nearly 6 weeks in the country I finally have a new place to live - right next to Reston town center. The rent is reasonable and the big bonus is that I'm within walking distance of the job, which is good given how hard it is to get a drivers license in the state of Virginia when you were born outside the US.  Go take a look at the  urlLink requirements (pdf)  for yourself and try to figure out how many of those documents you might have. It turns out that the only thing I can use to prove my identity besides my passport is the I-797 form I got when applying for my Visa. Not too bad you might think, but then I applied for the Visa in January, so my memory of forms I obtained is a little hazy. It was only when I got desparate and started Googling every form listed on the sheet to see if I could get one that I found out I had the I-797 already. Once I get the learner's permit it's just 30 days until I can take the test - that should be just in time for delivery of the new car :)  Other than that things have been going pretty well. I'm finally going to learn PERL tomorrow - properly this time too - not my usual half assed attempt - the company are paying for an intensive 3 day advanced course - it would be nice to know at least one programming language properly.  Most importantly, my lovely (and far too good for me) girlfriend is visiting in a couple of weeks - all I have to do now is make sure there are things like a bed, chairs, tables in the new place before she comes. Another trip to IKEA is needed methinks.....  That's enough for now - more when I get bored :)
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Not so much from the what happened point of view as from the "thank God it's over" point of view.  For some reason I was shattered this week - I essentially passed out around 9 p.m. on Wednesday night and slept right through.  Then my bloody ankle started to act up- just when I thought it was getting better.....  On the plus side I found the excellent  urlLink Dia  program which should do as a nice replacement for Visio - who needs licensed software anyway?  The IC department in work finally delivered the Linux box I ordered.  They'd imaged it with Redhat 9, but I didn't like the way they had the disks partitioned and I like to stay a bit more current, so following a plesant experience with  urlLink Fedora Core 2  on my laptop, I installed that instead.  The box itself is a decent spec considering they gave me whatever they had spare - it's a 2.4 Ghz P4 Dell- not bad at all.  Now I'm going to watercool my shuttle system so it stops making so much noise.  Annoyingly it looks like I might have to replacethe RAM in that system - seems to have developed somenasty errors - every time I try to view a Windows Media player video on it the program crashes - and games work for about 5 seconds.  Strangely  enough Quicktime seems to play fine so maybe it's a directx memory addressing issue or summat.  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, now that things are settling down a bit I find I have a bit of spare time on my hands.  I have plenty of things on my to-do list but I've got some stuff done.  First off I have kicked off the transition of  urlLink Comerford.cc  to  urlLink PHP Nuke .  I won't be using Dreamweaver to administer the site anymore, because I no longer have a license for it with the change of job, hence the transition to a more web based management of the site.  You can view the initial template here:  urlLink Nuke Site .  In fact now that I have switched jobs a lot of my licenses are hosed - Photoshop is gone too, not to mention Windows XP Pro (I do have an XP Home license, but why bother.....).  There was a time when I would have just kept on using them illegally but that's over.  Usually I can find an alternative that's free and usually Open Source, so that's what I intend to do - just for kicks, here'sthe list and the alternative:    Windows XP --> Linux (currently Fedora Core 2 but that may change)  Dreamweaver --> PHPNuke & BlueFish/Quanta  Photoshop --> The GIMP  Firefox --> Same, just on Linux :)  Thunderbird --> Same, just on Linux :)    Fedora Core 2 is currently running happily on my little Sony R505DL laptop, and all of the bits and pieces, besides the scroll wheel (which I never used anyway) is working.  I'vealso managed to get an RSS feed to work on PHP Nuke by converting the Atom feed.  I put a little guide up on how I did it here:  urlLink Atom to RSS .  So, left on the to-do list:   Install Linux on the Xbox  Build out my two other dual CPU boxes and get them up and running Linux  Design a new theme (or use an existing one) for the Nuke Site    And there's probably more I'll dream up along the way.  That's it for now......
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Woohoo! - I got my learners permit!  This time I got every question right, though if I'd had this test last time I would have had no trouble then either - just the luck of the draw I guess.....  Now all I have to do is learn how to drive before my car arrives next month :)  Yesterday was a pretty good day all round in fact - as well as the successful test, the Pistons destroyed the Lakers.  Since I had 20 euro on the Pistons at 8-1 odds I was pretty happy :)  A fact that I am now paying for since my happiness inspired me to drink 7 or 8 beers, oh well.  So, no going out for me tonight - have an 8 o'clock start in work tomorrow and I need some sleeeeep.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just realised I never mentioned the new chair - My Lazboy arrived on Saturday and I'm glad tosay it rocks :)  On the bad side of things - I managed to fail the theory test on the Virginia drivers license exam so I have to re-take it tomorrow........grrrr  What's annoying is that I needed 20 correct out of 25 and I got 19 - the last question was how much more likely you are to have an accident if you are drunk - 5 times, 7 times, 10 times or 12 times.  How the hell am I supposed to know that - so I went for 12 times and got it wrong - pain in the ass. At least I can get another lift down to the DMV early next week.  Guess I better get studying :)
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Finally got around to installing linux (fedora core2) on the laptop - it is working quite well, I even have wireless networking going on it, using the Netgear WG511 card I bought a while back - Nice :)  Also have the bare bones for 2 new systems - one dual PIII 1Ghz and one dual PIII 866.  The second one will be donated at cost to Mr. Irwin who has been good enough to drive me around the whole time and populate my apartment :)  The other will be my default file/web/whatever server on my home network.  Since it has RAID capabilities I should be able to come up with a nice fast machine :)  Haven't decided what to run on it yet - BSD or Linux......Fedora doesn't seem too bad so far, gentoo is a possibility if I'm bothered putting the time in, then BSD is as stable and secure as it gets, hmmmmmmm...  Anyways - back to watching the basketball, after seeing England go down to France tonight, a Pistons win would be the icing on the cake :)
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday wasn't bad - in order to keep myself busy I cleaned the place up a bit - moved a book case to where it is going to live permanently, relocated all of my computers to the new desk, fitted a mod-chip to the X-Box and fitted a half length PCI graphics card to my Qube - whew!  At least now I can use the nice shiny new  urlLink LCD  that I got from  urlLink Iiyama  rather than the television.  Next thing to do is get Linux, probably  urlLink gentoox , working on the Xbox.  Not because I need another box, but because I hate it when companies like M$ try to dictate what you can and can't do with something you bought..........  On the bad news side, my lazboy chair which was going to be delivered today will have to wait til Saturday - they picked the one time to deliver it that I absolutely could not make it home - so much for a 4 hour delivery "window".  Roll on Saturday :) At least my bed will be complete by this evening, I'm working from home (at the new desk) so I can accept delivery of the base.  Sin é for now......
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Jen left last night and it was 10 times worse than when we said goodbye back in the Old Country - at least then I had all the excitement of going to a new job, a new country, a new apartment etc.  Even the fact that my Lazboy recliner is coming tomorrow can't cheer me up.  It's DMV time once again this week too which does nothing for my mood - though hopefully they'll at least accept my application.  Last thing I want is to have a nice shiny new car and not be able to drive it........  Anyways, I can't wait for September when she'll be back, then all I have to do is help her find a job here and she can stay!   Here's hoping.....
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My apartment now looks like someone actually lives there, my DVD's, CD's and books are up off the floor, though not arranged in any meaningful order yet ;)  As soon as the desk arrives (should be tomorrow) I'll post some decent pictures of the whole thing.  The only disaster was the CD storage unit I got from IKEA - I put it together, after having a few drinks at 1 a.m. and managed to essentially put all the shelves int he wrong way so that the screws are visible - uh oh.  Anyway, once full of CD's you can't see the screws, so not too much of a disaster :)  The sofa/couch is ordered too, now all I need is a lazy boy and I'm sorted - should be going to the lazboy store tonight/tomorrow night to take a look at the options there.  Of course none of this would be possible without the arrival of my lovely girlfriend who can drive while she is here.  She's also pretty nifty with a screw driver and allen key :)  Right now I believe she is amusing herself in Leesburg Outlet mall while I "slave" away in work.  Speaking of slaving, I better get back to it.....
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Unfortunately it sems that my webhosting company has gone tits up.  Urban-ISP.net no longer resolves, they don't return e-mails and their phones are disconnected.  Looks like that is that.  Because I recently lost my back up of the site I have lost most of the content too :(    A few exceptions are my blog (obviously) and a couple of pages I found in the Google cache.  Ah well, I suppose the site needed to be revamped anyway - still, it is incredibly annoying.....  
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OK, I knew that the whole Atkins diet low carb thing was big in the US but I was still surprised when I got here at how pervasive the whole thing is.  I'm prepared to live with it because, lets face it, most of us could stand to shed a few punds - me  definitely  included :)  But just now I saw an ad on the TV - it was for a low carb  DOG FOOD  from Pedigree!!!  That is taking things too far - I mean, sure I got a great laugh from it, but it is getting ridiculous - if your dog is too fat, the TAKE HIM FOR A WALK MORE OFTEN - DUH!   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Decided it was time to flex my coding muscles this week so I've put together a little tool that converts IP Addresses, URL's and Host names into Autonomous System numbers and gives a few other little tidbits while it's at it too.  It can be found here:   urlLink AS Number Tool   Of course it can be found on the old  urlLink homepage  too.  It all came about because I couldn't find anything to do this for me - needless to say there's a command line version that I use personally too.  Now most people reading this are probably wondering what the hell an Autonomous System is - well first off I'd like to clarify that I mean an Internet Autonomous System, not a Mathematical one.    To use a poor analogy, think of them as the country codes and area codes used in the telephony world - without them you wouldn't have long distance calling because the exchanges and switches would have no idea where to send your call to.  Well AS numbers are something like that in the internet routing world.  Go to  urlLink Wikipedia  to learn more about  urlLink them .
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Went to see Spiderman 2 last night - have to say that I liked it - didn't have the fun of the first one when you were learning how they were going to implement all the superpowers and stuff but still good none the less.  Some soppy bits - to be expected in a blockbuster these days - but the effects were good and the action scenes were well put together.  Special effects weren't as jaw dropping as The Day After Tomorrow that I saw last week - never has a film with such a weak story line been saved so well by special effects in my opinion.  Oh, and I've found out that I'll have a  choice  as to where I can watch the Euro 2004 final.  There's a bar in Arlington - Summers - and, if I'm too hung over, there's always Comcast PPV :)
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The site has been down/slow for the last couple of day - no idea why and I'm too lazy to find out.  Hence the reson for the lack of new entries - I have confirmation that my shiny new Audi A4 is on the way to the dealer and everything is in motion - now all I need is that license.  Unfortunately I have to wait until 15th July until I can do the test since there's a 30 day waiting period before you can take the test.  Still, at least it gives me a little while to learn........  I may need the full license to get the car registered and released to me too, which is probably a good thing - having the car parked outside the apartment and not being able to drive it would drive me nuts.  Hopefully I'll know today or tomorrow exactly how much of a dent this will make in my finances too.  With insurance, the downpayment, the initial loan payment and sales tax - it's adding up pretty quickly.  Fingers crossed the up front total is under $20,000 - anything more than that and I'll have to put off buying anything else for a couple of weeks - like food for example :)  Back to work...........
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got a letter yesterday, from Audi Financial saying my credit application had been turned down.  Naturally, this frightened the crap out of me and it was too late to contact anyone by then.  Thankfully it was all a false alarm, the letter was generated by accident and everything is fine with my car again :)  Hopefully I can get my license by next week - I've booked an appointment for a test for next Friday (yes I know it's the 13th) which gives me another week or so to get everything down, which should be plenty.  Now there's a change from Ireland - no 9 month wait to take a test..... 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Picked up the new car yesterday - I still can't drive it without a licensed driver in the car too but that should all be rectified soon enough. Pictures can be found  urlLink here .  On the techy front, I finally managed to get some of my content back up following the Urban-ISP disaster.  The  urlLink How to flash a FireWire/i-Link DVD  page is back - people seemed to find that helpful, so I'm happy I got it back.  Most of the other stuff is hosed however :*( 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>