<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday I went to the softball picnic that was fun nope not really and today Im just going to my moms friends house for her kids B-day yea real fun. and then idk well g2g bye   Jordan 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I am so bored&nbsp;idk what to write. There is nothing to do. Im going swimming at vanessa's. fun. well Im out.    &nbsp;  Jordan  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       This weekend was fun. Saturday-went to the St.James fair and did nothign because it was boring. Sunday- I went to the Greatful Dead concert and it was very fun. I had a great time and im glad I went. I even bonded with my dads girlfriend. I didnt smoke no pot becuase people problay think&nbsp;I did but&nbsp;I didnt.&nbsp; I did drink though. That was the only illegal thing I did. And today we just got back at 2 p.m.&nbsp; And then I went to Emilys house with Jensen and Erin and we did nothing becuase my mom was being gay. And today Chris got his new car. Yes. A new pimp moblie. lol, but I went to the mall with Chris and Jensen and Chris and I were looking for our Mario and Luigi hats at lids seeing if we can make them there, but then we ended up not getting them and gettin a SOX hat yea becuase they are better than the cubs, and chris got a A's hat. And we met the fagest guy in radioshack.&nbsp;Man he was gay. As Danny would say&nbsp; Whoa this guy is gay. Well thats it. bye    &nbsp;   &nbsp;  Leave some comments    &nbsp;  Jordan   
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      &nbsp; Well i just started this thing and today i am going to the saint james fair n shit  i am currantly happy and the summer has been going pretty good so far   ~Jordan    
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well today was very interesting. it was fun though. With Chris,Danny,Emily,and Colleen. It was exciting i would have to say. and basketball was a bitch. but other than that it was fun. we all went swiming at vannessa's yea shes a pimp. fer shur. and&nbsp;Chris and&nbsp;I mak some damn good pancakes. Mario and Luegi all the way   &nbsp;   leave me&nbsp;some comments   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   ~Jordan&nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       &nbsp;Well today was kind of boring I had open gym at 8 in the morning fun huh nope not at all well it wasent as bad as it usually was, and I had two games, J.V. and Varsity I did ok in both of them. We blew out griffith in the J.V. game. And the Varsity we blew out bishop noll. and after that I went to the fair and talked to a cop and got yelled at fun shit     &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;   ~Jordan    
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink http://flickr.com/photo.gne?id=146444         I love De Paul I want to go there for college 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today is Serena's birthday so I will be with her.And theres really nothing else to do. Tommorrw im going to the national night out so I can obay the law for at least one night. Yay. Well im out   Jordan 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>