<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The theory is, is that we all get coupled up for the winter, so that on all those cold and snowy nights we have someone who will stay in with us and watch those movies under the big comfy blankets.  Its that we can pack on our holiday pounds  and not worry about how it will affect our ability to attract a mate.  The theory then goes on to say that you will spend so much time with this person stuck in cramped New York apartments and you will grow visciously resentful of them, and come Spring, when your vision is flooded with tank tops and mini-skirts, you'll dump their fat-ass and start embarasssig yourself chasing after the new crop of Spring chickens.  Isn't that the theory?  Then why does it seem like, here at the height of Spring, that everyone is all coupled up again.  Maybe they aren't, but it really seemed that way as I struggled to find a dance partner last night at Motherfucker.  I came to Motherfucker with little to no cash, as I am broke.  I decided that I could swing a drink or two on the ol' CC.  After the second drink, I tried to close out the tab, only to then learn that it was a $50 minimum.  I can't afford that.  But it was too late, so it was time to drink.  Maybe it was that I could barely stand up straight.  Maybe it was that whenever I took the hands of a potential dance partner, she ended up either smashing into a wall of people or accompanying me on my trip to the floor.  But within this slanted world, there were moments of clarity where my dancin' feet were right on the beat and workin' just fine.  Luckilly I was able to find Miss M. at one such moment and we were able to pull of the acrobatic wonder that is the Greg and M. dance.  It is quite a feat of strength and grace and it cannot be described, but it has been known to silence the most raucaus London pubs and to create spontaneous outbursts of applause.  Miss M. is super skinny and light.  It can only be done with her.  I have damn near killed poor strangers who do not share Miss M.'s slender frame.  I think I damn near almost killed one or two people last night trying to replicate something that shouldn't be faked.  I felt like I was forcing something. I felt like everyone already had their partner.  Whether platonic or romantic, it seemed like everyone I ran into was all paired up.  Partners in crime, two peas in a pod, etc., etc.  I felt like an unneeded extra part.  Something that didn't seem to fit into the evening's plan.  A square Greg in a room full of round holes.  It was like walking around with one broken heel, always feeling off-kilter and I never really got into the spirit of the whole evening.  By 5:30 am, they kicked me out.  I don't know how I came to be one of the last people standing there in a near empty room.  All my friends had long since left leaving me confused and alone.  I went outside to way too much daylight and cursed the morning sun.  Having no money for a cab, I started the mile and a half drunken walk that would take me to the proper subway train.  I probably could have gone to a closer station, but the idea of waiting for a transfer was much to much for me in my drunken state.  The walk was grueling and the blocks stretched as long as work days.  After realizing I had not eaten anything since an omlette 18 hours before, I stopped and rested, spending the last $2 I have to my name on an egg and cheese.  I made it to the subway and got on.  I think I thought that was the end of my mission.  When I awoke 2 hours later in buttfuck Brooklyn on a train that had long since past my stop, I realized I was wrong.  My goal was my bed.  Fighting one hell of a headache and a monsterous urge to pass out, I switched to a train going back to my apartment and bit my tongue to keep me conscious.  Finally, about 3 hours after I was kicked out of Motherfucker, I made it home and debated whether or not crawling into my bed at 8am was a victory or a defeat.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I went to Misshapes last night and spent some quality time seeing Sarah, whom I never get to see enough of.  That was nice.  I danced a bit, drank a bit, and went home.  I learned one very important lesson though.  If you try and phone a girl for a booty call at 5 in the morning, its best to refrain from actually using the words, "booty call."  They don't take to that.  One of the roommates is making a short movie.  I spent Sunday dressed up in a military officer's dress uniform filming scenes in our building and around the surrounding neighborhood. Its shocking how easy it is to make Williamsbirg look like a fucked up cold war era eastern European city.  The area really does look like shit.  But we took a lot of shots from moving cars and all that fun stuff and had a productive day.  Then, we totally dorked out and drove around blasting Wagner and other dramatic pieces of classical music like the 1812 Overture.  I'm not sure why we did this, but it was fun.  Things I learned from watching the footage we shot.  My ass is so much bigger than I thought.  Put me in a military uniform and I do not look tough.  I look gay.  I look really really gay.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I hardly live my life perfectly and often upset the ones I care the most about.  Yes.  Sometimes I do need alcohol to live with myself and my actions.  Somes I just need a dark room to be alone in.  That was the case last night when I got very disgusted with myself and left all my friends without saying a word and came home to an empty apartment and went so sleep frighteningly early.  Sometimes I think the best thing for me to do in this world is to stay out of its way.  Elle is totally selfish.  I know that.  She knows that.  Yet, there is a spark there.  Sparks between people becoming rarer and rarer the older you get (or at least in my experiece.  I hardly proclaim myself to be an authority on anything).  During certian moments, she creates a sense of warmth and peace that no one has been able to create in me with years.  And yes, i make poor decisions based on that feeling and every day I am closer to ending them, but occaisionally, I like to feel that warmth once again.  And yes, I did totally gloss over the fact that I went home with someone else.  That someone else was an old friend.  A long time ago, we had one date and I was so nervous that I had one too many margaritas while waiting for her and I was falling over drunk the entire date.  Needless to say, she lost any romantic interest in me.  After that, we got to know each other and became friends, and so yes, we went home together.  It was nice, it was fun, we both knew what it was and what it wasn't.  I was actually quite shocked at her suggestion that cross that line for just one night.  Maybe I shouldn't have taken her up on the offfer.  Maybe I was frustrated with my situation and made yet another poor choice.  I knew I was no one special to her and that as soon as I walked out the door, whatever had happened would stay in the past, but in the end, it was really peaceful and relaxing and we spent all morning laughing and joking, and for a few hours there, I didn't feel like my life was a complete trainwreck.  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I left work yesterday at about 3pm.  I was feeling very sick.  Came home, cancelled a job interview, slept and was awakened at 8pm by a call from Elle.  She was in the neighborhood and wanted to come over.  I told her I was sick and she said she didn't care, that she was bored.  Her boyfriend works until midnight, and she moved here with him and doesn't know too many other people.  It kind of hit me.  I am just a sort of distraction to her from her boredom.  Just someone to fill up those lonely hours.  But a sucker is a sucker, so I said yes and she came over.  By 9:30, I was feeling better and decided I could take on an open bar.  Elle came with me.  We drank.  I tried to kiss her and she gave me this dirty, "you know we are just friends" look.  But once we were on the dancefloor, once the drinks were in us, once our hips started to sway with each others, it was back like how it was.  Full of smiles, hugs, kisses, and eventually real making out.  I looked up into the DJ booth and saw Sarah shaking her head with disapproval.  All my friends wish I'd stop this nonsense and give up on this foolish and doomed attraction.  I told Sarah I was only kissing her to get her sick as some form of petty revenge.  Sarah said I was full of shit.  She was right.  She's always right and I am most often wrong.  Eventually midnight came and went and Elle's boyfriend kept calling, asking her to come home.  She kept delaying and we had about 10 last dances before she finally ran off to be with him.  That always kind of hurts.  I am petty.  I do things for entirely the wrong reasons.  i am a dirtbag.  I went home with another friend and we spent the night being friendly.  This morning as I walked home from my friend's place, I opened my wallet and saw that all my money was gone.  I bought one drink and tipped for the free ones.  Total money spent $10.  Total money missing $55.  Total money Greg now has to feed himself with for the next 7 days $0.  Now I am just getting home, and I am so sweaty and dirty and in need of a shower but I only have about 10 minutes until I have to meet up with Elle again.  We're going shopping.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm really confused.  Elle has been calling and emailing me nonstop.  She is desperate for us to be friends, but it can be so hard to be friends when one person has thrown themselves so emotionally at the other.  Its even harder when, at times, those feelings are reciprocated, but only sometimes.  Its like I am dealing with a split personality.  She regrets we ever stepped past the lines of friendship, but if you were to read the emails, or hear the phone calls, you'd sense the flirtation in all of it (telling me about taping a picture of the two of us on her computer, etc.).  I feel like I am just some tool she can use to continually validate her desirability while she stays in her relationship.  When  I am apart from her like this.  The whole friend think is ok.  I can keep my emotional distance.  But as soon as I see or touch her, I turn into jelly and I want to break down and cry and fall to my knees and beg her to be mine in some ultimate display of how pathetic I can be.  I think this means I can never be in the same room with her again.  I have no will power when it comes to her though.  I am a weak weak man.  On a better note.  I highly encourage everyone to come to Bar 13 tonight to hear the impeccable Sarah spin her tunes, dance with me, and, of course, drink all the free alcohol they will be giving away.  Plus, the CEO gave everyone the day off tomorrow.  That means I will be dancin and drinkin til the crack of dawn (or until my sickness kills me, which it might.  My throat is swelling up and my fever is returning).   All I have to do tomorrow is get my rat pack suit tailored for my brother's wedding.  PS.  Still no date for the wedding.  But if you do come to Bar 13 tonight, please remember that I am a sick sick man in case I look absolutely deranged and utterly unappetizing.  Its not me at my best. 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I just wanted to thank everyone who took the time to read the last post and comment.  I found it all very interesting (although I was sick of the topic by the end of today).  As Uncle Grambo would say, comments are so best.  Thank you thank you thank you for making it a more interesting Wednesday.  As I have been holed up at home with a nasty cough and fever these last few nights, my life is a bit dull, so expect the next post or two to reflect that.  Then back to the mayhem as usually.  And PS.  to the girl who said she'd give me food for head tonight and totally bailed.  You suck.  I am starving.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The post:  To us boys, a girl's planning of the future of a relationship is akin to her coming up and saying, "You know what?  I think, in like 10 years, I'd like to buy a house.  We should check out whats available."  And the boy is thinking, " A house?  OK, first of all, prices are going to change SO much between now and then, not to mention whats available, or what neighborhoods will be like, or if I'll even still be living in this city, or, for fucks sake, whether or not I'll still even be alive!"  There are just so many variables out there that we see no point in planning until the time has come.  But more than that, we need the future to be open.  We need to think that our band might get signed, that the book deal might come, that we will star in that major movie.  That we will be rich and famous enough to finally snort coke off some supermodel's ass.  And frankly, unless your girlfriend is already a supermodel who lets you snort coke off your ass, you just can't hold onto that dream and simultaneously plan a future with a girl.  Give us our dream.  We will fail, and then we can get serious.  But for now, whenever you say, "where do you see us in the future?" you are crushing that dream.  You are telling us to just give up every fantasy we've had since we were twelve.  You are stealing our motivation to get out of bed in the morning.  You are taking away our will to live.  And don't get all high and mighty on us, for we are not dumb.  We know that if we were to make these plans for the future with you, and then you met some guy who was a rockstar, a doctor, whatever, and he was into you, you would leave us in a heartbeat, all the time thinking to yourself, "now here is someone who can provide me with the secure future I want so much."  That same pragmatism that makes you want to plan a future with us, is what also allows you to leave us so coldly and easily.  So yes, when you say, "So what am I to you?" to a boy, he really is thinking, "well you ain't no supermodel with a line of coke on her ass," and when you say, "So where do you see this relationship going?" he hears, "so you're free to pick up Timmy after soccer practice on Tuesday?"  So remember that often what draws you to a man, his confidence, his dreams, his promise for a brighter future, is exactly what you destroy when you ask him too much about your future.  A note on the post:  This is written a little over the top.  I know that.  But as there were requests for more insights into the male mind, so I am posting this anyway.  I have run this by a couple of boys and they all seem to agree that it is fundamentally true.  Maybe the coke on the ass thing is a bit shallow, but it serves as a metaphor for those things that we want to do that we couldn't do if we were in a relationship.  Instead of coke on an ass, it could be a 3 year trek around the world.  It could be finally being able to date your celebrity crush.  The point is, that in order for the dream to work, we have to live our life in a way so that we can completely adapt to it when it happens.    Now it is true that sometimes we do fall in love, but as one person told me, "the ones we fall in love with, are the ones that we think are cool enough to stand by our sides when our fantasy comes true."  This hope that the future will contain some completely remarkable surprise is the basis for most men's lives.  It is our driving force, and sadly, as we hold out for our preposterous visions, we purposely limit the amount of baggage we will have to carry over from our old lives to the new one.  The second you take that dream away, you break the man and extinguish the flame that you fell in love with that lives inside of him.  One sentiment I recieved from a boy who read this was, "Honestly, I won't ever be able to fully commit to a girl until either I have achieved my dream, or am certain I failed, but that doesn't mean I can't have some decent relationships in the meantime."  Yeah.  We are totally fucked up.  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      No money and no health means no good life stories.  I could dredge up one from the past, like the time I was so broke I had to rub old men's nipples for money, but that one is just kinda gross.  I've been thinking about this mediocre Swedish movie I saw with Elle about a month ago.  The basic premise was that there was this guy with a girlfriend but he just sees this other girl and he is so fixated he runs away from his girlfriend just for the chance of meeting her.  He does.  They kiss and fuck and all that and he totally falls for her.  It totally fucks up his relationship with this girlfriend.  The new girl though, she is married.  She has a husband.  She puts the night of lust behind her and ignores the boy, pretending not to know him as she returns to her normal married life.  At the end, her life is exactly the same and his life is totally fucked.  It reminded Elle and I of our affair, the way she had a man that she was planning on returning to normal with, and the way I was running around messing up my life like some fixated mongoloid.  There was this line that struck me.  It said something like, "For men, love is something that happens, that they cannot control, and it is usually something to be avoided, because more often than not, it is an inconvenience.  For women, love is a choice.  It is something they plan on and it is built into their vision of the future.  Being in love is something they decide on."  Although I am not sure I really believe that, I was shocked at by how much thought and decision making Elle was doing with regards to her love life whereas I was a complete victim of emotion.  I started watching female friends of mine and I noticed something peculiar.  I noticed they were all much more ready for the future than I was.  They were more on top of grad school applications, they had 5 year plans, they had a definitive sense of what they wanted and were working towards acheiving that.  A friend of mine was later talking about how girls working in his office were having a harder time dealing with the fast-paced tempo and the ever changing list of priorities.  Basically, they couldn't deal as well with an inconsistent present.  They couldn't handle the lack of plan.  Another person commented that boys were a mess, a complete wreck who lived in the moment and dealt with the present constantly, never thinking more than a week or two ahead.  I notice this in me and many of my male friends.  They also said that if this is the case, then if things go chaotic in the present, boys don't really notice it as much for it doesn't contradict any preconceived ideas about what should be happening, whereas to girls, it messes up their plan.  I love sweeping generalizations.  And I love when people tear them apart.  I find it interesting.  But if this one is true, it really gives me a sense of hope that relationships really are a complimentary thing and that by having two people become one unit, we have a lot more power and diversity in dealing with life's hurdles.  But also, I think this leads to major relationship issues.  I feel that women, because of this future sense are more likely to say things like, "i know there are issues right now, but we can work through them, because there is something special in this relationship and we have to nuture that, make compromises, etc. and eventually we will get to this goal of a stable relationship." or conversely, "Although this seems fun now, I know this won't work in the long run, so why am I wasting my time?"  Whereas, a lot of boys I know have the simple philosophy of, if it seems fun, keep doing it.  If it gets tiresome or too draining, get out.  There is no sense of fighting through a rough time for the sake of the relationship.  There is only, "how is the relationship working right now?"  I think this idea explains many of the stereotypes of men as being non-commital etc.  its not that they are against it, they just don't understand it.  I mean, they understand the concept, but it is just not the way we think.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am starving.  For every 15 calories you give me, I will give you head for one minute.  That means, a bag of Doritos will get you 10 minutes of head.  Before you go running for your calculators I must warn you that as I have never given a blow-job in my life and that it wouldn't be a fair trade in that regard, this stands for girls only.  Or, if you want, you can just give me food and we can negotiate some other sort of barter.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I got an email from Elle.  It was actually sent last Thursday but I've been out sick and haven't checked my work email account since then.  It was long.  The basic point was that the first kiss between us should not have happened and only happened because of alcohol, and everything after that was my fault and I made her be a bad person by making her cheat and that she resented me going to LA because, in her mind, I only did it to even further screw up her relationship with her boyfriend.  Maybe there is some truth in that, but it hardly was my sole purpose.  The point being is that she doesn't really want me in her life because I make her a bad person and she needs to get her life back to normal, aka, without me.  Its funny how such simple and expected words from a lover can change all your feelings of love and longing into a bitter and wicked hatred.  Sometimes turning love to hate is the only way to move on.  It make the word seem so wicked though.  I spent way too much money on this LA adventure and the raise I was promised at work did not happen.  I am now beyond broke and will not be able to eat food for a couple weeks.  I feel like a cliche.  I feel like the "Friends" theme song, "Your job's a joke, your broke, your love life's DOA."  Oh God, you know you are in a bad bad place when you starting taking some shit show to heart.  Just kill me.  I'll consider it an early birthday present.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I think sometimes I get a bitterness towards pretty girls.  Sometimes it makes me really upset about the amount of attention they get just from being physically pleasing.  People hang on their words and give them attention, no matter how crappy their personality is.  It probably happens with cute boys too, but I don't notice it as much.  I like to think that girls, being the more reasonable of the sexes, aren't as shallow and don't humor the cute boys so much.  I think this happened to me at dinner the other night while I watched some pretty girl own a table with her vapid monologue.  I think I get angry because I fall for it too it and it makes me so angry when I realize that I am just as shallow with my own desires at time.  I think I misdirect that anger at the wrong people at times.  And most importantly, I think even if you are really really bored from staying at home with a fever for most of the weekend, it is not a good idea to go out drinking while feverish, with no food in you, while on numerous cold medications.  You end up acting weird to your friends and friends of friends and feel very ashamed the next day.  I hope my friends accept my flaws and forgive me.  I also hope I didn't get anyone sick.  Tomorrow is Elle's first day at her new job.  I offered to treat her to dinner to celebrate afterwards.  I made that offer last week and haven't spoken to her since.  Still no word as to her silence.  I think she has put me out of her mind.  I wish I could do the same.  I am still sick and my mind isn't clear enough to write anymore thoughts down this weekend.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      After work yesterday I headed over to see D.'s band play.   He's 18.  I met him when he was 17.  It was a rooftop party at Sarah's building and he approached me, saying he had no place to stay.  I told him, he could crash at my place but he couldn't slow our night down.  After the building kicked us all off the roof, Mr. Red and I bought three 40's and gave one to D.  We told him we only had 2 blocks to drink them because we were headed for a bar where we knew this cute girl would be working.  We had been drinking all day and there was no need for 40's.  By the time we got to the bar, Mr. Red and I were a bit too drunk.  By a bit too drunk, I mean, I was trying to suck on some girl's neck as her boyfriend yelled at me to get away from her and Mr. Red was physically climbing over the bar to talk to the bartender.  They asked us to leave.   We decided to head over to Shout! and when we arrived at the door, the bouncer refused to let Mr. Red in due to his level of intoxication.  The 17 year old D. walked in no problem, despite being drastically underage.  It was at this time that I got the brilliant idea that if Mr. Red and I were to walk around the corner, we could switch T-shirts and return and the bouncer would not recognize us.  We are not the same size.  We stretched and ripped each other's shirts apart and returned to the bouncer wearing rags.  He was not fooled.  We were denied access and went home, leaving the 17 year old to party it up by himself.  Maybe we should have tried to live more like D. rather than ask him to live like us.  That is what I was thinking that night, and I thought it again as I stood downstairs at NorthSix watching his band pump out very very catchy energetic garage punk.  I was very pleasantly surprised.  They were so much better than I expected.  The rest of the night was supposed to be just a quick trip to say hello to Sarah as she was DJing and then to head home and rest up for my performance review the next day at work.  Instead I got way too smashed, running over a parked car, setting off its alarm and staying out way too late.  Luckily, there was a person who took it in their fine heart to let me crash at their place, avoiding the electricity-less apartment of darkness that I have been living in, and who was also kind enough to let me sleep in when I called in sick this morning.  I really am sick now.  i have a huge fever and I am in one of those moods where I hate what I am.  I hate that I cannot function like an adult and am more child than man.  I am hoping this fever isn't the same thing that sent Elle to the hospital.  Speaking of her, I haven't heard a peep from her since that one call a few days ago where she told me she had been in the hospital.  The lack of interaction has caused me to fluctuate between feeling rejected and actually moving on.  Part of me is also really scared that she had to go back to the hospital and that something is seriously wrong.  Silence is so scary.  If only I knew which way to direct my feelings.  The world seems very lonely and empty to me right now.  I think i have to curb the drinking, start meeting my responsibilities and stop making such a fool out of myself and my life.  There are things I want to do and people I want to be nicer to.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This isn't a story about me tricking girls into showing me their panties.  Ok, it is, but its about other things too.  Its about the eternal dilemna of cute girls who are instantly sexually objectified every time they walk out the door.  Its about the constant harassment, lascivious looks, crude comments, and unwanted attention they get everywhere.  Its about boys who are attracted to cute girls, who are instantly labeled sexual predators for having this uncontrollable attraction.  Its about one boy lying about taking it up the ass so that he and this girl can get to know each other in a normal healthy way.  It was strange how instantaneously the Pixie took to me once I was no longer a sexual threat.  Soon we were hanging out all the time, going shopping, watching movies, regular friend stuff.  It was fun and we got along really well.  Sure, sometimes we'd go to bars to check out guys together and I'd have to fake a lot of my personality, but for the most part, she was getting to know the real me.  Then the sleepovers begain.  It was summer.  The bedtime outfits were small, if there were any at all.  I'd lay there, watching her slide out of her clothes, standing there naked, looking back, smiling at me bashfully as she decided which little number she wanted to sleep in that night.  She'd climb into bed and we'd lay there all night long, arms wrapped around each other in the most comforting of innocent embraces.  God, how I wanted to kiss her.  Just one long tender kiss to show her how much my head was swelling with emotions for her.  I'd give her little pecks on the cheek, probably holding one or two a little too long, but never did I slip and reveal my secret.  Not yet.  It was still too soon.  If I told her too early, she would be completely pissed off.  It would be a huge betrayel.  I would need to wait until our bond was completely solidified before I admitted my lie.  In the passing weeks we became very close and open and one night I drove my roommate's minivan to the Lower East Side to hang out with her.  We got drunk and stared at boys and at the end of the night it was time for me to drive home.  I was a bit drunk and so the pixie asked me to hold off on the driving for a bit and offered to hang out with me in the back seat of the minivan until I sobered up.  I asked her why she didn't have a boyfriend and she told me she was actually quite shy and doubted her abilities to perform in the bedroom.  I was shocked.  Seriously.  Up until that point, I always figured girls had it easy in the bedroom and it was up to the boy to "perform".  I mean, its pretty easy (although not too fun) for the girl to resort to just laying there.  So I asked her to go into more detail.  She said that it wasn't the actual sex, but other sex acts.  Specifically, blow jobs.  It was then, that she looked at me with these really timid embarassed eyes and said, "I know this sounds really really weird, but, I mean, you're a gay guy, I mean, the way I figure it, you've both given and recieved.  Do you think you could teach me?  I mean, could I practice on you?"  I thought to myself that any man with any sense of morals would realize that it was now time to tell her the truth.  Instead, I said, "Ummm.  I guess so, but if it gets weird and I say stop, you have to stop. Promise?" "yeah," she said.  And with that she pulled me onto my back, lying me down on the bench seat, start to straddle me, undid my pants, and "practiced".  We became increasingly more sexual, and I allowed her to think that she was helping me to find my more "bi" side.  One day, at dinner, I couldn't take it anymore and  I finally told her the truth.  She was shocked and felt used, but admitted that she had grown to like me and that she would forgive me.  We started dating.  I completely stopped my gay routine and became another straight guy.  This was a drastic change in personality and it really messed up the dynamic of our relationship.  We were both thrown off.  And honestly, I had spent so much time deceiving her, that it wasn't easy to become completely honest with her, and so when things started to get weird, I started seeing my best friend's ex on the side.  That was weird too.  So here I was, in two weird relationships, wanting to get out of both.  The thought of ending both seeming exhausting and I totally copped out.  I decided to let them both do it for me.  One night I called them both and invited both of them to meet me at the same bar at the same time.  Knowing that they knew who each other were and would say hi to each other and that at least one would mention that she was meeting me.  By the time I showed up, both their eyes were aflame with anger.  I started to regret my decision and braced myself to face the wrath and scorn of two decent girls who I had totally been an asshole to.  But what happened instead (as I should have known from watching Jerry Springer) is that instead of getting pissed at me, they were battling each other.  Both spent the night trying to make out with me in front of the other one.  Finally, they both cornered me and demanded I make a choice. My first choice was neither,  but the realization of going from two girls to none sunk in and so I decided I would continue seeing one of them.  But which? The face of the pixie looked so hurt and sad, and after all my deception over the past few weeks, I couldn't help but choose her, and together we left. (a side note.  The other girl is actually an amazing girl and just got married and her husband is one of the luckiest guys alive.)  After that, the pixie and I went home, I left the apartment for a minute to stop by the deli downstairs.  I ran into a friend of mine and recounted the whole story.  He laughed and asked me, "well, did you pick the right one?" and I replied, "No.  The right girl would have too much pride and character to have been 'picked' like that.  I chose the one who would forgive me."  I've always felt guilty for doing that to two wonderful girls.  I should've stayed gay.  Straight guys are such jerks.  
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      We forgot to pay ConEd, so they shut off our power.  My roommates opted not to stay at home in the darkness and suggested I also find another place to stay.  I have no one.  I would have called Sarah but I didn't have her number because I left my cell phone at work (or so I had thought.  I am at work now and not seeing it.  Did it make it home with me the previous night?  this is distressing).  Instead I sat in the dark for a while before going to bed insanely early.  I felt like a farmer as I awoke with the sun.  I didn't get a chance to write anyting last night and probably won't be able to today at work either.  That means no posts for a bit.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Before I knew Elle had been in the hospital, I had no idea why she wasn't returning my messages.  Maybe she got back home to her boyfriend and decided that I really should just get LA and that it was all over again.  I was upset and heart-broken all over again.  It was as if the trip meant nothing and I was crushed.  I called Sarah at work just to hear the soothing sound of her voice.  She invited me to hear her read, which I wanted to do, but she was going to be leaving immediately afterwards and the idea of girls talking about sexual firsts was enough to make me want to cry.  So after work, holding the tears in my eyes (because boys don't cry), I made my way over to the Streets CD release party for some free boozin'.  Miss M says that if you are heart-broken, the best thing to do is to stay sober as little as possible.  Mr. Red's eternal advice is to kiss a new girl.  In my current state, I needed to do both.  Quickly.  At the Vice store, I met up with Jawn, Mr. White, and Mr. Red.  We talked to friends and proceeded to drink the free beer at a furious rate.  The party was too big for the store and spilled onto the streets, forcing the cops to bring an end to the fun.  I was still feeling a bit sober and I knew Miss M would not approve and so we followed the ever wise Jawn to a bar that had free Vodka (but not before I made a pit stop at San Loco for a shot of tequila).  Mr. White noticed that this older lady was vying for Mr. Red's attention and so we encouraged him to get her story.  She had a giant scar on her arm and so Mr. Red turns to her and asks her if she had been shot.  She hadn't been.  They talked, we all drank free Vodka.  They stopped giving us free vodka.  Mr. Red is not one to buy overpriced NYC drinks, so as I played lookout, he grabbed an open bottle of wine from behind the bar.  It was only about a third full.  So he grabbed another.  It was all very sly.  I am a good lookout.  All we needed was a good excuse to leave the bar.  Mr. Red supplied us with that when he said, "That's only 2 years younger than my mom!" when the lady hitting on him told him her age.  The look on her face would have sent anyone running.  She was horrified.  I paid him to say that.  Best $5 I ever spent.  So Mr. Red and I headed over to Happy Endings and got there a bit early and the place was fairly empty.  The DJ gave us free free tickets.  I think because we were dancing.  We were drunk.  Too drunk to use the drink tickets.  By that I mean, we paid for our drinks because we forgot that 20 seconds prior we had been given drink tickets.  Once those were downed, Mr. Red threw his glass against the wall, shattering it and decided to switch to wine.  He was brazenly walking around the bar drinking straight from the bottle.  I used the glass that I didn't throw against the wall and drank it through a straw.  In time, we ran out of wine.  Then, Mr. Red comes running up to me and hands me a bottle and says, "What did I get?" "Vermouth," I say.  Not a good score, but nonetheless enough to anger the management.  Within moments, the bottle was confiscated and Mr. Red was escorted to the sidewalk.  Lesson learned:  Don't steal bottles unless I am doing lookout.  So I had succeeded with part one of my mission, getting smashed.  Part two would be trickier.  No one wants to kiss a boy that can barely stand up.  Not only that, but the problem with heartbreak is that its over ONE person and only that one person can make it go away.  But then, in walks a girl I had a huge crush on in college.  Absolutely beautiful and very smart.  She modeled for an ad campaign once and I was tortured by having to stare at her face every day on the subway.  It nearly killed me.  That, and the fact that she had a long string of boyfriends and was never single.  We said hello.  It turned out she was also heart-broken as she had just broken up with her boyfriend.  How perfect is?  How better to get over a crush than to kiss an old crush that you thought was hopeless?  Unfortunately, she didn't take to the idea.  Not at first.  But in the end she humored my tongue just long enough for me to forget about Elle for a second.  She really wasn't into it though, and eventually we parted ways.  I went to sit down and saw  urlLink last year's crush .  I decided to talk to her.  Bad move.  I spent the next 30 minutes listening to her tell me about what hell I made her life last year at her place of work, where she couldn't escape me.  That's the last time I give flowers to a bartender.  That's for sure.  I bought her off with a drink (after many demands that I do so). But, in the end, I realized she was right and sat there thinking about how intrusive I was in her work life.  This made me sad so I left and went to Niagra and tried to convince some Italian girl that I knew her native tongue and failed miserably.  In the end though, I realized it was way too late to be out on a worknight and that it was time to go back home and face the fact that I was alone.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      She was just in the hospital with a 104 degree fever.  She wasn't ignoring me after all.  It turns out she was pretty much near death when I last saw her and bought her the tylenol.  I'm jealous that her boyfriend gets to stay home from work and take care of her.  
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I was  urlLink spotted  last night. 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I was planning on writing part II of the Gay Memoir, but instead I got drunk.  Elle won't return any of my calls or emails.  Its really getting me down.  I fight tears.  When I get down, I get drunk.  I have a rule that you should sleep at least as many hours as the number of drinks you had.  I broke that rule.  12 drinks, 3 hours of sleep.  This 4:1 ratio is not pleasant.  Nor is work with a headache like this.  So I am totally copping out on a post (for now).  1.  The number of roommates kicked out of a bar last night. 2.  The number of bottles of wine successfully stolen before number  one happened. 3.  The number of former crushes I ran into.  One of whom made me listen to a 30 minute lecture about how being the object of my obsession is NOT easy and is worth at least a free Amstel  Light.  I bought her one. 4.  The number of bars visited 5. through 12.  The drinks I shouldn't have had.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This is an old story.  It sounds a bit shallow now, but I was young then.  After years of consecutive longterm monogamous relationships I found myself alone, broken, dejected and bitter.  Then, one night while out dancing at Tis Was (this was years ago, when it was still fun) I spied this cute pixie girl dancing alone.  I made my way towards her.  Threw a few gestures her way.  Got the feeling it was ok to dance near her, and proceeded.  The dancing started off innocently enough, but with every passing song the intimacy grew.  Hands found their way to the other person's waist.  Fingertips explored the skin hiding underneath waistbands, then travelled up under the bottom of shirts.  Bodies pulled closer together, knees and thighs interlocking, hands moving up around each other's heads, fingers running through hair, faces pulled so close together you start breathing each other's breaths.  Eyes only inches apart staring intently as noses start to graze.  Lips parting, one final little pull, bringing the mouths together and finally, a "what the FUCK are you doing?"  The pixie wanted nothing to do with my kiss and pushed me away.  Shooting dirty glances at me she quickly distanced herself from me.  Sad and bitter I made my way back to the bar and watched and she started up again with a different boy.  Same sexual dancing.  Same teasing sway.  It was unbearable.  Eventually he made his way over to where I was at the bar to freshen up his drink.  Quite embittered I get his intention and tell him not to waste his time, that she's a fucking tease.  He shrugged it off and laughed, insisting that it was going pretty good for him.  I rolled my eyes and walked out the door.  A couple weeks later I see the girl at Lit.  She approaches me and says I look familiar and asks how I know her.  Embarassed by the failed kiss, I deny knowing how and we chat about where we hang out and speculate how we recognize each other.  Then, the boy I saw her dancing with comes up and laughs and tells her I am the one who called her a tease.  Instantly, she is FURIOUS and starts berating me about how I have no right to label someone I don't know.  At first I take it, knowing that she is right, but the venomous words don't stop and my blood starts to boil and I start firing back retorts about how girls like her can't lead men on like that and it starts to get really ugly.  Right as tensions are at their highest, when the next word will lead to a drink being thrown in someone's face, my then-roommate interupts us to inform me he's going home and wants to know if I will be leaving with him.  This roommate, he's quite cute and quite the popular local gay boy and when I tell him that I am not leaving, we exchange the usual hug and kisses on each other's cheeks.  When I turn back, the look on the pixie's face is that of an epiphany.  "Oh my God, I should have seen it!" she says, "You're gay!  I mean, you said you worked in fashion.  Its so obvious."  "what?" I reply back.  "Here I thought you were just some straight asshole, but if you're gay and you think  I am a tease, then I should really listen." she says.  Just relieved that the tension has subsided I nod in agreement and she quickly pulls me over to sit with her.  She asks me all about her behavior and what I observed.  She still has not placed me as the boy she had once scorned on the dancefloor.  Before long we are laughing and chatting away and I am just BLOWN away by how drastically her attitude towards me has changed since learning I was gay.  "Listen," she says.  "I need your opinion on something." "Sure." "OK, come with me."  And with that, she takes my arm and whisks me off to the girl's bathroom, pulling me inside and locking the door behind us.  "I just bought these new panties, but I'm not sure if I look cute in them.  Will you tell me?"  "Sure," I reply.  She unbuttoms her pants and pulls her jeans down to her knees and spins infront of me, letting stare blatantly at her little pixie body in teeny undies.  "Well, what do you think?" She asks.  "They're OK, I guess," I say with an air of disinterest.  But what I am thinking as I'm locked in a bathroom with a half-naked pixie is, "this is pure genius Greg, evil genius, but genius."  -To be continued-
     

    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Coming from California back to New York City is always odd.  You forget how dirty it is.  All the dog shit, the syringes on the street (OK, I only saw one today, so the plural is a bit excessive), the trash, the noise, I love it.  You can hide your sins so easily.  It all blends into the cesspool that is New York.   As for Elle and I.  In the end, I don't think there was any change to our relationship.  She read this blog and it upset her.  I should have remembered that you can observe something without affecting the outcome.  As with all things real, endings are never concrete like they are in the movies.  Its all amorphous and we will let time tell us what to do.  I must recover physically and financially from my little adventure which means my life will probably be a bit boring this week.  I will fill up that time with a story from the past.  Hopefully my alcohol ravaged memory won't hinder me.  As a PS.  I doubt Elle will accept my invitation to be my date to my brother's wedding.  Its in Northern California next month.  I have a room already (two beds for the platonically minded), but the (un)lucky girl would have to get to Northern California herself.  Any takers?  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Elle was sick.  I was on two hours of sleep.  We both passed out.  A Bay City Rollers Saturday Night we did not have.  Now it is Sunday.  I leave in a matter of hours.  I awoke early and walked down the street to buy Elle some Tylenol and a Kinder Egg to help her spirits.  There is something amazing about being so close to her.  I feel like a child.  Shaking with nervousness, desperate for attention and recognition.  I feel so weak and tender, like a hard-boiled egg without its shell.  This might not sound pleasant, but its the first time in a long time, something or someone has been able to own my insides.  So the trip is basically over.  Was it a success?  It depends on what I wanted.  I don't know what that was.  My first night surprising her and getting her to myself was grand.  But really, she was here to see other people and eventually I felt a bit like an outsider.  Maybe I wanted too much from her.  I think that selfishly, I wanted her to give me everything, so that I could pick and choose what I wanted.  Maybe I would have taken everything.  But this speculation is all moot.  That is all from LA.  New York, I know I strayed from you, but please take me back.  Look past my infidelity and welcome me back with open arms.  You know you are my one true love and that I would never really leave you (except for maybe London.  I'm sorry, but she's Hott).
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Friday.  Went to the beach.  I am so pale.  I frighten seagulls.  I swam in the ocean and made sand castles with Elle and her LA friends.  It was nice.  WAY too much driving.  I hate cars.  They make me angry.  Elle and I got dinner and waited for her ex to come into town.  He did.  Hmmm.  So we all went back to her friend's house to pre-party, but it soon became evident that no one was going to be leaving the apartment.  That is boring.  Plus, Elle totally passed out at like midnight.  And, with the addition of the ex, there was no room for poor old Greg to sleep.  TWO friends said I could crash at their place that night but I couldn't get ahold of them.  So I left the apartment and went to the dirtiest rock bar I knew and pounded drinks while I waited for my friends to call me back.  They never did.  The bar closed.  Screwed, with no place to sleep, I drove all over LA searching for a motel.  No vancancy.  Damn convention.  The hours were passing and I was becoming more and more screwed.  I was sick of being in a car and needed a place to pass the time until I could get ahold of my friends.  Only one place was open.  A strip club.  I am not a strip club kinda guy.  I've been to two in my life.  So I enter and just sit in the back and mope.  Some stripper does the usual, "you wanna dance?" routine and I pass.  She asks why, I tell her about how its 3 am and I have no place to sleep.  She bitches about her day, about being sore, so i give her a back rub.  She likes it.  To pay me back, she offers me a free lapdance.  Free is free.  So we go back to a private booth and i am just sitting there, hands hanging from my side.  Tired and scared of my lack of a place to sleep.  She notices my lack of interest and tells me that I should get more involved.  She informs me that I can touch her.  So I rest my hands on her hips and mildly rub them.  And she says, "no, not there." and takes my hand and puts in inside her panties, pushing my finger inside of her.  She sits there, grinding me with my finger inside of her and she gets noticably excited.  She leans over and kisses me.  With tongue.  Strippers don't french you.  Do they?  I think not, for she kinda freaked out and got scared her boss might have seen, so we run off towards the bathroom.  She tells me that I am free to stay at her place, but that she is kinda-sorta dating someone and doesn't know if he will be home.  She borrows my phone and calls her home.  No answer.  So she tells me that she is going to go home soon and to call her house in an hour and she'll tell me whether or not he is there.  She leaves.  The place closes.  The bouncer is about to kick me out when TWO other strippers grab me and pull me back stage.  They tell me they had been watching me all night and thought I was cute.  One asks me to go home with her.  She says she has a boyfriend who lives with her, but its cool because he is "open" to these sort of things.  I get a bit sketched out and tell her i will pass.  I tell them I have no place to stay, so she takes my number and says she will "ask the girls" if any one of them will take me in for the night.  So, eventually I have to leave and I go to my car.  I have a ticket.  I have no place to go.  So I sit in the back seat, and lie down.  Its about 5 am.  I wait til the hour is up and call the first stripper.  She answers and quickly and quietly tells me the boy is there and I can't come over.  So I close my eyes with my phone near  my head and lay there thinking about how I am sleeping in a car, HOPING some sketched out stripper will have found a place for me to crash.  She never calls.  Two hours later I wake up when the sun starts beating down on me in the car.  I drive around pointlessly.  Its 7:00 am.  I  kill time until 9:30 until i think its late enough to wake up Elle and her friends.  i stop by there and lay down for like 5 minutes until my sister calls me.  Its her birthday.  She, her husband and daughter are meeting up with my other sister and three of her kids to go to Disneyland.  I go.  Disneyland sucks.  Seeing siblings you never see rocks.  Being on Space Mountain with a horrible hangover and 2 hours of sleep totally sucks.  Now I am back from Disneyland, back at Elle's friend's place.  She is sick and laying in the dark.  I am dead tired and trying to nap, but all the caffeine I've been putting in myself is preventing that.  I am shaking.  I am totally cracked out.  Elle isn't going out.  I am wondering if another visit to the strip club is in order...  All I know is I must NOT sleep in a car tonight.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      After some celebration champagne, it was time to hit the town.  Elle's gay friend/the guy she is staying with, decided he was tired, so the girl and I headed off to Hollywood to soak in the bar scene.  Its the same shit everywhere.  Same kids, same tunes, whatev.  Left that shit.  Drank vodka poolside at a friend's instead.  She put us on a guestlist for some place downtown and so Elle and I went there.  It wasn't our scene, but getting late, so we talked on a patio the whole time.  Her boyfriend is soon to be out of the picture.  Hurray!  Wrong.  Girl has a taste for meat and has decided that she needs a string of lovers with no promise of commitment.  I am the first notch.  Maybe this is ok.  I don't think it would work anyway.  I don't know.  The future is a mess.  We are all kids of the 80's.  We have these idealized views of love from all of our images from John Hughes to John Cusack.  A perfect someone out there for all of us.  We might have to fight and go through some struggle, but love is out there waiting for us to find it.  But also, the 80's was basically the beginning mainstream society's admittal that homes are broken, that divorces happen, that parents die.  From Different Strokes to Full House, we learned that This Love that they taught us to hunt for, more often than not dies.  So here we are, all cynics and idealists simultaneously.  searching for perfectin in love, and prematurely looking for flaws so we know when to run away before we get hurt.  Doing too much too young and having too many failed relationships by the age that our parents were married at.  Having so much self-preservation to prevent being hurt again that we can never really give ourselves to someone else again.  Yet we still expect, even with all our selfishness, that love will find us and make us happy.  Maybe I hunt out the doomed relationships to avoid any sense of responsibility. But enough of the future.  I asked her to give me LA and she has given me that.  We left that downtown place and realized we needed a place to crash and it was too late to go to her friend's place (his roommate had a final the next day and we couldn't come crashing in late and drunk).  So we searched every hotel downtown. All full. Some fucking convention in town.  ALL FULL.  Driving around streets that neither of us knew.  Finally, one place, said they had one room but it was reserved.  At 3 am that reservation would be lost.  We waited in the car.  Got bored.  Started making out and then the concierge knocked on the window and told us to take the room. (which is much better than hearing "Get a room!")  So, this room.  Two words.  Hot tub.  Elle totally passed out.  I filled the tub.  Stripped her clothes off, picked her up, and dropped her in the tub.  We sat in there. Relaxed.  Kissed.  Touched.  I learned one valuable lessen. Going down on a girl under water is tough.  You inhale a lot of water.  So we moved it to the bed.  Afterwards, as I fell asleep, I could not help but think that the first day was a success.  And I am posting with her in the room, so this is rushed and not written so well.  My apologies.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      That last post was so anti-climactic.  I will post another one when I have time.  Right now I am too absorbed in my own private world of secret kisses.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      After almost an hour in the car (listening to indie FM, Magazine, Franz F., PiL, Pulp all in a row!!!) I found the house she is staying at.  She called almost at the right moment, and said she was bored and since I knew LA, if I could recommend something.  I suggested she get out of the house.  That moment.  I made her walk outside.  And there I was, standing there.  We had a long hug and now we are off to buy champagne to celebrate...
     

    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I just got an email.  She is watching Pretty in Pink and Sixteen Candles telling me she wished I could be there and that our lives could be like those movies.  Those words stung me.  I mean, why am I doing this?  Is it just the chase?  Is it really her?  Or is it just her fantastic boobies?  I can sense she is not right in so many ways.  She is hardly the person I'd choose to talk to if I could only talk to one person, but there is this bit of magic that happens when we are close.  The way her eyes smile at me.  They surround me with this magic barrier that protects me from all my self-destructive thoughts.  The world turns white and its just her and me.  But the world can't disappear forever and there is a reality.  She has a LIVE-IN boyfriend.  Do I want to fuck with that?  Mess with two people's hearts and homes?  Where do I expect her to move?  In with me?  That would be way too much way too fast for me.  Then what do expect come of all this?  Maybe I am flying to LA to have LA.  One city, so far from our lives, where for a few days, work, rent, boyfriends, and obligation disappear, and for a brief moment, the world will just fade to white on the beaches of Southern California, and for a moment, even if just a second, there can be a place where its just her and me.  And we'll say, Fuck tomorrow, Fuck New York, Fuck whatever may come, for right now, I give myself unto thee, do with me as you please.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Elle just called me.  It turns out her ex-boyfriend (the one who she dumped to be with her current boyfriend) is staying with her in LA the SAME EXACT DAYS I will be there.  Complications.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Tomorrow, I leave for LA.  This is probably a bad idea.  Background:  About six months ago, a cute girl started freelancing in my office.  I became somewhat (read: VERY) infatuated.  I arranged to meet up with her for drinks one day after work and she agreed.  But you know what she did?  She brought her boyfriend.  He seemed nice enough.  It turns out they had just moved together to the city and had just started living together.  With this new knowledge, I abandoned my office crush on Elle.  Then, months later, she comes up to me in the office and the following dialog takes place:  Elle: "I had a dream about you last night.  Isn't that weird?" Me: "I dream about people from work a lot, its normal." Elle: "Yeah, but it was a sex dream." Me: "Oh?" Elle: "And it was HOTT" Me:  "Do you wanna get a drink after work?"  That drink turned into about 15.  We started at 5pm (Good Friday I believe it was).  Eventually, we made our way to MotherFucker, where, while dancing, we slipped into a minor kiss.  The kind where the lips just barely part and your tongues just barely graze each other.  She ran away.  I followed.  She was upset with herself because of her boyfriend.  I convinced her that if she was going to feel THAT guilty, it should at least be a real kiss.   This worked and the hardcore making out soon followed.  At some point we scurried to the back room where it was more private and the next thing I know, she has her pants off and expecting me to have sex with her right there and then.  Now, I'm game for a little sex in public, but my nervousness was a little high seeing how I had had a major crush on her, she did have a boyfriend, there was no protection at hand, and some girl was like standing 3 feet away staring at me in shock.  So, instead, I pulled her on the floor and went down on her.  All of a sudden, this giant light shines on us, and I peer up and see a security guard holding a flashlight and giving us a shameful look.  We left.  Her boyfriend went out of town on business and thus started a torrid affair between the two of us.  There was kissing in the elavator and secret afterwork rendezouses.  It was hott.  It was fun.  Many drinks were drunk, much dancing was had, and not nearly enough sex took place.  Then the boyfriend came back and she called it off.  Then she quit work and I was like a junkie running dry, and so when I found out she was going to be in LA on vacation, I bought a ticket to follow her and proclaim my love John Cusack style.  That was a week ago.  My heart is fickle.  I think I've made a big mistake.  So LA, in 24 hours, I will be on a plane to see you.  Be good to me El Pueblo de la Reina de Los Angeles.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Friday.  Friday I was raped by Michael Caine and I'd just like to put that all behind me.  One of those nights where my mouth was just a shame factory.  From words to innappropriate kisses, my mouth got me in trouble all over town.  Damn you Michael Caine, damn you to Hell.  Saturday.  People fornicate.  I don't.  Not even in my dreams.  Other people get married.  I don't.  Some people just go to other people's weddings.  I don't.  But after they are done with said weddings, they dance.  I do that.  I danced a lot.  I danced with the roommate and other good friends.  I kissed the DJ.  She had super soft lips.  That's why I kiss her.  That and the fact that she's the best girl ever.  Well.  All these people who fornicate.  All these people who get married.  They went home so I decided to leave.  Outside, some girl was standing in the rain.  I grabbed her and spun her around.  My hands went on her hips and I lifted her into the air and together we twisted and turned in the cool air of New York at 5am.  The rain fell on us and I let her fall into my arms.  Holding her like a newlywed, I lifted her onto a newspaper stand where I proceeded to force my tongue down her throat.  She screamed, "You just frenched me!"  So we danced some more.  We danced like we were in love.  Dancing in the rain.  I then let her hand slip from mine and hailed a cab and went over to Miss M's house and shared her big comfy bed.  Don't get any ideas in your head.  I don't fornicate.  Sunday.  I awoke with Miss M. and we made plans to have brunch at First with friends.  They all ditched us, so we went alone.  I had never been.  I was sitting there looking at this menu thinking, "$16 for FUCKING SCRAMBLED EGGS?!?!?!" but Miss M. assured me it was all going to be ok.  Then I learned the secret.  With that comes a bottle of champagne.  When you drink that bottle, they give you another one.  When you drink that one, they give you another one.  When you say, "Where's that fucking waitress, with my fucking champagne!" very loudly, and they notice that your shirt says, "Instant Asshole: just add alcohol" they ask you to leave.  So Miss M. and I ventured back to my place in Brooklyn where we were reunited with the roommate and the neighbor.  We proceeded to pick up last weekend's key purchase.  Junk store golf clubs and golf balls.  After walking a couple blocks to the wonderful secret that is the abandoned lot on the river, we set up our tees and hit many a golf ball into the East River.  Afterwards we braved the long skinny cement wall that was once part of a dock and spent the dusk watching the sun set over the city, listening to the East River slap the shore like it was some young honey's ass.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I awoke Sunday unnerved by the presence of the two naked girls in my bed.  The one would have been ok.  She was nice.  the other.  The sex-crazed one.  I could have done without her presence.  Luckilly, they wanted to get the fuck out of there was quickly as I wanted them gone.   I think they sensed my unease about the events that transpired the night before.  They showered, left the room, and drove home.  Breakfast was fucked up.  Everyone at the table knew.  My brother gave me funny looks and teased me.  It was weird as fuck to see J. there.  I couldn't look him in the eye.  Soon, I jumped in a car with my parents and we drove away.  They dropped me off in San Francisco before heading off to their house in the South Bay.  My best friend from college and roommate of 3 years was in SF for a job interview, so we arranged to meet up.  It was really nice.  His name is Lionel.  He is probably the one who set me on the path of debauchery.  He'll deny it.  But I think he got me on my daily forty binge drinking.  He taught me that girls will go a lot farther on a dance floor than you think they will.  He took me to bondage parties.  He dragged me into dominatrix dungeons.  He did a lot of things that my mother would have disapproved of.  But now he lives in Texas and he has calmed down and turned into one of the most pleasant and endearing men I know.  We traveled around the city.  He told me of the Pride Parade, which sadly I had missed, but I saw enough drunken gay men dressed to the nines and drag queens on mini-motorcylcles that I caught a bit of the vibe.  Up near Fisherman's warf we paid a man to take us on his boat (with a handful of other tourists) and we took a very wet and windy boat ride around the bay.  Fucking hell.  San Francisco is so pretty.  As Lionel said, its actually as pretty as they make it look in the movies.  Being back in the Bay Area fills me with a full and complete happiness that I do not get in New York.  Lionel and I spent the afternoon dissing New York and its filth and shallowness, eventually ending up in the Mission getting burrittos.  Holy Goddamn Hell if it didn't make me remember just how horribly shitty Mexican food is in New York.  Later, friends from high school drove into the city to meet for a drink.  We then met Amber, who writes the female version of this blog.  The group of us went out to a couple small bars in the Mission with Lionel and another friend Jessica.  I was bouncing off the walls with happiness.  I think they all thought I was quite drunk.  I wasn't.  It was happiness.  FUCKING HAPPINESS.  Pure ecstacy.  Maybe its the sea air, but I can't help but smile whenever I am in San Francisco.  I think I definitely left my heart there.  It was a fantastically calm and quiet night.  Exactly what I had been needing, and was damn near perfect for my mood.  The only problem being when my old friend, in a drunken fervor, caused my body to violently slam into the sidewalk.  The sound was horrible.  Imagine thousands of oversized pieces of bologna fired by a rocket into a brick wall.  It had a horrible slap sound that is still echoing in my head.  I think I might have a hairline fracture in my wrist.  It hurts a lot still.  Eventually we all parted ways and Amber was nice enough to let me crash at her apartment where I forced her to listen to Controller.Controller.  They are the only band I can listen to these days.  I think I have had this 25 minute EP on repeat for about 6 hours now.  Everything else makes me want to vomit.  I think SF really fucked with my head, but in a way that it needed.  My head needed to be fucked like that, it needed that lay.  I seriously think in order to move on in life, I might have to end my New York life and accept adulthood in the city of my youth.  A break from the alcohol and sex.  A return home, close to family, where my mind can free itself from vice.  Maybe its foolish to think that simply changing location can do that much, but there is just something that happens to me in San Francisco.  The memories of my youth, a return to innocence, an apprecation of beauty.  I am seriously just so much nicer and friendlier when I am there.  I want to give the whole damn world a hug.  All my bitterness, self-protection, and self-destruction, it all just melts away.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Damn.  I must admit.   I pulled off the rat pack theme pretty well.  I looked pretty sharp in my suit.  Or maybe, I was just drunk and had an inflated sense of worth.  Either way, I felt good.  The ceremony went well.  My toast went well.  All was well.  Open bar, fun music, dancing, good times.  Everyone was trashed.  My parents.  My sisters. All the guests.  It was a sloppy wreck.  This one girl kept trying to kiss me.  I kept stopping her.  Word had spread amongst the family that I was a slut.  I didn't want to perpetuate that.  I wanted to be the classy one.  I danced with my mom, my sister, my nieces.  A perfect gem of a son.  Then, the family went to sleep.  The rest of us kept up the dancing and drinking until about midnight when the DJ called it a night.  A few of us tackled my brother, stripped him to his undies, and tossed him in the pool.  Soon, everyone was tossing everyone in the pool.  People started stripping off their nice wedding clothes to various degrees.  A lot of skin, and occaisionally some underwear.  I was thrown in the pool.  I threw people in the pool.  Naked bodies tackled each other.  I ended up kissing the girl who had been trying to kiss me all night.  I walked away for some reason (probably to throw more victims into the pool), and when I returned, she was kissing J., the guy who had successfully bedded a bridesmaid the night before.  Oh well.  No big deal.  I wasn't that keen on her anyway.  What I was keen on though was the hot tub.  The pool was fucking cold.  Many people were big on this idea as well.  The hot tub soon filled with people.  All pretty much naked at this point.  Maybe 10-15 of us.  This super cute girl climbs in naked next to me.  She had been hiding this teeny perky body under a dress all day.  Somehow, I had not noticed her.  We started to kiss.  We continued to drink.  I think I had been drinking for about 10 hours at this point. (Yes, 2pm til midnight).  And so, I found myself lost in a sordid world of senses, of naked girls, hot tubs, and endless alcohol.  My mind simply stopped thinking.  I became a moving body of instinct and no feeling.  This girl's lips felt soft and tender against mine.  I loved it.  Then, the first girl climbs back into the hot tub, pulls us apart and starts kissing me.  I was a little bit annoyed, but mainly, in my drunkenness found it all comical.  She stuck her hand between my thighs and started to play with me.  I got excited.  I felt weird about that.  The hot tub was full of people, including my brother.  But sometimes sexual excitement and sensual adandonment take over, and I decided to reciprocate and I moved my hand down her thigh only to find another hand already there.  I looked up and saw that J. was behind her.  It was his hand.  He was also making out with the second girl.  I guess, in order to balance out the equation, I slid my hand between the second girl's thighs.  I was definitely weirded out.  The girls noticed this and continued to pour me drinks.  I sort of have a gap in my memory, but what I do remember next is finding myself in a hotel room, sitting in a chair in the dark, realizing that two girls and one boy were about to enter the room and that they all expected things to happen.  I don't think I really wanted things to happen.  I was nervous.  I wasn't really into the idea.  I'm not one of those kids who had the whole orgy thing in college.  I think those things only happen in schools where there is nothing better to do than fuck.  But I went to school in NYC.  I had other things I was interested in than sharing multiple sex partners.  So, as it was, the two girls came in first and quickly grabbed me off the chair and I found myself intertwined with both of them, kissing, fingering, eating them both out.  Back and forth, lost in a sea of flesh.  Like some hero in a Homeric tale, I got lost in this sea, sucked into its siren called and bodily delights.  I barely noticed that J. had entered and now also had his hands all over the girls.  We traded off kissing, fingering, and eating out the women for a bit, and soon the condoms came out and it was obvious that sex was iniment.  I wasn't sure how I felt about this.  I wasn't alone.  The cuter petite girl then announced to the group that she didn't want to have sex.  She was just interested in touching and kissing.  I bent down next to her and told her I was feeling the same way.  She looked at me with eyes of disappointment and told me that her friend really wanted to fuck me.  That she wanted me to fuck her friend.  Soon she was putting a condom on me and her friend was climbing on top.  I wasn't sure how to politely stop it with all these people determined to make it happen.  I felt trapped.  Sex is a shared experience.  It is passionate kisses, arms embraced, body against body.  Even the shallowed of fucks still contain moments of two people becoming one.  I wasn't feeling this, "four as one."  It all seemed so impersonal, so devoid of emotion.  It had a level of detachment from the feelings of physical pleasure that made me feel very alone.  I found myself laying there, with a stranger on top of me, with J.'s hands all over her body, feeling like I was some apparatus being used to get others off.  I felt sick.  I stopped.  The girl got a bit peeved at me leaving her hanging like that, but I didn't care.  J. continued where I left off and I announced my desire to go to my own room.  As I assembled my belongings, I saw that the petite one had moved to the floor to pass out and begin a night of sleep.  I woke her and asked her if she'd like me to take her to her room.  She had no room.  I offered to share mine, and she accepted.  And while the other two were still busy, she and I snuck out the door and went to my room.  There we collapsed into bed and held each other in a naked embrace.  I held onto her tightly, hoping that the feeling of this body, so close to mine, the two of us alone together, sharing only each other, would partially fill the void that was growing inside of me as I sobered up and realized what was happening.  Peacefully we spooned with no thoughts of sexual acts and it felt very innocent and very pleasant.  Then, there was a knock on my door.  The other girl entered and said she didn't want to sleep up there with J. and wanted to know if she could share our bed.  Her friend said yes, and before I knew it, I was once again, surrounded by one too many naked girls.  I felt robbed of my shallow salvation, but said "fuck it" and went to sleep.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Friday I awoke early and drove with the family to the wine country.  We stopped at a couple wineries on the way and my father tried to culture me with the nuances of various grapes and aftertastes and all that shit.  All I really learned is that wine gets me drunk.  Actually, I already knew that.  But fucking hell!  California is the most beautiful place ever.  EVER.  At least Northern California.  Maybe I am just more homesick than I care to acknowledge, but whenever I return, I am shocked at the cleanliness, the mix of man and nature, the serene beauty, everything.  I sat on a hill in Sonoma, with the Bay off in the distance, felt the sun, and stared at the rolling hills of the wine country.  Fuck New York.  Fuck dancing.  Fuck rock'n'roll.  Just give me sun, peace, and green green trees.  We arrived at the lodge and did the whole wedding rehearsal and all that shit.    We killed time at the pool where I spied a girl in a bikini and then I realized she was probably only about 17 and I felt ashamed and went away.  My mom came up to me and started talking about her: "Did you meet Vanessa yet?  I can't believe what a beautiful young woman she is!  Look how developed she is.  She is so grown up!  I mean, just look at those curves..." on and on and on.  I thought,  "Is this what it is now?  My mom trying to get the last single kid to get hitched?"  Maybe my mom was just trying to relate to me.  I really don't know...but she continued.  "I just can't get over how womanly she is!  Don't you think she is attractive?"  Me.  Awkward.  "Umm...I guess so.  Yeah.  I mean, she's still very young, but she will probably be beautiful when she grows up."  (That was me, trying not to sound like a perv to my mom).  Then, my Mom: "Yes.  She will be quite beautiful when she grows up.  I just can't believe she's only 12"  TWELVE.  Fuck if that didn't make me feel really wrong inside.  Fuck.  I found a twelve year old girl cute.  That's disturbing.  But so did my mom.  Does that mean she understands how I could be fooled?  Or does that mean my mom is just a dirty as me?  Actually, don't answer that.  Mom, twelve year olds, sex.  This was not a good mixture.  ANd so I decided.  That's it.  No more sexual thoughts.  They are trouble.  Lets just watch big brother get married and keep our mind out of the gutter.  We then had dinner and got trashed.  (we bought 45 bottles of wine for about 30 people).  Completely smashed, I sat there shocked in the realization that my big brother was tying the knot.  I grabbed my nine year old nephew and in proper drunk uncle fashion, lamented to him, "I'm the last single one left!  Do you know what this means!"  To which, my nine year old nephew replied, "Yes, you are now the lone cowboy.  You are the only one who hasn't been shot."  Fucking hell.  My nine year old nephew can out metaphor anyone of you fuckers any day of the week.  After a quick soak in the hot tub, I went to bed.  I awoke in the morning to find half the men in the wedding party pissed at me.  Apparently, I was seen as a pretty safe bet as to who would first bed a bridesmaid.  Apparently, my lack of sex, (and another's excess of sex) had cost a few people to lose some serious money.  That made me feel slutty.  The fact that I was seen as "a sure bet." I don't want to be a slut.  No more sex for Greg.  That's what I decided.  My decisions seem to be short lived.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      There will be an elaborate post coming soon.  I have not had computer access, which has actually been very very nice.  All I will say right now, is that I learned a very valuable lesson this weekend.  I am not an orgy kinda guy.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A conversation from home:  Mom:  I hope Persephone has a better attitude when she's working. Me:  I'm sure she does. Mom:  Because, you know they pay her $600 a day! Me:  I know. Mom:  Thats more than you make in a week... Me:  I know! Mom:  But of course, she'll sometimes go months without working. Me:  Mom, thats fine.  She's only four years old.  Yes...Getting compared to your 4 year old niece who is more successful than you.  The joys of being home.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm off to California for big brother's wedding.  In the meantime, here are some  urlLink pictures  from his bachelor party.  The one he had in SF, not the one that I was a part of on the east coast.  Don't even ask me to explain what the fuck is going on in them.  I have no answers.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am super busy at work.  No time for a real post.  So random thought.  I watched Rosemary's Baby last night for the first time.  God, that 23 year old Mia Farrow looks eerily like my ex-girlfriend.  I mean, strikingly.  I went to look  up her photos on Friendster and show someone who was watching the movie with me.  She had de-friended me.  I guess because I had sex with her roommate a couple weeks back.  I guess thats fair.  In concept, one should not have sex with an ex's roommate.  But what about if you only dated for a month?  What about if it was years ago?  What about if they ended things coldly with you?  Part of me thinks that by her dumping me harshly, she gave me a free pass to break some of those courtesy rules, such as, "Don't fuck the roommate."  But even if she didn't.  What is the statute of limitations on such obligations to an ex?  I mean, she has a new boyfriend and is in love, plus this roommate was not her roommate back then.  Hell, they didn't even become friends until a year after the breakup.  The roommate never even knew us as a couple.  I heard my ex was so pissed at her roommate, she moved out.  Oh, and if you're curious, the roommate was the one I "girled" too much and is thus weirded out and doesn't really talk to me.  So, now I don't talk to either one.  One night of sex cost me two friends.  Fuck.  Thats much more than any whore would charge.  And I really actually like them both a lot.  They are both good people.  Now I remember why I abstained from sex for six months.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The wonderful mood of the weekend has passed.  Maybe its the grey skies and rain, but more likely, its because Elle emailed me asking a favor.  Not a favor for her, but her boyfriend.  You can ask me to stop communicating with you because you want to smooth things over with your boyfriend, but, for Christ's sake, I'm not going to do the man whom you stopped talking to me over any favors.  I'm sorry.  I'm too immature for that shit.  Now I am pissed.  Former lovers can ruin such good moods.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      After missing the sun on Saturday, I decided that no day was better for catching the sun than Sunday.  The weather was perfect.  It was like living inside yourself.  You couldn't feel the air.  It was not hot, it was not cold.  It just was.  The boundry between the body and the world disappeared.  I walked around the city and my mood was still glowing.  Not even the massive crowds on Broadway could get me down.  I walked, laughing, as I meandered my way through the gluttony of shoppers.  Eventually, I ended up in Soho, sitting on a stoop, waiting for a couple friends.  I people watched.  Then it hit me.  That despite the plethora of short skirts and tank tops, I was not lusting after a single body.  my sex drive was non-existent.  No dirty thoughts, no ideas of crude sex.  Nothing.  Was this the reason why I had been so happy?  Was Buddha right?  The way to peace is the escape from desire?  Why do I even want a woman in my life?  Is love a fallacy to help me just procreate?  Is it just about continuing the species?  Do I want to do that?  Do I really want to bring in another life into this world to contemplate, life, death, mortality, morality, longing, failure, purpose, God?  I shrugged it all off and enjoyed the company of friends, sipping cool drinks, walking breezily through the city.  The streets that had been boring recently all of a sudden felt comforting.  The avenues greeted me like family and I wandered freely, knowing every block that was to come.  Smiling at it and giving it a proper "good afternoon" nod.  Friends were everywhere.  I saw people, stopped talked, caught up, then went on.    I felt loved by both man and machine, by birds and buildings.  Simply, by all that was. It was such a comforting afternoon.   At one point, I stopped into Crif dog to get a hot dog (the only substantial warm meal I could afford with the $2 in my pocket).  Inside there was a girl.  She had one of those faces that makes you glow.  The kind where you know you would never tire of it.  And you know that you'd wake up happy every morning that you woke up with that face on the pillow next to you.  But longing still escaped me and I just stood there, smiling, appreciating the peacefulness burried in that smile.  I blinked my eyes like a shutter and captured it forever in my head and went on my way.  As Ice Cube said, "Today was a good day."
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Friday.  Left work at 1pm, but wasted the afternoon catching up on the sleep I had been skipping.  Mr. Red and I left the apartment sober.  An odd thing, and left to meet Miss M. to see !!! at the Bowery.  They completely cemented my idea that they are the best live band in NYC (recorded, its an entirely different story).  Sorry Franz, but you have nothing on !!! when it comes to getting a crowd to dance.  Abso-fucking-lutely nothing.  Maybe it was the Vodka chugged at Miss M.'s right before the show.  Maybe it was the uppers.  But I felt like it was my fucking birthday.  I was happy and relaxed, smiling and playing with strangers.  After the show, went to a bar to see friends DJ and celebrated birthdays.  Still all smiles and happiness and spent most of the evening kissing a girl with a very pleasant disposition.  Eventually, at about 6:00 am, I found myself walking home in the morning sun, still twirling and jumping.  Saturday.  Slept in late.  Missed the beautiful day.  Watched a movie.  Sat there contented, and thought that I might not NEED to go out.  I told Alex that I was actually happy and had no desire to bury my problems with alcohol.  He said, "Oh, no, that's not good at all."  And so eventually, I left the house, sober, again.  Wow, two nights in a row.  and met up with Mr. Red and barhopped briefly before Mr. Red, who had been drinking continuously for about 15 hours, decided it was time to call it a night.  I met up with Alex and some of his friends, and we spent the night dancing away with good people.  At 4:30 in the morning, I started the journey back to the subway.  I witnessed two men attempting to rob a pizza place, with fake guns that were so obviously their fingers in their pockets that despite their yelling, were completely ignored by the owners and patrons.  Down the block a flock of Frat boys were harassing some poor drunk girl where I heard the wonderful piece of reasoning, "and then her skirt blew up and I saw she was wearing a skimpy thong and I just KNEW she was good at numerous sexual acts."  Yes boys.  Thanks for showing the ladies how deep we are.  Then the sweetest gay man in the world tried to hit on me in a deli and it nearly broke my heart to tell him I wouldn't go home with him.  He was such an angel.  The subway ride home was fun, as I twirled, swung, and hung upside down on the bars as the traine rushed under the river back to Brooklyn.  Some young girl, maybe 18?, wearing a cute flowing yellow skirt smiled and jumped up on the bars and asked me to spot her and she showed me her gymnastic skills.  We hung and swung laughing together as a man near by threw up.  I left the subway station and found myself in the morning sun again.  I stopped and lit a candle at the shrine for Frank, a local neighborhood fixture who died recently.  Walking home in the morning sun usually depresses me, but I found it quite pleasant.  I think this summer may be ok after all.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Meloncholy has sunk in.  There is nothing I feel like saying.  Contemplations of putting up fun links were rejected.  There is too much of that.  I made out with the girl who replaced Elle.  She's from Brazil and cute.  She said I was trouble.  This other girl in the office pulled me aside and said it was deja vu and told me not to.  Maybe I shouldn't have.  It was innocent though.  Just kissing.  I think I am trying to recreate the situation that made my heart go flutter flutter.  I can't.  Its not working.  Her glances aren't as flirty.  She doesn't bubble as much.  I don't think there is any real spark.  I think maybe I have been too desperately seeking Susan, trying to create feelings for something that isn't there.  Trying to make an idea that I am in love with tangible. -  Last night, I went to see Franz Ferdinand (THANK YOU MARITSA!).  It was near my work, and I didn't feel like going home to Brooklyn, then just coming back, so I walked around for a bit, avoiding anything that demanded money, watched some b-boys breakdance in the park, then fell asleep on the grass.  I was rudely awakened by a sudden downpour which soaked me.  I scurried back to the office (as it was the only indoor place I could think of that was free from the pressure of spending money).  Eventually, still soaked, I went to the show, cursing my soaked socks, and managed to have a pretty decent time, although I kept to myself for the most part.  Afterwards, I found Sarah who was, for once, drunker than me (as I was pretty much sober).  She was adorable as usual.  We went off to the after party, but I was in no mood to party like a rockstar and instead opted to go meet up with someone to hunt for fireflies in Central Park in the middle of the night.  Apparently, the fireflies had already gone to bed for we saw none.  You never find what you want when you're looking for it too hard.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My job is always in flux, but the one constant is that it requires me to spend many hours a day staring at pictures of some of the most beautiful models in the world for many hours a day.  I remember my first Spring Season here and I sat staring at the girls in their bikinis for hours.  Some days I would damn near lose my mind from sexual frustration.  Staring at all that T & A all day long.  I became obsessed with it.  I realized why most successful men in the fashion industry are gay.  Us straights get distracted.  But then I'd catch myself turning my nose up at every girl on the street.  They were all so fat, or so short, or had crooked noses.  I became a superficial snob.  No one was pretty enough.  I'd only approach the most insanely beautiful girls.  They all rejected me.  I went back to the pictures.  I realized all these beauties were photographed with men.  Men who I did not look like.  Men with amazing abs and perfect smiles.  I became obsessed with them.  My self-esteem vanished.  I felt lower than low.  I couldn't look anyone in the eye.  I became convinced I was below the desire of every woman on Earth.  Later.  My job changed a bit more, and part of my duties included closey examining every photo and looking for flaws.  Here is what I learned.  All models have bony shoulders.  They have ugly elbows.  They have veiny hands.  When they get too thin, the body compensates by making more body hair to keep their fatless bodies warm.  That has to be airbrushed out.  Making teeth the same shade of white makes them look straight.  Shadows can make boobs where there were no boobs.  Shaving off thighs is sometimes needed, even on twigs.  Angles can make things look bigger than they are.  In short.  I learned to think that even the prettiest girls were still ugly.  my mind was fucked.  I walked down the street and everyone I saw was just another heap of flaws that should be airbrushed away.  But also, it helped.  it helped to walk by the news stand and realized all those dreams on the covers were all fake, and to be able to look at them all and know they were all illusions.  later, I was asked to actually make girls heavier.  The models were too thin and the new CEO didn't like them.  So I had to photoshop weight onto them.  I got to decide how healthy to make them look.  It helped to normalize my views again.  Sort of.    Its so funny how easily it is to shape one's idea of pretty.  Mine has been so fucked with I can't even tell whats pretty and whats not.  Children should not be allowed to read these things.  Some days I think about all the eating disorders I help to cause.  All the suicides and low self-esteems.  The image is a powerful thing.  Especially one's percieved image of the self.  Looking at girls is weird now.  I've become obsessed with the flaws in a loving way.  A crooked tooth.  A bump in the nose, a funny birthmark.  Anything to break the cookie cutter ideal of perfection.  That's what gets me about girls these days.  My ex girlfriend hated it.  She knew I was staring at all her flaws all the time.  She didn't understand how I could love them the best.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I went straight from work, to drinking with a bunch of girls from work.  Always scandalous...anyway, didn't have a chance to write a post, so here is one from a couple days ago that I never posted because it was poorly written.  ------------  Elle won't speak to me or see me.  I understand.  Anytime we hang out, we end up kissing, and that isn't good when she has a boyfriend.  She has my favorite hoodie though.  Gotta get that back.  Even if it is hot as fuck in the city.  I'm over her, so its ok.  I will have to admit that I'll miss having an afterwork friend though.  All my friends have the sort of job where you get there at 10am to Noon and stay until like 7 or 9.  When I get out at 5:30, its either kill time for a couple hours, or just go straight home and be boring.  And if they do go out, its late, and I am just getting too old to cope with the bodily pains of staying out until 2-4am drinking, then getting up at 7:30am to get to work.  I only do it on special occassions now.  So after work I meandered through the streets of NYC.  I'm getting bored of them.  Six years and its all memories of faces that have come and gone.  I stopped in to get pizza and sat down to eat.  That Pretenders, "I'm Special" song was playing.  It always makes me think of the Special Olympics because of that commercial that used it in my youth.  That in turn makes me think of my parent's friend's son, who was like 10 years older than me who had Down's Syndrome.  I used to babysit him and we'd play legos.  It was always kind of scary for me because he'd sometimes have tantrums and he was so much bigger and stronger than me.  I was eleven.  The next song was "All I wanna do (is have some fun)."  Which was written for that horrible Miss Crow by the father of a girl i'd met.  I was at his house once, admiring his grammy, and I slipped into a child's bedroom and snorted a line of meth.  this was years ago when I still bothered with that shit.  A friend found me sniffling in the room and thought I was crying.  Turns out, the kid who's room that was had just died by falling off a cliff.  he was young.  really young.  I think he might have been mentally challenged too.  the connections our head makes.  the associations.  always going from point A to point B.  I wish I could stop them and just for a second, be there, doing nothing but just enjoying a slice of pizza.  But I can't.  I feel pity, fear, my age, old drug habits, death, friends no longer in my life.  dumb bullshit.  I wonder if either of those mentally challenged kids had that problem.  Then again, I wouldn't trade my experiences for anything.  I truly think that every question has two right answers and that they contradict each other.  I've said this before, but its how the square root of 4 can be either 2 or negative 2.  You see an ex.  You want to kiss them.  You want to punch them.  You try and be nice.  you end up an asshole.  you enter a room and think you are better than the others.  the drones.  you can't look them in the eye.  you're two shy and feel low.  I think I stole this idea from "Ask the Dust" by John Fante.  The main character will talk shit about someone one page, then profess his love the next.  Neither was false.  Mr. Red says we all battle ourself everyday.  Yeah, so I have no idea how to wrap this thought up....
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Are you an alcoholic? I don't know.  I drink a lot, but it doesn't affect my work, so probably not (ok, thats a bit of a lie).  In New York, you have no cars, so there is no need to stay sober.  What exactly is your occupation? I work in a cubicle for a corporation.  I push papers around.  I'd prefer not to mention the company for many reasons.  Whose boyfriend are you anyway? No ones.  Its a nickname Sarah used on her blog.  Have you gotten ever gotten kosher with Sarah/Ultra? I'm a goy, so I don't think anything I do is kosher.  We've kissed before.  We are both kissing sluts.  Is writing the profession you want to go into? No.  How did you meet Ultra? At a Clinic show a few years back.  I was dancing drunk with a lesbian on each knee.  She thought it was funny and invited me to a party she was having.  Do you have a hobby? This blog.  Sometimes I fuck around with music until I realize I have no talent.  I used to paint murals.  There are some in the Bay Area, only I think the building that most were on was torn down.  Maybe not.  But I stopped painting years ago, so its not a hobby anymore.  I read a lot.  I like to hit golf balls into the East River as well.  What did you study and where? Economics at NYU.  Hopefully grad school at The London School of Economics, if I ever get off my ass to do that.  Why did you go to LA to see Elle when you both live in NYC? I went there because she went there without her boyfriend and I wanted to tell her how I felt in a place far away from him.  Can we bone? We'd have to meet and see where the chemistry takes us.  Any more?  Post them in the comments section.    
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I don't when it started, maybe a couple weeks ago, but I've gotten into the habit of hugging my pillow as I sleep.  I wake up spooning it like a lover.  A goddamn pillow.  I've always despised sharing a bed.  Partly because I like my room to roll around and I get too hot with another body near by, and partly because I know I am a terror to sleep with.  I kick, snore, steal covers.  I spontaneously get naked in my sleep for no reason (more often than not, while sharing a platonic bed, thus making the morning weird for all involved).  For a while, I even thought that if I got married, I'd want my own bed, if not my own room.  But now, I want there to be a nape of a neck to kiss.  I want to feel the soft underside of someone's arm.  I want to brush my nose against someone's hair.  A tummy to put my arm around.  A breast to cup.  A head on my shoulder.  A thigh pressing against mine.  Something more than just a fucking pillow.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I only got to sleep for a couple hours before I had to wake up and meet my brother.  We drove to south jersey and stayed at a beach house with a bunch of his friends.  They are all older.  They think I am depraved.  my brother didn't know that my life is as foolish as it is.  he and his friends enjoyed the stories but I think overall I gross them out with my immaturity.  They are all married or almost married.  Relationships are shit.  Thats what married people taught me.   So much time spent fixing things and working on issues.  I am in no place to do that.  Thats what I learned.  I heard them talk and I just thought, "why?"  Thats a lie.  Having a partner sounds nice sometimes.  I realized I only have one partner.  The anorexic one in Miami.  I love her.  I tried to call her.  No answer.  I hope she is doing better.  Back to less sad things:  We drank a lot.  They wanted debauchery for the bachelor party.  They were too chicken to follow through.  I dropped my pants for strangers and hussled girls into the hijinx but my brother and his friends just laughed in the background and never really played along.  i even ditched them at one point on the trip.  Jersey girls like really lame jersey boys.  Jersey boys are fucking obnoxious.  New York makes you a snob.  You really do think you are better than everyone else.  Because you are.  I've had way too much alcohol in my body this weekend.  But it was for my brother.  I didn't want to be so drunk.  I can't write right now.  I haven't had anything but alcohol pass my lips in 2 days.  my head is pounding.  I feel like I want to puke.  Wow.  This post is boring.  This is what happens when you leave New York.  Nothing.  This is what happens when you hang out with married people.  Also.  Married people get fat.  I am so excited for that shit.  Look at my tummy bitch.  more of me to love.  You too.  You can get fat.  Lets get fat together.  Lets just give up on everything.   Also.  I rocked the casino.  I made $100 at the blackjack table in Atlantic City.  I am good at blackjack.  Who knew?  No strippers, no sex, no lies to be told.  Pretty tame bachelor party weekend, but good to see the brother.  I love my big brother.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My brother came to town.  I met up with him.  We did karaoke with his friends.  They are older and fatter than me.  they get worn out.  they go to bed.  I left and went to live it up.  I went to Lit and met up with Mr. Blue and Mr. Red.  I saw two girls dancing.  They were both cute.  I started bustin' my best moves near them and they gave me welcoming looks.  Hands were on hips.  Pelvises were pressed against each other.  Lips met foreign lips.  I was kissing one of them.  Then.  I was kissing the other one.  So hott.  Kissing friends is so fucking hott.  Dancing.  Sliding thighs.  Spit stained lips.  One girl.  Then another.  oh god.  Then, they went outside to smoke.  I followed.  They said they were going to another bar.  I didn't know which one to kiss goodbye.  They left.  I stayed.  The bar was packed and too much trouble.  Like a fool, I walked on to the place where they said they were going.  They were not there.  i returned to the original bar.  It was too packed.  I headed off for another place.  I ran into Miss M. there and we danced.  I also ran into Jezabel, the girl whom I've known for a while, the one who I finally went home with a week or so ago.  she said that I had totally "girled" her and it had weirded her out.  I had called when she wasn't feeling well and asked her if there was anything I could do to help her.  Apparently, this is too much.  This weirds girls out.  Jezabel wouldn't really talk to me.  I also, wisely, decided there needed to be distance between us so that I wouldn't smother her.  Yes.  one concerened phone call was smothering, even though that was a week ago.  I understand.  Its a strange situation.  She is the roommate of my ex afterall (and that ex is now moving out since learning about me and jezebel knocking boots).  God.  i fuck up lives.  Mr. Red came.  We left after dancing on stage for a bit.  A cute blondie danced with me, but I told her I wasn't in the right place to be so flirty.  We left.  Now I am home.  Not enough hours between now and when I am supposed to meet my brother for the weekend trip to the beach house.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Last night a man convinced me not to stop the blog.  I think I was just really depressed yesterday.  So, without skipping a beat.  Its back.  For better or for worse.  I went home afterwork, sad as fuck for no reason and collapsed into my bed and slept.  I had terrible visions and woke up soaked with sweat.  I showered and decided to accompany  urlLink Mr. Red  to see Radio4 perform at Spirit.  I was only able to do this by the gracious kindness of  urlLink Alex , who was able to get my broke-ass in for free.  Thank you thank you thank you.  Alex is always impeccably dressed and always has the perfect demeanor.  He is also from San Francisco.  Thats tops in my book.  Olde English.  Why must you lure me with your siren call?  Why must you ensure that I cannot show up anywhere sober?  Once I had a dream where I went back in time and met an old British sea captain and he took me to a magical isle where he grew "forty" berries, the juice of which, was the fine nectar we now refer to as malt liquor.  So yes.  Me drunk.  Old news.  I danced with friends, some of whom I hadn't seen in a while.  Saw Radio4, who unfortunately, did not impress me.  Drank some more, then left to go to another bar.  Mr. Red and I were graced by the fine presence of  urlLink Leigh  in the cab, who informed me that I am not her friend because, apparently, I threw a shoe at her last week.  Mr. Red and I ended up at our next destination, but it was a bit quiet, and decided that 2:30am was an acceptable, albeit, sadly early, time to call it a night, especially when you have to be at work at 9am.  We got pizza and took a cab across the bridge back to Brooklyn where I forced Mr. Red to watch a horrific video clip that someone had emailed me of very extreme female ejaculation.  "Oh dear God! its like a fucking garden hose!" was the last thing I heard coming from his room as I passed out. 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The voice of this dumb blog is straying too far from my own, so I am stopping it.  That and I am bored of talking about relationships and God knows there is no need for another New Yorker to talk about parties and shows or worse, pop culture.  It was fun.  Now its not.  To paraphrase my favorite author:  Character 1: I wasn't always wicked.  I started out trying to be honest, but people called me a scoundrel.  The more people called me a scoundrel, the more I became one, until I finally did become a wicked man.  Character 2:  You aren't wicked.  You're just an ordinary man, and a not very original one at that.  bye,  Greg, a non-boyfriend.  PS.  If it becomes fun, I might do it again.  But for now, its corrupting my thoughts too much.  It makes me bitter.  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      When the fuck did it get so hot!  Left work and walked to the LES, ate, then went to Miss M.'s to put up shelves.  All those years at the hardware store finally paid off.  Then walked back home.  Now I am a sweaty mess and I'm tired.  So I am condensing the rest of theories.  That and I am sick of talking about assholes.  I think a lot of why I liked Elle had to do with how I continually had to win her over.  She had a boyfriend, so there was always guilt and it was always a struggle to hold her hand, to kiss her, to make her forget about him and fall into me.  Sometimes, when you're in a relationship, even if you're happy, you can't help but miss a first kiss.  The magic of touching someone's lips for the first time.  The first "Oh my God, they like me back!"  Unless that first kiss is a drunken makeout session with a stranger, which can also totally be hot as you fuck their face with yours.  Damn.  That can actually be really fun.  Sliding hands up foreign bodies.  Ok.  I strayed there for a second.  But seriously, that first bit of mutual attraction is powerful.  I think everyone is insanely self-conscious.  Even the most confident of us can crumble at the thought of your object of desire not wanting you.  Its the most humiliating thing and nothing crushes you like rejection.  But that first kiss.  Its like your eyeballs fall back into your skull and your scalp lifts up to the heavens.  All the breath in your lungs becomes pointess, for you are living off them, and it rushes out of your body to join theirs in the heavens.  Now when someone treats you like shit, you can't help but think they don't really like you, and you get down.  You want them to like you.  You fight for them to like you, and sometimes you win, and you get a magic kiss again.  A kiss of approval, of validation for your feelings and time invested.  Dating an asshole is like having the security of a normal relationship without losing the magic of new ones.  Its like a drug with amazing highs and shitty lows.  Plus, the make-up sex.  Lots of make-up sex.  And some of that "I hate you" fucking the hell out of you sex thats totally twisted but raw and hot.  But more than just that, its also drama.  If there is one thing that can be said about drama, its that its not boring.  It keeps the mind occupied.  Off the routine of jobs.  Off the fear of death. Off money troubles.  You obsess about feelings and emotions and love.  You can't stop.  When a relationship is stable, you don't worry about that shit.  I think this might be why whenever you visit small towns where there is nothing to do, it seems like high school drama is everywhere, and all these great people date such lame as mean douchebags.    We also all know that stable relationships can become stale, and stale is boring, and we leave people, or we cheat on them, anything to feel some excitement again, when we get bored.  You just sit there watching them being lovey dovey and for some fucking reason, you just want to scream at the stupid fuck.  Boring is for the old, and the old are for death.  Then the psychologists will insist we bring up the Daddy syndrome.  I think this can go two ways.  Either your dad was an asshole and you look for that little piece of home for all those Dr. Drew reasons, or your dad was so nice and such a square, that you rebel by fucking the biggest prick on the block.  So no matter what kind of dad you had, you're screwed.  I don't believe in that one this much...the cycle of abuse and all that...blah.  fuck abuse.  we abuse ourselves enough.  lets not fuck over each other too.  This is my blog damnit.  So back to me.  I think I am over Elle finally.  On Monday, when I was sad, she sang a song on my voicemail and it was so sweet, and I felt strongly for her, but it was a feeling of thanks for the friendship.  I am glad not to be lovesick anymore.  Plus, damn, when the heat comes out, the close go in.  So much skin to be seen on the streets.  Its really funny though, how you can see all that skin and think its so sexy, and just know that they are so different from you, and not be attracted, then you see that girl who looks like she is into the same things you are, and you forget all about that skin, and then you remember how totally different you were from the one girl you totally fell in love with and you realize, you don't know shit about shit.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The new post is below this one because I wrote it prior:  After a conversation with my fantastically bitter roommate  urlLink Mr. Red , I've decided that this whole week will be dedicated to our preposterous theories on why girls go for assholes.  Its true.  They do.  The next one will be the weakest, but I already wrote it and am too lazy to write the others.  Why do this?  Because my life is boring right now.  I am poor.  Being poor is boring.  The following exchange just took place and its making me laugh.  Mr. Red: New York is just hard to live in.  You spend money where you don't expect to.  The subway stops and you have to pay for a cab that you don't have money for.  Drinks are too expensive.  Food is too expensive.  Girls are too expensive.  But its exciting.  The city kicks your ass everyday and makes life interesting.  So what if you move to someplace else?  So what if you have a big place?  Enough money?  What the fuck are you doing to do then?  Me: Find inner peace?  Mr. Red:  Who the fuck needs that?  Inner peace is for your deathbed.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A few months ago, I went to a Brooklyn warehouse party for the photograpther Terry Richardson.  He was doing test shots for Suicide Girls.  Anyone there could go in the back room and get photos taken of them naked.  Ask a girl to let you see her naked in the privacy of your room and she'll slap you. Tell her you'll take a photo and show it to the world, she'll say yes.  Anyway, at this party, I'm just sitting there drinking my forty when they start doing a live video feed of the photo shoots.  Nude live girls thirty feet tall on the walls.  The crowd was funny.  At first they all kinda laughed and had this prententious, "yes, we go to wild Brooklyn parties," then as the shoots continued, the atmosphere changed to a bit of disgust and uncomfortability.  Americans are prudes.  Too much naked and we get weird.  My favorite part was watching all the boys who weren't looking at the screen.  You could just pick out all the types.  The "I have a girlfriend here and she'd get mad guy".  The "I brought a girl here and I don't want her to think I'm a perv, I want her to think she holds my attention" guy.  The "this is reminding me that I haven't gotten laid in a really long time" guy.  The "I get so much pussy, seeing naked girls is boring" guy.  The "girls here will see me not looking and think I am more mature than the other boys who are looking" boy.  And finally the, "I think I am too cool for school and can't admit that I wanna look" boy.  Me.  I looked.  Naked girls are hot.  I mean it.  They are.  I was really profoundly affected by it.  I remember this girl who was sitting next to me.  We had a brief chat.  She barely made an impression on me.  And if she did, it wasn't with her looks.  She was just average.  All the girls were average.  It was an average party.  Yet, get these average girls to strip and the inherent sexiness of woman comes flooding out.  All those curves and sway.  Hot damn.  I couldn't believe how these average girls became sexual icons just by being female.  Women have a sexual power over men.  Many religions make women cover themselves from head to toe, partly, just to try and stop that power.  We are suckers for it.  We stare, we make lewd comments.  We are pigs.  We hate it.  Maybe some don't, but any decent guy does.  He hates that he is so superficial.  Most guys have dated.  Maybe even fallen in love.  We know that the more emotionally attached you become, the more beautiful you find someone.  We know how special a connection is.  We want a friend to share with.  We know that looks or only exciting in the beginning, that its not what is really important.  But fuck.  Girls are hot.  But we really want the girl to know that we are above that.  That it is those other things that we are searching for.  Of course, we only try to express that to the ones who we think are hot, but nonetheless, all those cat calling assholes on the street piss us off just as much as you.  Those assholes in the bar chasing after the pair of tits in the red dress get us riled up too.  Stupid fucking meathead.  Fucking lame ass jock.  Did he really just walk up to her and say that?  Fuck.  That was crude.  Fucking jerk.  These are the type of guys we just shake our heads at.  The ones we think ruin it for all us nice guys. The ones who wanna fight when you accidentally bump into them at the bar.  We are above that.  But girls.  Poor girls.  All that hotness.  Scared to ride the subways at night.  Straying from certain streets at certain hours.  Men attacking and groping them.  Horrible.  That's why they should like us us.  The kind of boy that won't treat them like that.  But what happens if someone does get fresh with her on the subway?  What the fuck is this skinny white boy with no muscles whose never been in a fight going to do?  Not a fuck of a lot.  Thats what.  Who would?  Who could tell this asshole to fuck off?  Who could make the girl feel safe walking down that same street?  That same asshole who wants to kick your ass because he blames you for him spilling his beer.  Another asshole.  Thats who.  Fight fire with fire.  But, a lot of girls are really turned off by those kind of men.  And a lot of girls don't even know about their desire for protection.  But somewhere inside, they know they want someone who will stand up for them.  And if you are a really skinny white boy who has never been in a fight, you gotta prove you have balls somehow.  And you definitely don't do it by telling them how pretty they look.  You walk over with confidence and talk to them like you know them, like you you've already won them over.  One man's asshole is another man's confidence.  Fuck, and if can combine those balls with unthreatening looks, they will be caught completely off guard.  You will be unstoppable.  Be brave, be ballsy.  Prove you can step up during a stressful moment.  That you can take care of shit.  Most "nice" guys are just so indecisive and wimpy to give anyone else any sense of strength and confidence in the face of adversity.  Maybe thats another reason they lose out.  
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      There are boys, and I have been one in the past, who are dating girls.  Now maybe they both know that its just a young relationship, not leading to marriage, etc. etc., but its fun and they both really truly care.  One leans into the other and says, "do you love me?" and the other says, "yes."  What does this mean?  right now? Yes, I really care about you? yes, I am madly passionate for you?  God, its so vague.  It makes me sick.  But we say it.  Sometimes we mean it, maybe in that sense where you feel your forehead getting all airy and lifting from your head.  But sometimes you just say it for that moment, so you two can melt in each other's arms and feel the peace of the heavens resting on your lover's heart.  Sometimes, you know, in your heart, you don't mean it, but you really do care about this person, and you want to hold them, want to see them close their eyes and melt into you with happiness.  Sometimes, you'd kill yourself before you hurt them.  You'd do anything to make them happy.  You're such a fucking asshole.  You do what they want to do on Saturday night.  When they ask you if they look fat, you smile and tell them they are beautiful.  Its all really great for a while and you're such a damn good boyfriend and she brags about you to your friends, but you know what?  You get boring.  And predictable.  And, we all know its this nice boy front, that sometimes you really do think that shirt is ugly, that sometimes you'd rather be at that party with your friends without her.  She'd probably like a night away from your death grip stare too.  You're over protective, and not only that, you are haughty about it.  Look at all the fucking sacrifices you've made for her, all the meals you've paid for, all the times you comforted her when she cried.  The time you took her to the emergency room in the middle of the night (OK, for some reason, girls go to the emergency room A LOT!  Like, boys, we have to be shot, and like, shot 4 times, before we go.  Girls, in the infinite complexity of their body chemistry will feel one strange pain, and its off to the hospital...ok, sorry for that tangent).  And you know what?  Those sacrifices aren't sincere.  Saving her from any teeny thing that might make her sad or upset isn't a virtue.  Its a pussy cop-out.  Have the balls to tell her when she's annoying.  She'll give you the dirtiest fucking look she has, march out of your place, call you an asshole, and you'll sit there going, "shit, I fucked up."  But you know what?  She'll calm down, call you back in an hour or two and apologize for storming out.  Its only fair to tell her she's annoying.  She tells you what shirts of yours she hates.  You change the way you dress for her.  Why do you do that?  Maybe even you start to question it, then you become resentful and you start throwing your haughtiness and ego at her.  Everything spirals downwards.  You start to get really annoyed with each other, but its still all smiles and unspoken unease.  Eventually, for what seems like no good reason, she is going to get sick of your passive aggressive bullshit and leave you.  The guy she leaves you for will be an asshole.  He'll be someone with a back bone.  Some jerk who treats her like shit.  You'll sit their crying and being all heartbroken.  You'll write a song about it, or god help us, a poem.  Maybe you'll even show it to her to win her back.  You won't win her back.  But why?  You were such a nice guy.  You never cheated on her.  You always complimented her...what did you do wrong?  You were annoying as fuck.  You were whiney and needy and wanted her to give you all the same little compliments you peppered her with.  And you thought you were so fucking great for doing it.  You are an dishonest egotistical shit head.  You are an asshole.  Just be straight with people.  Is it really an asshole thing to do to go up to a girl and say you just want to make out with them?  Yeah, when you see it and hear it, it makes you sick, but sometimes, that girl just wants to make out too.  Bam.  Both people happy.  No one lying.  No false pretenses.  Isn't that a lot nicer?  Good guys don't always wear white.  More about nice guys and assholes will come in the following days...
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Holy fucking shit.  I just saw this play at PS 122 where they reinact real life plane crashes from the viewpoint of the cockpit.  Lots of loud airplane noises and alarms, screaming freaked out pilots about to die.  Its called  urlLink CVR  (Cockpit Voice Recorder).  Totally nonsensational or exploitive, just honest human emotion.  I had a death grip on my seat the entire time.  Many people couldn't handle it and left.  I am going to need the world's largest gin & tonic before I get on the plane to go to my brother's wedding in two weeks.  Also, remember this:  The fear section of the brain is located near the section for sexual arrousal, so bring that hottie you wanna bone.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Last November I broke up with a girl.  We had dated for a while.  She was absolutely terrific to me.  For some reason it wasn't feeling right inside of me.  I wasn't feeling any spark and as it was, things had gotten increasingly serious, and not wanting to  let things get even more serious, I ended the relationship.  I realized I was in no place to date someone, that I couldn't open up enough, that I didn't take things seriously enough, that, basically, I was a selfish fuckup.  What followed was months of celibacy and introspection.  And really, Elle was the first one to wake me from this sleep and reintroduce romantic feelings and desire within me.  I think that is why I fell for her so hard.  All my ability to love and all my repressed passion that had been bottled up all came pouring out.  But obviously that was a doomed situation and only recently have a realized that.  My heart hurt a lot and for the last few weeks, I have been burying myself with drink and new women in an immature attempt to forget.  But my heart has been opened and once again, I crave love, and with that craving comes back all your insecurities about all your flaws.  On Friday, my neighbor and good friend held a party.  He is leaving the city for a month to work on a television show.  The party was fun and was a nice change of pace from the usual Friday night bar debauchery.  Another neighbor introduced me to a girl she knew.  All her features were all a bit off but somehow they came together in this unusual and intriguing way.  We talked.  She was witty and quick.  Lots of spunk.  I was highly fascinated.  We danced, talked, and kissed.  We spent all night together.  I was probably a bit pestering, but I was highly drawn to her.  I wanted to tell her as much, but knowing there is nothing less genuine than the slurs of a drunk, I decided to wait until I could see her sober and show her a better side of me.  We kissed goodbye and went our separate ways.  On Sunday, the neighbor called me and told me that she and this girl would be hanging out and asked if I was interested in joining them.  I was.  I made the walk over to where they were and entered the meeting place and found them on the patio in the back. Standing with them was one of the most striking men I have ever seen.  He was tall and slender, dressed amazing, with probably the coolest haircut I have ever seen on a boy.  His face made puppy dogs and babies look like gargoyles.  The girl was fixated, never pulling her eyes off him.  He stood there telling amazing stories with such wit and charm.  Stories of living in bookstores in Paris, of crawling in secret passages underneath the river into the catacombs of Notre Dame, of being in trains that exploded, of a knife fight in Granada where he could only keep his cool by singing Beat It in his head as he and another man circled each other with their blades drawn.  I stood in silence.  My neighbor pulled me aside and said I had to talk to her, but I couldn't think of anything I could say that anyone could find interesting compared to endless adventures he recited.  Defeated, I left.  Every piece of ego and confidence that I normaly struggle to hold onto had been ripped out of me.  That mixed with my obnoxious drunken behavior of late has sent me into a talespin of self-loathing.  Its time to make some changes in my life.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I posted the head for food comment as a joke.  I mean I didn't expect anyone to take it too seriously.  I am seriously broke at the moment.  HR fucked up and I am not getting paychecks.  They will resume next Friday but for now, I am screwed.  LA totally robbed me of my savings.  It was probably a mistake to spend that money.  I thought I would still be ok, but I didn't realize how backed up I was with my bills.  I blew through a grand like that keeping the creditors off my back.  I still would have been ok, but this lack of paychecks is totally fucking me up.  I have dipped so deep into rent money that its a joke to even call it rent money.  My landlord is going to have to wait for a while to get paid.  But as I've made clear, I do not except charity or loans.  I've already sold off most of what I have to sell.  So jokingly, I offered to sell myself.  I mean, giving blood, giving head, its all the same.  Giving away some part of yourself for the almighty dollar.  Money sucks.  Its such a limiting factor no matter how much you try for it not to be.  But enough of money.  I expected the comments from people offering to take me up on the offer, no doubt, all anonymous and not serious, but one email seemed to blunt to be taken lightly.  I tried to find out more from the sender, but she wouldn't tell me anything.  I am not just going to agree to anyone.  That would creep even me out.  So I was ready to dismiss it when I got another email from someone claiming to be a friend of the first sender, saying it had all been done on a dare.  She also said I should do it.  That I'd be happy I did.  Now I knew it was some girl being dared to test me.  A double dare.  A dare to the girl, to see if she had the guts to go meet a random guy, and a dare to me, to see if I'd back up my words.  I thought about this.  It intrigued me.  And really, if I can't stand behind what I write, what right to I have to write anything at all.  Did the writers of the Declaration of Independence back down when the redcoats showed up?  Sometimes, in order for words to keep their meaning, you have to back them up with physical actions.  All this anonymous, you can't touch me in cyberspace BS is complete wimpy shit.  But at the same time, what I was confronting was just that.  Anonymous words floating through the internet into my inbox.  I was standing up to a ghost.  It didn't seem real.  Its like those spam messages you get promising cheap valium from Thailand.  You don't actually expect valium to show up at your door.  So I accepted and agreed.  Me and this email would meet for head and food.  Days past and emails went back and forth.  I really thought one of us would back out, that we were just sharing a running joke, but as the emails started dealing with the specifics of time and place, it became clear that we were entering a game of sexual chicken, seeing who would take it farther.  We made ground rules.  No kissing, clothes stay on, she'd wear a skirt and we'd just hike it up, etc. etc.  I found myself walking around the city staring at every girl, thinking, "is that her?  Oh, she's cute, I hope its her.  Oh god, I hope that isn't her..."  Pretty soon any female on the street became someone that I might realistically have to lick.  It was creepy, it was dirty, it was intriguing, it made walking to work the most sexually exciting thing in the world.  We all stare at cute people everyday, but to think that there was actually a real distinct possibility that one of them could end up in my bed was hot.  I will not deny my perverted nature and my sex drive.  Its true.  You have sexual thoughts too.  By this time I had forgotten about the food.  I didn't care if she brought any or not.  I told her as much.  As the day in question approached, my nerves went haywire.  Could I actually do this?  Could I, moments after meeting a stranger, sight unseen, actually sexually service them?  I mean, I could back out at the last minute, but at this point in the game of chicken, I didn't want to be the one who backed out.  I emailed her and admitted my nerves and told her that I would have to be really drunk to actually go through with something so absurd.  She said she felt the same way.  So we agreed.  We'd both be trashed.  Work ended and I came home.  I realized, holy fucking shit, this is real.  This email is about to turn into a person.  I distracted myself with washing my sheets and cleaning my room and drinking vodka.  Lots and lots of vodka.  I showered, made my self presentable, and headed across the street to face reality.  I walked into the bar and much to my dismay, there were more than a few girls sitting there wearing skirts.  I sat there checking them all out, wondering who's crotch was about to be in my face.  If it wasn't for the vodka I would have puked from nervousness.  No one was approaching me.  I started trying to catch their eyes one girl at a time, giving my best "so are you the stranger I am eating out?" look.  No one seemed to be responding.  I looked at my watch and it was past the designated time.  I got an all too uncomfortable realization that maybe one of these girls was the girl but that she didn't like the looks of me.  I mean, the few photos of me out there are more flattering than real life.  I became embarrassed and went to sit outside.  She rounded the corner, saw me, sat down and told me I didn't look like my picture.  I think thats a bad thing, but at least it wasn't bad enough to flee.  She was drunk as promised.  I had a drink in my hand and I drank it and made nervous conversation, rambling about something or another.  She looked at me and told me she thought I'd back out.  Taking a big gulp and pulling in all my drunken confidence, I slid my hand up her skirt and lightly rubbed her panties.  She didn't flinch.  She wasn't backing down.  I slipped my fingers inside of her.  I didn't even know her real name.  She was wet.  Wet pussies are a fucking turn on.  She looked at me and said that it was making her want to makeout.  We said no kissing.  We through that rule out the window and kissed.  It was going to happen.  Neither of us were going to back down.  We headed across the street to my place and entered my room.  She sat on the edge of the bed and pulled up her skirt.  I started.  I enjoyed it.  She enjoyed it.  Sarah said there were only two realistic possibilities.  Either one of us would back down and nothing would happen, or we'd both be into it and we'd end up fucking.  So Sarah demanded I buy condoms beforehand.  Sarah is always right.  It wasn't long before we were a mess of flesh and sex.  Hours past.  She missed the band she was going to see.  I was surprisingly at ease and comfortable.  I had never sex before where there was no fear or concern for the future.  Where no one is nervous about how this will affect things tomorrow.  Will this person like me more or less?  All of those feelings associated with first times.  It had none of that.  It was an absolute capsule of the present.  It was as if you said, if all your life is just this moment and nothing more, what would you do?  You'd do it all.  But eventually, we both collapsed from exhaustion and smoked a cigarette.  I offered to let her spend the night.  She declined, got dressed, and just as suddenly as she had come into my life, she left.  Sadly, there is a tomorrow and I was really weirded out by the whole thing when I woke up sober this morning, but I've sinced normalized for the most part and don't really have any regrets.  I don't think I'd do something like that again.  I'm just glad my first (and probably last) venture into the world of premeditated loveless sexual encounters with a stranger was that pleasant.  As for her, she wrote me an email saying that she was glad she followed through on the dare.  I was too.  She was really nice and sweet and I probably would have backed out had it been anyone else. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I wrote a post about last night.  For the sake of privacy, I deleted it.  The short version is Yes, I really was serious about the food for head exchange.  But I think one bout of man-whoring was enough.  Its too risky a lifestyle, but once was fun and mysterious.  I think both of us thought the other would back down, but neither of us did.  Of course we both had to get a bit drunk to follow through.  We'll see when the regrets and fears start kicking in.  I am still thinking about what I am willing to share, if anything, about last night, so in the meantime, read my two roommate's blogs:   urlLink Mr. Red    urlLink Mr. Blue 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Elle made me wait on a street for an hour for her yesterday.  Stupid bitch.  Well, more like Stupid Ass Greg, since not only did I wait, I didn't even get mad at her when she came and was all smiles and hugs as we drank ourselves stupid after work.  After literally being the only two people in the bar for numersous hours, we headed over to the trendiness at Delancy Club.  Fucking hell, nothing makes a mayhem out of a nowhere place like putting Sarah on the decks.  Ok ok, MAYBE some of the people were there for the free vodka, but for once, I wasn't.  I was about friendship.  The place was way too packed with alcoholics and shoulders and hips and bags and other things that get in the way.  Elle stuck around for a bit, then sensibly went home.  I did not.  I drank.  I drank.  I also drank.  Sarah was there with Niki.  her new roommate.  I think I tried to manhandle her all night.  I was pretty creepy, but short skirts, free vodka, and Greg is just a dangerous combination.  Being the completely upstanding girl that she is, she had none of it and properly did her best to keep me in place.  She probably could have broken my nose and it would have been justified.  Thank God she didn't.  Instead, she made me the strongest drink ever.  After like 6 Gin and Tonics, 3 beers, and 3 vodka drinks, I really didn't need it, but if we start turning down the drinks, then the tourists have already won.  That made no sense.  I am super hungover.   Forgive me.  OK.   Back to the beat.  Really strong drink.  Really really strong drink.  night gets blurry.  Things I remember:  Hiding under the turntables smoking cigarettes in proper outlaw fashion.  Getting really really bratty and rumpling my face up like a grumpster.  Trying to kiss everyone.  Storming off to find the man with my big mac that Sarah was making me eat to counteract Niki's drink of death.  Finding a pair of women's shoes.  Black chunky boots.  The kind with really thick 3 inch heals.  Jamming my feet into them.  Marching up and down Delancy denouncing people I didn't know with my new supermodel women's boots swagger.  Remembering not to lose my bag.  Finding the porn store Miss M. now lives above.  Collapsing into her bed and passing out.  PS.  Miss M.  If you read this.  A box spring is not a bed.  The key part to the bed is the SOFT mattress that goes on top of the box spring.  PPS.  Good thing i work for a fashion company.  I have yesterday's smoke and gin soaked clothes wadded up under my desk and I am dressed on the company dime.  Finally, I am brand appropriate.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I can't sleep.  I've been laying in bed for hours thinking about what witty answers I could come up with for the questions asked, and then I realized there was only one real question to answer.  It was a question of my own.  Why am I such a pathetic lovesick drunk?  This requires a long answer.  During my last year of college, I fell for a girl.  We had a beautiful relationship and I was the happiest I had ever been in my life.  She was great.  I still love her, but back to then.  One night she came over and told me it was over.  She loved me too much.  She saw no reason for us to ever break up.  Everyday we grew closer and everyday we relied in each other more and more.  She saw that in her future, there were no more first kisses with new boys, no explorations of herself or adventures with new friends.  Just me.  This scared the shit out of her and she left. (later she would come back but that is a whole other story).  She cried her eyes out as she told me all this.  I'm a sick fuck.  I took a photo of her crying as she dumped me.  Its in my hand right now.  The day after she dumped me was the day my new roommates were supposed to arrive from Florida.  They were two 19 year old girls that one of my other roommates knew.  I had never met either of them, but would be the only one there to greet them as everyone else was in France while my broke-ass was stuck in Brooklyn.  They arrived.  The second one was this skinny tan blonde girl.  A bit trashy but in an endearing way.  She made me smile.  We bought a bottle of vodka to get to know each other and the three of us drank our way to friendship.  The blonde girl, C., turned out to be a bit of an exhibitionist and quickly was topless, looking me in the eye, telling me I better get used to it as her new roommate.  I liked this new roommate.  I wanted this new roommate.  I wanted her to help me forget that such a wonderful girl had dumped me just the night before.  Fucking a new roommate the day they move in is probably not a good idea, but its what happened.  It continued to happen and the poor girl had to spend too many nights listening to me bitch about my broken heart.  She pulled me in, held me, nursed me back into confidence.  She let me pour it all out and let my fill myself with her.  She pulled me back from a deep abyss and pushed me into the sun.  We'd wake up early and fill our bags with rum and spend our days getting drunk in Central Park, laughing and joking, watching the rollerskaters dance to funky beats coming from the outdoor soundsystems.  We'd come home, pass out, wake up, then drink some more.  We were reckless drunks and she pulled me into her exhibitionist world.  We started fucking in the kitchen, then in bathrooms at bars, then on tables at bars, then against buildings in the East Village.  She made me feel free.  She made me feel alive.  We'd spend our quiet nights in bed bitching about our parents, and we'd spend our mornings laying there, dreaming about our kids.  I was in love again.  I had to finally take a job and our good times calmed down.  She'd still go out with her friends when I went to bed early.  At first I worried about her wild ways, but eventually I gained enough confidence to accept that she loved me back.  Sometimes she'd come home trashed and wake me up, naked, straddling me, ripping off my clothes and making love to me without saying a word.  Other nights, she'd slip into my arms without waking me and when the alarm went off in the morning, I'd find her naked body curled up against the warmth of my body.  She was getting skinnier and skinnier.  She was getting really fucking thin.  She wasn't eating for days at a time.  Thighs shrunk to the size of my biceps (which are not very big at all).  I had no idea what to do.  At first, I hounded her to eat, but then I realized this only made her more self-conscious about eating.  I started filling the fridge with foods I knew she liked, hoping she'd go off to eat when I was asleep.  Nothing did any good.  She'd cook that food for me, "so one of us eats right," she'd say.  She was dying in my bed a little bit more every night.  I spent countless nights on the phone to her father in Miami, begging him for advice and health.  Eventually, I realized I was completely out of my league and got her father to accept just how fucked up she was.  We agreed to send her back to Miami and check her into a hospital.  There was a lot of drama.  She was pissed, but eventually realized she had to.  And then she left.  Over the course of the next couple years, I'd fly down to Miami and see her when I could afford to do so (which wasn't often enough).  The last time I did that was a year ago.  It was devastating.  "I look like a fucking holocaust victim, don't I?" was the first thing she said to me on that last trip.  She was right.  I held her and cried and made the most of the few days I had with her.  I cried all the way back on the flight to New York, convinced I'd never see her alive again.  I never was able to bring myself to see her again.  It was too much for me and I felt too helpless.  We had so many dreams together.  So many plans.  All that stopped them was this one fucked up disease.  If I could choose anyone to be in my arms right now, it would be her.  I think every girl since her has been a distraction.  A way to forget about the cruel circumstances of life.  Right now, I am thinking of all my promises to her, and realizing that any promises I would make to anyone new, would be breaking ones I made to her.  Ones, that somewhere in my heart, I still hold true to and always will.  So did that answer the question?  Maybe not.  Maybe the concise answer is: The past haunts us all and we do what we can to forget that we can never escape its shadow.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Someone left a comment saying that I needed a Q&A session to straighten out some fallacies and holes in my posts.  I am game, so ask away.  I will sort through all the questions and post the answers tomorrow. 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Part of me wants to post about politics.  About Kerry's speech.  About the state of the union.  Etc. etc.  its so tempting.  With the US in an absolute shit-hole.  I want to talk about my pledge to leave this country if Americans don't shape up and smarten up during this next election.  I will abandon you all.  I will have lost faith.  It will be sad.  I want to talk about all that, but politicking is not what this blog is about.  So I won't talk about all of that.  Instead.  There is something that just begs to be mentioned.  I've written about it before, but I just can't seem to bring myself to click the "post" button.  But here it is.  Pussy Size:  Every day I come to work to find my inbox flooded with adverts for penis enlargers and sexual helpers, from viagra to no-name herbal enlargement pills.  Some men have complexes.  These things prey on that.  Its sad.  me.  I am happy with what was bestowed upon me.  But other men.  They are sad.  It makes me sad that they are sad.  Worried about something that they can't change, that in many ways doesn't matter.  I cry a little bit for them every day.  And part of me can't help but think that part of the problem might be the sloppy ass pussy of their lover.  OK.  here's the deal.  Some girls are so tight that even after hours of lubing and coaxing, the thing just ain't goin' in.  its frustrating.  That's rare, but some are very damn tight and its a struggle every time.  Then, many girls are within the normal range, some snugger than others.  Then, there are those where its like, "fucking a glass of water" as one article put it.  The only article I have ever seen on the subject by the way.  That article was really graphic.  It talked of theories about how overweight girls had more fat and such in their bodies, squeezing things tighter.  All inconclusive stuff as no one talks about it.  I mean, for man to talk about a large vagina, opens the doors for comments on the possibility of a small penis.  No matter what.  It fucks things up to talk about it.  Its a little secret.  Men don't mention it to women much.  If we insult your vagina, we ain't ever getting in it again.  So we suffer in silence, listening to girls making cracks about unsatisfying men, while thinking to ourselves, "you know it goes both ways."  You very in size as much as we do.  And just as there is such a thing as too big for us, there is also too tight for you.  And just as some boys are too small and you just don't know what to do, some girls can be too big.  But like all things.  Technique, emotions, love, skill, they can all overcome it.  But still, size and compatability can be an issue in sex, and sex can be an issue in a relationship.  I remember a quote from Whoopi when she was talking about having sex with Ted Danson, she said, "It was like throwing a hot dog down  a hallway."  My old roommate was well known around the neighborhood as a very well-endowed man.  I remember him dating a girl for a while, and then they finally "did it" and a day later, they were broken up.  I just assumed that maybe, for him, it was about the hunt, and that once he got it, it was over.  So I asked him.  He said, "Dude, I couldn't even tell I was inside her, it was so loose."  So sad.  Yet girls don't go around fretting about their size.  There's no market solely based on a woman's feeling of inadequacy of a body part she cannot control.  Where is this sexual equality we were promised?  I don't see it coming anytime soon.  And if you think this was shallow, I'm sorry.  I was always taught that its what's on the inside that counts.  [ed.  Originally, I had the word "genitalia" in that sentence referring to body parts she can't control.  I took it out because I hate that word, and I realize that without that word the passage sounds as if I am neglecting the numerous facets of our society that make women feel insecure about everything from their lips, to their thighs, to their boobs, to body hair, so on and so forth.  So, please understand that I meant solely the vagina, and yes, I forgot all about vaginal reconstructive surgery when I wrote thisk, so you can fault me there.  Also.  Obviously the sexual equality thing is a joke.  I do not base equality of the sexes on SPAM content.  I know about in inequality of pay and gov't representation, etc. etc.  (and in case anyone was curious, every single girl I know makes more than me.  In my own broke ass way, I am helping the equality of pay by taking down the male average, one broke day at a time.)  But I'm talking about SPAM!  People.  Lighten up.  If I was running for office, sure, put me through the ringer, but I'm just lunchtime reading.  But comment as you wish.  The point being is that it is just a topic that doesn't get mentioned much, and now I see why, because if anyone dare mention it, then it opens up the discussion to every single facet of sexual politics since the stone age, which is all well and noble except that its slightly misdirected at this blog, unless you want to correct the minds of the few boys who read this.  Ok Fuck.  This is longer than the post and my brain hurts.  I think this is why I never pressed "post" before.  Uggh.  PS.  Don't be insecure.  Men are pigs.  They'll appreciate whatever they get.] 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      When my grandmother died, we didn't have a funeral.  I asked my mom why.  She said that it was because no one would come.  "You mean she didn't have any friends?" "She did.  But they are all dead.  She outlived them all."  Come to think of it, I recall her once saying to me, "I have more dead friends than I have alive ones."  My mom goes through periods where she thinks this way as well.  She told me once, "I'm getting to that age where your friends start dying pretty regularly."  Not the odd accident or the tragic illness.  Just inevitable death.  One day I got to work and there was an email from my mom.  I've since deleted it, but to paraphrase, it went something like this:  "Greg,  I would just like to remind you that when I die, I do not want a funeral and I do not want to be buried.  Please have me cremated.  Unlike your father, I don't have any specific place where I would like my ashes spread, just someplace pretty.  I really like roses, so maybe just drive around until you see some pretty rose bushes in the neighborhood and spread them there.  But do it at night as I am pretty sure that the dumping of human remains on other people's property is illegal."  That last line still makes me laugh.  I deleted the email because I felt guilty about laughing at my mother's death.  I like old folk songs from the 19th century.  Many of them center themselves around death.  All those diseases that we now can cure.  So many deaths during child birth.  Kids often never made it to adulthood.  And the wars.  All those wars.  Death was everywhere.  Death was part of life.  And we still have wars.  In Chad, Sudan, the DR Congo, Serbia, Middle East, etc.  Throughout the world, most people still have to live with death, and not just the memory of a person or two, but the constant threat of it on a daily basis.  With that probably comes some level of acceptance of the facts of life and death.  Not that it makes life any more pleasant.  Just a little bit more honest.  I mean, we should try to curtail it and help people's suffering, but its not a disease.  Its not something we can eradicate.  Here.  Many people can't even stand the idea of consuming a dead animal.  I remember a passage from Fast Food Nation where a farmer says something along the lines of, "Have you ever seen what a coyote can do to an elderly cow?  Its a hell of a lot worse than turning him into hamburger."  Sometimes I think I'd be better off if I had to kill animals on a regular basis.  Not for sport, but for survival.  Maybe I'd be more accepting of it.  Maybe out of sanctity, or maybe out of how casual and rote it may become.  Listening to all the politics these days centered around security, about securing our lives, I find it sort of funny that we don't talk about the thousands upon thousand of lives that are dying in other lands for our security.  I think what Americans are really trying to say is,  "Not on my front door."  Lets keep that death unspoken, like our pedophile priests and retarded uncles.  Lets keep those skeletons in those closets, out of sight, out of mind.  Maybe I should ignore my mother's final line.  End the secrecy, walk up to a front door, ring the door bell, introduce myself and say, "This is my mom.  She's dead, like you will be one day.  Can I put her on your roses?  She would have liked that."  If I came to your door, what would you say to that?  Maybe if we had a little death at all our homes, we'd be more aware of what we are doing abroad. 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I just ran into Corky from Life Goes On.  He was wearing a backpack, hunched over, talking to himself, making odd hand gestures and hauling ass down the sidewalk.  He damn near ran me off the sidewalk and into the oncoming traffic on Broadway.  The man is obviously troubled.  In other news:  Apparently my choice to stay home last night caused me to miss a night of drunken partying with Brazil's top models.  Its ok.  Models are bothersome.  And I'm not that cute.  Also:  Someone has been text stalking me from LA for almost a week now.  I'm obsessed.  I text back.  even during sex.  Finally, she had the nerve to answer when I called.  Apparently, I gave her my phone number when I went to LA to hunt down Elle.  I don't remember her.  But I was drunk.  Refreshingly, she knows nothing of this blog.  She has a cute New Zealand voice and tells me explicit stories about fucking her husband (a rockstar) and various other B-list celebrities.  My spies are confirming the facts as we speak.  Maybe she just perks my interest because she shares her name with my favorite lager.  Life is interesting.  PS.  I could use more spies.  Email me if you live in LA.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I need a roommate by the first.  You'd get the biggest room in the place.  Dare to Dream, people. 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      One friend to another:  "Where were you last summer?  You're not in any of my memories."  "I was in boyfriend land."  Boyfriend land.  As Greg the Boyfriend, a trip to the motherland was definitely in order.  Maybe the fact that she was leaving and there was a set end date really did allow me to open up the heart, to care, and earn that passport into boyfriend land.  The transition was quick.  A toothbrush in the medicine cabinet on the first day.  Spare clothes for work on the second.  The assumed weekend date.  So much, so quick.  It has been a while since I've experimented with a full on relationship.  Shit, its been a while since a girl stayed the full night.  (usually they slip out in the wee hours of the morning...I am a terror to share a bed with).  OK.  So shit.  I had forgotten what that land was like.  First of all, what's with all the fucking ice cream?  I don't eat that shit by myself.  But, in boyfriend land, its a daily occurrence.  Refusal to take place in the ice cream/cake/dessert ritual is akin to saying, "I don't love you anymore."  I mean, after all, what kind of lunatic would refuse sweets?  Obviously one who doesn't love you.  Also.  I now understand it.  The major motion picture studios secretly own Hallmark, so that Hallmark can make you feel shitty on Valentines Day, so that you get into a relationship, so that you inexplicably quadruple your movie viewings, whether rented, or at the theatre.  I mean, you are supposed to spend way too much fucking time together.  That's the first rule, but we all know we can't handle that shit, so we watch movies, where we can both individually be taken to a magical alternate universe, and most importantly, avoid having to strain for conversation for two hours, while simultaneously experiencing a shared experience together.  Plus, it will give you something to talk about afterwards.  God knows you've heard all each other's stories and aren't creating any new ones to tell because (s)he was there with you when you had them (and face it, they were boring stories anyway).  Also.  Fucking hell.  Friends.  When you date someone, you also date their friends.  They are the in-laws of youth.  You go out with your partner and meet their friends.  You try and be nice so they don't hate you, so they accept that their friend likes you.  Even if this douchebag is the complete opposite of what you like in a friend, if he's a close friend to your partner, you'll smile and make jokes, thinking, "ok, I just have to be polite and friendly this one night."  No, you jackass.  This is forever.  You're going to have to hang out with this jackass a billion more times.  But then again, sometimes they are cool.  Sometimes you get introduced to new and interesting people.  Sometimes you like them more than you like the person you are dating.  Also.  They will meet your friends.  You will have to be a liaison.  You will have to prove to your friends why this person is so good that you are now ignoring them to spend time with this new person.  Some of my friends date cool people and I like it when they are around. Maybe this person will be like that. Others don't and those friends have slowly withdrawn to their private sector of boyfriend land.  Its a shame, because you know that that relationship will fail, and their entrance back into friendship land might be a cause of celebration or an awkward return of the prodigal son.  OK.  Maybe it won't fail and they will marry, and you will lose them to the lame land of married couples where boggle replaces beer.  Fine.  Some couples are fun and some retain excitement, but, face it, most are on a slippery slope to suburban silent suffering.  Those friends become like the elderly we stash in old folks homes.  We still care, and when its not too inconvenient, we visit, maybe share a meal, smile, fake a good time, and make excuses as to why we gotta get the fuck outta that hellish home as soon as possible.  its ok though.  They won't notice your terror.  married people have glossed over drugged out eyes and are oblivious to the plight of the single.  [ed.  I will ignore any comments posted by the married as you are all drugged out wackos, high on the smell of baby poop and your opinion means nothing to me in my world.  its like giving me a handful of yen.  It gets me nothing in my country]  And so.  here I am.  Facing the end of my stay in boyfriend land.  my work visa is about to expire.  Will I miss the massages?  The comforting words of a lover breathed lightly into my ear as I drift into sleep?  No.  Here is my conclusion.  Everyone is fucked up.  I have major fucking issues.  You have issues.  you are annoying.  maybe I am more annoying.  The point is, is that we won't ever solve each others shit, but we will have to deal with it.  If they want to stay in, you'll get pressure to stay in.  If they are upset, you'll have to act concerned.  You both double your problems.  Well fuck that.  Come find me when I am 80.  I'll be the old single guy sitting next to the other guy who is bitching about his wife.  And I'll probably be drunk.  And happy. 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      What is it about dating, or relationships, or whatever you call it when two people decide to spend too much time together, that leads the the excessive eating of rich food and the viewing of too many movies?  Why are we all of a sudden too tired to go out?  A boy needs his drinking and dancing time.  The Shocking Pinks have finally overtaken Controller.Controller as the only album I can hear without wanting to vomit.  As mentioned before, real posts will resume Wednesday.  Full of details and such.  There is much to say.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Posts have been infrequent.  They will resume soon.  Probably Wednesday.  I hate obligations.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I think taking things slowly made all the difference in the world.  Months past from meeting to the first kiss.  More time elapsed between that fateful lock of the lips and the first late night under the covers game of wandering hands.  And finally, the first time we....um....you know...did...it, I was, get this, sober.  And it meant something to me.  A lot to me.  And it still does.  And I can't use words like "fuck" or "bang" or any of my other mainstays.  I've turned sincere.  Our time is spent talking, not drinking.  Its spent hugging, not groping.  I smile and yearn to do to good things.  I strive to be nice and selfless.  We went to the Elefant after-party the other night.  Mainly for the free beer, but I also wanted to see the Elefant boys.  I spent a good amount of time with them as the sole Americans one week in London.  Up too late in the hotel partying, searching for British food that didn't want to make you vomit, making up songs in cab rides.  They're all swell boys.  Too bad that week of London shows made me never want to see them ever again.  A complete overdose.  I mean, I think I am much more a fan than most, but even I have my overdose level.  A bunch of other friends were there too.  It was nice seeing so many people.  I think I overwhelmed her a bit with all the people I was introducing her to.  I don't know why I was.  Maybe she just brings me so much joy that I want to share her with everyone.  Maybe I think her goodness will rub off on me and that the people will see, that in my eyes, I am glowing, and it will help to erase the mistakes of my past as they see the goodness this girl can bring out in me.  She thinks I am just trying to show off to her how many girls I know.  She thinks maybe I am just using her to make them jealous so that when she leaves next week, they will be more interested.  I don't want her to leave next week.  It makes me so sad.  Some friends say thats the only reason it works.  That her departure frees myself from my fear of commitment and the future.  That such a short deadline, frees me from responsibilities of the future, and allows me to emotionally open up and care.  I think its just that she's genuine, and outside of NYC bullshit, and open and honest, and sweet.  But enough about her.  She'll kill me when she realizes I wrote about her today.  In other news, we interviewed our first roommate applicant.  the mess, oh, its from a party we just had.  No, no its usually much quicker.  Thats our story and we're sticking to it.  My Shocking Pinks cd arrived yesterday from New Zealand.  Yum.  So fucking Summer.  Dancy death disco ESGesque grooves that slip into reverb filled dream tone melodies.  So fucking blissful.  Just like my gal.  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Sorry for the lack of posts.  Work is super busy and I am spending as much time as I can with Ana before she disappears out of my life and goes back to Brazil.  I really like her.  Its so sad she is going.  Hopefully posts will return soon.  But its not very high on my list of priorities on how to spend my time at the moment.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The comments got too personal.  Too much of an expose.  So BAM.  They are gone.  Yeah, so, this post is a lie.  It leaves out so much.  Therefore it is boring.  So don't read it.  its the souless version of my weekend.  If you don't like it.  Then too bad.  And, no, you can't comment on my life anymore. ----------------- After no sleep on Thursday night, I had no choice but to pass the fuck out when I got home from work on Friday at 1pm. I waste all my Friday afternoons. It fucking sucks.  I woke up in the evening and went out for Mexican with Mr. White and Mr. Red. We were all planning on going to the Siren Festival at Coney Island the next day so we opted for an early night with a rented movie. But before that, we had one mission. To free Mr. White's bike. He had lost the key to his kryptonite lock and for the last YEAR his bike has been locked to a parking meter by the subway station. With hacksaw in hand, we went to recover the imprissoned bicycle.  FUCKING HELL. Kryptonite locks are good. We couldn't even Scratch the metal, much less cut it. A locksmith was demaning $60 to free it. After examining the bike, and seeing how much gum and rust was coating the bike, Mr. White decided it wasn't worth the $60 bucks to free it considering how much money it would take to fix it up and get it back in running condition. So what did he do? He sawed the bike in half. Why? For laughs I guess. The hacksaw tore through the frame quite easily. We left the front half of the bike locked to the meter and threw the back half in a nearby pile of garbage and went back to my place to watch a movie.  Afterwards, Mr. Red went to sleep and Mr. White went home. It wasn't even midnight. I was full of red bull. I went for a bike ride and came back a sweaty mess.   I love New York. Nights can change on a dime. It was almost 1 am and I was about to crawl into bed for my early night when I get a call. Ana called me and told me she had an extra ticket to a "party cruise". It was to leave the dock at 2:30.   I started my walk to the subway when I noticed a cell phone laying on the sidewalk. About 10 feet ahead of me were two girls getting into a car, so I picked up the phone and ran over asking them if it was theirs. They said no. Feel an obligation to now return the phone to the rightful owner, I investigated the call history. The last incoming and outgoing call were both to the same number. An entry labeled as "Sexy". I called Sexy. From the sound of her voice and the the screams in the background, I placed sexy as a 35-45 year old Puerto Rican woman with numerous children. She told me that the phone belonged to her husband. She lived too far away for me to deliver the phone. I had a boat to catch.  I took the subway into the city and met up with Ana and her friend and we made it to the docks and got onboard the "party cruise".  We danced and drank and "other stuffed" until the boat came back to port around 5am. The sun was coming up. We opted to go to her friend's fantasically nice apartment in Chelsea before finally crashing at around 7 or 8 am.   My roommate called me and woke me up. I was supposed to meet up with my friends at 1pm. It was 12:30. I was still dead tired. I fell asleep and missed the meeting time. I woke up at 3pm cursing, in a strange apartment in Chelsea, said my goodbyes and hauled ass back to Brooklyn.  I called up Sexy, got an address, hopped on my bike and made my way to South Williamsburg to drop off the found cellphone. I rolled up to the corner and a posse of about 4 young girls, the oldest being 10 or 12 greeted me and thanked me for finding their daddy's phone, and one of them pulled me in close, and total drug deal style, slipped a bill into my hand and said, "here's ten bones for your troubles." Brooklyn kids are so fucking cool.  I peddled up to the subway and started the long and grueling trek to Coney Island. I hate getting there.  I didn't show up at the Siren Festival until 6pm. MANY hours late. It was exactly what it always is. A dirty beach and boardwalk with rides, overrun on this one day in summer with about a trillion hipsters. I tried to get a hold of friends on my cell, but Siren is always a logistical nightmare. Phones barely work, the crowd is so huge, the noises are loud...fuck. So I met up with Mr. Red and his girl for a bit before deciding just to wander. I forgot bands were even playing. I was a bit sad. I had already missed TV on the Radio and the Constantines (who are one of my favorite bands ever). I saw a bit of the Electrix Six and Mission of Burma before wandering the beach in search of Sarah. I eventually found her with her friends, like Brian and the Fatty of I Keep A Diary fame. I finally just relaxed for the first time in a while and sat back and enjoyed Brians mimecocking (or was it cockmiming?) and Sarah's near fruitless attempts to order beer on the beach by screaming out her requests in poor Spanish at the top of her lungs to the general populace of the beach, hoping, just hoping, the beer guy might be within earshot. In the end, she got her beer.  After catching some of Death Cab for Cutie, I met up with Mr. Red and we headed back home. After drinking many sparks, we headed into the city. We went to Misshapes, my first time in many many weeks. I don't know if it was all the "zing" in the sparks, or the news from Ana that she was definitely moving back to Brazil, but I was just absolutely incapable of losing myself in the moment and just couldn't seem to just relax and have a good time. Even more amazingly, was that I was getting a lot of attention from a wonderful female or two, but my mood was just complete shit.  The next morning, I woke up and called Ana and asked her to join me in a trip to the Museum of Natual History. I was really excited to see the exhibit on tree frogs. I have a mild obsession with tree frogs. She joined me and we went uptown to the museum, but the frog show was sold out, so we ended up just touring the rest of the museum (which I think Ana was happy about, since I don't think she has any positive feelings about frogs whatsoever).   Afterwards, we went home, made sandwiches and talked.  I am really going to miss her when she leaves. I think I am really falling for her.   
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Finally, all those days of screaming my ass off in Times Square paid off. &nbsp; I'm a  urlLink fan .&nbsp; Didn't you know? 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      We got to the place and the line was already around the block.  Thank God for guest lists.  Lines are for suckers.  Seriously.  Even if you aren't on the guest list.  Just get in the line.  Even when they find out you're not on the guestlist, they just say you'll have to pay and let you in.  Bam.  You skipped the line.  But of course, its just easiest to be on it for real.  The free red stripe didn't start until 8:15.  Some people bought beer, but for the most part, we all hovered like vultures around the beer tables, waiting for that minute hand it hit the 3.  When the moment came, the girl at the table, with ruthless German efficiency, started popping off bottle caps and the beer was flying out of the cooler.  I think I got two before they ran out.  We were savages.  "This party was over before it began," said my roommate.  My roommate, his girl, and I stood there watching the mediocre early bands.  There were two cute girls sitting near by.  My roommate's girl said that one was obviously staring at either me or my roommate.  She couldn't tell.  He was with is girl, so the two of them looked at me and started to plot and plan tactics for approach.  Eventually, after some pushing from my friends, I go over and introduce myself.  She says hello, tells me her name, then its silence.  I stand there awkwardly for about 30 seconds before I bolted off in silence like Napoleon Dynamite.  A drink or two later, I came back.  I was more talkative.  I like to think I was even a bit charming.  But not one to over do it, I excused myself and found my friends.  I came back again.  Another couple drinks had passed.  Those couple drinks transformed the charm into simple obnoxious drunken behavior.  The girl seemed a little put back, so I once again scurried off again.  I was standing there having a cigarette when this really cute girl comes up and asks me for one.  I give her one and she tells me she likes my shirt.  I say thank you.  She asks if she can have it.  I think about it for a second and suggest a trade.  I like a nice exchange of good.  So we decide.  A shirt for a shirt.  On the count of three we both rip off our shirts, and much to my surprise, she isn't wearing a bra.  She has fantastic boobies.  They are just staring at me.  As my roommate later asked, "why didn't you grab them?"  I was in awe.  She quickly grabbed the shirt from my hands and whipped it on.  I grabbed hers but the slinky satin tank was really struggling to get itself over my shoulders.  I started screaming, "tradeback! tradeback!"  She screamed back, "no tradebacks! no tradebacks!"  I begged.  She relented, and I whipped my shirt off her, baring her breasts again, and tossed her shirt back to her.  Afterwards, we laughed, hugged, and then she introduced me to her boyfriend, doing her best to explain why she had just taken off her shirt for me.  I gave him a very awkward, "yes I just saw your girlfriend's fantastic boobies handshake."  It was a little weird.  But damn.  Those were some cute boobies.  I like boobies.  Especially bare boobie.  Then I switched my attention back to the show, and eventually the mediocre bands finished and the Moving Units came on.  I really like them.  I think they are fantastic.  I was standing there watching, when the drummer screamed out, "can someone call an ambulance?"  I thought it was part of the song.  then the music stopped and he repeated the statement.  I asked the person next to me what happened.  There was some sort of stage diving incident involving a girl.  Whether she dived and no one caught her, or someone landed on top of her, I do not know.  But.  Apparently, she was just laying lifeless on the ground.  I tried to make my way up (as I have mad first aid skills, and I didn't want some fuck up trying to move her in case of a neck injury), but I couldn't get too close.  I did my best to voice my concern over not moving her, then backed off.  Then I heard some clapping and I think she woke up and was ok.  I hope so.  I couldn't see what was going on.  I came back and found my friends.  My roommate asked me, "Did you see who that was?"  I said, "no."  He said, "that was the girl you were hitting on all night."  Well fuck.  As my co-worker pointed out this morning.  maybe if I hadn't run off that last time, I could have been there to catch her.  That would have been romantic.  More romantic than an obnoxious drunk making small talk.  And by an obnoxious drunk, I obviously mean me.  She wasn't having any of it.  But anyway, I hope she's ok.  We can't afford to lose any more cute girls in Brooklyn.  I left during the Unicorns set.  I was drunk and I needed to get home.  But first.  I needed pizza.  I hadn't eaten much all day and was starving.  We got to Ana Maria's and it was closed.  What the fuck?  I didn't think it closed until like 4 am on a Thursday and it wasn't even 2 yet!  So I crossed the street to the falafel joint, saw that they had a "pizza knish" and opted for that in my despair over not getting a slice.  Hear me you.  A pizza knish is no substitute for the real thing.  Not at all.  My bedroom is a furnace.  No sleep.  Now I am exhausted, waiting for 1pm to come around so I can go home and nap.  Speaking of which.  I was informed of a place called Metro Nap, where for $16, you can rent a "nap pod" for 20 minutes for a nice lunchtime power nap.  I wonder how long it will be before people start turning tricks in them.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Tonight the Unicorns are playing with Erase Errata and the Moving Units.  I fucking love the Moving Units.  Plus.  Its at the fun warehouse venue up the street from my apartment.  Plus.  Its only $2.  Plus.  Free beer.  Oh my God.  I never get excited about shit these days, but I am looking forward this.  It combines CHEAP, with MUSIC, and FREE BEER.  its the Holy fucking Trinity of Greg.  PS.  I am officially overdrawn on my account.  My dinner last night was condiments.  Mr. Red said I would wake up in the middle of the night and throw it all up.  I didn't.  I just had terrible terrible nightmares instead.  Also.  In other news.  It looks like Mr. Red and I will be needing a new roommate very soon.  Balcony, Kiddie pool, Us.  You can't get any better than that.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Holy shit.  OK.  Um.  Thats too many people.  I feel pressure now.  Fuck.  How the hell did you find this blog?  Why the fuck do you read it?  You are all insane.  Jesus.  People in South America know where my penis has been.  Thats gross.  I can never run for politics anywhere now.  Also, a lot more blue/green/grey eyed people than I thought.  That rocks.  I have a secret fear that they will all be destroyed by the dominant brown eyed gene.  people who date me know my irrational fear of brown eyes.  Yes, I know according to the laws of Biology, there is always going to be recessive genes buried away that will show themselves with the same level of frequency within the general population, but fuck.  I don't know.  Completely irrational and I don't know why I care.  And.  Iceland?  FUCKING HELL.  let me stay crash at your place.  Please?  I've always wanted to go.  I even had a "send Greg to Iceland" fund here in the office for like a year.  I think I collected 32 cents.  Want to know my problem of the moment?  Its this paradox.  You be honest, so people who read the blog want to know you, then you meet them, then you want to write about them, but you know they read it, and you know that your honest opinions might hurt their feelinds, so you just don't write about them, then the blog becomes a shell.  I might just have to be honest and deal with the consequences.  But no one is ever entirely honest.  And what is honesty?  Sometimes doubts pop into your head.  Sometimes they linger.  Sometimes they are fleeting.  Emotions aren't ever black and white.  But once you write them out for the world to see, they seem pretty constant.  But they aren't.  They were written in a fleeting moment of me at a keyboard.  But they sit there.  On the screen and seem so permanent.  Like a mountain.  It becomes scary.  The Himalayas form from a fleeting thought, so the thought gets neglected and this blog becomes a lie. 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My friend Ana told me she booked a ticket to Rio.  If she doesn't get a job soon, she's moving back there.  That makes me sad.  So after work I went to her apartment and hung out.  She makes me feel innocent and young.  I hope she doesn't go.  I'll miss her.  She showed me pictures of her life in Rio.  Fucking hell.  Brazilians are hott.  The beaches look amazing.  I don't blame her for missing it at times.  I was supposed to ride bikes with her on Sunday, but I didn't.  Instead, I woke up late, met up with the sparkly girl and saw Napoleon Dynamite.  Its pretty funny.   Ana was telling me how she doesn't get movies like that.  She said that in Brazil, they don't have nerds and popular people.  She said those movies never make sense to Brazilians.  She said when she came here as a foreign exchange student in high school, she all of a sudden understood all those weird American movies where kids divide into factions and act like assholes and bitches to each other.  The funny thing is, is that she said since she didn't understand, or rather, agree with the clique system, she befriended everyone.  The popular people wanted to know the new Brazilian girl and were nice to her.  And she wanted to be nice to the unpopular kids.  She said, the funny thing was, was that the "losers" were the ones who stopped being friends with her for being nice to the "popular" ones.  But I guess I probably hated the popular kids more than they hated me...  I was a loser.  I think we all were.  Or we all say we were.  Who wants to say that you were popular in high school?  Fuck.  Saying you were popular is like siding with the enemy in every great teen drama.  Its like rooting for the asshole.  Its like hoping John Cusack fails.  Its hopeing Christian Slater's pirate radio station gets shut down.  Its like hoping the Heathers survive the poisoning.  Its like being a Nazi sympathizer.  Imagine a world without all that.  Damn.  Brazil sounds pretty fucking nice.  Maybe I could move there and use my econ skills to get it out of the financial shitter.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Satisfy my Curiosity.  Everyone who stops on this page.  I ask you to leave a comment with your gender, age, and location.  Everyone.  Damnit.  Fucking rain is making me sad.  Its such a grey day.  I have decided to ignore work responsibilities and to just listen to "The Sky's Gone Out" on repeat.  I just want to ride my bike.  Apparently, that is too much.  I had the distinct feeling this morning as I walked down Broadway that I would never live to see 2005.  I also had the distinct feeling that I was being melodramatic.  remember to leave the demographic information.  Oh, and include eye color.  Me:  25, Male, New York City, Green/bluish.  You: ?
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Half-day Fridays are the best.  I left work and bought a soccer ball.  Went home and played a game vs. the wall.  It one, but only by one point.  It was a fine match.  all that running and kicking in the midday sun was actually a decent workout.  Later Mr. Red and I tested out the skateboard he got for his Birthday, then we kicked the soccer ball around some more.  It felt nice to be physical.  My last few half-day Fridays have been spent in bed recovering from the night before.  In the late afternoon, I took the subway deeper into Brooklyn to met a man who sold me his bike.  Its a cheap BMX.  I fucking love it.  Mr. Red pumped up his bike's tires and we hit the streets.  Going almost all the way to Queens.  It was a nice little ride.  We saw little boys who had beer bottles on strings "fishing" in the creek.  When I was little, I didn't use beer bottles as lures.  We dropped the bikes off at home and made our way to the Mercury Lounge to see  urlLink The Five O'Clock Heroes   (But the website seems to be down).  I think they are the best unknown band in New York.  Oddly enough, I met their manager in London, came back to New York, found out one of my friends was quasi-dating one of them (who lives in my building), and another person in the band is friends with Sarah.  Its a small world.  But the point is, see them.  Also.  They have a fan base entirely comprised of young young females in short skirts.  Believe me, the sight of that alone is worth the price of admission.  The set times were pushed back a half hour and so my friends and I had time to kill in the front bar.  I figured after my show of restraint the night before, that I could socially have one drink and still be ok.  Yeah right.  The night snowballed into another drunken fest like always.  More making out with girls.  More drinks.  More Greg being a complete asshole to really really nice girls.  4 days.  Whoever guessed four days had it right.  Eventually a bunch of us ended up on the rooftop of Miss M.'s in the Lower East Side, but once the sun started to come up, I finally convinced some of the Brooklyn kids to share a cab with me back over the bridge.  Saturday:  Woke up late.  Pissed off that I slept through the nice weather.  Cursing myself for slipping so easily.  Weak weak man.  Mr. Red started to fill up the kiddie pool with fresh water and put coals on the BBQ.  I jumped on my new bike and went to the store to get meat and buns and such.  Errands are fun with a bike.  Hurray for bikes.  The afternoon was spent BBQ'ing and sitting in the kiddie pool.  It was nice.  I decided I needed to avoid Manhattan.  Its too much temptation.  So Mr. Red, Mr. White, and I all opted for a small bar in Brooklyn where The Vanishing were playing.  I love them.  The first time I saw them, they were playing in someone's apartment during your average Brooklyn apartment party.  They are kinda gothy, very dancy, amazing drummer, good thick keyboards and an insane front woman whose reverb filled vocals grab you by the balls.  She also plays sax, which works surprisingly well within the context of their freakout atmospheric dance goth sound.  The singer also runs through the crowd dancing like she's a baton twirler in a marching band, only she's just wearing a mini-skirt and pasties and she's spraying beer on everyone and rubbing against them.  We stuck around for a bit after the bands, then the usual suspects, me, Mr. White, Mr. Red, and Miss M. headed back to our place, bringing along some Swedish girl we befriended (but only after my poor Spanish skills got me trapped in a bathroom with a girl blocking my way out and a guy very forcibly trying to jam his tongue down my mouth).  We bought forties and had a "nightswim" as Mr. Red says.  The 5 of us sat in our kiddie pool from 3 am or so, to god knows when, drinking, laughing, enjoying life.  Sometime, probably about 4 or 5 am, everyone but Mr. Red and me opted for either bed or home.  Then, after some pleading on the phone, I was able to convince a friend to bring herself and two friends over at that late hour, and so 3 other girls showed up and experienced the joys of a "nightswim."  At least I hope they found it joyful.  I think we called it quits at about 9am.  I think I spent a total of 8 or 9 hours in the kiddie pool over the course of the day.  Its the greatest thing ever.   Except that our apartment looks like it has been through a flood.  All those people soaking wet running through the apartment between the balcony and the bathroom.  You have no idea how much water that drags in.  We still have a 10 foot wide puddle in front of the bathroom.  PS.  If I wind up dead in the next few days, tell the police it probably has something to do with the sketchy-ass drug dealers in an SUV parked at our building who gave me some drugs  "as a souvenir" and then disappeared before I could figure out what the fuck was going on.  Brooklyn never ceases to entertain me.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I feel really bad that I chose this week to curb my drinking considering my roommate and very dear friend was celebrating his birthday.  He's a drinker.  All my friends are.  I knew they'd all be out and wasted.  But if I can resist the birthday night, then the rest should be easy.  Dinner was fine.  I decided I could have one glass of wine.  But then, it was off to the bar.  And guess what?  It was an open bar.  Fuck.  I couldn't even use my financial excuse as a reason to why I couldn't drink.  And believe me.  My drunk friends demanded reasons.  Sarah and I hung out in the back where it wasn't packed and we could sit down.  We talked about music, relationships, music video ideas, life.  Things.  The kind of things drunks don't, or can't discuss.  It was nice.  But honestly, it was a struggle to be social while sober.  Naturally, I am very very shy.  Insanely shy.  And quiet.  People think I am mean sometimes.  But I'm really just timid.  Taciturn.  That's the word.  I like it when Spoon sings, "we seek out the taciturn."  Mr. Daniels must not have been there, because no one really sought me out.  Scott Stereogum showed up.  Apparently I called him Steve last Saturday.  I was very drunk that night.  This is why I want to stop drinking.  Rude things like this.  Scott, obviously, was not avoiding drinks like me.  He was tipsy.  He wanted others to be tipsy too.  He even offered to buy drinks and seeing how it was an open bar, it didn't seem too rude to accept.  When he asked me what I wanted, I told him a Shirley Temple.  He returned later with a Gin & Tonic.  Apparently, bartenders don't actually make Shirley Temples. I went back and forth about whether this one drink would be a slippery slope, but I needed a social lubricant.  I was feeling awkward.  I drank it.  Then.  Scott's friend managed to actually get me a Shirley Temple.  They're good!  Having a large drink to nurse and hold helped me feel like I was fitting in a bit better and I became a bit more social.  Or maybe the gin kicked in.  Either way, I was doing ok.  So many people showed up to wish Mr. Red a happy birthday.  It was really an amazing turnout.  Friends of mine, friends of his.  At least a dozen very close friends, and all of my best ones.  They were all drunk as fuck.  I did my best to hang with the conversations and slurs but it was odd.  I didn't realize just how drunk we all got.  Scott showed up again.  This time with tequila shots.  he didn't get me one, as he knew I wouldn't want one, but Sarah said if she did hers, she'd puke, so I did it.  I don't let alcohol go to waste.  I talked a bit more, looked at my watch, and a funny thing happened.  Reason kicked in.  It was getting late, (12:30!!! Fuck, thats when I usually show up to a bar!), so I decided to go home and sleep.  After all, I do have work at 9am.  This is odd for me.  I have half Fridays.  My usual philosophy is that I can get through 4 hours with the severest of hangovers and usually stay out til 4am on a Thursday night.  But I'm also trashed when I decide that.  So anyway.  I took the subway home.  I know from experience that usually the craziness happens late and the sober ones miss it.  I wonder what I'm missing.  more than anything, I am just scared of missing the shared experience of so many friends, especially on someone's birthday.  I will hear a tale instead of telling one.  That makes me sad.  But then again, I didn't steal or break anything.  I didn't obnoxiously harass girls.  I wasn't crass or lewd.  i didn't insult anyone.  I didn't bruise myself.  In short, I didn't do any damage to me, or to other people.  I can't remember a night out where that didn't happen.  Maybe I'll enjoy being the voyeur and hearing the tale from someone elses mouth.  But on the other hand.  What the fuck am I going to write about on here now?  That was my life.  That was Greg the Boyfriend.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The train is so fucking crowded in the morning.  so many strangers packed together.  I keep thinking about if a bomb were to go off.  Or the train derailed.  Something.  Boom.  And we all fell down. A bunch of strangers all brought together as a group in a single moment, in death.  But it wouldn't even be the moment.  It would be the place.  People die at the same moment around the world but no one groups them.  Only because we all died standing together would they care.  Location, location, location.  It wouldn't be just Greg that died.  It would be Greg and the guy next to me who's breath smells like ass, and the lady with the baby, and the student to my left.  It would be the "L-train victims" or whatever the newspaper men coined us (the commuter casualties?).  We'd be talked about collectively.  How we were all so brave.  So innocent.  Even the thief in the corner.  Even he was innocent.  Our faces would be shown on TV, one after the other.  This group.  We all rode the train together every morning.  There would be memorials.  Hell, if ass-breath's last name starts with a "J" as well, maybe our names will be next to each other for ever and ever.  Maybe my mom will sit next to his wife at the service.  Maybe they'll introduce each other.  Maybe they'll cry together.  Maybe my mom and Mrs. Ass-Breath will hug.  Maybe they'll even become friends.  Or maybe they'll sit next to each other as strangers, just as we did.  But we didn't die.  Not this morning.  We're just another group of strangers riding a train together.  It reminded me of when I used to work in LA and every morning, I'd find myself stuck in traffic on the 10, blasting music by myself, and I'd look around at all the cars and think, "So many people, yet they're all sitting alone."  I used to blame the cars for keeping everyone separated, but it wasn't the cars at all.  But here's to tomorrow and making friends.  You'll make friends too.  You'll be able to say you knew someone on that train too.  You'll hug a stranger who understands your loss, and you won't feel so alone.  See you on the train.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I think someone is drugging me.  For the last few days I've been clenching my jaw.  I've lost a lot of my appetite, am dropping in weight, and I can't sleep.  I've also lost all desire to post.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So there was all this crazy crap that happened over the weekend and I sat down to write about it and a couple things happened.  First.  I couldn't remember most of it.  Second.  It sounded old.  More drunken hi-jinx.  It sounded really old.  I felt pretty shitty too and didn't even get in the kiddie pool (which was finally erected on the balcony and not the living room).  My roommate got all the cute girls in bikinis himself.  Then, I went to a BBQ at my friend's place and talked to one of my good friend's mother who was there.  I was telling stories about London and my youth and shit like that and doing my best impersonation of a young charming man with a bright future, and I realized that at one point in my life, I actually was a young charming man with a bright future.  It made me sad.  I went over to my friend Ana's place because she is good at making me not feel bad and still yelling at me and making me want to make myself better.  She doesn't by into my shit at all.  She rocks for that.  So.  Bam.  After weeks of talking about change, I am finally going to do something about it.  The drinking will be curtailed, if not cut off completely.  Any bets on how long I'll last?  Also.  Time to get in gear about the future.  That means more job hunting, applying to grad school and all that shit.  I hope all the drinking hasn't caused too much irrepairable brain damage.  I fear it has, but here's to hope.  This all means that this blog might get very boring, and if it does, its going to go the way of the dodo.  Boring blogs suck and are a waste of space.  In the meantime, my roommate posted a couple pictures from the fourth of july.  They are all from really early on before too many people showed up to the BBQ and before anyone was really drunk, but there is a picture of a hairless dog.   urlLink 4th of July Pics   But there are good shows coming up soon, so maybe I could blog about that.  Yes.  Another blog about the New York music scene.  I'd rather jump in front of the L Train.  But on that topic.  It appears others share my lack of enthusiasm for  urlLink the Killers . (Although it is overly harsh and obviously written by someone with a serious grudge against any sort of hype).  But then again, they are no  urlLink Controller.Controller  (but actually I'm past that obsession).  Oh fuck.  I already have two links about bands.  I guess I better start walking towards the subway station.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Saturday, we kicked a red kickball back and forth on the street while drowning ourselves in wine.  The ball flew over the barbed wire fence.  After some investigation, we found a spot to pull the fence up from the ground and the roommate put on a sweatshirt and gloves and braved the bramble.  4 foot tall prickly weeds, razor wire, used condoms, empty beer bottles, and now a flattened kickball.  The razor wire had shredded it.  I found it very telling that we left the flattened ball back there.  It had no value to us anymore.  The thought that maybe we should remove this item that will never biodegrade from the landscape never occurred to us.  Instead we went inside and watched the A-Team.  Did you know that Mr. T. and Murdoch both wear Chucks?  Mr. T had red low tops.  Murdoch had the classic black high tops.  Saturday was another drunk night, only instead of heading home, we went to a friends house for she promised us kittens.  We all laid in bed and played with baby animals.  They were so cute.  In the morning, I got up and headed to the park on the Hudson river ro find my friends brazenly ignoring the no alcohol sign and downing a breakfast beer.  It was the Fourth of July for fucks sake.  Lets celebrate some freedom.  The BBQ wasn't starting until late, so the three of us went back to Brooklyn, bought a lot of wine and drank it while watching the entire first season of Who's the Boss? on DVD.  My roommate's job.  That's why we have all these shows on DVD.  We are no 80's obsessed like many of the kids these days.  We went to the BBQ.  Then we went to the bar.  Then we went to the other bar.  Then the other bar.  Then home.  The plan was to set up the kiddie pool on balcony and have a BBQ.  Unfortunately its raining.  I mean, its really really fucking raining.  So the kiddie pool will have to go in the living room instead.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "I find it funny when people first move to New York and they have a certain set of values and you know that in six months they'll be giving blow jobs on the sidewalk."  That's the quote of the day so far.  It might be an exaggeration, but I have indeed seen many people go from saying they don't really drink to getting drunk nightly.  I've seen people who won't kiss on the first day go from that to fucking strangers in a bathroom.  Straightedge kids snorting hard drugs.  Just a thought...  Last night was Motherfucker.  It was at Eugene's.  The last one I went to there was the one where I decided I liked this girl that I had met a couple times.  She totally ditched me that night.  Within two weeks we were dating.  We dated for 8 months.  It was strange being back there with that as my last memory.  This coming of summer reminds me of last year when we had the blackout.  I loved the blackout.  Everyone took to the street.  People played musical intruments and paraded around the neighborhood.  People filled the streets with forties in hand and the sidewalk turned into a giant dance party.  It was so much fun.  Then the electricity came on and people went inside to watch TV.  But back to last night.  Before going tp Motherfucker,  Mr. Red and I went to Sarah's.  She wanted me to meet "Bruce the Devirginizer."  She didn't remember but I had met him before.  I met him in London last November.  Actually, the first time I ever "saw" him was when Sarah and I were in some cheesy Wet Seal type store and they were playing music videos on a giant screen and Bruce's band's video came on.  Sarah grabbed me, pointed, and screamed "Greg! that's the boy who deflowered me!"  by the way, if you are a girl and you are getting robbed, scream that.  It gets a lot more attention than screaming "help!"  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So I haven't written a real post for today.  I haven't been home much.  Slept at a friends house just blocks from work.  I loving doing that.  Waking up 20 minutes before work, showering, and walking here.  No subway, no commute.  I mean, my clothes smell like cigarettes and gin.  Good thing I work for a clothing company and can just wear photo samples.  I hung out with Sarah last night for a bit, which was really nice.  Oh, and she said she likes Controller.Controller too.  I think I'll go to the Motherfucker party tonight.  I had fun at the last one.  I hadn't had any fun at the last few.  I actually hadn't really had fun at one in years.  My favorite one was probably the one where the AC broke in the middle of summer and it turned into a sauna of about 1,000 drunkards all absolutely soaked with sweat.  I spent the night dripping wet making out with a very beautiful girl as our soaked bodies rubbed against each other.  It was fucking sexy.  I actually saw that girl last night.  She's married now.  I met the guy.  He's nice.  It made me realize that one day I will be out with my wife and I'll have to be pleasant to some deuchebag that used to make out with my wife.  But seeing as how I don't even have a girlfriend, I won't have to face that situation anytime soon.  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've always founded it fascinating that this silly blog seems to appeal to women more than men.  maybe its just to look into the male mind a bit, but really, I'd think that this blog would piss most girls off.  Afterall.  Its really just about me being a drunk and uncaring dick and I get more than a few emails from boys telling me how I am destroying the hard work they are putting in at trying to be sensitive and nice and trying to change the perception that all men are sex-crazed assholes.  In the last week, I have heard so many numerous stories, from numerous sources, that have turned my little head topsy turby.  Stories of orgies, cheating on boyfriends, numerous discussions on cock size, complaints about men who won't fuck them after coming home from a bar with them, guys who are too needy and want relationships too soon...it goes on and on.  And now.  I am a booty call.  Drunken phone calls in the middle of the night asking if I am available as a lay, passing out immediately afterwards, leaving before I even wake up.  Don't get me wrong.  it totally kicks ass to just lay in bed reading a book and then two minutes later have some cutie stop by for some hot sexin'.  It fucking rocks.  But my question is, is when the fuck did this happen?  Married girls calling, wantint to know if they can listen to me have sex.  Girls convincing boys to fuck her in the ass.  Girls keeping numerous lovers, "because they don't want to be tied down."  And on the other end...  When did my male friends start paying $70 for haircuts and insulting each other's outfits behind their backs?  When did they start wondering why that girl who slept with them on the first night they met won't return their phone calls?  When did they start getting ditched half-way through a date by a girl who had a more sure thing come up?  When did they start asking their girlfriends if certain outfits make them look fat?  Jesus.  What the fuck?  When did the sexual revolution come full circle like this?  Girls proudly displaying their bodies, flaws in all, while boys with not so tight abs hide under t-shirts, ashamed of their bodies.  Is this just a pussy-boy new york hipster thing? Or are the times a'changin'?
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Friday night.  I drank two forties before even leaving the house.  Went to some wine bar.  Then to another bar where I discussed how to clean your ass the eastern way with some girl who was about to head off to India.  Then to a string of other bars to where I don't remember shit, until I finally woke up Saturday morning with a girl who was rightfully mad as to why I was so confused as to how she ended up in my bed.  I mean, I wasn't upset that she was there at all, just really really confused.  We then went and had a nice brunch.  Afterwards I spent the day alternately napping for an hour and watching episodes of the Family Guy.  It was the most hungover I had ever been in my life.  I managed to scrap up enough energy to head over to the Curiosa after party where a surprisingly high number of friends were, including a very dear one who was in from out of town and I hadn't seen in a year.  That was nice.  She was doing well.  The night itself was nothing great aside from the sight of a fat, make-up smeared mess of a Robert Smith having a pow wow with our local rock boys.  But the theme of the night seemed to be "People pissed off that they weren't being treated like VIP's" (which sometimes was justified and other times, was unfair, as in the case of bands who actually played Curiosa, not being able to get upstairs).  And also, since when is the Delancy entirely staffed by the exes of friends?  Or is everyone in NYC someone I know's ex now?  I think so.  I am no longer shocked that people I know from South America have screwed people I know from Texas, and that they might both end up in the same bar in New York.  Everyone has fucked everyone.  No ones parts are private anymore.  I think I kissed a co-worker, which so far has never led to good things.  I also pissed off another co-worker by being too drunk to remember that we worked together.  Anyway, Sunday morning was a repeat of Saturday.  A nice brunch with a nice girl and then off to home to clean.  Sunday was the first.  meaning.  It was the day that the new roomie was moving in.  We had to take the only person interested in the room.  I had met the guy for 2 seconds.  Red had never met him.  He was found by the roommate that is leaving.  scary thought.  We now have a large loud newbie to the city sharing our walls and hallways.  I'm fucking scared.  I might have to become seriously romantically linked to someone with a quickness, just for the option of sleeping somewhere else.  Recently, Sundays have become a day of rest.  My partying past of continuing the drinking binge through Sunday night has faded and only on a rare night will I still venture out.  The sight of a large strange man telling me he is now living with me is enough to make me wanna get out of the house and drink.  So Mr. Red and I went out to see our dear friend who is in from out of town.  In the process we ran into other friends where we discussed the dangers of how easy it is to blow way too much money on conveyor belt sushi in London.  We then realized that conveyor belt shots at a bar might be the single easiest way to become a billionaire.  the glasses would just slide by and you just drank whatever you wanted and each glass would have a different colored stripe on it signifying its price.  The waitress would then come and pick up the empty glasses and add up the total and make you poor.  But no one would have the willpower to turn down these magic shots that would appear on the belt like your luggage at the JFK baggage claim.  I don't need conveyor belts to challenge my will power.  I need a credit card I can't afford to use.  I drank an insane number of gin and tonics and succeeded in forgetting about the new roommate.  I also succeeded in forgetting how to walk.  OK.  Here is brilliant Greg logic.  Monday.  I have an important interview for a new job.  So.  I always feel weird about showing up at my current job in a nice outfit instead of jeans and a t-shirt, so I thought I would just call in sick, avoid that whole debacle, get some rest before the interview, and be able to stay out a little bit late and see an old friend.  You see?  Getting drunk and calling in sick was actually the responsible thing to do.  Good thing they called and post-poned the interview until tomorrow though.  I was nothing but a pounding headache until Noon today.  But I don't want to call in sick again tomorrow, so I guess I'll have to face the awkwardness of being over-dressed for my current job tomorrow.  And I am obsessed with my LA text stalker.  I even sleep with my phone in my hand so I don't miss her text stories of jealous husbands and Hollywood orgies.  I'm such a loser, but also so easily intrgued by the mysterious.  Strangers fascinate me.  I like the fantasy of molding them into your vision.  Real people are so disappointing.  Well fuck.  back to bed I think.  I drank way too much.  fuck.  I hope I don't have any more nightmares about my Mom reading this blog.  Which I think she may.  because she hasn't called me in over a month.  I think I've been disowned.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Friday night.  I drank two forties before even leaving the house.  Went to some wine bar.  Then to another bar where I discussed how to clean your ass the eastern way with some girl who was about to head off to India.  Then to a string of other bars to where I don't remember shit, until I finally woke up Saturday morning with a girl who was rightfully mad as to why I was so confused as to how she ended up in my bed.  I mean, I wasn't upset that she was there at all, just really really confused.  We then went and had a nice brunch.  Afterwards I spent the day alternately napping for an hour and watching episodes of the Family Guy.  It was the most hungover I had ever been in my life.  I managed to scrap up enough energy to head over to the Curiosa after party where a surprisingly high number of friends were, including a very dear one who was in from out of town and I hadn't seen in a year.  That was nice.  She was doing well.  The night itself was nothing great aside from the sight of a fat, make-up smeared mess of a Robert Smith having a pow wow with our local rock boys.  But the theme of the night seemed to be "People pissed off that they weren't being treated like VIP's" (which sometimes was justified and other times, was unfair, as in the case of bands who actually played Curiosa, not being able to get upstairs).  And also, since when is the Delancy entirely staffed by the exes of friends?  Or is everyone in NYC someone I know's ex now?  I think so.  I am no longer shocked that people I know from South America have screwed people I know from Texas, and that they might both end up in the same bar in New York.  Everyone has fucked everyone.  No ones parts are private anymore.  I think I kissed a co-worker, which so far has never led to good things.  I also pissed off another co-worker by being too drunk to remember that we worked together.  Anyway, Sunday morning was a repeat of Saturday.  A nice brunch with a nice girl and then off to home to clean.  Sunday was the first.  meaning.  It was the day that the new roomie was moving in.  We had to take the only person interested in the room.  I had met the guy for 2 seconds.  Red had never met him.  He was found by the roommate that is leaving.  scary thought.  We now have a large loud newbie to the city sharing our walls and hallways.  I'm fucking scared.  I might have to become seriously romantically linked to someone with a quickness, just for the option of sleeping somewhere else.  Recently, Sundays have become a day of rest.  My partying past of continuing the drinking binge through Sunday night has faded and only on a rare night will I still venture out.  The sight of a large strange man telling me he is now living with me is enough to make me wanna get out of the house and drink.  So Mr. Red and I went out to see our dear friend who is in from out of town.  In the process we ran into other friends where we discussed the dangers of how easy it is to blow way too much money on conveyor belt sushi in London.  We then realized that conveyor belt shots at a bar might be the single easiest way to become a billionaire.  the glasses would just slide by and you just drank whatever you wanted and each glass would have a different colored stripe on it signifying its price.  The waitress would then come and pick up the empty glasses and add up the total and make you poor.  But no one would have the willpower to turn down these magic shots that would appear on the belt like your luggage at the JFK baggage claim.  I don't need conveyor belts to challenge my will power.  I need a credit card I can't afford to use.  I drank an insane number of gin and tonics and succeeded in forgetting about the new roommate.  I also succeeded in forgetting how to walk.  OK.  Here is brilliant Greg logic.  Monday.  I have an important interview for a new job.  So.  I always feel weird about showing up at my current job in a nice outfit instead of jeans and a t-shirt, so I thought I would just call in sick, avoid that whole debacle, get some rest before the interview, and be able to stay out a little bit late and see an old friend.  You see?  Getting drunk and calling in sick was actually the responsible thing to do.  Good thing they called and post-poned the interview until tomorrow though.  I was nothing but a pounding headache until Noon today.  But I don't want to call in sick again tomorrow, so I guess I'll have to face the awkwardness of being over-dressed for my current job tomorrow.  And I am obsessed with my LA text stalker.  I even sleep with my phone in my hand so I don't miss her text stories of jealous husbands and Hollywood orgies.  I'm such a loser, but also so easily intrgued by the mysterious.  Strangers fascinate me.  I like the fantasy of molding them into your vision.  Real people are so disappointing.  Well fuck.  back to bed I think.  I drank way too much.  fuck.  I hope I don't have any more nightmares about my Mom reading this blog.  Which I think she may.  because she hasn't called me in over a month.  I think I've been disowned.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>