<Blog>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I know some ppl from a website (Planetside-universe as i state a lot in my buddy profile), and they made blogs.   I noticed it was free so what the hell, I GOTTA BLOG!!!!  This is sweet, i can post somethign every day about some crappy ass day i had in school or something.   Not that yall gonna read this shit, but what the hell.  Well i did nothing, something smells, and 24 is on in a few minutes.  Wooptyfuckingdo!  Well yay for 24, but fuck everything else!  WOOT!!!!!11  BTW....i might (want to) move to florida.  Kinda sucks but i rather live a new life somewhere else.   YAY!
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, if you see a post similar to this screw it, i dont see it.  Saterday night....and god damn I want to see the nascar race tomorrow but my mum dont wanna move the tv into the living room (the tv in the living room crapped out and her tv in her room cant get the channel).   I'm so fucking bored.  Now when i say a weeks rest I mean this past week i've been at weight training for football (not fooseball), its been up and down. Tiring and fun.  learning stuff, hating stuff, noticing that i'm the only freshman (yea i can call myself that now) that doesn't laugh whenever the coach says shit (i mean when he doesn't mean it in a funny way).   2 Varcity(sp) guys hate me, 1 just likes my additude, and 1 just...dunno what he does.     I dont bench much atm or atleast doesn't lok like much (the bar itself is about 45lbs so ya), though everyday we increase the weight by 5lbs as of next week cause we didn't know we had to do it next week.   Man once i start benching close to my own weight (and tahts gonna fucking hurt)....well damn, wheres the NFL when ya need em.  Waking up the past week at about 8:30 every morning kinda buggin me, i was just dreaming of going to sleep at 4 in the morning and waking up at 5 in the afternoon.   but as i see it, it wont ever happen.  Disneyworld coming up in alittle more than a month, cant wait.  Miss my last week of training but wth, I CAN SLEEP FOR AS LONG AS I WANT.  WOOT!   Although its jsut really me, mom, and bro, so i'm just gonna be with them or maybe i might have a day with my dad (as you know he lives in florida).  This summer as very few know (very few), I might not be going to this one area up at Clear Lake called Pine Grove this summer.    You ask wheres/whats that?  its lika trailer park, but i've been going there since i was 6 months old.   Me grandparents went on a rather long trip into the east coast to see my to see their sister's b-day and to a baptizem (me sisters actually).    SO i might just miss going there this summer.    Rather bummed, but eh, we got ourselves a big trip to eastcoast too, so why bother.    Course i say that when this place is about to be ripped apart by a retarded new owner that is screwing the place too hell.     It might not be there in les sthan 5 years.  Tomorrow....boring, dont wanna do anything but sit and see if theres a radio station to listen to the nascar race thats takin place at infineon raceway....yep, fun stuff, good roadcourse for cars that only turn left.   Aight, i'm tired.  too much stuff i typed....byebye
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SO, its a day after graduation from CT Engilsh (this is the last graduating class of CT English since now its going to be called Loma Prieta like the elimentary school across the parkinglot.    It was fun i guess u can say.   walked up a isle, got some sort of papper i could use for the fireplace, walked down the isle, done.   Only one besides Ben that was completely dressed up.   Kinda made me feel/look older by another 10 years (cause i feel like i'm 23 already).   After that i got bored/depressed and spent the rest of the after time in the car with top down and music blasting.   9 years of school on a mountain with an ocean view wasted, now a whole new lifestyle will errupt.  Now I'm with the big kids, screw all the people I can talk to after school, now its like walking through costco just that all the shoppers are jocks and sluts.    After that we went to Double D's, best sports bar grill evar!  Coming down the hill was....hmmm.    I saw like 5 people from my school on the highway all going to dinner.   3 on the freeway, 1 came onto the same street as us, and i saw another walking on the sidewalk.   Sure thats what highskools gonna be like, but we haven't even entered it yet.  back to the restrant.  We watched the Lakers game...though i was like the only lakers fan there, everyone else was a Pistons.  Though my mom's friend wanted those cussion seats instead of a chair, so we switched tables.   I was like WTF, we are right in front of the bigass screen tv and you want to trade to a 20'x16'???   Then she and my mom drank a few beers wich threw this thing all down hill (i dont mind it, but when you gotta drive your children, stay off the fucking beer).   After that we were goingt to get a game but her friend saw one of her friends and went talking to her untill about 15 minutes before that store closes.    So we had to go speeding down the highway to that store (remember the beer).   We made it just before they closed, i mean just before, they were at the door locking it when we came.  Got the game, yippee.   But still, kinda pissed me off cause whenever my mom brings her friend, she try's to include us (me and my brother) but then...she tries.   Come to graduation, please, but dont forget, its my day, my dinner, my fucking bigass screen tv.  Well i've been playing that game all day, pretty fun, computer kinda sux with it tho.   Now i dunno what to do.   perhaps sleep, tomorrow is a bday party.  After that i'll see no1 until weight training.     btw, i'm staying.  no highskool in florida.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So much for a "daily" blog.   Like 3 weeks ago my computer for some time had been fed up with viruses and then it suddenly popped after I was done with a bigass homework assignment (thank god).   It went into safe mode and started to screw itself up so we had to fix it alittle bit.   2 weeks later i'm on the computer fixing all the personal setting cause when i cleaned the computer everything was saved but personal settings, so that was a really big pain in the ass.   Now the thing is working much better, though its still got 6 corrupted files with the viruses that we cannot get rid of.   I guess thats my fault.        BTW, for gamers especally for ps, year aniversary was back on may 20th, on the 25th was my full year playing and paying for it.   yay.  oh and the crappy skool year is over.   I'm tired of always saying school was boring when i come home.....cause 99.99996% of the time school is boring.    Gradtuation is on the 10th.    Oshit.  Oh, and whoever stole my money ($30), give it back and i wont fuck you up.  I'll give a $10 reward (lame but eh) to whoever tells me who took it.   What happens, person who stole gets fucked.   (don't be gay here, you know what i mean)   Last but not least, for all that don't know, i have a 10 month year old sister in florida with my dad and stepmom.    Few weeks back i got really pissed at her and talked to my dad.     Now soon we might be disscussing plane tickets.......and there might be no return flight.    A dishonest man you can always trust to be dishonest, honestly, its the honest ones you have to look out for because you can never tell when they are going to something incredibaly...stupid.  -Piriats of the Carribean 
     
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well today is 2 days from goin on a plane to disneyworld, so we all decided to get our hair trimmed.    Mums friend came down again (bah), so they talked so freakin loud in side the place, it was louder than the haircutter ppl speaking their jappanises(sp) talk.   But compaired to how that went, i got myself trimmed to a "mr. Arias" cut by a nice lookin asain chick, we both talked alittle bit and i actually understood her unlike the others i tried talking to in previous cuttings.  Then we went to one of my moms friends house to get her friends watch from her friends house (confusing aint it).   We went in, got it, stayed for like 10 minutes.  When we are about to leave, this hot chick comes walking in that they said she was feeling kinda bad.   Wow, all these weeks of conditioning really paid off, cause it was a pain in the ass just to hold my jaw in one place.    Kinda looked like an older taller Avery but hotter.     Dunno why she decided to stay out whether it was to stay out because of guests or just to watch me in my posing bouncer stance (heh i had my backstage security shirt on too).     I saw her sneak a few peaks too.  Har har.  Practice was good this week, hurt my arm doing something, embarraseed myself in a play and the coach thought it was a simple mistake (and he was screaming at the guy who made a mistake on the play before this one).  So its been a wierd week.  Now as i finish this post up, i see in my mom's friends bag o close, there is a red thong.   She has been talking about a friend she was seeing earlyer, but damn common, your like 37 years old. grow up.  Its a pain trying to amagine her in it, though i have been trhough her whole lingerie drawer when i was 12 (assuming its from her highschool year), but seeing it in her bag here just makes me think less and less of her.   ugh. 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last week was a week of uniform.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Pants, jersey(unoffical), pads (including the ass pad), mouth piece, and finally the piece that makes everything go boom, shoulderpads and helmet.&nbsp;&nbsp; I swear, once you get your helmet, you feel big bad and fucking awsome.&nbsp;&nbsp; You big now, you can grab a hammer and start nailing your helmet and wont feel a thing.&nbsp;&nbsp; Its the part that we all love.&nbsp; ITS A HELMET!!!!1&nbsp;&nbsp; Then the pads are like bullet proof armor (atleast hte shoulderpads), its the things that go smash!&nbsp; really, now i can run into robert and wont feel a thing.&nbsp; Its the part we need the most.&nbsp;&nbsp; Then we got those tight pants and all the lower torso gear like thigh, knee, hip and ass pads.&nbsp; Thats the stuff no one cares about that stuff go bash.&nbsp;&nbsp; But without it, we couldn't have the smash bash boom going on.&nbsp;&nbsp; those are some of the important things ever.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I just cant wait till we get the offical jersey, once we get that and get on the line of skrimage down by a touch down at our 20 with 2 min to go, fans cheering, cheerleaders stripping (i wish), thats i swear thats the time where you feel you can do the impossible, be supperman, spiderman, wonderwoman(maybe) all at the same time.&nbsp;&nbsp; I swear thats the best part of football, that and the smell of hotdogs in the stands.  &nbsp; That was a week ago, i'm too lazy to update stuff anymore, doing to much i'm not supperman yet....haha cheesy siperman movie quote....*cough*....  I saw spiderman 2 last wensday, I swear I KNEW THE 3RD MOVIE IS GOING TO BE BOUT HARRY.......kinda obviouse if you watched the cartoons.&nbsp;&nbsp; But i cant wait to see the 2 gliders cause harry uses the same small one and then another bigass one that could hook on the the small one.&nbsp;&nbsp; Really this is something big.&nbsp;&nbsp; Oh yea if any1 finds kristin(sp) dunst nude, please tell me.....*cough*  Ha me and liz wer talkin earlier bout cars/trucks (wow&nbsp;i'm impressed&nbsp;she knows her stuff or just likes all the good cars and trucks), but we got to the subject that she was going to drive to summit store with her mum.&nbsp; I wanted to say how i drive and everything, almost did but i shall only tell close friends.&nbsp;&nbsp; If you really wanna know, ask Jordan, he saw, he's proof of what i've done....cant really explain me on HW17, but i'll get proof of that somehow too, everything is proove it proove it prooooove it.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Stupid stupid stuuuupid.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Now i hope my grandparents screw that 87 honda acord for a honda pilot, i need a new feel...still learning clutch when me mum aint around....damnit y wont my mum just start teaching me now....i hate learning myself....  Oh and also when we wer on the topic of cars, i said hell i'll just draw what i want......ummm, i am a nerd, cause i will.  &nbsp; Tomorrow i'm going to paint the table thats on our deck. Its metal btw, and will soon be a green rather than its rusty white.&nbsp; I'll show yall before and after pics.&nbsp;&nbsp; We also painting a wooden bench too, so this'll be fun.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   Then maybe next week we'll cut a tree we think will fall on the house if it snows like it did 3 years ago.&nbsp;&nbsp; it'll be hard cause my grandpa will cut it and i'm suppose to pull it while its falling cause if i dont i could damage the roof alittle.&nbsp; Thank god i can run normally with tires tied&nbsp;from my back in football. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well it was yesterday, but eh.  What did I do?   Well, friend from Vallejo(sp?) came down and we went to a deserted part of a mountain and lit a propane tank afire.   Fun.  Then right after that we drove up to SF and watched fireworks.   It was ok, bit foggy though.  My mum's friend came over again and stayed wtih us all weekend, and I have to say after my mum ran through the disneyworld routine like three times, even she was bored.   And as i said, I dont mind the beer.   Well now i kind of do.     6 beers for one weeked and she didn't drink any on saterday, so ALL OF THEM on 4 o july.   D-A-M-N.   Eh, evenly gapped.   But besides my mum who said she quite a while ago(*cough*BULLSHIT*cough*), she was drinkin beer everywhere.     Kindof pissed me off.    And in the morning my mum made me bring her tv out even though I couldn't last week (read last post).     Besides the tv is in full use, still it pissed me off.    And to top it all off, i dont want to be included in anything.....cause whenever i am, she has a stupid laugh.      Oh and never go with her to a movie, she talks throughout everything.      Nother thing that ticked me off is that they wer talking about how a friend keeps telling her what to do and my mom says she shouldn't do that and my mum agrees......really, my mum needs some hearing aids like her friend.     And then they started talking about a car she gave to this one person and i was like damn, how many people do you know???   Really, "I game it to jim cause he's a nice guy, not saying that micheal isn't nice or carren,    but after that incident with John and larry, i couldn't stand Josh with kevin."  Last thing on my list is the worst that might happen.    When we are in disneyworld, mums friend considered coming with us.        NO.  DO NOT WANT HER HERE.    NO NO NO.  NOOOOO.   I can't explain it but NO.   This past weeks been gay.     football and thats about it.   This week seems no change, though since my mums friend went back home, it'll be alot of stuff finally off me mind.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>