<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *Listening - still to LotR, more specifically Howard Shore's Two Towers piece*  I was having a quick browse here, and was awefully shocked to see some people had written in excess of 200,000 words! Unless they've been on here since the beginning of Blogger, these people may have some worrying lives. I'm a nerd, first and foremost, I'll be first to admit, yet even I have a limit, and personally, a blog is merely to keep a log of what you are doing day by day in your life, like a digital diary of sorts, not something amazingly important!  Though, I admit, some others may use it for book ideas, or something extremely heavy like that, theres got to be some limit. You cannot spend your life talking about the world if you have not been out there and seen it!  I do enjoy writing this, merely as I know I myself will end up re-reading this in the future, and I have a very high regard for recording the journey of my life for myself later, as if you don't, it seems that your life has been washed away, which is certainly not the case. If ever you get depressed, stop for a moment to look how far you have come, and through what fields you have fought.  Anyway, good night for the last time, I still have to do homework and if my parents catch me, *eek*  Fare the well! =P
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *starting now, every time I start I'll tell you what I'm listening to, so* *Listening - Lord of the Rings Soundtrack, by Howard Shore, a phenomenal composer!*   DLF, a resource for Aussie Artists  Over the length of the weekend my whole idea on the world has once again skewed, in a good way I hope!  Recently I joined a mailing-list specifically for Australian CG artists (Digital Labourers Federation,  urlLink site here ) and after observing the posts for a few days I asked a question, and an overwhelming response!   Hello, I'm currently a Year 9 student. Been to two AEAFs (or as some of you refer to them, DMW Festivals) and have grown to love CG =)  I am using Blender (www.blender.org) and Maya PLE for my CG, and have had about 2 years experience now.   But, to my question =)  If you could restart your paths in CG and do it all over again, what would you do? What skills do you think employers would prefer to see in a prospective internship/student?   At the moment, my plan is to go on to Year 12, and then to try and pursue an internship (Rising Sun Pictures offer a 3 month paid internship which looked quite interesting). If I'm not at a high enough grade to get into an internship, I'm going to try and get tertiary education (I'm doing TAFE in my spare time at the moment) and go from there...   Anyway, I'd be thankful for any help you can give, and I'd like to say hi to you all =P    From this simple email, I got almost 20 responses, from people who do the major commercials and adverts for local TV stations and also from one of the artists at Digital Domain, who brought  The Day After Tomorrow  to life!   Of tertiary education  The weekend past I also went into the city to investigate one of the academies I am thinking of going to. So far it greatly interests me, as it can move from a grounding in all the essentials of a CG artist to a degree and diploma. Extremely expandable, and the institution itself is great! The teacher himself also ended up being part of the AEAF Education Panel in 2002, and did something in 2003, although I'm not fully aware of it! =P From my short talks with him, I feel quite pleased, though in the end I do hope that I need not go down that route and merely get a job straight in the industry! lol (BTW, one of the best things he said to the group was 'And even if you don't chose to be a member of this course, I expect to see you as a fellow artist in the industry')   Of 'Art'  Occasionally I've been accused of acts of art =P Creativity, insanity, drawing, dancing (not so much, but what the hey) and the occasional form of writing *cough cough* Anyway!  This is for a short animation I'm planning! *WooT!* This is my own concept, and will feature a beautifully animated cuckoo bird as the clock's aforesaid owner.    Please note this is only a WIP, especially the base, and is more only a 3D concept of my 2D version!   And, as I promised myself, creativity exercises everytime I post (or at least every time I feel bothered!) Today I'm going by a bit of a stranger method, go to  urlLink Dictionary.com  and browse the "Previous Word of the Day Archive". Grab some strange word you seem to like and go with it. I have chosen   chicanery  - The use of trickery or sophistry to deceive (as in matters of law)   Because of my love of Norse/Viking (both the same, just different names, prefer Norse personally) this reminds me heavy of Loki, the god of trickery! (funny old chap, quite evil and vicious in his own rights, and the cause of the worlds earthquakes [long story, don't worry] but overall lots of fun!) I see him as a kind of crazy teen, a wicked smile on his face, with hair as if he'd been electrocuted during a 70s Disco [WooT! lol], sitting on a giant crate next to train tracks. He has one foot on the box, in a semi-crouch position, holding a rather large and important looking screw. In the background, smoke arises from a recent traincrash, obviously nothing to do with poor old Loki =P   I really like that idea =P Maybe I'll make a sketch on it! *hee hee hee* Anyway, one more for tonight (really quick, my dad's trying to force me to bed, and is 'interested' in this... more of an annoyingly joking way of course, but hey, better than most fathers =P), one more word from  urlLink Dictionary.com   didactic: conveying instruction; teaching some moral lesson  Well, my brain isn't quite kicking straight into gear with this one, so I'm going to go to strange old habbits. Now, my first idea was of a student sitting at the front of the class, feet up on a desk throwing a paper aeroplane around with a teacher stalked infront of a blackboard with the word on it 'RESPECT', but obviously that's a little too plain and simple... So, blackboard reminds me of water for some reason... (don't ask me why lol), water, dark, pain, red, sun, ... Well, I have teacher, student, blackboard, water, dark, pain, red, sun... Weird eh? lol Okay, a teacher is standing at one side of a frame, scribbling mathematical equasions onto a blackboard, his hand a blur with speed, as all the environment to the left of the teacher begins to lose life and fades into a mere wireframe version of the world, with the formulae and equasions responsible for the beauty of nature overpowering the beauty of it all, while the student stares into a deep pond, among green plains and a beautiful sunset, avoiding all of the manifestations of the literary world and focusing specifically on the beauty infront of him, not the one found in books, written by those who have never explored it...  Well, so much for short and simple lol. Not as good as my first one personally, but it at least has a deeper philosophical grounding, although strange in the abstract =)  Good night, and remember,  Knowledge is power. Power corrupts. Study hard. Be evil =)  (not my own quote, but don't you love it! lol)
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Or that's what they tell you =) Supposedly it isn't necessarily depression, so my GP is just kind of easing me onto the possibility of other problems effecting me... It's all good =)   Creativity  Now, I'm generally searching for a topic in my head to babble to myself about. My main idea, is unfortunately  creativity , of which I have little. I'm right handed, and my brain usually lacks any creativity, until I'm on the border of falling asleep. Vivid crazy things then, of which little I can remember (These aren't dreams by the way, but it's a lucid state. One weird thought I had was a bunch of dwarf party crashers, one filling himself up with helium! Oh that was fun lol) The way which I usually come up with strange out of control ideas when I'm non-lucid *sigh* is mainly a form of trickery. Basically, you think one thing then lead onto others. So, you take the most normal thing, and go on from that, for example  Rock   A rock has moss growing on it, moss grows in forests, forests are wet, wet is clouds, clouds have birds. So from that strange thing, my head has assembled an idea of a stalky bird carrying a giant boulder on his back and with rollerskates (don't know where I got the rollerskates from, but =P )  That's basically how I get my "ideas" from. I have a few other weird tricks, mainly involving an archive of about 7,426 pictures, contained in 307 folders and taking up 721 megabytes... Thank god for today's hard drives! I might do one of the creativity exercises everytime I post just for practice. (Even though 0 people read this! wooT!) Another good  idea is to go to  urlLink Concept Art.org's Daily Sketch Group  which always have a strange variety of ideas and topics, and at the moment 439 days of logged ideas and thoughts =)   School  I go back to school tomorrow... *sigh* And I'm in a worse state than before. When I get back I have to catch up on an English Common Test (on POEMS! *eek*) and then on my Practical Music, and then accept the annoyance of my band conductors (I'm in 3 bands, Concert Band, Orchestra and Jazz Band) about missing so many rehearsals near a performance (we have Showcase night coming up). But in truth, I really do like band. Yes, I hate getting up at an insanely early time in the mornings, and the occasional insult from a few other members (at heart they're nice, so I leave it at that) it's all good. And music, even though I may not necassarily be great at it, does help to relieve tensions (as long as the music you're doing isn't due for a practical exam tomorrow lol)
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, I've been home alone all day today, since I had a really serious migraine, stinging pain in the right eye. Hopefully won't happen again, but hey, I'm out of school aren't I? (unfortunately, being out of school caused a whole lot of other problems, like my English common test being readjusted and Music exam going out of wack, but...)  Now, I spent half of today in bed, fearing all bright lights and trying to avoid a little puppy dog (his name's Monty) who kept jabbing me viciously in the ribs to play ball with him =) The other half I spent readjusting my RAM and booting into and out of Linux trying to get my Windows partition to work (if you're not a nerd, don't worry by what I mean, just computer troubles), and then the rest watching Fellowship of the Ring DVD and doing some quick tests and tricks in CG.  Well... Depression became an onset. Hopefully due to some of the pain it was under, but I'm guessing quite a bit of it was not. By the way, this is the kind of depression where you just don't feel productive and think you're wasting your time, not the quite brutal and vicious kind of depression that therapy is needed to fix (well, hopefully it's not... lol)  I feel that I'm not making headway with my CG, feeling worried that I'm going to fail myself... That's the biggest problem with being self-taught, failures has no reassurance, only that you are to blame. I'm trying to work hard, but I'm just not making any progress, and then I get the fears that I could be wasting all my time and that I may need to be born with a specific mindset to be successful, like left handed people being more creative (and I'm  right  *sigh*)  So, in desperation, I turn to the only place that has really ever helped me... The Net... My parents, although loving and supportive (as any good parents should be =P ) wouldn't have a clue about computer graphics (tho my dad is on the thoughtful and philosophical side and my mum is quite a techy, works as Web Content manager for IBM's IBM.com/au site and taught me HTML in Year 3! =P ) and some of my friends are wacky enough to start up their own cartoons (and I'm sure some have lol) none of them can offer the help I need.  urlLink  CGTalk  (which I noted earlier) is the home to thousands upon thousands of artists, and is a larger version of my home sweet forum  urlLink Elysiun , which is much more friendly but not quite as advanced.  Searching it discovered  urlLink this thread  which may help me! Even if it doesn't help me progess, I've been broken out of the slum, usually only broken by a good night (or good nights) of sleep and a morning that would make Dory from Finding Nemo look knowledgable! =P I am also underage for any alchohol consumption, which people have hitherto told me that it cures depression, only resulting in a mild feeling of being on fire the next morning =P  Of the greatest help in that thread so far is Mooncalf's comments... People like that I respect, they don't simply go on a forum to get the highest post count, and even if they do, they get to the highest post count posting helpful information all the way. Apart from Mooncalf's awe inspiring approach, the others suggest DVDs and training videos... *sigh* If I had the money... of course... I'm a Year Nine student, who is even legally allowed to work yet, living in Australia with most of the DVDs being American... I would have to pay for a DVD in Australian dollars (I hate the price of the dollar at the moment, whether or not we get more tourists lol) and then ship it all the way around the world and hope they don't stuff the 8 for a 4 and get my package delivered somewhere in the red centre... *sigh*  Maybe I have bi-polar depression lol! *after doing a quick Google* Hmm... This isn't good... After checking out the  urlLink five main types of depression , bi-polar does actually fit me very well... The site  urlLink here  describes bi-polar, with the very unfortunately snippets of -      I doubt completely my ability to do anything well. It seems as though my mind has slowed down and burned out to the point of being virtually useless. I am haunted with the desperate hopelessness of it all.   (sound similar to above to you?)    At first when I'm high, it's tremendous...ideas are fast...like shooting stars you follow until brighter ones appear...all shyness disappears, the right words and gestures are suddenly there...uninteresting people, things, become intensely interesting.   (if you know me on a hyper day, this is me...)    The individual often will deny that anything is wrong. In its early stages, bipolar disorder may masquerade as a problem other than mental illness. For example, it may first appear as alcohol or drug abuse, or poor school or work     performance.    (Quote from above -  By the way, this is the kind of depression where you just don't feel productive and think you're wasting your time, not the quite brutal and vicious kind of depression that therapy is needed to fix  and look at the bad work performance part,  I feel that I'm not making headway with my CG, feeling worried that I'm going to fail myself... )    Well, that's not great... lol... Maybe I should get that checked out... I'm going to have an appointment with my General Practitioner anyway, may as well bring it up (preferably with my mum out of the room, not that that'll stop her finding out lol)  Anyway, was just on the phone with her and already told her... No freaks, just an overtly calm mother saying "oooookkkk.... Remember, 9:30 tomorrow, I'm going to have to get you up early... Well, actually, you'll be getting up later than usual... anywayyyyyyy...." =)
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Exams are over, and the wretched stench of hard work and stress are finally beginning to wash out of the air.   Overall, cramming didn't go too badly (apart from one night/morning when I had to study for three exams the next day... Not fun! =P) Of course, now I can joke about it, but if you caught me two or three days ago I wouldn't been a possible homocide case lol  Anyway, paradise is ensuing, and I'm starting to relax. I also bought Lord of the Rings Fellowship of the Ring Special Extended Edition (the names nearly worth the cover price itself lol). Excellent making ofs (two DVDs) and high quality widescreen movie discs including commentary. Overall, darn excellent (not as good as Pixar, but who can beat them? =P)   Quick thought    Also, quick note on exam marks, 93% in Latin (non difficile est), but 85% in Maths (starting to show the midnight burn, but I am in top class, which is pretty good for it being my worst subject). Others should be coming back soon.   ----  I also did a quick artwork, relating to an award competition in 3D, link to the JPG here   (copyright as this is my actual work, if you want to use it slip me an email) Basically a spun polygon mesh, some procedural textures, ambient occlusion, new angular mapping (same technique used to compress HDRI images) and of course good old  urlLink Blender  for all the 3D! =) Just a quick work to get the rust off of my fingertips. Really could have done better on the handles, but apart from that I'm happy
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, may I just note here and now, I only post what's worth reading (hopefully lol) Not everyday like a diary, only when I think it's important.  Two things btw, it's 1:08 (1:28 as I reread this lol) in the morning as I type this, and in two days I have exams (of which I haven't studied for, but I always do reasonably well just by cramming), so excuse incorrect grammar or spelling (also, I'm at the point where I feel guilty for not studying and therefore am not doing anything productive, neither studying nor my hobbies, but spend my time by reading forums like  urlLink CGTalk  etc... [not nessacarily a waste if I think about it])   What really shocked me tonight was a story about two brothers, both into art. I was reading their  urlLink interview here  and absolutely loved some of their work. They're twins, and work closely together, and both go under the alias "Twincruiser". I was just imagining how great it would be to have a twin brother work with you, share your successes and happiness, talents and fun... (Just a note, I have no siblings, so I know little of the hair pulling and backstabbing normally associated with brothers and sisters =P )  This made me extremely shocked, when, going to  urlLink their website  to look at more of their work, I saw this...    To my dear, loving Brother    Why did it have to be so quickly...  You and I were destined to walk this life forever...  You knew that we could have done so much things together...  Still, In my heart I know you are here with me...  Thank you for the joy, inspiration and lessons you gave me...  You will always be with me, my brother.     His  twin  brother died only a month ago... I don't know the details, all I know is that it shocked me... I had a perfect image of paradise, two brothers working side by side together doing something they love, and then bang, it was all gone. The worst part was I was thinking to myself "Hey, they like mythology, this and that too, they sound like me!" and I felt I almost knew them... Bit of a shock eh?  Anyway, their artwork was and still will be excellent, they worked on many of the Warcraft manuals, and their work is stunning! Check it out if you have a chance.  Anyway, that's it for tonight, I'm going to be going to bed now since I really should get some sleep in preparation for exams (just another point, I  hate  the idea of sleeping, to me it's a waste of a perfectly good 8 or so hours which could be used for so many more things, and I also love the idea that people perform almost as well on 20 minutes of sleep [REM is the most important form of sleep and only occurs in the first 20 minutes]) Also, to note, if I was to be reincarnated, let me be a dolphin! They can rest each hemisphere of their brain seperately, thus never actually sleeping, only being awake in a dumbed down sense =P  The main problem though is that I suspect tomorrow I'll freak and spend hours and hours studying =) Got Latin up first, then Maths, then English, Geography (do History next term), Music, and finally Computing, which I won't have a problem in the world with =) I know that even if someone tested me at this very moment I would get in excess of 80% for every test (my brain works amazingly well without having to study, I actually find a lot of the stuff I learn interesting and as such stays in there) but I'd still love to get 90-95%... I studied about 2 or 3 days in advance very heavily in Year 7 (first time I had ever had exams, I was freaked) and because of that I became an Order of Merit student and subsequently got a 25% scholarship at my school (well over AU$10,000 a... quarter I think... not sure, ask my parents, they get the bill! =P ).  Anyway, here's for hope and a good nights sleep! =P
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       First post!  This is the perfect place to babble about my insanity, eternally WIP (work in progress) projects etc etc.   Quick background about me first, just call me Smerity =) I'm currently in Year 9 (at the moment with mid year exams in one week *eek*) and have the greatest passion towards computing and other related fields, and reside in Australia.    My main interest at the moment is computer graphics (and art in general), which I do with a fabulous  free and opensource  application called  urlLink Blender!  Blender, other than what the name suggests, is a 3D application, featuring modelling, texturing, animation and rendering capabilities, clutched from the hands of its previous owner (Not A Number, gaming company, and it was closed source) with thousands of Blender users digging into their pockets to raise a 100,000 Euros (I'm Australian, I don't want to deal with conversion rates, but simply put, it's a lot!) Anyway, more info is available onsite, and while the interface is daunting at first, check it out, you'll love it in the end!  BTW, I discovered Google's Blogging service thru a news item on  urlLink Slashdot  (News for Nerds, Stuff that Matters =P) about the curators of Google themselves getting a blog ( urlLink Their Blog Here ), then them linking me to here... Weird huh!    For my first main thought, TERMS OF SERVICE!  While signing up, I read the Terms of Service on the site. Yes, all of it, lots and lots of it =) My main concern was whether they held any rights to my content, which they don't (Thank you Googlers! You guys always treat me right!) thank heavens. But my main thought was how many people actually read those things? Do  you ? I know in my time I've glossed over the contents (and quite often finding I'm not allowed because of being "underage"), but obviously there are times where there might be a serious matter. Copyright issues etc  Just something for you to chew on, and... Welcome to my (encoded into English and represented graphically using a strangely simple and not quite a real programming language HTML) world! =)  Oh, ps.  Terry Pratchett  and  JRR Tolkien  rule! (Both book authors, and if you really don't know who at the very least JRR Tolkien is, do yourself a favour and go grab the Lord of the Rings from the local library! Really, how big a rock are you living under! =P)
     
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm straddling the gap between feeling okay and complete depression... Don't push me...  I am trying to stay happyish, hopeful, ish, and everything though. It's just hard!  BTW, I created the site I was talking about. Three days work... Woot... Woot...  urlLink .: My site:.  The whole site in total is only like 50Kb, should be almost instant, even for us poor modem users  It really sucks, I couldn't go to Spiderman-2 today. It just came out... I'm on holidays... I haven't gone anywhere yet... I've literally stayed at home the whole time... I tried arranging it with my parents... And... For all that hard work... Nothing... At all... Except that really annoying feeling like you've just swallowed liquid lead, and the whole inside of your stomach and heart are trying to meet the floor...  You shouldn't feel like this on holidays... It's just not right, nor logical. Should be happy, brimming with happiness... Yeah, right, theories suck... Dang nabbit. My dad wants me to go into his work, fix some computers there, and link one from home to the office, yet he doesn't know I haven't been out once since holidays... Once... I feel like a prisoner in my own home!  I guess what I'm saying is I don't want it to be this way. I just don't know how to change it.  If that makes any sense...   Eh  On a positive note, a friend of mine in CG invited me to work on one of his projects, a project to recreate the cinematics of a game called "Crusader - No Regret". He talked me into it, and hyped me up about it =P Prospects for it are very good. There is still a huge fan base, and I implanted the idea that he could make an opensource recreation of the game, like  urlLink Freedroids at Sourceforge , except this would be even better as a result of the huge fan base still obsessed with the game. This is also another sad story about what Microsoft can kill, the company who produced the game, Digital Anvil, a spin off of Origin, was bought out by MS, and nothing has been heard since. Ouchie, poor Natronio.   2D  I'm falling in love with two dimensions all over again. It all started with a DSG where I did a quick sketch of a Goblin King and digital painted over the sketch, and the flames were eventually fanned by an ex-Blender artist called Landis Fields, who has just updated his site to include  urlLink Flash animation tests . I want to try some stuff soon, really really want to try.   TV  A TV show I really enjoyed has it's series finale today. It was called Grounded for Life, and featured all of the kind of fun you want from a TV show. A crazy and cool uncle who hasn't married and seemingly never will, a father who doesn't want to stop you drinking beer but join in and chug a cold one himself, a mother who is just lovable, and a daughter who is a predictable teen. You of course, also have the grandfather, who's living with them instead of the home... Anyway, it ended, with a mixed flash back to the day the two parents got married, lots of fun. I'll miss it though.   She who must be obeyed...  That's how my dad refers to my mum. She set the beeper to 45 minutes. Like it matters. If I don't get up early tomorrow morning, it doesn't care, I'm not going anywhere anyway. Apart from possibly my dads work. But we all know how much I want to go there... Well, it's not that I don't necessarily want to, it's just like I'm going straight from school to work, instead of school, fun, work, fun fun fun... Just typing the word makes me sick. It's like eating a sausage infront of a starving man. Worse than that, it's like cooking them and then eating them infront of him. Eh, stuff she who must be obeyed, I'm staying up. *goes to reset timer*   Steve C  'The energy stored in coal, crude oil and natural gas all comes from the sun. Im supposed to "Explain this statement."' Well, I helped him out, and, for the record, 'I can't express how much you have saved my ass', it was an assignment due tomorrow for him =P (he's at a public school, we get holidays a week earlier and longer than they do) Always happy to help an oppressed school student!   Planning for post-HSC  Hmm... I have a few [insert word meaning imposing and clashing] plans for the future.  For example, I want to do the three following -  1. I want to go straight into an internship at Rising Sun Pictures, and get a job there 2. I want to go and get educated in 2D and 3D graphics, at preferably a place like VFS or somewhere which offers Pixar certified training, or even better, is taught by Pixar employees. 3. I want to go and learn the theory and coding behind such a thing, at universities like Berkeley and Harvard.  Hmm... Let's consider all three... Fat chance... I literally feel really sick at the moment... It's just not working out, and it's not like in those cruddy movies where everything is falling apart for the nerd (who under the surface is actually a 'cool guy'), and then some guy, or girl, or chic, or girlfriend walks up to him and says 'It's alright, life's a million paths, you couldn't predict the ones you were going to take, blah blah BLAH...' Well, ya know?  I just wish it wouldn't always feel like a fight to try and firmly plant my feet anywhere outside of school...   Endeth  And on that note, tune in tomorrow to discover how Smerity valiantly escapes the clutches of depression,
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What is with the above name, I'll never know =P  ANYWAY! Less depressed than last night, actually, I can say without a lie leaving my mouth (nor my fingers =P ) that I'm actually happy,  and  hopeful! Added bonus eh?  While I'm typing this, my internet connection has been on for 1 day, 4 hours, and 8 seconds =P I forgot to turn it off last night when I fell asleep waiting for Cowboy Bebop to go on TV (in Cartoon Network's  Adult Swim , who would've known =P ), and so far 'Saturday Afternoon Fever' (a funny little animation from a guy at VFS), two trailers for 'Sky Captain and the Day After Tomorrow' (looks very promising, love the retro 30's style, and the guys at RSP.com.au are doing the graphics =P ), downloaded a few TV themes, updated (and added) a few people to my Examples folder, and am in the process of refreshing my 3Dnspiration issues (online magazine for 3D peeps).  So, yeah... It's all good   Art  Today, I've spent a lot of time redoing some of my old projects, like cleaning up some aliasing on my weekend challenge for Atlantis (the link below will have updated, and it's nothing major, my little nit picks) But, more recently, I have rejuvenated...  PEDRO!  Pedro's, I guess an oldish man, which I made in 3D. One of my first wades into the organic realm on my lonesome, and all my concept too. Here for your enjoyment is the good old man himself,  PEDRO!  =P     I have a sketch of him, which I used in initial construction, but in an artistic sense it's pretty hideous, so it's not linked here =P   I also need to find a project to become dedicated too soon, or I'll go mad... Getting a project makes you focus your creative energy, and it'll make you work until you can get it right, because it means something to you... Like Sormann's  urlLink ThemePark World ! It is one of the funniest concepts I've seen, something to keep an eye on =P   Inspiration  This one isn't really a long winded, heavily articulated one, merely a few brim ideas... I got this idea while getting my sketchbook out of my bag, while mum was asleep infront of the TV on the couch, and my dog was asleep too... My dog woke up, so I quietly put him back to bed. When I finished grabbing my sketchbook, I noticed I didn't have my small lamp, and didn't want to turn on the large light, so I snuck back across the lounge room into the corridor and finally into my bedroom to claim the lamp... After having a quick duel with my Lord of the Rings Return of the King poster, I snuck down quietly in the dark and begin the tedious task of finding which cord was the lamp's. When I finally found it, I yanked it out, only to find it was the wrong one, nabbit... Then, I finally found the one, and softly pulled, as if worried a giant spark'll leap out and engulf me. That was when I got the idea. What about an extremely successful thief, of extreme expertise, who is in the middle of a project. He's sorting out which is what, and finally thinks hes got it, when the most unlikely situation arises and he is caught (even though it's not his fault). He ends up working for the people who caught him, probably the government, and ends up meeting a 'baddie', who, in his words 'You can't steal the planet!' "Exactly, that's why I don't want anyone else to have it...", ie, this baddie is the kind who blows up anything he can't have, ie, the world =P I can imagine it now, episode one is introducing the main thief, working his way into a top secret facility, hiding among the shadows while people run past (have him slink into the shadows, and have 2D cutouts with a projected shadow onto the ground/wall run past), and finally getting caught unexpectedly, with the last shot being the alarms starting to go off and the look of complete disbelief (I mean, really, he's an experienced thief, but part of that experience is having  never gotten caught ! He doesn't know how to react! lol) Episode 2, introduction to the 'Justice Gang' I guess it's the policeish guy who basically plots him against all evil, fire against fire sort of thing, and probably the good old nerd like Nigel (sp?) off of Alias! WooT WooT! (can have an extra sequence about having the Nigelesque character saying it was his technology that caught the thief, and then after the extremely disconcerning look from the thief, have him splutter something like 'Yes, well, of course, a lot of luck was involved afterall...')  And there are the first two episodes, created in probably less than 30 minutes, in a nutshell =P  Also, for my first animation project I think I'm planning to do a sort of complexified sphere, with arms extruded out and probably two eyes just to add that 'human' factor to it... Something so simple it's gotta work... =P lol I hope to have this animation done by the end of holidays, which will give me three weeks to work on it (and since, as I said in my previous post, I have no plans, it should be pretty easy =P)  Anyway, that shall be the night for me, at least, the night recorded in this journal. I plan to do some odds and ends, and then eventually go to sleep *sigh* and, for the sake of my computer and my ISP, disconnect the bloody internet connection! lol
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      And they just started...  I'm literally on the verge of tears... I know I should try and keep all my posts positive, but that just isn't going to work here...  I've just started holidays and lets look upon what the world has put forth. My parents are growling at each other, as per usual, I don't have _any_ plans for the holidays apart from braces (oh, great...), two of my best friends I can't really communicate with (both without computers, one's grounded, the other, well), and generally I feel like complete... yeah...  In these times, one of the main problems is that we dwell on all the bad things, it's almost like we're trying to give ourselves a reason to feel so bad. Personally, I still do it, but if I want to feel bad, chances are I'm not inflicting damage on anyone but myself, and so I have the ultimate control in decisions of mood. I usually only break down at home, I don't think I've ever broken down at school, at least since Year 3...  I'd love to ask  the girl  out, but I just keep putting artificial limits on myself. And, I mean, there's a difference between sitting here and saying 'She'd probably say yes' and standing next to her, the mind reverting to another answer...  Okay, I don't like how I feel at the moment, so, this I must ENDETH!   Creativity, a good pick-me-up  After picking up some of my old txt documents, blowing the digital dust off them, and having a revising read, I feel inspired, ish =)  Actually, I'm not so inspired   To disappear  I'm going to disappear for a bit, go read some Elysiun stuff... Sorry for such a short post (even though, as I said a million times before, no-one's reading)
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I started off the stupid line above depressed, but all the sudden I became happy =P At least it's good practice, see things from the other way they were meant to be viewed. Get kicked in the groin, at least you can join the Boys Choir, etc etc =)  Anyway, something which I'm trying to persevere and cultivate in my head is that it's the quantity of ideas, not the quality, that is important. It is better to have lots of strange ideas, all different in their own right, than one or two extremely defined and carved idea, as you can always continue concentrating and improving a thought, but you can't get the same inspiration you had at that very moment back, and that may just be the difference between a smoking crater in the ground or your science experiment (made that up on the spot, a little OT, but just deal =P)  I do also note I have been negligent in my blogging performance, therefore I apologise to the ghosts or umbrae reading my blog, since no humans seem to be =P   School  Got a Distinction in Computing, whoop diddy. The main thing I remember about getting it was putting my mind in a blender to try and find a way of getting out of the middle of an isle without annoying anyone else. Luckily, I was adjacent to a walking corridor (well, not really a corridor, just a gap in all the chairs to walk through), so I pulled my seat out into the corridor and walked along it, therefore not annoying anyone else and having to leap over others feet =P Even one of the girls noticed my 'heroic' attempts and criticised someone else in our row for not doing the brave and daring maneuver.  Had parent teacher, overall, very happy with it. Main criticism was 'Stephen can't rely on his natural ability anymore...' Darn, they're forcing me to study now =P lol Was very pleased with my English teacher though, she told me that the story I wrote in the exam (had like 40 minutes), the nightmare one I talked about earlier, really revealed a 'light and fluffy' side to me (she didn't say light and fluffy, just thought it was the perfect description lol)  Everyone was expecting a futuristic, techno, over the top, serious, etcetera, story from me, and instead they got a romantic comedy, and NO, I didn't plan to write a romantic comedy, it just... Happened... Pretty good while starting from the word 'Nightmare', huh? =P   Shrek 2  Saw Shrek 2 on the weekend, was crammed into a tiny spot at the back of the room as we were late lol I had a very kind girl next to me (I also had to help give her back her handbag, it was accidently kicked to the left as my mum walked through the isle) and her annoying (what I thought) boyfriend, who kept complaining about the smallest things, like a child crying a bit, and babbling about the Box Office returns of the movie.  About the movie though, I liked the story overall, but they may have to create a new story soon as they're beginning to massacre it. Graphics, as per usual, were excellent, especially with the implementation of global illumination in all rendering and that of fast subsurface scattering, made some of the characters at least the quality of Final Fantasy imho. Of the main two things I remember is a mushroom splashed in a potion, which, from one corner of it, becomes cocooned in an aura, and then puffs into smoke and becomes a rose. I also loved how Shrek was played out as a human.  AND ABOUT MOVIES IN GENERAL A few of the biggest movie names, I'm using Scary Movie and Shrek & Sh-2 as examples, are making huge amounts off of a mock plot. While Shrek may have a bit of a deeper plot, a lot of it is made enjoyable by the mocking of other stories, such as the Lord of the Rings and other legends or myths in Shrek 2, or the use of scary movies and completely mock playing them such as in Scary Movie. These have all made giant gains at the box office, and are not to be underestimated.   Creativity  Thinking about creativity also, I think I prefer making full worlds as the larger the world, the more things I need to make to exist within it, and therefore the more ideas I am able to generate. Small disconnected ideas are fine, but this makes the idea seem to have a depth around it, as if it does come from somewhere, by the ways it links to other things. Stuart has really fallen in love with my story about a flying world (project name is Aerial Spires, and a beginning story of it is below) The whole world is beginning to be based upon Hallows Peak, and it has become partially destroyed during a war. Stuart and I may be planning to make a story based around it, but how far it will get (whether it gets anywhere at all lol) is questionable =P  'The only power I believe in comes out of the barrel of a gun' A quote from the movie 'The Phantom' (on in background) Well, that's an interesting statement. A society based around settling all of their affairs through singular gunfights, almost in a Western style, but I've never been a fan of Westerns =P Singular gunfights being one on one warfare, with great dishonour coming from having outside help. Preferably these gunfights aren't a one shoot kill kind of thing, but a way that the world becomes partially seperated into certain clans, and one clan's actions may have a reverberated effect on all else. Well, that's weird enough at least =P Then of course, you have either the singular hero, or an ungoverned group, a group not associated with any others, a group with no bounds.  Or you could have a singular hero, and a servant of him, who will take his place once he falls... Imagine it now, the hero is draped and hidden, but with a strange gun clutched in his right hand, elongated to look almost like a blade, and engraved with a symbol of a tiger, with claws upfront, ready to strike. The gunfight starts, everyone moving in a dash, dust is beginning to build up in the air untill almost all you can see is the wake left behind the movement of the bullet. Suddenly, *chink, chink*, he's out of bullets, so he almost slides to a corner of a building. There, his servant is waiting for him, with bullets dangling from clips on his shoulders, and a vest full of armaments on him. There, he does a last check of the golden bullets, tipped with a translucent blue, and with the speed of lightning, drops them into a clip and passes it to the hero, where he succinctly replaces his ammo and returns to the fight.  If you could only see the dust and bullets echoing inside my head... =P   STUART  One of my best friends, and a great buddy when it comes to creativity, has been GROUNDED... ahhhhhhhhhhh..... Why you ask? Because he forgot to hand an assignment in on one day. His mom is an authoritarian, very very rigid, and because of this he has been grounded, at the very least, for the whole of holidays. DARN!
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Screw everything else, music's going great...  [babble mode] On Wednesday afternoon I missed out on last period to go and get fitted for my Jazz suit. Oh yeah, love missing out on school! It ended up being black pants, shirt, with a silver tie and vest. (silver was highly reflective, I'm sure I was aiming to blind a few people when the spotlights hit me)  On Thursday morning, I woke up, got prepared awfully slow and then was driven to our Musical Showcase venue. I arrived at the venue (late) and had to whip my instrument out extremely quickly as everyone was about to start.  Fantastic rehearsal for jazz, my only two issues was I had to play up, and play, in Justin's words, "LOUDER!" One of the guitarists got a wibble-wa peddle (very weird =P ) and ended up using it for his solo improv. Around 9:30 we packed up, left for school at 10 after when the bus arrived. When I got back to school, I didn't go to class, I went to something called Musica Viva (not sure on spelling), and listened to that. Great jazz artists, the one who played trumpet/trombone was a hippy with eyebrows that looked a bit like Guy Sebastian's hair, another was an old man who always played the cello with eyes closed, the percussionist was generally cool, very quiet though, and the final guy had a trim haircut and wore glasses, he played sax. Anyway, got out of there, had recess, got back to my first and only class of the day, and that was... Music! =P Unfortunately, we got a replacement teacher and just sat around doing sheets, but then just before 12:30 we left for the next bus. Luke and I caught this one, and we listened to his Christian rock on the way down... Good to know Christians know how to write songs! =P When we arrived there Intermediate Band was on first, so I went and watched Luke play. He was extremely bored, as the majority of his notes were single handed and crotchets. We're actually thinking of making me play it, as I need to learn piano, and, well, reality's the best way to learn =) Next was flute ensemble *insert sleeping sound here* They weren't actually that bad, but my ex-girlfriend is one of them, so of course I've got to pretend to be bored lol And then, we were on... WOOT! Senior Concert Band, conducted by the awesome Hutch (don't worry, it's a nick name for our teacher =P ). The band performed fabulously, apart from the small situation involving the oboe-ist and the Pizza guy (his sister was supposed to pay for the Pizza, but, well =P ) Anyway, I was supposed to go back to school then, but the bus was filled with Junior school kids (shove them in the baggage compartments!), so we had to wait until the bus came back... That was a very long time, excessive to the extreme. I ended missing out on all of last period. After that, I went to the bus stop to *sigh* 'hang out' *sigh*, and everyone's bus turned up in the first 5 minutes (Thursday remember, shopping spree night lol) and after saying bye to Elyse (Elyce, Elise, spelling *sigh*) and to Josh, and giving her a chip packet, I went in the library. God knows what I did in there, something to do with raytracing and trying to find out how to calculate translucency utilising a similar technique to ambient occlusion I think... Anyway, finally got picked up. When we got there I went to Orchestra rehearsal. Boring. Orchestra isn't the greatest unfortuntely, we played Mission Impossible  again  for like the 2nd year in a row, and a song called Finlandia from the Babe movie. Wow, some way to start a show.  Start of the performance we played the two Orchestra songs, it was alright, nothing fantastic though. Then I had to wait until past second intermission, when we play Senior Concert Band and Jazz... So, I went up looking for Luke (he said we'd wait around together), couldn't find him, so I hung out with Anistasia, a friendly girl in Year 10 I think, plays the clarinet. Then, she found her friends, I saw Sophie and Jenny and I hung out with them for a while.  After 15 minutes, it was interval, I got prepared for Senior Concert. It was an absolute BLAST! Only problem was 9/10ths of the crowd went home because they were in Junior School... Oh, hurray... They should lock the doors lol The song we played was Pablo, fast, sharp, and absolutely a lot of fun to play, the kind of song that gives you an adrenaline rush. Went back, I changed (with lots of difficulty) to the suit I'd gotten on Wednesday, and was teased by probably every single student, and even by Hutch, our conductor/teacher/generally cool guy, he did the whole mother thing where he got my tie and straightened it and fixed it up *sigh* lol Justin ended up wearing "shades", and so did the drummer (he also wore suede, cool huh?)  THEN! Jazz! Started off with "This Ain't Love", a 1930s style swing song, usually used for dancing back then. We began playing into our stands, quiet, muffled, then blew EVERYONE away! =) Fantabulous, absolutely excellent, always fun. Then we played "Blue Bossa", which is once again another great piece, and I can almost play all of it lol This song was Justin's solo chance, lots of fun. After this, we were supposed to leave and go home, but the guys had planned to break into "Chameleon" after, unfortunately the crappy music to fill the gaps started, and we had to wait for them to switch it off. Once that happened, we waited around for about 10-15 bars playing it, then packed up and went home. And I was told on the next day Hutch made kissy faces to Luke and Lauren (my friend, who's going out with Lauren *der* as they were sitting next to each other). Luke at the moment is attempting to avoid Hutch, with little success! =P lol  Friday - *phew* No-one really congratulated me, but that's alright, no-one usually does lol I ended up cutting my inner lip or causing some kind of unfathomable pain in my mouth Generally went back to school *sigh*  But the main pick up that night, was, I went to the  Lord of the Rings Symphony  at the Opera House! We got there early, I 'dined' on two hot dogs and some plain rice, and strolled around admiring how big the Opera House was. Even though I'm an Australian, the last (and only other than now) time I went there, I was four and all I really remember of it was sitting outside, very bored and cold, waiting for intermission so we could get back in...  Anyway, it began in an excellent manner, with Howard Shore being a... quite interesting? conductor... He actually conducted on off-beats I think, or something strange like that. I have four pages of notes beginning at the end of intermission. It was an excellent performance, get the soundtrack! =P Also, I discovered that there is a crushed car at the Opera House, crushed by a rock with a smilie face... Quite peculiar...  Anyway, it's 11:04 on Sunday now (I kind of got to finish this last night) and I'm going to sum up Oh yeah, yesterday I got an electronic compass for my Robot *woot*  Bai Bai
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Your heart suddenly has an urge to become a drum, your pupils think it'll be funny if they dilate, and your world becomes a little confused about which way's up... Well, that's how it generally feels when she walks by =) Words cannot describe such a feeling, but words have never been much good anyway =)  Stuff keeping details to a minimum... I don't think anyone has read this journal yet, so stuff it, it's a journal for myself! =P I know a crush usually occurs due to a physical attraction (which is certainly the case lol) but she does have some depth to her. She takes Latin, which is difficult, and is very kind, although a little shy =) I know, this is all really small stuff and probably doesn't mean anything to anyone but me... But... Well... In a way, I'm my main audience, so if you really want, skip to the next section, cuz I'm going on =P She had her books in my way this morning, and she said in the sweetest way "Oh, sorry"... Yes, very very small, but... Yeah =P I guess what I really like about her is she isn't outspoken, she's not zany, she's not loud, she's just, in the best possible description, seems a little shy =) I doubt she likes me unfortunately, and if I really want to a go, and ask her out, I may have to take a very very large leap. But before any of that, I just need to make some sort of small connection... I remember reading in an entry to CGTalk's 'Lost and Found' sketch competition, a little picture. Supposedly someone lost their gym card in the university dormitory hall, so he went to return it to the room number. He knocked on the door, and out popped the a fabulously beautiful girl... Well, that would be the perfect, absolutely heavenly, sort of way to connect to her for the first time. Of course, that's implying that anything like that happens out of Hollywood movie sets or children's stories, and even then the guy who met the girl didn't go out with her, but was merely 'haunted by her beauty' or something to that effect. Well, chances are it's never going to happen, but I'll find a way... I mean, it couldn't be worse than a million to one chance, or at least perfectly equal to it =P   Never play leap-frog with a unicorn, Murphy's Law states. This beautiful unicorn may make me break that golden rule...    urlLink       ----  Firefox 0.9 came out today =P I've already downloaded it and am going to install it after I finish this post. If you're getting sick of Microsoft, or Internet Explorer crashes on you/attacks you with spyware, go to  urlLink Mozilla.org  and try either Mozilla or Firefox out (Firefox looks a lot better and is much more slimline)  ----  I'm failing in my attempt to use every moment to its fullest. But I'll try to keep the practical part of the theory in full effect, no matter which way the coin falls... I just need something to get me moving again!  ----   Creativity  I just noticed something, all my ideas are based on quality. They should be based on quantity, because you can always develop an idea later down the track, but you may only have the stimuli at that moment to create an imaginary masterpiece. To help me develop a new way of innovation, I have enlisted the help of a random word website. Very random, not punctually random =P I'll take the first ten and try and write down what comes to head first, creative or non-creative.  ( urlLink site for random words )  Damn! Site's out at the moment due to DNS problems affecting the net (Slashdot story ( urlLink here )  New temporary word generator here -  urlLink Word Generator   This isn't quite as good as the other, as the other generates random words, this just generates made up words... But what the hey =P      * handian - An ancient culture who live ontop of the vast forests of floating sea-weed. The sea-weed growth is so thick that it creates a hard surface for them to survive on.     * rendeleckilopetels - (rend-el-ec-il-o-pet-els) A telepathic condition that the gods give some humans for their own amusement. Rendeleckilopetels allows you to see that you will injure yourself, but not how, therefore making you know you are going to hurt yourself with no preventitive measures! For example, you may know you are going to feel an intense 'pain' in your crotch, but you don't know exactly what'll cause it, so they avoid angry women, baseball balls, and any projectiles, until, when still trying to avoid everyone, he doesn't pay attention to the ground, and a man hole remains open. He falls, and... Well... You know =P     * pennelisits - I won't say what FIRST came to my head... This is strictly a PG13 site ;) A covert group of pencils who write propoganda, with topics similar to 'We're all wood you know' 'You'll never sharpen me alive' and an all time favourite 'Freedom to the LED!'     * ting -      * menter - It is the capacity that an object has to indirectly change the future of the world. If it has a high menter rating, for example, a nuclear bomb, it can instill a huge change, while a blade of grass may have a low level of menter.     * counkers -      * impingler - A person who makes a living by stealing barbed wire from prisons. These people are therefore indirectly responsible for a large percentage of successful prison escapes.     * ackiddentiont - A young      * dwely -      * belly -   ----   MUSIC SHOWCASE TOMORROW!  Music Showcase, when all the schools bands come together and perform. I have very high expectations for Senior Band, and ESPECIALLY Jazz Band =P Don't have quite too high expectations with Orchestra, but that's just because Mr Hutchins's such a great conductor, and musician in his own right =)   Center stage is set, the lights are focusing on you, and it's time to discover just what I'm made of!   The best thing though, of course, is I miss out on lots of school because I'll be going to the Hills Centre during the day to do final rehearsals and sound checks! WOOT! I also took last period off today to get a black suit/tuxedo type thing, to wear when we play in Jazz band. I was only told this morning, and kind of had to... Rush? =P Hopefully I'll fit in, but I am wearing silver, and spotlights on silver might blind a few people *sigh* Oh well =P And I have been getting a lot better with my music. I can play almost all of my jazz band pieces without fudging a single note (fudging in bands is a  lot  more common than you think). Heck, Justin hasn't even insulted me for the last few days =) (Justin is first trombone, in charge of being bossy and talented =P )  ----  Another night finished... Good night, and I wish you a happy future =)
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My idea on trying to use every moment to it's fullest is on a kind of confusing verge. I don't know if it's working too well, could just be me. Either way, I'm still persevering with it, even though it isn't going too well =)  /me crosses fingers in hope of a new speed modelling topic at CGTalk  *sigh* Not a new subject... AGAIN! I can't take this. I need something to push me. The Weekend Challenge really did a good job, even if the result didn't turn out too well. It pushes you just to MAKE SOMETHING... Must stop sitting around and complaiming.  Just giving a link to myself - SUPER COOL FERRET MADE IN XSI!   urlLink Mr Ferret ;)   Anyway, SPEED MONSTERS! =P Quick 3D models I made, took about 20 minutes each   *heeheehee*  Watching Alias, and guess what... We just discovered, the Passenger... It's her... *horror music* SISTER! *background scream* Yeah, well... I knew about it before, because E! News doesn't respect the fact Australians are like two months behind all the TV shows... *sigh* lol... Also, Von found out that the Australian actress (oh yeah, go Aussies! Melissa George RULES! *innocent whistle*) was a double agent! WooT! They killed Sloan! WooT! Jack revived Sloan! Wait a sec... Eh? =P  Stui has been helping me out since this morning when I told him about the "Aerial Spire" thing (just remember, that the name is only a working name, not final), and its been quite fun =P We could become a double team of writers! WooT!  I've got a terrible terrible cough, which isn't getting anything out of my throat, but more specifically it feels like razors being run down the insides of my throat... Ouch... I stayed up until literally 4 AM yesterday (or more specifically, this morning) and went through three episodes of BBC Lord of the Rings Audio Series.  It's 10:30, and Alias just finished. Anyway, time to go, for the night draws close, and the world is beginning to withdraw. Farewell
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Every moment should be used. No excuse. Procrastinating is not an option. This is a purely raw theory I'm spitting out, so it may seem crude, but I trust you, it is not. Everything must be a stepping stone to something else. Waste not on things which have no destination. You must push yourself, for if you do not push yourself, nothing will ever come out of you. You cannot rely on the world around you to do the pushing for you, because it will not happen. People who succeed in this life do so as they push themselves, or if they don't push themselves, they do something lots because they love the thing they do.  The main problem with my blog at the moment is that the ideas are so refined, I write, read, rewrite, everything I think. This should be a null issue now. Pure essence is what makes a character. In real life you don't have time to think a comment, rethink it, do it again, so why should you as you are writing? From now on I will cease to use the Preview button (as technologically cool it is) on all things, other than to check that link or image tags work.  I cannot slow down, or not keep pushing myself. Pushing myself will force me to do things I have not done before, which is good. One thing which I did stop writing for then, is for a moth. A moth landed on my computer screen, I think they're attracted by the static electricity on it, or merely the bright light, but I'm not sure. It had the most magnificent texture on it, and was brown, the colour of sandpaper, and was translucent in a fuzzy kind of way. As he was inside, and they don't survive very long, I softly got him in my hands, made a protective sphere, and released him outside through the dog door.  Always have time in your life for creatures that need help, even if it's a spider, snake, or anything.  I'll also mention my tadpoles at the moment. I saved them in December I think. Their eggs were put in a dam after heavy rain. Problem is, the dam is a quick drain dam, and all the water in there is gone after a few weeks. I found out they were up there, and knew they were going to die without my help. I went and got a bucket and began sorting the water. Spiders, some weird kinds of leeches, and weird insects which looked like leaves annoyed me, but I kept going. Today, I have saved countless lives of tiny tadpoles, and as small as that may seem, it is significant to me, and I'm sure that in the far future it will make some difference. Just remember, if you save one thing, you are therefore saving all it's descendants, so in the act of saving one tadpole, you may have just saved hundreds, if not thousands of frogs. And if the act of even saving ONE life is not significant, I ask you then, what is?   Every moment  Every moment you should be giving your hundred percent all. Everything you have is sitting there waiting to be used, and even if every limb you have is broken, you should still be thinking all the time. Trying to sort the world into logic, trying to observe everything you see.  Pick up a leaf and see everything there is to see. Notice the bumps? The veins? The translucency (that's light getting through the object, like transparency (like glass) but you can't nessacarily see straight through, if you know what I mean), the colours. Everything! Everything in this world is infinitely complex. Your body changes every atom it is made of in 8 years. The simplest thing still has a myriad of rules about it. Nothing is too small to be observed.  Everything observed is easy from someone else's point of view. You never know how complex a job is until you do it yourself.   Everything has an essence  A picture is just an array of colours, and hues if it contains no essence. Essence is what separates a picture from an illustration. An illustrator is from the Latin verb "lustrare", which literally means to illuminate.  urlLink This site  has influenced me in such a strange way. Look at it, respect the artwork, respect the brother who has passed to the other side. An illustrator, literally illuminates a person, gives them an amazing idea, redefines a thought, something of great meaning. To be an illustrator can relate to any part of your life, not just art.   Relaxing to some degree  Okay, I have to smile at least once as I write this =) Remember, that without other people, your development as a person, as an artist, cannot grow. I'd like to end this weird section and go into creativity by saying, enjoy everything you do, or try to find some way to do it. Even the worst task can be a competition of how fast you can get it done! Also,  ask yourself, "ARE YOU SERIOUS!" Of which, I shall always reply, "YES!"     Creativity  Ok, straight from talking about being spontaneous and quick thinking to doing it.  Veins. Hands. Blood rushing back and forth. Life. Essence. Birth of the world. Everyone must come from somewhere, everyone must have a story before themselves. Everything has an origin, of which it is almost always complex and confusing. Respect it for it.  Must try to find an aim. Instead of shooting bullets wildly into the night, try to find a target and aim not to shoot blanks.  Wait, before even that I have to find out what exactly I want out of creativity. New ideas? Strong characters? Realistic plot? WHAT?  Dictionary.com, Creativity - Characterized by originality and expressiveness; imaginative: creative writing. This essentially means creating anything. Including a short story, which I may as well do now.   Aerial Spire  The world as we know it, is no more. Recreate the world, remold it. The human race has not had a massacre, and had to rebuild itself, merely that the world has never had to go along that certain path. High above the ground, hidden within the deepest breaches of the clouds, are great aerial fortresses. Helium is the life force, keeping their world afloat, while hydrogen, created by splitting the water of the clouds, is their movement. Some people live in a settlements of thousands of people, the metropolis's of the skies. They are similar to countries. They all have their own way of subsistence. Their own economies, and their own rulers. Then, there are two kinds of free-rangers. First, is the traders, who usually move in small groups of vessels, from metropolis to metropolis, and survive through trading. Then there is the rogues. People who live by pillaging others. They commonly target the small traders, but some have vessels large enough to take on, and often beat the metropolises.  Well, that's good babble. Not really going anywhere though. I wonder how you develop such an idea... Only probably by practice. Exams are good for that, they force you to work in a small timeframe and give a reasonable result out of it. The computer may actually be working against you, as it gives you a world of options on what to do, yet when you're in an exam, with a pen, some paper, and only 45 minutes remaining on the clock, you cannot spare to waste anything.  The airship began it's slow crawl across the sky, leaving a tiny vapor trail in it's wake. In the cockpit of the vessel, sat an old man, with a cane across his lap. On the top of the old man's cane, engraved into the wood, was a sculpture of an eagle, with two gems for it's eyes. He was staring out into the calm blue sky, wandering what it would be like. Whether it was still the way it had used to be. The silence was broken, by the energetic sound of someone running up the spiral stairs from the lower hold behind him.  "Grandpa, where's our next stop?" He turned slowly in his chair, and looked through his spectacles to his grandson. The boy was growing to be more like his father every day. "You have heard of the haven of Hallows Peak before, haven't you?" "Hallows Peak? Are you serious? Wasn't that where the Kailen Wars took place?" "Yes it was. Just remember that a war doesn't just involve guns and explosions, but people too." "What're we going there for then? They have the best of everything don't they?" "They  used  to have the best of everything, remember the hydrogen cells we've been making? I have an old friend there who makes them. He'd be very interested in our new design." "Tell me about Hallows Peak grandpa, you've been there before haven't you?" "Not just been there, I used to live there. That was where I met your grandmother." "Was dad born there?" "No, your father was born on this very vessel. We left Hallows Peak almost fifty years ago now." "But why'd you leave Hallows Peak! It's part of legends! It's, it's, it's..." "It's the tallest mountain on all of Earth, and the only habitable bit of land left on this world..." "Why'd you leave then?" "The war came." "Yeah, and?" "The war took your mother, your father, and my wife. You were the only one left..." They both stared out the windshield, into the clouds, where, if one had the eyes of a hawk, one would have seen a glittering peak, covered in a permafrost that has been there since the dawn of time. Neither of them were really paying too much attention to the sky though, mainly to how to avoid the next step of logical conversation. Breaking the silence had a feeling similar to that of dropping a glass vase. "How long until we get there?" the young boy muttered silently under his breath. "About half an hour. How about you go and get the cell ready?" "No problem," The boy ran down the spiral stairs, and the sound began to fade away.  The haven of Hallows Peak is believed to be the last bit of habitable land for humans. It is the center of the civilised world, and is real estate which only the richest can afford. Being the only bit of land left in the world, it has commonly come under attack, the worst of which being the Kailen Wars. Half the peak was ripped off of it's foundings, and plunged to doom, by a cruiser's suicidal attack.  (first sentence, wake is used in boats, slipstream in aeroplanes, but I'll use wake still, as the airship is slow, more like a boat than a plane) {second, [Middle English halwen, from Old English hlgian. See kailo- in Indo-European Roots.], Hallows Peak, to Kailen Wars) (third, possibly add in a necropolis to the mix, a floating city that had been wiped out by a threat [dragons burning all the city?] but it mysteriously floats. It is said to be cursed, and no-one has gone there since, or at least none have returned to tell of the story)  I'd love to continue the story, but it's time for me to "go to bed"... In other words, that means pretend to be asleep, but more essentially go to my room and do my homework. I really love this world so far. I really really do =)  This post has been amazingly successful, and it actually takes me a while to scroll down through all the babble! Farewell, and may we meet again at the haven of Hallows Peak.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A tug-a-war has begun over my life. On one side, depression, the other side, happiness... And may I just say, they are evenly matched at the moment =) I'm disappointed with my Weekend Challenge entry, but nonetheless, here it is     I'll post @ndy's (@ndy is a great 3D artist) entry when he finishes it, but I shall warn you now, @ndy rules =P His site is at  urlLink Artificial3D.com  if anyone wants to have a look. Purely inspirational artist, and he reminds me of LohnC (Australiain Blenderer who I know well)  I haven't been too happy with the results of that... Not sure if it's the bad post processing, or whether its just me, but yeah... This is the main reason I want to keep working on my computer graphics, my sketching, my everything. I want to be able to look at myself some day in the future, and say, "You are a good artist"... When you say something like that to yourself, you know whether or not you are bending the truth...  In other news, great thread by an artist called buzzz3d (although he's a 2D artist lol), of which he is trying to force himself to draw everyday. Good idea... Good idea...  urlLink Thread here   Also, I'm being driven around the bend... The Brady Bunch have been on TV1, mucking up all regular programming, for the last THREE DAYS! That's SEVENTY-TWO HOURS AT LEAST of Brady Bunch   Here endeth the previous babble...  Well, as the LONG weekend draws to an end, and we thank the Queen for having a birthday (whether or not we care about the Queen, go public holidays!), we must look back and reflect... Reflect upon the world, and it's being... And remember that, no matter how long a rest period we may receive, remember that, I HAVE HOMEWORK! ARRRGGGGG!  *sigh*  I really don't quite manage time the way "I should"... I use it quite well I think, but I usually leave unimportant things to the last minute (for example, _homework_) I always do it, no matter what. And if the homework is going to take time to finish (like a writing assignment), I WILL start that earlier. Assignments, I occasionally start before the night before it's due, but that's a rarity ;)  This kind of concludes my report for today. I'm not pleased with it... So, I'm going to go check what homework I have and then, either finish now or finish it midnight plus tonight, and then learn how to rig a 3D object (or, in my hope, an object that'll soon become a character)  Also, I'm running out of ways to say farewell, goodbye, or good night... So...  Out of the shadows I shall return, to reclaim my lost home... Farewell...
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have been very negligent with Blogger, but at the same time very busy =) Ok, after checking my last post, I haven't been  that  negligent, only 3 days lol Long weekend this weekend, and I've decided to participate in Elysiun's Weekend Challenge (given the topic "Atlantis", I'll show you the results soon enough)   Enanami  Enanami is still going strong, the map is getting small bits and pieces thrown onto it. Some are of purely original merit, others influenced by TV shows (I was watching "The Seven Great Wonders (of the) Industrial World", featuring the lighthouse constructor Robert Stevenson), and others are taken from my previous ideas (remember, I  never  steal other peoples ideas, very heavily against my morals) Really, from a few random squares, scribbling at the points they meet up, you can create a situation to let your mind wander. The best thing though is that it even lets your logical mind, not just creative, to wonder, as it is considering what could happen at a given location (near a volcano, etcetera)   Robert Stevenson  "You cannot build a lighthouse on a rock that is submerged for the better part of the day and receives gails at every other time!" said the Chief Executive of the Northern Lighthouses.  Oh boy was he wrong. Robert Stevenson became the builder of a lighthouse (Bell Rock, completed on the 1st of February 1811, which stood 11 miles out to sea) which saved dozens, if not hundreds, of lives. He had originally wanted to do it as ships crashed upon it regularly, but it was not until an English Navy vessel ran upon it, and thus lost all of its 300 crewman, that the Northern Lighthouses Association supported him financially to do so. He not only calculated the angle (although there is disagreement if it was nessacarily him or John Rennie who decided it, and of whom designed the lighthouse) but also developed an amazingly bright array of lights, utilising parabolic dishes and by using many different techniques integrated (like putting a tube over the candle, therefore making it burn brighter by using the convection currents it makes)  Either way, both Robert Stevenson, John Rennie and the crew who built the mighty monument, deserve a mention. As do many other people on this greater Earth...   urlLink About Bell Rock, and who built it... This is made by (and using the same picture as) the people who made the TV documentary I saw (BBC)   urlLink About Robert Stevenson (BBC)   urlLink A more fulfilled biography on Robert Stevenson    Personalities  A Slashdot article recently came up with something quite interesting. It relates to me in some ways, some ways may I note, but I never flunk subjects (getting the equivalent to Ds or Es, which would be 60 or 70% correct? Sorry, Australian schools usually only give percentages), I always do reasonably well (around 90% most of the time)  urlLink Slashdot Article  It also ended up giving a link to an interesting site detailed types of personalities,  urlLink The site, with example personality   And, as usual, if you look down, you'll see the hundreds of Slashdot comments, a place where the occasional drop of wisdom can be found (and starcraving lunacy at all other times =P)   this "stick-to-it-ness"...    TENACITY!  It's called tenacity! I swear, the next grade-school teacher who I hear use the word "stick-to-it-ive-ness" is getting a swift and painful English lesson.  Seriously! It's a syllable shorter! Let's do a comparison! (In list form, because Slashdot's support for preformatted text is bad.)     1. Is it a real word?           * Tenacity: Yes, and a good one as well!           * Sticktoitiveness: No, and it never will be.    2. How many syllables does it have?           * Tenacity: Four. Rolls right off the tongue.           * Sticktoitiveness: Five. It's an ungainly hippo-in-a-tutu of a word.    3. Does it make you sound like a Special Ed teacher when you use it?           * Tenacity: Not in the least.           * Sticktoitiveness: Yes, if not straight-up retarded.   Stamp out sticktoitiveness wherever you see it. It's the red-headed stepchild of the English language...  lol  Of other points noted in there, intelligence is useless without dedication, "We all say that intelligence is the highest achievement, but that's not entirely true. Intelligence is distinct from knowledge, which is distinct from dedication. All three are necessary for success.", there's a lot of "unusually smart people" out there, "You are a unique and beautiful snowflake. Snowflake number #3857493 to be exact." lol, "Life is basically a vacation from death some author once said.", "Reiterating what many others have said, stop whining and prove your worth."  LONG!  "People tend to hold overly favorable views of their abilities in many social and intellectual domains. The authors suggest that this overestimation occurs, in part, because people who are unskilled in these domains suffer a dual burden: Not only do these people reach erroneous conclusions and make unfortunate choices, but their incompetence robs them of the metacognitive ability to realize it. Across 4 studies, the authors found that participants scoring in the bottom quartile on tests of humor, grammar, and logic grossly overestimated their test performance and ability. Although their test scores put them in the 12th percentile, they estimated themselves to be in the 62nd. Several analyses linked this miscalibration to deficits in metacognitive skill, or the capacity to distinguish accuracy from error. Paradoxically, improving the skills of participants, and thus increasing their metacognitive competence, helped them recognize the limitations of their abilities."  LONG! , "The fellow who edited your comment mentioned that you were probably an INTP. This is true; so am I. This means that you are devoted to finding logical solutions to problems, and are dreamy and absent-minded if you're not involved in something that interests you.", "Be prepared for your spirit to be crushed", "you can't call yourself something unless you can back it up", "You will have to focus and refine your talents to get anywhere. The ability to work really hard for a short time when you happen to feel like it won't help you any. Otherwise you will feel cheated when those without your "raw ability" whiz by you in life.", "My only advice would be to stop telling people you're "uniquely bright." It doesn't go over well. That kind of thinking is something you just keep to yourself...instead, demonstrate your intelligence through action. If you're interested in programming, I'd suggest picking a pet project and getting your hack on.", "Your talents will take you wherever they take you, but friendship will fill the gaps"   *phew*   As you can see, those are the SELECT comments from a Slashdot article. They have about 12-24 of those every day, and I try to read them all... Takes a long while... Some of the suggestions in there ARE novel, and will affect me for some time to come.   Robocup  I haven't mentioned this before, but I am involved in something called Robocup. It's essentially programming a small robot to play soccer =P I've participated for sometime now. I won't say too much more, other than this, since I need to remind myself something... GET A COMPASS! =P It is quite fun though. Realtime programming. Programming in a way that has to interact with all the inconsistencies of the real world. And I have a great team with me =) And this year may be the best year of them all!   Coding  Made some quite large steps with my coding. I have essentially all the theory for raytracing downpat, now just writing an implementation. The main problem I have at the moment is getting the right result returned lol. Working on it. The arrays seem to be a little wacky (or more specifically, I seem to be a little wacky with the arrays) lol I plan on writing a tutorial on Sourceforge ( urlLink http://www.sourceforge.net ), to exhibit the code and explain it in terms that I would have loved (I've been battling through explanations that quite literally take a degree in mathematics to solve). But that's all bee part of the fun I guess =)  Ideally I'd love to have various levels of raytracer construction (bare bones, diffuse shading, specular shading, reflection, refraction, etcetera etcetera) and also have a forum for everyone to talk to each other in (newbies with older people, all kinds of graphic theories merging together), and a version of the raytracer that will keep on growing, of which I will add ANYONE'S code if it does not break the raytracer and any previous functions, and also marks a small landmark. This will allow newbies to go in and see all the kinds of things people have developed.  I am also very peeved that a book called "Graphics Gems" has not been evenly partially published online. It has a whole chapter on Writing Raytracers, of which I've never seen, and probably never will, which every institution or programmer refers me to. Very agitating =)  Anyway, I just updated my WIP (work in progress) for the Weekend Challenge entry. I'll have finished (probably) by tomorrow...  Goodnight, and here's to hope... =)
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      On the next day, will I ever remember the world as it is? As it was? Every small detail, the houses I see, faces I should remember, the valiant pen fights with Stui, how I felt when I saw Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban for the first time. It's a tradgedy you never remember the small things. That's what I hope this diary will help out with, a vague recollection of events, enough to recreate a small world. They say that your life flashes before your eyes just as you are about to die. I personally think that's a little unfair, you've lived x amount of years, and for all those years, millions of hours, billions of seconds, you get a mere flash of your life? Or is it a Hollywood style moment when the world around you slows, and a million life times could fill that very second... And, if it is true you see your life flash before your eyes, is it a chain reaction of neurons sending off bursts of messages?  *phew* Babble babble babble...   School  Got a Distinction for computing... Oh, yay... 96th percentile of state... Oh, yay... Proves nothing worth knowing...  I should be getting skipped forward for computing studies anyway. Doing some online training courses, which should turn out useful.  And yep, still staring at my crush... Staring staring staring =P (and a theory has been proposed to me that I will never be "on the inside", but I rebutted the theory stating that I have never had an aim of being on the inside, and anyone worth discussion on the inside is therefore abducted out of it =P)  I also started on a map today, of a purely fictional world called Enanami. Quite amazing what a few random squiggles and ideas can turn into, a world full of rogue continents, Aganthean trading oceans, a single mine spanning over continents and the everpresent threat of the trade ships being raided by pirates =P   And now...  Now I'm up, with my mum sitting in the next room waiting for me to do my homework. Hmmm... I've finished memorising Latin (takes like 2 minutes), but, well, the rest'll take a while =P It's annoying, she's staying up of 'her own free will', and later dad will blame me for keeping her up. And she just said I have ten minutes. Ten minutes. I guess she doesn't know I stay up till midnight  every night  then. Neither does my dad. Just a hint for any adults reading out there, putting a limit on a teenager is like wrapping a noose around your own head, not smart nor suggested. I do go to bed at midnight every night, I know what my body and mind can take, yet they don't trust my own judgement.  No time for creativity tonight, but I think the map did the same task pretty well. Oh, and last night, while up at night drawing, I came up with the idea of a small figure (tribesman, and small meaning two inches) who religously sticks a fork into a 240V socket =P They believe that they are electrocuted by the mighty deities for a job well done on earth, and that the smoke rising from the steaming ashes/corpse is the soul finding it's final resting place =) Well, it's good to dream...  Anyway, fare the well for tonight, I have to work my way around parents/homework/music... It'll be fine though, it always works out in the end.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The moon lit the snowflakes like tiny chandeliers as they made their descent down to the ground. The wanderer walked the long path into the night, as the frost began to take hold. It was too late for him to turn back now, he had already strayed too far from home. He must hope the path he has taken will lead to a better end, and not one forever cold.  Stephen Merity, 7:27   That's generally how I feel at the moment. I just hope I haven't taken too many wrong choices so far, and that the hopes I lean on do not fall =) I'm pretty sure all hopes will hold, and if not, there will always be other things to grab before I fall!  I think I'm generally feeling like this because of two things. CG, computer graphics, output of the imagination, and something not going too well at the moment ;) And I have a crush on a girl... Girl girl girl... Geez lol... (notice the alliteration, repeated use of the letter g... right... too much English work at school =P) I'm not actually going to say who it is online, no knowing what kind of prying eyes see this (not general people, just possibly friends from school) but seeming that I don't think I've gotten any views I should be perfectly fine ;) Anyway, I barely know the girl, so yes, I'm attracted to her from the shallowness of my heart *sigh* But I'm hoping she has a smart spark, as she takes a quite difficult language at school, and mainly I guess it's just hope though... I haven't asked her out yet for a myriad of reasons -   Obviously shyness, grand characteristic =) - I'm not sure it'll work out, we're kind of different social groups - I'm not even sure if I want a relationship - Freaked she will say no (but of course, typical fear =) The last two girls I dated were quite a different matter. The first one I asked cuz my friend spilled on who I liked, and thought it would be better to straight out ask her than tip-toe around the whole issue, and the second asked me out, lots of work on my part =P) My self esteem on this subject is not the highest ;)  *babble babble babble*  Yeah... *phew* Girls *eek* =P (not eek in a " shes got girl-germs! " way, but in a " oh! I wanna ask her out but chances are a million to one, and then it isn't "Lived happily ever after" but more probably "Lasted two weeks before beginning a shout match at each other, then broke up in an explosive display that would make New Years Fireworks look like a set of sparklers"... darn " kind of way... Long explanation huh? =P)   Creativity  Well, today I'm going to start off with a word, go through a random picture archive on my computer, mix my thoughts with that and see how far that gets me =) Ready? =P    vade mecum  - A useful thing that one regularly carries about.  This reminds me so much of my sketchbook, it goes  everywhere  with me and is always on the verge of falling apart! =)  Okay. A guy in a gaol, carrying around a giant weight supposed to stop him getting away. Ice Troll was one of the images that came up from my archive... So... An ice troll... What do they need... lol, tissues!  A giant ice troll, living high in the mountains, composed mainly of gnashing teeth and bulging muscles, blowing his nose, cuz it gets damn chilly up there! Always the threat of a terrible cold, or even flu! =P That's weird enough for that =P   A quick other creative note  A group of three travellers have made their way into the marshes. Something is strange about these marshes tho, for water is always a degree from freezing, and a permanent frost grips the land. Later that night, one of the travellers was awoken by a strange sight. A glowing ball of fire, vaguely man shaped, but more of the sorts of a demon. He quickly awoke the wiser of the other two, "What's that! What do we do!" "Be quiet, he is of no risk to us at the moment. He is a permafrost beast, an Ice Cursor. They suck in the heat from the world around them, giving them life, form..." "Are they dangerous?" "Only if you are foolish. They are no raging beast, but if you are near them when they begin to burn out, you may find yourself frozen in seconds. They merely do not attack us now, for it would be too much trouble for them"  GO THE ICE CURSORS! =P   Anyway, that's it for today. Dinner is here (McDonalds =P)
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *Listening - Nothing, just got on*  Hm... You may notice I'm not pumped up and excited. Well, it's that time again! The world's crumbling around me, and I'm trying to not fall by clinging onto things that may not be there. To clear that up:    The world's crumbling around me  - To explain, my family is extremely confused at the moment. Believe what you will, but a smaller family doesn't make it any easier. The only time I see my dad is essentially when he tells me to go to bed or catches me up in the middle of the night. My mum isn't feeling well recently, stress seems to be getting her down. My best friend is having a rough time, but I'm not depressed about that, just a little worried. I was asked on the bus "How old I was" when they noticed I was reading an animation book (*hint hint* to illustrate some of the concepts they used cartoons...) I've got a crush on a girl who probably only notices I'm alive because I accidently nudge her with my locker (It's not her fault she doesn't know me though =) ) and overall, things are looking down.   I'm trying to not fall by clinging onto things that may not be there  - I'm hoping that by being a generally good person things should work out in the end. That theory is still under scrutiny though *sigh*. I'm also hoping that I'm good at CG. Or at least get better. Or discover some hidden interest. Something! Time will tell...   Anyway, =)   Exams  Got 19 out of 20 for my creative writing, and it wasn't prewritten! =) The given topic was "Nightmare", and I came up with an idea of a guy getting drunk, and waking up a few hours later to see a huge sparkling diamond on the finger of his girlfriend =) Marriage for him is one helluva phobia lol I think a majority of my marks would have come from some of the sentences like:   She gave him such a cute look that it made bunny rabbits seem aggressive =) Ryan walked into the kitchen, wearing a grimace that would make the dead feel sorry for him   Of course, these aren't the  exact  quotes, mainly because I haven't gotten the story back yet   Of beautiful people, conversations, arguments and romance  Beautiful people are commonly thought of as a little stupid, but is that true? My personal thoughts are that "normal people" usually spend much more time reading or something similar to that, even if they are quite active socially, but with "beautiful people" they spend a very large majority of their time on a superficial basis, parties, friends, walking around and showing off, etc. I wouldn't take me as the best resource by the way, just a personal theory =)  ----------  Conversations & Arguments I'd like to try and find out why the main conversations and arguments take place. Here's my small compiled list so far... (by the way, thought about this while on the bus)  Actually, I won't list them quite yet. I just noticed as I was writing them down I was making a sweeping generalisation in some of my comments. Not very realistic at all. But the main one is that people usually find things interesting if they are immediately related to themselves. For example, I asked on a mailing list, instead of "What should I do to get into the industry" I asked people "What would you do if you could start again?". From that, people listed a vast resource of things they HAVE done, and whether that worked, and what they WOULD have done, and how they thought that would work... Very thought provoking stuff they wrote  ----------   Romance, Romance, Romance  =) I'm always wondering how you should go by "romance" (instead of love, I use the word romance, because it isn't just love. Love doesn't come and go like the tide, and it doesn't relate to the lower level feelings like having a crush or an attraction etc)  Should you ask any and every girl you have a chance? Wouldn't that make you a little sluttish, and also, wouldn't you compare all the girls with other girls you have had before? Won't you just begin to expect more and more?  Should you wait on that one who you think is the dream of dreams? What happens when you find out you've been building her up in your head, having a fake perception of her? Or when they turn you down, and you've been thinking for all this time that she is the perfect? What then, fallen one?  Should you try to separate yourself completely?  Or should you wait till someone comes to get  you    In wrapping  My mum has just arrived, or will be arriving soon (I thought I heard her car, I guess I was wrong) there are about a  million things  fighting for attention in my head at the moment, and none are getting that which they deserve... Strange huh
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *Listening - Bring Me to Life  Oh man I love making up quotes =P That was pretty weak I assure you, but it's none the less a good way to start the post.    Exams  97.54% in Computing exam... Oh yay... =) Obviously you may notice my lack of enthusiasm. At my school, I don't seem to really have a choice to skip Years for my computing studies, but I am SO far ahead of everyone it isn't funny. *sigh* Time will tell...   Of midnight and drawing  At a few minutes before midnight last night, my dad caught me drawing... Dang eh? The really annoying thing is that I go to bed at midnight, that's  my  time to go to bed. If he had come in only 5 minutes later he wouldn't have saw the light coming out of my room. My dad really doesn't understand that my dad never works out how it's supposed to, and that night for me is the only time to make up for the mistakes of day. Getting better at drawing though. Only marginally, but if I don't have that I don't have anything eh? =)   Commitment of Interest  To make sure I keep improving in my attempt to become an artist (unlike others I do not assume that I am an artist, being an artist is much more than drawing on paper or making a beautiful model)   Every week I shall attempt to produce: * At least one purely original drawing * A 3D artwork * Attempt to write in my blog and come up with some creative/crazy ideas =)   Just a note, I will not be posting everything I write, draw, or render up here. I don't have the webspace for it, and I don't really think there is an audience to be listening.   To want to do so much, and yet achieve so little  I want to write a book, become a traditional (pens, paint, paper) and digital (3D graphics, digital painting) artist, and to be happy, and all of these seem to be out of reach to me... Maybe I am diluting my interests too much... Maybe I'm talking more than I'm walking... Whatever it is, it's not going well... Gotta work on that =)   Wrapping up  Well, it's 9:37 now, and I can feel that my dad's going to walk up to me, try and steal a peek at my screen, and then say in childish tones "Time to go to bed Stephen, without sleep you won't be a good boy..." Either way, I'll stay up quite a bit longer, how at the moment I'm not  exactly  sure, but by the time I finish cleaning my teeth I'll have an escape plan ready =) (dad just switched off the kitchen light, he's coming for me) Nitey nite, before he gets a peak at my screen =)
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *Listening - LotR _again_*  Creativity... Creativity... The real sense of the word, the inherent genius behind the gears of the world's clock... And I'm not born with it... lol...   New Technique Coming Up!  Okay, while browsing the Daily Sketch Group, I have arrived at the conclusion that my previous method is good, but could possibly be more advance. Considering that in the world there is an infinite number of ideas and choices, letting my humble mind bumble down to only one conclusion is a little shallow. So, I am thinking of a new way to add some creative iterations. Categories include:     Time  - Future? Past? Present? Have a pick from the history of the Earth! You have a hunter,  Is he a hunter of the past, spear in hand wearing an outfit that would make Tarzan blush, Or is he from the not so past past, a knight armed with a traditional mace and chain, wearing heavy leather armour following tracks in the mud, Or even the present, (mad detective style) featuring multiple layers of magnifying glasses, wearing a slightly singed and dirtied suede jacket, staring at a group of select cards in his hand (lets say for insanity's sake its a joker who's got a sling shot, a queen just saved by a Prince only to find he is already married, and a king who has a suspiciously ominous shadow!) Or the future, with a sly female spy agent against a wall, pony tail wrapped into a tight spray of fine hair, lipstick in hand. Well, maybe that's going a little strange =)   Angles  - Smooth? Sharp? Angles exhibit the creators geometrical fascinations, and is commonly used in evil instruments and architecture, while smooth may exhibit the plump face of a friendly barman.   Ample?  - Is the character fat (wealth, carelessness for personal image) or thin (undernourished, poor, self-conscious)   Movement  - Is it a slow lumbersome movement, meaning great mass or age, or a quick darty movement, emphasising youth and agility.   Social Class  - Rich, poor, famous, common. All these influence certain characteristics about them. Could you imagine a poor dragon, who ends up using passed down flames or burrows =P   Fusion  - Already got a goblin? Throw a crown into the mix, ta-da! Goblin King, owner of the deeps, danger of the wealthy travellers.   Antithesis  - You have a kind old bunny rabbit, carefully sitting ontop of a present, happy to see the world go by... Boring right? Well, ok, a fat mean bunny rabbit, who is viciously ripping apart your present, pieces of wrapping paper flying into the air like a spray of limbs =P   Human Or Animal  - Are they based on mainly human or mainly animal characteristics... Earl Bird? etc etc  Anyway, got to go, dad's about to rip my head off...   
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      That's a excerpt from a conversation I had to a very depressed friend.   Sure, not all tears are a release, crying from pain is certainly not, but when it comes to emotional situations, a tear is the starting point.     Anyway =P      An Upgrade!    Seems like Blogger has had a GUI update, don't know whether or not I like it yet, but at the moment it's fine. Like the option to edit HTML manually though, very good idea (not that I'm going to use it lol)      Dream on =P    Yep, that's right, they're still going. Latest one was extremely weird, had something to do with France, some very stylistic architecture, old Gothic Cathedral style? It also happened to involve my school, friends from school, a clown, and having a talk to a clown about losing people "I know it's hard, I lost a friend once myself" "But my cow left me!" (the cow was like a spray painted coloured cow... enough said eh?)   Funny dream, very strange lol     Another one involved me having Spiderman powers (but I later found out that the Spidey powers only occurred in my dream's dreams, though I think I did attempt to bring my dream's dream to my dream's reality... Yeah... lol) and strange giant steam engine tanks, and I had to destroy them. So, armed with a rocket launcher, I took a few out, until I tested the alternate attack (right click =P) and that charged up a little bar and took over an enemy vehicle... Yes, it was about as weird as it sounds lol      Homework... EH?    School starts again on Tuesday next week *eek*   I have an assignment to do, in four parts, and I'm going to absolutely hate all of it... Some of it may have been bareable if given in seperate chunks, but who wants to do a new cover for a book, a short story, a character study and a book review all for the same thing?!?!? It's not sane!      Of VSG    Well, I just started with the list, started to get bombarded by their mail list =P   Oh well, heavenly creatures really, I'm sure it's going to get uber-fun very soon...      Of horror stories and power cuts    Well, I was reading a thread at CGTalk entitled "Strangest experiences that happened to you", absolutely freaked me out. These people don't lie (or at least the majority of them) and most of them I would trust with my life (well, almost), and it was really scary stuff. Anyway, page 14 out of 19 and the POWER WENT OUT! It never goes out here! What are the chances! Anyway, I was scared as hell all that night and didn't fall asleep till hours later when the power was back on... lol     Goodnight, it's almost midnight (11:59 as of writing) and I must up and away... Farewell one and all (even though, as I have pointed out many times before, no-one reads this but me lol)       
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well well well =) I've had a dream every day (or more specifically night =P) since the nightmares, and I'm happy to say they aren't nightmares (or at least don't scare the hell out of me!). I can remember them, if I really try, so that's an extremely good thing. Dreams are actually a lot of fun, a purely original show playing out in the deep abyss that is your brain.  Anyway! =P   The Girl =)  I've got to make sure I don't chicken out on this =) I've got to make sure I don't screw it up monumentally. I just want a fair chance at asking her out, without any trip-ups, or half broken sentences. If I make a good stand, and she says no, I'll be happy, because I made my stand. Then, it'll be even more confusing if she says yes =P We're kind of in different social groups, both kind of inbetweeners, and that means that at school we probably wouldn't have a great amount of contact. Oh well, at this stage, it's a dream, but a dream which I hope has at least some foundations outside of the Wonderland playing itself inside my head.   My teeth are imprisoned in bars of metal! =P  The braces are going alright, I guess =) I got them in two days ago now, and they're about as bad as the spacers I had in before, but with the major difference it hurts to chew on anything at the moment =) Yes, anything, biscuits, sausages, and  especially  calamari! It takes a lot of getting used to though, especially when I tried to whistle for my dog, and then all of the sudden noticed it wasn't working too well. After a few stops and starts I found out it worked, but haphazardly lol Only time will tell, I so hope I get used to them! =P   Last Exile  I still haven't gotten that last episode of Last Exile! Episode 26, the final one, that's it. Still haven't got it... *sigh* lol. It's actually not that bad, if I leave my connection on for approximately 26 hours and start downloading, it'll be done, but the problem is that it isn't a resuming one, so an hour here or there won't work. It's an amazing series though, so I'll get the end of it eventually.   Star Trek  Star Trek Season 7 Marathon finished today, and I hadn't even noticed that Star Trek: The Next Generation had finished in 1994, silly silly me =) I quite like the series generally, I mean, nothing really challenges you mentally since Macguyver, it's good to see something which expands the general ideas of consciousness and of possible relaties, time, anti-time, etcetera =) It was good while it lasted! =)   Homework  It really doesn't seem fair, but my last week is going to be partially ruined by homework. Fabulous me has left an assignment off until the last minute, a writing one, so I'm going to have to test how fast I can write this week, should go well, on a computer I can type faster than I can write. Anyway, that's my main bother =)   Forrest Gump  An excellent movie, makes you feel every major emotion during it's length... I don't have too much to say about it, apart from that =)   Creativity  It's that time again, to release the mental anguish =) Perfect time too, my music just clipped over onto Linkin Park, In the End, my favourite song, EVER!  Like a whirlwind inside of my head =)  An alleyway with ladders running up and down to the ceiling around it, and electronics, and wires, hanging out of every wall and sparking - A man is standing in the middle of it all, turning around, in a relaxed stance, to look at you. Two men, fighting on rooftops, which are tiled, running up and down with an agility never seen before - one falls off of the edge, but rebounds quickly using some kind of cord and the gutter of the building - they continue fighting and leaping from rooftop to rooftop. A man walking down a street, in the dark cold of midnight, and down a run down alley he encounters two guys, and rises slowly from his slunky walking pose to fight them off quickly. A electric train is running it's route between different flying cities, all connected by a small runway between them - All of the sudden the train is attacked with a kind of high-tech ballista, which fires a connective rope from far below straight into the vessel, letting others take over the train - the floating buildings it travels between look like pyraminds, but with quite a few extensions mainly below it. A vessel, meant for anti-grav transport, with a rudder at the back to direct airflow, it's coloured green and marked with golden runic symbols, on the bottom it has an engine which fits snuggly into the whole design - the whole thing looks like a fish with it's head and tail cut off, ie, tapering towards the end. Like in X-Men, with the girl who can go thru walls, someone fades into a building's wall and starts pushing out the bricks which hold it together - the guards come over to inspect what the hell's happening, and all of a sudden, out of the darkness just caused by the brick's hole, and hand comes thru - WOOOMPH - and knocks the guard stone cold =P ...   Oh well, not quite as good tonight, but I've been talking to my cousin Kate quite heavily =)  Here's to another day over, and yet another long night just begun!
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Apart from a bad dream or two I had (involving death of family/dog and the end of the world, end of the world in a way which no-one could stop, they were just waiting for death), my subconscious is actually beginning to act really well. The only negative effect apart from nightmares is that I can't recall certain words like I used to, don't know why.  But other than that, I just noticed my sb (subconscious from now on) has been working in overdrive everwhere. I'm able to imagine completely original and independent things, like the African-American young boy, on a train, looking at his watch, and even though they may not be amazingly sparking ideas they are completely original and not derived. I think I hit the first step in breaking into my brain. I also noticed that my sb is working on MY problems now, not just running off in random directions (which was why I was probably so good at word recollection). For example, I found out that my sb was thinking about my crush all through my English exam, and when it came time for creative writing I just out of the blue decided to write one on a romantic comedy.  I really don't mind it too much, it's amazing to sit there with your eyes half open and let your mind wander to the strangest places you've ever been. You just start slowly swinging your head, and you feel only semi-there, and start melting away in your head. You can imagine whole worlds on your own doorstep.   General  Anyway =) I have once again gone no-where today, and the VSG school hsan't gotten back to me yet, and I'm getting braces tomorrow... Hmm...   Style and Simplification  Beauty comes through simplification and style... Simplification to represent only what needs representation, for example, like most comics, they only represent what needs it, and what's the use of highly detailing the left side of a car when you're never going to see it. Can you get the same effect with a sphere as a highly subsurfed and carefully tended model? Style, everyone needs style, as style is what will help you define a work. Some people's styles come through colour schemes, others through the use (or overuse) of certain techniques in post pro, or others just by doing something no-one else could. Some people try to develop for a world, so that people think of it and like it like a telivision series, waiting for the next 'episode'! A lot of things generally =) I must persevere to try and discover my style...  WooT WooT!   The Moon, Lunus pretiosum  I think that translate into 'the precious moon', but I'm not sure. Pretiosus/a is precious/dear, I know that, but there are some disrepcancies on lunus/luna. Either way, I don't have my Latin books here =) Just a general note, the moonlight has been excedingly bright recently. So bright infact that my alarm woke me up a few nights ago, and I thought it was broken, because there were shadows on my wall from all the light. It was actually the moonlight. This light was just so piercingly strong that I could see everything around my house, a good 5-10 kilometre view, perfectly, apart from a few areas bathed in fog.  Maybe it's a sign decreed by the ancient Hindus showing that the moon is at a perfect reflective angle to the sun, signalling that the moon shall fall out of it's orbit and crash into the earth... =)  Well, we can all still hope right? =P
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sounds like a bad science fiction name, but in all reality he is a fantastic musician. On par with Howard Shore, creator of the Lord of the Rings Soundtrack, and that's saying something. Klaus Badelt is the creator of the music for Pirates of the Carribean! The music has an amazing sense of mood and power, and I really love them. It also fits in perfectly among my Howard Shore, Last Exile (Dolce Triade\Shuntaro Okino\Hitomi Kurioshi), and the rest =P   My site  My site required a LOT of work it seemed, mainly along the lines of W3C Validation (that's the set of rules and compliance for HTML on webpages). Now that is all done, all I need to do is add little thumbnails to the galleries =) It also has a new domain, now it is located at  urlLink www.smerity.tk  until I can get www.smerity.com =)   Spiderman 2  Quite an excellent movie personally, all the effects looked excellent, Doc Oc's tentacles were composited in the scenes perfectly. It also had a nice balance of action/comedy/drama (even if in some scenes drama is over or underdone). I personally think it was much better than the first, and I love coming out of a movie and feeling I could run up a wall =P   3D  Considering going to AFTRS (The Australian Film Television and Radio School) for my post HSC studies, as it is available in Sydney, has a strong creative/traditional art foundings and education on that subject and will speed track me through learning Maya. It has also been influenced by the recent success of Sejong Park, a student who went there, and now has an animation about his experiences in war-torn Korea at Siggraph.   Invader Zim  Trying intently to download Invader Zim, a cartoon about a misfit alien trying to "TAKE OVER THE WORLD!" While it may sound typical and common story plot, the way they play it out is amazingly unique, and is one of my favourite shows. Everything has an overexaggerated personality, and that's half of the reason I love it so much =P (BTW, may I note here BitTorrent sucks! It's supposedly supposed to increase download speeds, well, I have a modem, and so far I've downloaded 47.2 Mb and UPLOADED 244.3 Mb! Where's the justice in that! I have almost another 1000 hours before the download is finished... Oh well...)   Art/Creativity  I think I'm getting better. There are sometimes, when listening to music, or lying in bed before I fall asleep, that my brain just wonders and sees a million different things, a corridor here, a winding staircase there, anything and everything, organic or inorganic, and all things inbetween. Architecture unfolds with every beat of the music, a dragon unfurls from it's shell. It's quite amazing, drugs except with no injection, at least not one I'm aware of =)  Of note, I created three new 3D works recently =P        The Techy Trashcan =)  More info available at my site in the gallery pages, but the general info is the original image was created for a speed modelling contest, and from there it evolved into a scene. I still have a long way to go on the scene, and I just noticed how lowly detailed the trashcan is (I've seen it with 'new eyes') May have an update in the future    The Blue Mushroom! =P This I really really like. It started off merely modelling a quick mushroom (nice and simple things lol) and then I started to work on the texture and material heavily, and then I added a quick branch, and then some leaves. I'd love to make a scene involving this in the future. Enchanted forest, with some sort of twist, maybe pollution killing them off, a "you don't know what you're missing" kind of thing =)    Anyway, I'm just going to let my imagination run wild until I'm forced to go to bed, just relax and listen to the waves and babble on typing. I saw this really weird scene with some sort of mannequin smoking, sitting lazily on a chair with it's feet on a desk. A scene with a car speeding along, the speedometer going wild, when all of the sudden something happens, and you go to a view under the car, and see ice start to travel along a pipe under there, freezing up the rest of the engine. Just a note, a really weird thing on Nickelodeon at the moment, they feature a pufferfish singing an old 1970s (or 60s, lower) into an old microphone while he's underwater in his fish bowl ("I'm waiting for the moon, a little sunlight, and just you...").  Nova 96.9 commercial ("Sounds Different") features an old guy peeling an orange, which screams every time he peels it. Imagination back, an old man, with an old pair of half moon spectacles, a top hat, and a gold chain to hold the spectacles. He is facing forward (forward forward, the same way as the photographer) but turning his head to look back, and has a mistrusting look in his eyes. I'm starting to lose it, so I'm just generally typing, typing helps to bring it back, and just looking forward with my eyes closed, somethings come quickly, others not at all. A control room featuring gears, and old mono style levels (pull the long level back to control something). Some sort of reddish crocidile, with  bags under it's eyes. A robot, facing forward, with something like antlers, and his hands on the ground forward infront of him. Some kind of superhero, holding onto a cloud with one hand and grabbing someone else with the other, while he gets dragged around by the cloud. An Egyptian wall, with block collums to the left of a doorway, with stairs up to a giant door, and an Egyptian style dog at the top of the entrance, sticking out and protecting it. The top of a building, and the gargoyles on the side are replaced with ravenous dogs, their mane's hair stuck back in vicious spikes, and their mouths open to let the rain water drain out through them. It's all about trying to remain on this stream of images, adding tiny variables to keep cycling through the imagination in your head. The main variation I'm using is light levels (with my eyes closed), I turn on my picture screensaver, and it flicks to a difference size and contrasting image, changing light levels. I'm cycling music through my head too, and if I see a flicker of an idea, a balloon, a ballast, I try to focus on it and keep adding detail, or just staying with that in my head and seeing what I come up with. Just be free..... A generator in the middle of the air, with a spiral of small stars and particle streams all flying down towards it, powering it somehow. A building with two giant barrels on the top of it (cooling stacks, missile launchpads, who knows?). A giant robotic foot, nothing else connected, and all of the sudden part of it detaches and slowly goes down to the ground (like the back of a horse float) to reveal an army. A giant pole with chains coming off of it, getting struck by lightning, and down the bottom it is connected to an old book, standing on it's own stand, connect by a pole shaped like an upside down L. A snake charmer, with one of those goofy giant hats on his head, and a moustache, curled at the ends. A ship throwing anchor, with the anchor streaming past in the water, and the cannon on the boat in full roar with an aura of red surrounding it, blurred by all the motion. A guy with dreadlocks (brown) and a metal face, with screws holding it in place here and there, with an expression of a rockstar on his face. A young boy, African-American (ie, black, but I hate having to say it cuz I sound racist, and I'm not) with a green baseball cap on his head, looking at a wristwatch.  Anyway, the time is now 11:19 PM, I kind of just left this window open throughout the day so I wouldn't forget to post, but all that creative stuff I came up with in the last, probably half hour. Got stuck in some trance, still half in it now =) Goodnight! =)
     
    
</post>


</Blog>