<Blog>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I went to my dinner dance yesterday, and it was pretty fun ^_^, but i managed to do a drawing.....that I'll post when I get my scanner working. So till then...I'll just be drawing :3 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       For all you peole looking for Kami Kaze manga, heres the url: urlLink kami kaze  I got it off a friend ^_^ 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yay! i just came back from the mall and got the Get Backers manga! but talk about expensive! they were about.. $10 each >_  
    
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Just updating as usual......Im currently working on a drawing, it took me 1 hour to do the hair and colour it all >_  to see the site. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This is my second blog, and i hope to make this better than my first ^_^ well i'll just start off by putting up my latest picture i drew..  urlLink click  
    
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       What's the big deal with me joining? XD You know this Blogger (Logger?  Booger?  Yeah, booger) hates you like hell when it won't send to like 2 emails, and only to the 3rd...baka booger...  Now what?  *bored to hell*  Artbloooooog.  
    
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well my internets been going wacko since I got back >_  
    
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey!!! sorry i took soo long to update ^_^ I just came back from Hong Kong...whew! but i still havent gotten my scanner fixed yet -_- But I managed to draw something on the computer....its not very good though.. urlLink click  
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       My scanners still busted :( but im trying to find a way of posting my drawings on this blog....oh! i just finished reading all 14 volumes of Love Hina ^_^ its really good! Im trying to find a site with scanlations of that manga...well I wont be posting in this blog for another few months because im on vacation! ^_^ well cya till then  
    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This post has nothing to do with anime (hence the title) I just wanted to celebrate becoming a Super Star ( urlLink The Sims ) It didn't take as long as I expected but it sure was hard work!! *whew* Out of all the Sims expansion packs, I most enjoyed  urlLink Makin Magic  and  urlLink Livin Large   But after looking at screen shots from  urlLink The Sims 2  I've sort of lost intrest in the first sims....anyways, I've posted a few screen shots from the sims, their kind of cute actually...like my  urlLink ghost cat  (yes I killed my sim's cat) for some strange reason...It's using the litter box.... -__-;; Making Magic has the coolest options, like you can make spells that change the  urlLink apperance  of your sim, you can also make a spell that will give you lots of  urlLink treasures  and my favorite, being abducted by  urlLink aliens  (Livin' Large Expansion Pack) ^_^ 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Finally! Im moving in 2 days, but I doubt I'll be able to actually HAVE a computer in my room *coughcuzofbrothercough* and I'm really starting to doubt I'll EVER be able to buy another scanner *coughstingydadcough* I'll have to rely on Drac~chan here... u_u but hey, I'll still be moving ^_^ (Ive never moved before) well I did doodle for a few hours on the computer and  urlLink this   and  urlLink  this   is what came out (very crappy yes I know >_ 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I keep forgetting about the blog >>; Thanks for reminding me.   urlLink  I finally finished this. &nbsp; But stupid Photobucket resized it, so it's all ugly and pixelated.  Petshop of Horrors is THE BEST   ~N  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I just updated because I put a site meter on the side bar u_u..well I'll be moving soon, so i wont update for half a month, so I hope SOMEONE will be able to UPDATE >_ 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I just bought a new manga yesterday  urlLink Peach Girl: Change of Heart  ;dispite the weird cover, it was pretty good ^_^...but a little bit too dramatic for my taste, but what the heck?! I havent bought&nbsp;that kinda manga in AGES (all I have are Pet Shop of Horrors, Saiyuki, Rave Master, GTO, Get Backers, etc.) I did find out that Peach Girl: Change of Heart was a sequel to the original , urlLink Peach Girl  So far I've been dying to go back and buy more ^_^    
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Finally! i found something worth being posted...Im soo stressed even though Im on vacation...(family problems..ick) Anyways  urlLink this  is just a doodle :3  
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I found an even BETTER  urlLink site  ^_^ hehe but some of the works have been took of the net because they were licenced... 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       According to one of my friends who is (very) obsessed with manga, found a site with some  urlLink manga  (because hes too stingy to buy the actual books teeehehehehe :D 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I almost forgot...    urlLink  This  is what a hairbunny looks like.   Stupid Blogger and its stupid errors.  Stupid Angelfire and it's image wall.  I think the link works now. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       WTF it deleted my first post, but whatever.  I didn't update because I have  nothing  to update about yet, except that street dancing lessons look like aerobics and I will suck at them next Saturday along with my sis.  Here.   urlLink New drawing.   ...  Hairbunnies.    Seriously. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It feels soo lonely being the only one updating this blog..u_u i wish that *SOMEONE* would also update even though SHE currently has drawers block...is there such thing as drawers block? well im assuming its just the same as writers block but only with drawing....*babbles on* I managed to get hold of 2 pictures one wich I did in  urlLink 6th grade  and it was one of my best drawings back then, so I redrew it again in  urlLink 8th grade  just to compare and to see how much I improved ^_^ hehe the picture quality isnt that great...but Im sure it doesnt matter (had to take photos of them because she's sick of drawing on the computer) ehe well enjoy  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I was just being curious after reading about a hundred reviews on Yuu Wataise's manga called  urlLink Alice 19th ...so I found a website with the first few pages of the manga "http://MangaProject.cjb.net and http://www.yuuwatase.org" its pretty interesting and not like Alice in Wonderland. *Makes me wanna buy it!!* well I just felt like talking about it ^_^ so enjoy the link  
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       LOL! well I kinda gave up doing those gothic style type of drawings (arg being bothered by brother -_-#) geeeeeze! ANYWAYS  urlLink here  it is..I didnt have much time to fix it up because SOMEONE *hint hint* kept bothering me >:( BLECH!  
    
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Sorry for not posting much yet, I'll finish something after I finish worshipping artists that are better than me... *prodding awesome Getbackers art*  *points at the post below hers* Awesome piece, BTW.  ~N  
    
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Lol I hate repeated titles....umm I just recently started using a new style...yes I know the legs are kinda off but still!! It tooke me along time to draw it and fix it up on the computer, and by the time I was done with the entire thing I noticed the legs wer crooked u_u....anyways  urlLink here  it is...for those who still want to see it... 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I finally drew something (took 2 hours) what a waste of time, but hey it looks okay...I tried doing a new style of drawing rather than my same old style..so heres my picture of a  urlLink gothy  girl 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I wouldn't be posting anything (I post so little, ne? But then I can't finsih an artwork to save my life...) but you-know-who told me this one was cute. Even if I totally suck at painting stuff X)  So,  urlLink here's this drawing from Gundam SEED of Asuran and Kira, with two little camera-carrying perverts in the background...   YES THEY'RE BOTH GUYS, IGNORE MY SUCKY FOLDING THAT MAKES IT LOOK LIKE ASURAN HAS A CHEST.  Yes, I draw guy/guy. Bite me.  ~N            
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yay! I finally moved from my 9 room house to my 5 room apartment, and have sucsessfully turned my apartment into a warehouse! I still havent replaced my scanner yet, but HOPEFULLY I'll be able to convince my mom that I need one for school or something. 
    
    
</post>


</Blog>