<Blog>


<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      dearest diary,  i do not know wad to put for today's  title..haha..so i will talk anything under the sun...haha...lets see...  i got back my papers and i FAILED BOTH MATHS!!!haha...well what can i do right?haha...chinese i pass and english summary is the best...normally i get 7 and 8 marks now i have 17!whoa..hehe..and well compo..i have 50/100...can lar.at least i did nto fail:)  somehow..i think i am sick..i start to imagine things when i have nothing better to do..i will think that i am a princess of a far away land or something...or maybe how i will look if some guy like me..how i will look with them...which is totally nto good...yesterdae someone asked me what do i imagine about..i did nto wanna sae anything cuz i don noe if i were to sae it or not..i don neo wad will happen and everything..y am i even talking abotu this?hehe...i have no idea..haha..  anyway..i am crazy for todae so i talk crap and more crap...haha...cya..
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      dear diary,   i would like to thank all te councillors for caring about me soo much during teh camp. when i was sick. i am feeling much better now. i am sorry i did not get the chance to sae thanx to one and all for caring about me the whole time:)  cya... love tze 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      dear diary,  i would like to tell u about my camp. teh council camp rock. it is teh coolest camp that i ahve ever been to and it made my relationship with teh coucil much better then before. but sadly there was a virus going around and i got it. teh whole coucil has got it sadly.  but, we had a great time.playing water games and getting all wet. having lots of fun is something that we all had.  well, unfortunetely i got home with the deadly virus and spread it to everyone in my family. my dad got it and had a fever my mom got it and got teh fever and now my younger sister has it and is emmitted in teh hospital. teh poor dear. how i wish i am teh one having it and not her.and i should be teh one in teh hospital rite now. at least it is not her and it is me. i am less a burden to my parents then her. i can be there alomne and my parents could do their work at home and everything.how i wished teh person is me.  but it happened to her and not me. there is nothing i could do but to preay that she will be alright. thats all. anyone of u reading this plz pray for her..she is onli tenyears old and she is young carefree and innocent. i do not want anything bad to happen to her.thanx  well i see you all round. bye  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>