<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I know everybody got the day off today and in most cases had a bar-B-Q. I have always taken this day for granted as another day off (usually spent hung over from Paso). I just watched 60 minutes (yesterdays show) and realized that our own individual lives are just parts of this larger scheme. I can make a decision to go fight for my country, or I can be lazy and do nothing and bitch about the way things are going...  I haven’t done either and think everybody needs some sole searching before they can complain...  You might not be happy with the man in charge but he was elected, and you might not be happy with the situation in Iraq but our soldiers enlisted...  I am very proud of everyone who fought for America, and our freedom, but there are those who fight for an unknown agenda and I feel for them. 60 Minutes just ran a clip for 11 minutes of pictures of everyone who has died in Iraq and I know that’s not a lot compared to other wars, but I feel as though they where unnecessary deaths and their families probably agree.   I would like to say THANK YOU and good luck to the rest over there!!!  I also want to thank all of the people who can support these people without passing judgment upon them for doing their jobs. If you don't support our current governments decision than vote and become vocal in your local communities. Don’t hate those that think different, and might support our government, but become active and make responsible decisions without judgment on other individuals.  Once again THANK YOU....  -Casey 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here are the photos from Yosemite, just click the picture of the falls...   urlLink    Yosemite Falls
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I haven't been able to update the BLOG lately because I've been so busy....  I went to Yosemite last weekend, which was pretty fun (minus all the winding roads). I'll post some pictures with a link later. I went to court to pay a traffic ticket, which really pissed me off. I got a fix-it ticket a block away from my house, the officer was just looking for some revenue for the good ol state budget. The ticket was $10 if I fixed the crack (by replacing the windshield which I couldn’t find for a 64 Galaxie very easy), or I could pay $ 110 if I chose not to replace the windshield and the ticket would be cleared up. I tried to pay by phone ($110) with my credit card which didn't work so I had to go in to the court house to do it, and they still didn't let me use my MasterCard (only VISA). Well by that time it turned into a failure to appear and the total amount ended up being $290....  I saw the same cop this morning giving another person a ticket for a crack in the windshield (I assume this because they had a crack in their windshield). I guess that cop is going to get a golden Donut Award for most revenue generated from people not doing serious crimes....   What a total Ass...  If Sacramento would fix there damn roads and not have rocks from potholes all over them there would probably be less windshield tickets and that would be less revenue so lets keep those roads dangerous out there...  -Casey 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well here are some shots of Pinball-A-Go-Go...   urlLink    Curtis like pinball   urlLink    Pinball shot 2   urlLink    Pinball shot 1  I had a pretty good time at the pinball show especially considering we didn't get there until they started loading up the machines. I didn't cause this by my finger, because I did the finger repair work on the road, we were just on Franklin time. I had a great time, although not a lot of Pinball but I got to hang out with some old friends whose company I actually enjoy, and got to meet a new friend who was pretty funny for how young he was (maybe I'm just jealous of being young again). We stopped at MURDER BURGER (not REDRUM Burger as all you lame ass Davis liberal Nazis know it as), the food was good but gave identically smelling gas to two of our group who seemed to feel as though there was extreme humor in it... 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As you can see I wasn't doing to good Sunday morning after a long night out, a little hung over, and trying to hurry and finish cooking, while everyone is waiting for me to go to Pinball-A-Go-Go (hey Curtis, they make these things called phones to give people a little notice). Well some first aid tape and gauze made everything all right. Here's a shot of my finger from Sunday night when I got home....  I'll stick some pinball action shots up later....   urlLink    A tough time Sunday Morning....
     

    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well today has been a very long one especially considering it started at 12:00 A.M. I guess I can start out at explaining the art car show last night  urlLink click here for photos . I showed up last night with Jerry and we had a good time checking out all the sh*t and saw some fun stuff like Blanchards car. I then proceeded to head into the "fashion show" and cheeked out a runway of girls that seemed to have a strong desire to be somebody, but they were actually pretty nice. Steve Vanoni put on the show (http://www.horsecow.com) which was pretty fun, but I seemed to have a little too much fun (too much booze). SLA played @ 12:00 which was a fun show, but they sure seemed to argue quite a bit. Anyway the show was good fun and I seemed to make it home before sun up.  Coming up next: Pinball-A-Go-Go 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I made it through the day today. Have I done something bad and ended up in purgatory?   pur·ga·to·ry  (pûrg-tôr, -tr) n. pl.  pur·ga·to·ries   A state in which the souls of those who have died in grace must expiate their sins.   My company used to have about 300 - 400 people now there are less than 5 (in the US that is). I now sit in the office with nobody around but myself (and my servers). Occasionally I talk to some people from our Mexico plant to fix their problems, but they should probably hire somebody down there to manage the server farm and cut me loose because they get paid in peso's not dollars.  I wish I had a project to do but nothing...  Maybee I should just start sleeping under my desk like George Costanza.  Oh well, at least it's Friday and I'm not going back to work till Monday.  until later... -Casey
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's a nice day here in Sactown, especially since I'm not working today (although everyone keeps calling me about their email problems). I am trying to take care of all these little things before the days over, but it's soooo nice outside. I can't wait for Pin-A-Go-Go this weekend in Dixon, it runs from Friday to Sunday (more info @ http://www.pinagogo.com ).   Kings won lastnight so I'm in a good mood...  Well the games on so I better get going (actually it started but Tivo RULES!!!)...    
     

    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here is a picture I took of my daughter on our train ride to S.F.  urlLink    Isabella riding the Train
     

    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is my first entry for this blog....  So far this day sucks! I spilled coffe all over my desk.  Oh well... how do I insert a picture? I guess I need to do some looking around...    
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last weekend was pretty crazy, here's how it broke down...  • Tattoo show at the  urlLink Toy Room Gallery  and some drinking at Jerry and Aimee's... •  urlLink The concert in the park  Friday then to Heather's for some drinking and then the girls wanted to do some  urlLink karaoke…  • Hoang’s going away party (w/ a pool and unicycle) all day Saturday into the evening... • Father's day on Sunday (my daughter Isabella made me some great gifts)...  and then Sunday evening I got very sick along with Isabella (although she's been getting sick for a few days). We were up until past midnight with stomach flu.  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Ray Charles 9-23-1930 - 6-10 2004
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I've registered www.CaseyRiddell.com but haven’t set anything up on the site yet, I've even got 2 years of web space. I used readysetconnect.com as the hosting provider, but I'm not sure how well this is going to work out, I've already had several problems. If any body else wasn’t to set up a site send me an email and I'll help you out (if this works out that is)...  Fourth of July was fun, Dan the Man had some good fireworks and we had lots and lots of food.  -Casey 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>