<Blog>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink What Gay Marriages Threaten   I couldn't believe this was on google news.  It looks like a cheap site to begin with, so I don't know how this constitutes news.  What the article is trying to do is prove that gay marriage is indeed a threat to society and that it has negative implications.  Now, what the article actually does is prove that only half of the website's name seems to be true.  Yes, the first half of it in case you were wondering.  Now I'm gonna rip this piece of shit article apart and see what happens.     I’ve seen two separate TV interviews with newly “married” gay people. Both interviews ended with one of the “spouses” plaintively asking, “What is it about gay marriage that threatens anyone?” That’s a "When did you stop beating your wife?" question. It hides two questions in one, making it impossible to answer the first differently than the second. Marriage is about the “relationship” between the partners, but it’s also about “family.” Whereas I’m utterly indifferent to their relationship with each other, I oppose what gay marriage implies about family.     Apparently "What is it about gay marriage that threatens anyone?" has two questions hidden in one.  However, the author doesn't say what those two questions are.  If this is indeed a set up for an argument, it's done badly.    And to compare it to "When did you stop beating your wife?" is not only ridiculous and unfounded, especially since no argument is set up, but I can replace that same question with "When did straight people start fucking their children?"  Who knows, and what's that have to do with anything?  Besides, if we're really asking "When did you stop beating your wife?" That's a cut and dry answer.  Usually it's, "I never stopped."  OR "I stopped a (Blah Amount of Time) Ago."    Now, for the author, can you answer "What is it about gay marriage that threatens anyone?"  Let's see...   Not every marriage produces children, but of those that do, the marriage is the foundation for being both spouse and parent. Therefore, what you rule about marriage has deep and lasting repercussions for what it means to be a parent. The Massachusetts Supreme Court's decision about gay marriage simply fails to understand this. Their argument presumes that marriage is solely about the relationship between the spouses. To this court, marriage is one-dimensional. They see no relevant contrast between same-sex spouses and heterosexual spouses, which is true. Since they only recognize the spousal dimension of marriage, they hastily conclude that the marriage as a whole cannot possibly be different. We're not sure whether the court's blinkered vision is intentional or merely shallowness revealed, but the effect is the same.   I don't see any point whatsoever in this part of the article.  Gay people can adopt, and, if their marriage is indeed FINALLY legal, then BOTH are parents.  And they would have to take care of the child as parents would under the law.  There are no special gay parenting omissions.  Besides, what gay people have been fighting for is marriage equal to those of straight people.  Regardless of the procreation aspect, we'd be equal to say straight couples who can't have children biologically due to physical problems.  Are they not indeed a true family either?   To oppose gay marriage is not to denigrate the relationship between the spouses. It is, however, to stand firmly behind traditional ideas about family.    Ah, there's the actual point the author's trying to make: Traditional ideas about family.  Why didn't you say that from the beginning?    To comment on tradition, interracial marriages weren't traditional either.  Care to tackle that one?   Let's start with the obvious. Society has always placed child-rearing responsibility with the biological parents. If you beget a child, then you're responsible for it, whether you like it or not. We don't care if it's difficult or inconvenient. You beget it, you be raisin' it. The biological parents acquire responsibility merely because they procreated. That's how it always has been, for many good reasons.   First of all, both parents don't have to be married to be responsible for the child.  A child's father, whether he married the woman or not, has responsibility over that child.  A woman can indeed chase a man, who ran off, down and ask him for child support.  Second of all, if you adopt a child, you are taking on the exact same responsibilities as a parent.  Once you sign those adoption papers, it's as if you are begetting a child.  Third of all, begetting a child has never been and never will be a requirement between any two couples who marry, whether gay, straight, married or interracial.    So, no, that's not how it's always been.   Gay marriage denies this. Since children don't come from same-sex unions, for gay couples to enjoy equal status as parents, you have to abandon the traditional link between begetting and raising the child. You have to say that it isn't necessary for the biological parent to be responsible for raising the child. If so, on whom does the responsibility fall? The inevitable result is that raising the child becomes voluntary.    Gay marriage hasn't denied anything.  There is still adoption, there is still artificial insemination and there are still amazing biological breakthroughs where two eggs can create a child now.  Begetting a child has never been a requirment between any two couples.  And, yes, in many cases getting the child would be voluntary, adoption.  Once you adopt, you can't just keep the receipt and give it back if you're not happy within the first 30 days, you fucking retard.   Is anyone comfortable with the idea that parenting is voluntary? It doesn't matter whether two gays would provide admirable love and affection for the child. It doesn't matter that plenty of heterosexual parents fail in their responsibilities. When you assert that two gays have the same status as biological parents, you can no longer insist that biological parents be responsible for the child merely because of their intercourse.    This author is all over the board here.  I can't even make sense of this article anymore.  Anyway, I'll try.    I and millions of others are perfectly comfortable with adopting if that's what you mean by voluntary.  If you mean that gay marriage is trying to make parenting voluntary in general. as in you think that gay people can just give away their child at will once they get bored, then I'd like to see where you read that because, last I checked, equal marriage rights means two gay parents would have to take care of a child like any other type of parents.  And, so far, it's impossible to have two gay parents to have the same status as biological parents since no one has figured out how to combine two sperms to make a baby, only ova.  If you're saying they have the same BIOLOGICAL status then I see what you might be saying.  You're talking about genders and gender roles.  But, since when was it a requirment for mom to stay at home and dad to work?  I think those traditional values were attacked long ago by women looking for equal rights as well.  I wanna see what you have to say about that subject.    Besides, no one said that once a gay couple marries they can just have a child and leave it in a dumpster if they feel bored with it.  I don't see where your fears are coming from.  And did you say that, "It doesn't matter whether two gays would provide admirable love and affection for the child."?  Oh, ya, you did.  Does a child not need love and affection?  And you're forgetting that, as the kid's new found parents, they'd also provide food and shelter for the child as well.  But maybe there's more than provisions and love when it comes to raising a child.  But you still haven't said what that is.  And, yes, it DOES matter if ANY couple with children fails in their responsibilities you half wit.  It seems like YOU don't care much about children.  I should write an article on why you shouldn't get married.   Let’s not kid each other. We all know what would happen. If we make parenting a voluntary choice, the moment the baby becomes inconvenient (i.e., within minutes), it gives cause to break the contract. The whole concept of parental responsibility becomes a merely admirable goal. The, since we don't use government to enforce virtue, we keep government away from enforcing parental responsibility. We can hear it now – “How dare the government tell me who to care for!” The Supreme Court will rule that if the right of privacy means anything, surely it means that individuals are free to love and care for others at their own choice. Meanwhile, the baby needs a change and a feeding.   WOAH!  Again, as legal parents under the law, they HAVE to take care of the child.  And like ANY OTHER STRAIGHT COUPLE WHO GOT 'BORED', SHALL WE SAY, THEY PUT THEIR KID UP FOR ADOPTION!  You're assuming that because there is no procreation involved, then the parents don't feel as close to the kid as parents who did procreate.  That is absolutely not the case.  Why are kids then put up for adoption if these straight parents had such an attachment?  Do they all come from parents who just couldn't afford them?  Gay parents will make mistakes like the BILLIONS of straight parents before them.  Does that make the mistakes forgivable?  Well, you did say, "It doesn't matter that plenty of heterosexual parents fail in their responsibilities."  So, maybe mistakes don't matter to you.  They matter to me, but the mistakes won't be any more or less severe because of the sexuality of the parents.  They are more or less severe depending on the mistake that was made.     And you're forgetting artificial insemination.  Then the kid is indeed from at least one of the parents.  And, with new breakthroughs, they are even able to combine to sperm to put into one egg.  And hence, the baby is both parents'.  These breakthroughs in science are obviously not perfected, but there've been tons of scientific journals on the subject, and I suggest you read up on them.  Here's a link to the men being able to make eggs:  urlLink Sperm Eggs  and here's a link to two ova becoming a baby:  urlLink Bye Bye Men! .  Yes, they're all tests on rats, but that's where all tests start.  And fuck you for thinking that a gay couple won't change and feed a baby because they wanted to go fuck each other.  Who do you think you are making these assumptions?   There is another option. We might legally separate family from marriage, so that being a parent has nothing to do with being a spouse. Marriage becomes one thing, family another. You can raise children in or outside marriage, so much that marriage is irrelevant to the matter. The biological parents don't have to live together, or like each other, or ever see each other. A child becomes merely a legal liability shared by two individuals, allowing each individual to pursue whatever spousal relationship they like, regardless of whether it includes the biological partner or not. Children become tax-deductible dependants, but nothing more. Children become the shared property of two legally liable individuals, but there is no presumption that the children belong to any stable social unit under the same roof. The relationship is legally amorphous, and can take any form. Of course, this disembowels any notion of family in the traditional sense, but that's the price.   Ok, this situation has already happened and IS happening between millions of married straight couples.  Just because you marry doesn't mean you have a family, and just because you have a family doesn't mean you're married.  They were never a one and the other situation.  This deals with ethics and morals and opinion.  I agree that if someone were to get married and have kids, they should provide a stable, loving situation.  To assume that gay people wouldn't do that is obviously a biased and uninformed opinion you've made based on stereotypes and hatreds.    But don't be so quick to put every negative thing you mentioned above about family and children on the homosexual.  Indeed, these negative aspects must've been ways paved long before this time since no homosexuals were ever able to marry, hence, the straight couple created these negative aspects to marriage and family.  To have a gay couple act as you have described here, would only be to mimic a certain type of straight couple.    Let's not pretend that all gay marriages will be happy and perfect just as we shouldn't pretend that straight people know exactly how to get married and be happy with a great, stable family.  There will always be bad marriages and there will always be broken families.  But gay people deserve the right to try.   You can entertain gay marriage only if you abandon either the spousal or the parental dimensions of marriage. You can have gay marriage with the spousal dimension alone. You can have gay marriage with the parental dimension alone. However, you can't have gay marriage and simultaneously hold both traditional dimensions of marriage.   Yes, you can.  You haven't done a thing to prove otherwise this whole article.  You still haven't even introduced the two questions hidden in the first question you stated saying, "What is it about gay marriage that threatens anyone?"   Those who support gay marriage portray opponents as bigoted bullies. They challenge us to show how gay people's love and devotion are any less valid than heterosexuals are. That's one-half of the "when did you stop beating your wife" question. Of course, no one can reasonably deny that gays love and commit as deeply as straights. At that point, gay marriage supporters throw up their hands in exasperation. Then how could one oppose gay marriage? The answer is that there's more to marriage than being a spouse.    No gay person said that there isn't more to marriage than being a spouse.  And since when did conservatives get so sensitive?   Then the other half of the "when did you stop beating your wife" question enters: Not every marriage needs children, does it? No, but for those families that do bear children, the role of marriage is critical. Supporters of gay marriage, like the Massachusetts court, have to specifically ignore this to make their argument. To soothe the feelings of childless couples, supporters of gay marriage have to offend the feelings of the vast majority of childbearing parents.    LOL!  What the fuck does this have to do with beating one's wife!?  HAHAHAHAHA!  I think that is SO funny!  But apparently the other question has FINALLY entered.  I have seen NO ONE say that a gay couple doesn't want kids and to raise them as a straight couple would.  I've actually ONLY seen that is what gay couples actually WANT!  In courts, there have been dozens of testimonies from gay parents who wanted to have marriage legalized to SHOW THEIR KIDS THAT THEY ARE A TRUE FAMILY!  Which is what this article is trying to pretend is not the case.  The gay people who want to get married want the whole package.  A loving marriage, and a stable family.  I don't know WHY this is offensive to the vast majority of childbearing parents.   I'll speak for myself. I have no desire to prevent domestic partners from visiting hospital bedsides. I oppose all of the abuses gay partners have to endure for being partners. No landlord should bar gay partners from renting an apartment. I frankly don't see why gays can't designate their partners as dependants or beneficiaries. I hate to admit it, but I care about the gay lifestyle as much as I care about turtles' sex lives: I'm utterly uninterested in it. I figure it's none of my business, and I couldn't possibly care less. Nevertheless, I'm a married man, and a father of four children. Please don't ask me to abandon what my marriage and family means, just to pacify gays who feel disgruntled by the traditions that have carried society through thousands of years.    These traditions haven't carried us anywhere.  I can easily say that the tradition to say bless you after a sneeze has carried society through thousands of years.  I'm glad you're finally speaking for yourself because I thought that's what the rest of the article was doing, but I haven't read a single argument in this whole article.  Traditions have changed through the years.  If you've seen Fiddler on the Roof, you'd know.  Interracial marriage wasn't traditional, women working wasn't traditional, women in the army wasn't traditional, women playing sports wasn't traditional, men staying at home to raise a kid wasn't traditional.  Why aren't those the traditions that have threatened society?  Well, because you just don't think so.  But you just think gays shouldn't marry because you really don't seem to like the idea for some reason.  You try to make it seem you have nothing against gays in your last paragraph, and maybe you don't.  But, if I were to say you shouldn't get married because you're straight, but I happened to like a lot of straight people anyway, I'm sure you'd think that I had maybe an INKLING of dislike for straight people.    Anyway, just because you dislike gay people on even a miniscule level doesn't mean you have to take rights away from us.  And just because we are getting married doesn't mean we're destroying anything of yours either.  Get over yourself and take care of your family for god's sake.  No gay person gives a shit about your family, they want to give a shit about their own.  Let them.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Pentagon: Hersh report 'journalist malpractice'    That's funny that the pentagon is denying that they knew.  Well, what were they gonna say?    Rumsfeld: "I think I'm turning over a new leaf.  Yes, I knew about everything that's been happening.    This whole administration is SO good at pretending that someone didn't know the problem at hand and hence the whole problem has just been a simple miscommunication issue.  What the fuck?  People are being killed, humiliated and abused, and we blame it all on miscommunication?  Fuck you!  The problem is that if you are the boss of a small store, the CEO of a huge company or the president of the free world, you better know what the hell is going on.  If you DON'T know what's going on, that is a problem,  NOT  an excuse.  And, in most cases, that kind of leader would and should be replaced.  As a leader, your job is to know how everything is running and to fix the problems that need fixing.  I guess this is a problem with humanity in general, but all too often if someone leads something or is the head of something, they think they don't have to do any work.  This is what seperates the good leaders from the bad ones.  The good ones take responsibility for the people they look after and take responsibility for their actions KNOWING that what they do may also affect thousands, if not millions and maybe even billions, of people.  And this is why this administration is not a good one.  Their leader doesn't know what's going on, and the people under him ALSO don't know what's going on.  If they don't know what's going on, then who does?  If that question has to be asked, there has to be some major overhauls.  Fuck you, Rumsfeld.  You knew exactly what was going on.  And, if you didn't, then all the more reason you shouldn't be the Defense Secretary of our country.  
     

    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, Nintendo is releasing their new portable console this fall, and, yes, that's true.  However, in USA Today today, the author of the article on the Nintendo DS has some misinformation.  It states that the carts that the console uses can hold up to 1 gigabyte of information.  However, it can only hold 1 gigaBIT.  At first, I thought that he just misspelled the word, but he then continues to explain that a gigabyte holds a bit more than a CD.  Every 8 bits equals a byte.  A gigabit is about 125 bytes of information, or about 125MB (megabytes).  Anyway, it's just rather irritating that these are the people getting paid by relatively large publications.    Ok, point is, they should hire me!  :)    urlLink Nintendo DS USA Today Article 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Rumsfeld Knew: Iraq Prison Abuse Part of Pentagon-Approved Black Ops Program   So, apparently, Rumsfeld knew of the abuse that happened in Iraq.  The 7 army reservists who are looking at abuse charges were told by superiors to humiliate and abuse the Iraqi prisoners.    Honestly, people, do you REALLY think these reservists would've done what they did without the order from superiors?  I think they're pissed enough they have to be in Iraq at all.  I don't think they went so crazy that they were to take Iraqis into a room, make them strip and have them create a naked human pyramid.  Operation "Copper Green".  At least the operation's top secret name is funny.  Actually, no, no, it's not.  You fucking bastard (Rumsfeld).  Anyway, Rumsfeld is definitely going to hell, and I'm just scared because Satan has some serious competition down there.  Good luck, Satan, you'll need it.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      E3 this year started off with a HUGE bang!  Namely Nintendo's conference stole the show, and they were able to show off their stellar upcoming software and new hardware.  As for Sony, their conference blew, but they have some good stuff coming up too.  Microsoft, well, they've still got Xbox Live and Halo 2.  That's good too.  However, since the conferences, there has been a definite fizzle of buzz.  The software coming up is looking quite promising on all three console fronts as well as the PC front, but usually, at this point, I'm looking at movie after movie clip of software previews.  I don't know if sites are getting lazy, but the coverage of this year's E3 is crap!  They have covered the major announcements, sure, but there has been no coverage of the random unannounced software or the software from the little guy.  Maybe there isn't any, but, if that's the case, I guess that would make this E3 less than stellar.  Which is sad.  Anyway, I am quite content with what's coming up.  More than enough stuff there to eat up my paychecks.  Until next year, E3.  We shall definitely meet again.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Not that this has anything to do with evolution, but I thought I'd tie in some more fun stuff that Christians don't believe in.  This just in from a Catholic Bishop:   Catholics who vote for politicians who support abortion rights or gay marriage will be banned from Communion until they have "recanted their positions" and confessed their sin, a Colorado bishop warned.    urlLink Pro-Choice Voters Are Banned From Communion   Although I like the idea of cannibalizing our savior and eating his flesh, I much prefer wonder bread.    As for the rest of these religious retards, I hope religion once and for all just admits it doesn't want you to think on your own.  Only then will it be so clear to so many more people what it's REALLY all about.  From the beginning God said we could not eat from the tree of knowledge.  However, he also gave us free will.  If you tell us how to think, you are indeed also taking away a GOD given right.  But, then again, who am I arguing with?  Ah, yes, hypocrites.  Sorry, my bad.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Gays can finally tie the knot!   Good times.  Let's hope there are no weird road blocks to come.  I think there's still a chance that this is able to be outvoted by the people, right?  I should maybe read the article in full...reading...   In March, the Legislature narrowly passed a proposed state constitutional amendment to ban gay marriages. The proposal won't go to voters until November 2006.   Fuckin heteros.  Anyway, enjoy it while you can, homos.  We still send lots of love your way!
     

    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      If you happen to call yourself a liberal lately, watching the news and just any media outlet out there will, to put it simply, frighten you.  I don't know how many times I've seen dead bodies on the news lately, and it doesn't seem to be stopping anytime soon.  My point?  Censorship.    I find it interesting that Janet Jackson's boob caused so much controversy, but when a person can turn on the TV and see picture after picture of a pyramid of dead Iraqi bodies, I don't understand where the priorities of people here in America lie.  I learned this year where a lot of our censorship in this country comes from, and it seems that a lot of it came from when movies first began to be censored.  If you have any inkling of a thought that all this censorship isn't somehow related to religion, then you're probably someone I'd wanna punch in the face.  So here is a history lesson, for all of you, straight from my college education:    "In the thirties there was no G, PG, R or NC-17. No rating system. Only a bunch of films floating around. Parents had to figure out which were suitable for their children (over half of the 90 million or so annual moviegoers in the thirties were kids). The Legion’s solution was to make all movies suitable for all audiences and called for the country-wide boycott of any film deemed unsuitable for public consumption by the Catholic church. The studios, not wanting to make waves or lose ticket money from negative publicity, instituted a special Production Code. It was presided over by a Jesuit Priest and a Catholic publisher and prohibited almost everything present in the real world of adults. The result were movies that were quite removed from reality. The facts of life – especially the interesting ones that make for good fictional screen dynamics – sex, violence, adultery, crime and injustice were not allowed to be shown. Yet as Mast and Kawin mention in A Short History of the Movies, these have been the elementary materials of playacting and storytelling from the beginnings. Its hardly a joke to say that the Greek tragedies would have been sent back for rewrite.   It seemed absurd, but suddenly, a movie could not show physical passion – even married couples could never be seen sharing a bed and any allusions to sex or seduction could only be hinted at. Showing childbirth was not allowed yet the code also required that the sanctity of marriage and the home be upheld at all times. Swearing – even “cripes” or “nuts” was a no no as well as obvious ones like nudity, drugs, provocative dancing and indulgent kissing. Showing machine guns or even discussing them or the details of a crime was prohibited and of course the police could never be gunned down by the bad guys –whose actions could not be seen as righteous. These were more than suggested guidelines or pleas. If your film didn’t get the Production Code Administration’s (PCA) coveted seal of approval it meant a twenty five thousand dollar fine. The process of obtaining the seal was long and often humiliating for filmmakers: First your story was mulled over as a general idea, then if OK’d, the script got written which was then poured over by the PCA and inevitably changes were ordered. Eventually, after change upon change, the script was given the go-ahead to enter into actual shooting. PCA officials showed up on set to make sure script changes were being carried out and eventually at private screenings to oversee the finished product. If any scenes remained that were still unsuitable you had to cut them out and re-shoot if necessary. Then, and only then was your film given the final seal of approval.   Many opponents to such totalitarian practices stood up and tried to defy these rules, however, the Studio heads realized that their job was to please dozens of millions of people week in and week out. The fact was that a good portion of those millions saw the code as a just, wholesome, Christian necessity and the studios – run mostly by Jewish immigrants - did what they had to do to keep audiences happy."    It's just hypocritical.  We are more worried about breasts than we are about the lives of human beings.  Why can't the FCC and other governing bodies at least say we shouldn't watch people killing each other, fictionally or realistically (not that I would want to censor ANYTHING!)?  Well, because we can't get what we want in this world without killing others.  So, that's ok.  But, from now on, just make sure you have some clothes on.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, E3 is upon us all, and many people out there don't even know it.  It's the Electronic Entertainment Expo (hence the name E3) and it shows all future things video games.  So far, I've been creaming my pants because Nintendo has unveiled their next portable baby, the Nintendo DS.  This bad boy has two screens, has 3D capabilities, one screen is touch sensitive, it has a built in microphone for voice recognition and to top it all off, it has Wi-Fi and Bluetooth capabilites.    Not to be outdone, Sony unveiled their newest bad boy portable, the Sony PSP (Playstation Portable).  This gorgeous little baby is essentially a portable PS2 system with just a little less horsepower.  It has amazingly high tech specs for a portable and, due to those, has superb graphic output.  It also has Wi-Fi and Bluetooth capabilities and also has an analog stick just to drive this system on home.    I will be buying both.    On the software end, Nintendo has unveiled Metroid Prime 2, Pikmin 2, Paper Mario 2, Mario Tennis, Mario Party 6 and...excuse me...just give me a minute...I...I just...please excuse these tears of pure...of pure emotion, but...Nintendo has unveiled THE NEXT LEGEND OF ZELDA GAME!  AHHHHHHHHHH!!!  I know, orgasms all around.  After the shockingly cute and ultimately gorgeous and great game called The Legend of Zelda: The Wind Waker, many Nintendo enthusiasts were sad to leave their realistic and serious world of Link behind.  However, Nintendo has heard their fans' pleas and have delivered something that looks to be extraordinary.  On the third party front, there's also the stunning Resident Evil 4 that will be coming out by the end of the year.  I can't wait.  Then there's Sony's line up...but that seems to be rather boring this year.  Same with Microsoft's.  There are still 3 more days to E3, so I'll definitely be posting on here more.  See ya.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, I bought an Apple iPod a while back, and I loved it...'til now.  It looked pretty and it functioned well...at first.  However, barely have it and I come upon our first year together, and it's already broken.  It quickly runs out of batteries, it has a lagged response to touch and now it won't even play music.  BTW, in case you didn't know, playing music is this baby's main function.  It's like making a baby and then it stops growing...ok, bad analogy.  The point is, don't buy an Apple iPod.  I'll be getting an iRiver mp3 player next.  I've heard those are great quality products.  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Bonjour, and welcome to The Gyro Rainbow Palace:)  I was inspired to start writing on a blog by a guy named Ryan Dunn.  He's a cool guy who I met at a party.  And I was also inspired by my friend Myles who ALSO has a blog...so, together, they've inspired me to make a blog.  Wow, so much excitement already.    So without further ado, here is Sisko's blog.  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>