<Blog>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lately, I've been thinking about the things we miss out on in this life.  One of my favorite verses in the Bible is Hebrews 13:2: "Do not forget to entertain strangers, for by doing so, some have entertained angels and not known it."  To think that I could pick a man up on the side of the road and he be an angel, interesting.  To think that on the day you step foot on the streets of gold and see an angel fly by that has the same face as sweaty and smelly "John" that you picked up on the side of the road in SC.  Strangers are very interesting, in a handshake, they become an aquaintence or maybe a new friend.    You can tell a lot about a person in how they treat people, mainly strangers.  On a date, watch how your date treats the waitress.  In the drive-thru at Zaxby's (of course Zaxby's is the only drive-thru you should be in), watch how people treat the person taking their order.  You can listen to a person talk all day long, but the real character comes out when you watch how they interact with the world.  One of my buddies tipped the guy at Auto-Zone the other day.  I dig that.  I love strangers and I love people that love strangers.    A few months ago, I was driving in my Jeep down a dark road in SC.  I happen to look to my left and see a glimpse of what I thought was a man standing in the road.  I slow down, pull over, and look back.  I see nothing.  I backed up a few more yards and as car goes by, I can see this person again.  The road is pitch black.  As I roll down my window, I can definitely now see that there is a person standing in the median of this major highway.  I am a little nervous.  The only time I can see this person is when a car goes by and the lights illuminate the side of the road.  I ask, "Is everything okay?"  As soon as the words roll of my lips, I see the shadow of this person as a car goes by and the reflection of a gun behind the shadow.  This is where fight or flight kicks in.  I'm 20 feet away and in the dark.  I must confess that I do carry a 9mm in my Jeep, I tucked into my jeans and jumped out the Jeep.  As soon as my feet hit the ground, the person starts walking towards me, I'm scared, I definitely see this stranger with a 12-Gauge shotgun.  This situation is not one I would recommend.  Everything in me thought something was about to go down, and it did.  The scary figure strapping a 12-gauge pump turns out to be a 10 year old boy crying in the middle of the road.  As he walked up and this all dawned on me, I asked him, "Is this gun loaded?"  He said, "Yes."  I took it from him and noticed that it was the same model of shotgun that I grew up with.  Sure enough, it was also loaded, 2 in the chamber, 1 in the hole.  I calmed him down, put the gun in my jeep and asked him what happened.  Apparently his mom's boyfriend left him out in the woods or either he was lost.  He didn't know what to do, so he walked to the middle of the biggest highway he could find in the pitch dark.  He was hiding the gun because he knew nobody would help him if he were carrying a 12 gauge, so he hid it behind his leg.  Wow.  Imagine that.  We called his mom and he happen to live in my town, so I took him home.  Also got a chance to talk with his mom once I got there.  She told me that she was going to try and start getting back to church.    This is so much like life and evangelism.  Looking from the outside in, you have a man carrying a 12 gauge shotgun, loaded shotgun and standing in the middle of the road.  In reality, you have a crying 10 year-old boy who just wants his mommy and a ride home.  How many times in this life do we ignore sharing the gospel with someone because they look smarter than us, they raised you, they have more money than you, don't dress like you, don't speak like you, or enter your excuse here.  The Bible says that the righteous are as bold as a lion.  Be a lion.  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink      You know, since I've been called to the ministry, I've come to realize a few things.  A person in the ministry is called to a different standard of life, not any better of a life, not a "holier than thou" type of life, just different.  A life that's not "normal."  You can't just marry any girl, the Lord has to be leading her in the same way.  I also know that I want to be real with people and unlike the stereotype that many preachers have brought to the world, good or bad.    I subconsciously made a pact, that if I ever had kids, I wouldn't incorporate them into all my messages.  I would not talk about the family for every illustration.  Well this post is a slap in the face of that.  Right now, I can't use a girlfriend for an example, I could use a dog, well I don't have one but my roommate does.  This animal entered into our house a few months back, I've watched her grow from this small puppy, to this big dog.  So big now that if she jumps in your lap, you will question your ability to have kids.  She's huge.  I've learned a lesson about life through a dog.  My roomie works a lot and I spend a lot of time alone with the animal.  When I walk in the door, the dog about goes nuts to see me.  She literally does not want to eat, only cares about being hugged and petted.  She doesn't even want to go outside to pee, she cares only for you.  When I eat, she sits at my feet, waiting on crumbs to fall.  She follows me from room to room, only to lay right back at my feet again.  She will do something mean, (like chew my $$ dress shoes) and i scold her, only to find her 5 minutes later, back at my feet, always staring intently, even for crushed ice to fall from my mouth, so she can eat it up! Nasty! but anyway.   I started thinking about my relationship with the Lord.  I was sitting at the table with a Zaxby's kickin chicken sandwich in my hand, just watching this dog stare at me.  I rarely follow the Lord like this dog follows me.  How often do I lay at His feet, after this life has scolded me.  How often do I sit under Him at His table, waiting for something to fall from His hand.  How often do I sacrifice my wants, my needs, to spend time with Him?  It's rare.  I'm stuck in this Romans 7 tongue twister life.  I want to do what is right, I want to seek Him, but I often don't.  My sin strangles the life from me.  I hear you Paul!  Just like this post, the thing I never wanted to do, I have just done.  Told a story though a dog.  Kiki Peaky is her name.  At least that's what I renamed her.  Hey! Jesus renamed His friends, aren't we supposed to do the same?  Just a thought.   :) 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          The title summarizes life as I have journeyed to know it.  I'm not sure if there is one person in this world that does not go through hard times at some point.  From the people with no money to the people with too much money, we experience hard times.  Hard times can come in the form of many things, loss of job, loss of home, loss of wife, loss of husband, loss of car, loss of love, loss of life.  Death is not something that is easy for us to talk about and again, I do not know of one person who can handle it well.  The statistics are in, 10 out of 10 people die.  The Lord even cried when one of his buddies died.  Jesus wept over the death of his friend Lazarus.    About a year ago, my best friend discovered that her dad had cancer.  At first, it wasn't sure exactly how bad the cancer was in his body.  Eventually, they found out that the cancer was all over and he had a few months to live.  Here is a man who had everything, a great job, a beautiful family, a nice home, a nice life.  Here is a man who had a smile on his face at every point in the day.  A man that brought joy to so many people lives.  He never met a stranger, everyone was a friend.  Here was a man with a few months to live.  I have often asked myself, would I want to know when my time would come.  I still do not know the answer to that question, right now I would say no.    During the last few months of his life, many things happened.  Gradually the cancer took his strength, his ability to eat, but never to smile.  The doctors told us that he had a month to live.  He went from walking around in one week to bed-ridden the next week.  When we are faced with death, many questions come to mind, many conversations come to mind.  I was able to sit down with him and ask about life, ask him about how he felt about the Lord through all this.  He said his faith never wavered, he knew God had not left him, he could see the Lord through the people that came to served him and his family.  Through the friends that showed him love.  He still saw the Lord.  I saw these friends, they were always at the house, always serving, never expecting anything in return.  I saw God's hand on all of them, through the service of his people.  Saints are not dead people, you don't have to die to become a saint, saints are people who have repented of their sins, and put their faith in Christ.  They love the Lord and serve Him and serve others.  To that point, I had never sat down with someone and talked about death.  The Lord worked in my heart through that conversation.  To see someone in so much pain, but occassionally still smiling, moved my heart.  A man a few days from death, able to look up with a smile, and say, "hey bud!"  Only to go back to sleep.    A few days later, we all sat around him and read him Bible verses.  Verses of hope, of a future.  It was the day before Good Friday.  Over and over, we just read the Bible to him.  A beautiful time.  On Good Friday, most of everyone had stepped out the room, I stood at the doorway, somewhat looking in.  He breathed his last.  I walked in the room, then walked back out to tell his daughters.  One 18, one 24.  Everyone came in the room, standing around just looking.  It was an atmosphere that I cannot describe.  The oldest daughter, sat on his bed, looked at him for a second, then with a heart full of hope told everyone that this is a day that we should rejoice and be joyful and put a smile on our face.  I've never seen one look at death like she did.  She put hope in what the world would see as hopeless.  We joined hands and just prayed, and prayed, and cried, and rejoiced.  There is a verse in Psalm 116:15:  "Precious in the sight of the Lord are the death of His saints."  As sad as it was to see a man who loved the Lord die, as Christians, we could still have hope. The Lord had not left us, He had not left this man, while we were crying, the Lord was in the process of welcoming him home.    How many conversations should we have had yesterday?  Time is short in this life, God has given us today, salvation is today, tomorrow is not promised.   
     
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, so I don't listen to OutKast much, but someone tabbed the song, so we had to play on the guitar. Yes everyone, this is General Taguba's daughter!    urlLink   
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    As a child, still chewing my tongue.  Mom says..."Justin, people are going to think you are special if you keep doing that."  I have ever since. Some Habits are hard to break!
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, so I simmered on this for a day, wondering what I might write in this special place on the internet that most people call a "BLOG."  I think this is going to be like jumping into cold water, it takes you a while to get used to it.  This teaches me to choose my words, I never know who might read them.  What if I lived my life like that.    So yesterday I realized that life is too short to complain.  I believe complaining is one of the biggest struggles today.  People do it all the time, sometimes not realizing it.  I sometimes complain but often try to catch myself before it's verbalized.  A positive aspect of being a Christian is that God gives us hope and joy through the tough times, something most of the world does not have.    For example, yesterday was a small demonstration of what the great Flood could have been like.  It rained like goats and cows.  And yes, the top was off my jeep.  So I jumped in my tug boat of water and headed to guitar practice.  People always give you a funny look when you are in a Jeep with the top off, while it is raining.  Or maybe it's because I keep an umbrella over my head at the redlights.  Anyway, after practice, it's still pouring and I get to talk to this guy at the door of the music store.  You always ask yourself, ok, how can I witness to this guy?  Sometimes I do, sometimes I fail.  I didn't get to witness to this man, but it was funny how we started our conversation.  He says something about all the rain and then..."Wouldn't you hate to be the guy driving the Jeep with the top down right there."  Of course I had to fess up and admit that it was mine and I was the dummy who didn't put the top on his jeep or remember to check weather.com.  But either way...the rain, my top down, a soaking wet ride led up to being able to meet a new friend that I will now see on a weekly basis at the music store.  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I never thought I would be the guy with a weblog, but here it is.  I'm not sure what I will post here, but time will tell.    You wonder how many of your thoughts you want the world to know, often times, I would say maybe 10%.    I will soak on this and get back to you soon.  :)
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There are times in your life when you just feel like you are floating through.  A month can go by and you really don't know what you accomplished or learned.  This past month has not been like that.  I'm learning.  Honesty.  What is the first word or thought that pops in your head when you hear that?  A few different images and thoughts enter my head.  For most of us, you probably fall into 1 of two catgories, comfronter or avoider.  The latter will do everything at all costs to avoid conflict and problems.  The confronter is usually very confrontational and wants to handle the problem right away and get it all out on the table, that's me.  Sometimes I wonder how honest I should be.  There are gray areas. When do you REALLY have the DTR?  Is it 1 date? two dates? 3 dates?  Haha. And we all know this one: "How does this dress look?" Well in all honesty, I don't like it at all.  That would be my first thought if I didn't like the dress.  But should I say it?  Probably not.  Do I say it, yes.    Honesty can be a very positive thing.  There are so many people that go around life with grudges in their hearts about people that have no idea they even have a grudge against them.  Truth and honesty can set you free from that, just confront them, say how you feel, settle things before the sun goes down.  Well it all sounds simple in theory, follow-through is ROUGH.  Sure, being honest and truthful will probably hurt someone's feelings, and possibly hurt your own, but it's what is right.  The times in my life when I have been very honest in truthful have been some of the most rewarding experiences.  I cannot honestly and truthfully say they have been the easiest, but the more rewarding and helpful.  There is something about saying how you feel that liberates you and sets you "free" as the Bible says.   I want to be free.  
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's late Friday night, well I guess it's actually early Saturday morning at this point.  What an interesting Friday it was.  It went something like this...  So I must admit that I am a cellphone enthusiast.  I'm not admitting that I talk on my cell phone all the time, only admitting that I like to have a nice phone.  So Cingular informed me that I have been with them almost 5 years and have never been given a free phone.  Thanks Cingular for telling me now.  I order the  urlLink Nokia 3300 , we are talking about MP3 player, recorder, games, phone, and more.  Yes!  FEDEX attempted delivery and I was not home, aww man.  So I tracked them down and found out that I could pick my phone up in Greenville, so off I went.  On the way to Greenville, I find a man on the side of the road, "Jump in, where ya goin?"  He says..."I need to go to Spartanburg.".  Cool, so off we went, his name is Danny.  Danny works near the same place I work and had been hitch-hiking to get back home.  So we're driving along and I realize that I still need to pick up my cell phone.  Danny says he doesn't mind if I stop by FEDEX, so we go to FEDEX.  Well the driver is not back with my phone, so we head out to Spartanburg to take Danny home.  We had interesting conversation, talked about work, what he does, where he is from, fishing, nuclear reactors, cars, and bass fish.  We finally make it to his house and it's pouring rain, has been all day.  He gets out, grabs his stuff, and tells me thank- you.  Here is the hard part.  I want to witness to him, but fear creeps over my body and I sorta go numb.  Ahhh shrug off fear, hell is real, so is heaven. :)  So I explain to Danny that I cannot just give him a ride, I have to tell him something else way more important.   Me:  Danny, what do you think happens when you die? Danny:  (stares intently at me, almost waiting for me to answer my own question) Me: What would you like to happen? Danny:  I Guess I want to go to heaven. Me:  Me too, how do you think you get there? Danny: I don't know how. Me: Let me ask you three questions...We then went on to talk about the 10 Commandments and sin, Have you ever lied before?  He says yes, What does that make you, he says liar, and so on so on.  Then we get to Jesus, I get to explain to him that because of our sin, Jesus was sent by God to be our sacrifice, to pay a price for all the bad things we do and think.  He understood.  He smiled.  I showed him a tract that says..."GODISNOWHERE"  He says....God is nowhere.  I say, read again, He says, GOD IS NOW HERE.  He asks if he can keep it, I say of course.  I could see care in his eyes and he knew I loved him because I wasn't afraid to tell him about Jesus.  He then went on to tell me about his family and how he wanted them to come to church and find Jesus too.  I dropped him off, we smiled, he said thanks again and I left.  Wow, what a feeling, but oh wait, the day is not over.  So my flesh kicks in after this and all I can think about is this cell phone.  I have 30 minutes to get to FEDEX before they close.  So I try to make it when all of the sudden BOOM, my tire explodes after hitting something on the interstate, a brand new set of tires too.  It knocks me to the side of the road and yes, I have a huge flat.  So I run back down the road in the rain and try to find the object that flattened my tire.  Nothing there. I look further, nothing!  It's vanished!  Well I run back to my Jeep and get out my jack.  Now of course, the jack is too small for my car because it has over-sized tires.  I watch cars pass, and pass, and some beep, some people say mean things.  Lexus rolls, probably some preachers roll by, maybe some deacons, nobody stops.  Finally a man named Ezeal stops to help me.  A black man around the age of 40 I would say.  He is so nice, he runs over with a hydro jack and has my car off the ground in no time.  I change the tire and bam, it's done.  I asked him if he was a believer (inside, I knew he was).  He says, YES!  He told me the that he passed me but the Lord told him to go back and help, so he listened.  A really great guy, put the jack back in his car, told him I would see him in heaven and away he went.    Well as I'm finishing up with my tire, (hole the size of a football in it with a completely shattered rim).  Something else happens.  A truck comes screeching into the emergency lane about 25 feet behind me.  I'm like, wow, what in the world.  I walk back to check on this man and he jumps out his brand new truck screaming.  (I am carrying a tire iron at this point)  He curses me out pretty much and continues to scream profanity.  He has a flat and has hit the same piece of "something" I hit.  I explain to him that I hit the same thing and he then screams back at me that his truck his brand new with a 1100 miles.  Now I must stop and be honest, I really felt like jacking him upside the head with my tire iron for cursing at me, but I know that is not Christ-like and well I didn't :).  So I walk back to my Jeep and finish up.  As I'm finishing, he comes back and apologizes to me and I accept his apology.  No big deal, it's raining and we both have flat tires.  So I go back and look again for this "something" in the road, I find nothing.   I return to his truck and help him change his tire.  I notice a funny looking sticker on the back of his brand new truck, looks like a flag with a heart in the middle of it.  I discerned something funny about him.  I asked about the sticker, he says, "you don't want to know what it means."  Well it turns out the sticker stands for..."I'm a man who likes men who wear levis and leather."  Thank the Lord I didn't have on my levis and leather, whew, thanks God.  He then precedes to think I'm 32 years old.  Humbled.  As I'm putting his old tire back under his car, I notice blood dripping from his hands, and then realize the blood is probably all over the tool I am using.  He looks at me and says..."Oh don't worry, I'm HIV negative"  Well ya know, that's good news to know.  He then goes to tell me that he does not have sex with men.  Why this information was volunteered to me, I'm not sure.  I call personal foul and TMI!  Well of course I try to swing the conversation to the Lord.  He then tells me that he is a christian but doesn't believer that homosexuality is wrong.  He even grabs his Bible out the front of his truck and shows me his cross on his rear view mirror.  This man was quite interesting.  His father was a pastor and died when he was 10.  His father never knew about his preferences.  We talked a lil more about the Lord and I felt the Lord lead me away from him and I told him bye and to be careful on his ride to ATL.    As soon as I get on the road, there is another car in front of me smoking.  I get out, see this guy that happens to be an aquaintence of mine's cousin, funny.  I hit the road and head home.  So I learned that no matter what plans I have in my heart, the Lord is going to place me and any other believer where He wants you.  I think about all the conversations today and all the people I met, it all started by picking up one hitch-hiker.  I challenge whoever reads this to make yourself available to the Lord and don't just pray for opportunities, TAKE THEM.  They are all over the place and there is not enough time in the day to get to them all, but try.  I'm so glad we can be labeled and identified with Christ, we were all once a bunch of hitch-hikers that the Lord, in His grace, picked us up.  To Him we owe ALL.  
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I luv when you have a weekend that is so interesting it makes the next Monday feel like a Friday.  So maybe I should explain.  So I went down to Columbia to help a friend with her A/C, did that, then hung out at the pool all day long, yep, burned again.  I will be moving soon so a brotha should try and find a place to live, so I went around Columbia looking for houses and townhomes, grown-up life as they call it.  It was a beautiful Saturday and very hot.  Many people call Columbia,SC the "armpit" of the South.  I can see why.  You walk outside and instantly these little beads of sweat appear on your forehead.  Found some cool houses then hung out at Barnes & Noble for a bit.  Let me ask you a question.  I saw a book there called "hacking for dummies."  Hacking is a crime and now we have books teaching us how to commit crimes.  Great.  I was rather amused.  Left Barnes $ Noble and went to meet someone for dinner.  Of course I didn't have a top on my Jeep and surely it begins to rain, we get soaked.  Pull into a hospital parking garage (haha) for about an hour or so, then head out, drop her off, then head home.  (2 hours away.)  Here is where the story gets weird.  If anything weird is going to happen on the road, it's going to happen to me.  I believe in my heart that God has ordained me for roadside ministry.  It is so fun and very amusing.  So I'm travelling down Interstate 20 around 12:30 AM. As I am leaving out of Richland County, I see brake lights flashing ahead.  And yes there is a traffic jam.  STOP THE TAPE.  This is not your everyday traffic jam.  Let me define...TRAFFIC JAM - two cars  in both lanes of I-20 completely stopped and parked sideways with one truck trying to go between them in a frantic maneuver.  So as I pull up on this scene, all I can hear is..."get her out, she's drunk, get her out!!!"  This is all coming from a woman who is standing in front of this truck.  A few people are yelling at me and commanding me to park my car in the road, similar to theirs, so this woman cannot leave the scene.  I oblige.  So now there is no real way to get through I-20.  (during all this, I got the feeling that this woman in the frantic truck has probably hit someone and is now trying to flee from the scene.)  As the frantic woman in the truck realizes there is nowhere for her to go, I see terror in her eyes.  On her driver's side, there is a man screaming at her, "GET OUT!"  In front of her, there is a woman screaming at her, "GET OUT of the car."  So I figured, well they are all screaming at her, I'll approach in nice guy fashion.  "Mam, please step out the car, we are trying to help you."  Ummm. Nice guy fashion does not help either and she is gearing up to run over the woman in front of her.  We then scream at the woman in front of the truck, "Move, she is going to run over you!"  The woman does not move.  The frantic woman in the truck gears into reverse and stomps the gas to reverse into oncoming traffic, almost taking out an SUV in her path.  I try and chase her on foot, not a great idea.  I could hear cars screeching off the road and into the grass.  I returned to my Jeep and waited on her to come back by.  Sure enough, she comes zooming by.  So I become a policeman for the night and chase her.  I followed her for around 10 miles or so.  She takes an exit in Camden and I call the hwy. patrol to ask them if I should continue to follow her or let her go.  They ask for her tag number.  Eventually she pulls into a police station and about 5 police cars meet her there.  I pull in shortly after.    So you're probably wondering what in the world.  As was I.  Troopers arrive and ask us questions for about 45 minutes.  The woman comes over to my Jeep to see me.  I introduce myself and we begin to talk about what happen.  Her name is Linda.  Linda was not drunk at all and was in a very normal state of mind at this point.  Apparently she dosed off on the road and swerved.  She may have swerved near someone and they then assumed she was drunk.  Road rage probably kicked in and they get help from another driver on the road.  So they corner her and slow her down.  Linda probably didn't realize what she had done, (the swerve.)  Well all she knew was there were about 4 white people trying to get into her truck.  She said there was no way she was going to let them in.  She told the police that I was really nice, but she didn't know whether I was "with" the other "people" or not.  Haha.  She told me she was going to protect herself at all costs, even it meant running over the lady standing in front of her.    So to sum up the story, I stayed in Camden for a few hours and ended up having an awesome conversation with Linda and her fiance, who came in later.  We had a great talk about the Lord, sin, and about the end of the world.  The Lord may not cause traffic jams, but He does know how to use them.    I finally made it home around 4AM, extremely tired.  I luv interesting weekends.    What I learned this weekend:  I like interesting people, challenging conversations, and interstates.  Anybody up for a road trip? :)
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was a good day, I really don't have bad days. Well rarely. There was that time when I got towed twice in the same day, two different states, two different cars. How could I get mad? That's just funny and could only happen to a man obsessed with gnomes. Speaking of gnomes, well I didn't see one today, but I did see this nice lil turtle at the shooting range. I would like your comments to try and explain how this nice lil box turtle found his way on top of this shot up Yoo Hoo can located at our local shooting range.  Don't worry, we saved his life.  My heroic friend Nick loves to save box turtles from the road.  Congrats Nick! 4 saved today!  Also, it has been brought to my attention that there is a "man-eater" in Columbia, SC. Watch out boyz, she will chew you up. If you see her, make way, and God forbid, do not be one of those guys that calls her. Oh my my. Her name is _ A _ _ _ N.  On a serious note, well how could there be a serious note when this blog has a picture of a turtle on a yoo hoo can? Well let's try. Why is there such a huge division between calvinists and armenianists? Don't we all have a common goal of reaching the lost? Don't we all have the same command, to go out and make disciples? It baffles me that so many Christians waste their time arguing these points...does anyone out there really know it all? I'm sure some would answer yes and I would say...goodnight, I'm going to bed.   urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      An interesting day in my heart.  Have you ever had those points in your faith where you feel numb?  The problem with the numbness was that it has been numb for many months and you have only now come to realize it.  That's me.  It is so easy to get comfortable with the way you are living and it gets even easier to get comfortable with the sin in your life.  One thing leads to another, gradually your faith weakens and weakens.  Your influence on people for the positive gets worse and worse.  I think for many years, I have been spiritually spoiled.  Spoiled in the way that little kids are spoiled by rich parents.  I've never had a really really terrible time in my faith, although I have had some slow spots.  Tonight was one of those nights that I saw myself for who I truly am, sinful and weak.  One of those nights that you can feel people praying for you.  It's a strange, but refreshing feeling.  To know that God has not left me on the side of the road and no matter how nasty the sin in my life has gotten me, He still wants to pick me up.  We are so blessed that God does not give up on us and we are even more blessed that He doesn't treat us how we often treat Him.  Oh I would really be messed up.    God continues to chase and no matter how many times we run, He will find us.  I'm so glad He found me.  
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What a beautiful night it has been.  The sky is perfect and when your car has no top on it, you really appreciate a nice night.  Tonight was not just about good weather.  I met a good friend in Greenville to catch a movie.  We had fun, drove around for a while with the top down and listened to music.  Not much was open after the movie, so I dropped her off and headed home.  As soon as I turned onto the interstate, there is a man stopped on the side of the road.  I pull up on the side with him.  An older man walks around the car with a disappointed look on his face, he's got a flat.  Flat, no problem, let's put on the spare, well, the spare is flat too.  Let's go buy another tire, he doesn't have a key to get his tire off the rim, trouble.  We came to the conclusion that we could do nothing for his Ford Escort and we decided that I would just take him home.  Mr. Bill is his name.  Normal looking man, mid 60's I would say.   He jumped in my Jeep was amazed that it had no top; he was surprised that he could just stick his hands up in the air.  "Where does this go?", he asks of the seatbelt.  Good question to ask in a vehicle with no restraints.  I enjoy picking up people on the side of the road, to hear and listen to their story.  This night was no different.  I asked about his story and he gladly told me.    He explained to me that he lived in Florida for most of his life and he was a tile mason.  He and his wife divorced when his daughter was 2 years old and he never saw her again.  He eventually left the tile business and drove freight trucks, only to get in a wreck in New Mexico and have the truck taken from him, forcing him to hitch hike all the way back to Florida.  He returned, had no money, and his landlord kicked him out of his apartment.  He then lived on the streets for 6 months, and slept under a bridge.  He had a terrible relationship with his ex-wife and had not spoken to her in years. His ex-wife eventually told his daughter that her father was not the man she was married to, but another man (Mr. Bill) that lived somewhere in the US.  She would not tell her where.  His daughter set out to find him.  Eventually, through the internet, she tracked him from state to state, finally finding him.  They were reunited in Myrtle Beach during the 4th of July.  He said it was a beautiful time.  She and her husband convinced him to leave Florida and move to SC.  So he did.  He moved in with his daughter until he could get on his feet.  His ex-wife found out and kicked him out.  (She owned the house.)  So he was back on the streets and living in his car, but had a job.  Mr. Bill found an apt after living 3 months in his car, only to find himself on the side of the road, with noone to call and no money in his pocket.    As I dropped him off, he wanted to get my number so he could pay me back.  I explained to him that it was my calling to pick up people on the side of the road. He smiled.  I gave him my number in case he needed anything else.  (Fear enters here)  How could I hear this man's life, love him enough to stop and help him, love him enough to bring him home, but then stop in that love and not share with him the most important person in my life?  As he was about to step out my Jeep, I looked at him and told him that I was not being fair to him if I just let him leave.  I got out a tract that says "GODISNOWHERE".  I asked him what it said.  He said, "God is nowhere." It's a trick, it should read, "God is now Here." We went on to talk about the end of life and what happens next.  He told me that he was born again and knows the Lord.  He also told me that he studied to be a pastor for two years.  Wow.  I asked him, "are you following the Lord?"  Good conversation.  He told me that he had been praying right before I drove up.  He said that many people passed by him, nobody would help.  I mentioned to him before that I had spent my fair share of times on the side of the road, sometimes in the rain and in the cold, while people just passed by and glanced over, only to continue on their path.  I explained to him that the Lord will never leave him stranded on the side of the road, never.    I've had my heart broken a few times in this life, maybe a girl, maybe a friend that lets you down.  I've never told any of those people, "hey, thanks for breaking my heart."  As much as it hurts, I love when the Lord breaks my heart, and tares down as I tear down, all the nasty stuff that's in there.  The Lord is the only one I will thank when He breaks my heart.  (Psalm 51:17)  There is nothing wrong with fear, but there is something wrong with shame.  I fear people sometimes, I fear witnessing to them, I fear what they will think of me, I fear they will look down on me, but I really pray that I will never be ashamed of talking about the Lord.  He's never left me on the side of the road and He never will.  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Most people might say, "Time Flies and then you die."  What a morbid thought.  There is a lot of truth in that statement, but life is so much more.  I just finished up a long weekend with Memorial Day off and a day off from work.  It's so nice when you can take a few days to relax, spend time with friends, and just chill out.  You think about all the days that pass that you wasted.  The days that could have been a great memory, but instead I slept in or wasted time doing something stupid.  Like yesterday, on my day off.  I spent most of the day doing nothing.  Then my friend Lee says he will teach me to wakeboard.  Sure enough, in no time at all, he taught me.  Time that I would have spent doing nothing, I now spent accomplishing something really fun and cool and also spending time with a friend.   I've realized in my 24 years one main thing.  Life is about forming relationships.  I'm not talking about "dating" but solid friendships and friends.  It takes effort to put yourself out there and share your heart with people, but that's how we grow, that's how we learn.  One great thing about living in a sub-division is that random people stop by all the time.  Salesmen, pest control, fund raising people, candy people, and can't forget the ice cream man who has the nice lil jingle he plays that you can hear approximately 1 mile away.  Today was the day of the pest control guy.  I hear a knock on the door and I get up to answer it.  A very young guy is standing at the door and explains to me our options on fighting off the rodents and other crawling things that lurk around Easley, SC.  We had a good conversation.  I got to know where he was from, what he does for fun, and where he lives.  Something inside me told me he was mormon.  Weird I know, but I felt it.  I asked him if he went to church anywhere and sure enough, he is mormon.  So we talked about that for a short time and then went on to talk about mountain biking and kayaking.  I invited him to go mountain biking with me sometime and told him that I would like the chance to talk about mormonism.  He politely agreed and hopefully he will call.  I realized during this time that I had a root beer in my hand that probably looked like a long neck beer.  Some people look down on beer and it is a hindrance to sharing the gospel, so I made it clear to him that it was root beer :).  It was good conversation because he's a big fan of the root beer, haha.  As am I.    So my goal in this life is to make solid relationships with people and to genuinely care about their feelings and cares in this world.  In reality, this is a hard world to live in and deal with, but the Lord did not leave us alone.  He gave us the Holy Spirit and He also gave us friends...how great they are...how great they are.  On a side note, one of my friends bought a car on Ebay!  Not only have I got him to blog, he now has followed my direction and BUYS CARS ON EBAY!  Congrats to   urlLink  Billy Rogers!  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's been quite a while again since I've written anything, hey, I'm writing something.&nbsp; It feels good to sit down and just vomit your mind out through your fingers.&nbsp; That sounded gross, sorry.&nbsp; It's liberating to tell the truth.&nbsp; Lately, I've been fighting with God and slowly growing, but growing.&nbsp; Things have picked up and I'm happy. &nbsp; This past weekend was jam packed.&nbsp; Drove down to Columbia, SC on Friday night, went bowling with my boy  urlLink Jason (he has added nothing) and some new girl_with a space_friends.  We had a great time and stayed out until about 4AM.  Why do I do these things to my body?  Either way, it was fun and worth the pain of waking up the next day.  I left Jason's apt and headed to Marion FBC to speak at a college cook-out.    It's always fun to think and pray about what you are supposed to speak on.  Sometimes the Lord just hands you a happy meal and you are confident that is your message.  Other times, it seems that it's more like a blender and you really don't feel clarity about anything, these are the times that can be interesting and fun.  When I got to Marion, I noticed two guys that I went to school with.  Erin and Jon Jones.  Both of these guys are really following the Lord now and leading worship at their church.  I love hearing and seeing my old buddies talk about the Lord.  I ended up talking abou Balaam and the Donkey.  Quite fun to talk about.  Proof that the Lord can use an ass and I'm not being funny either :)  If you want to read, it's in Numbers 21-22.    Sometimes I can feel the Lord all over me while I speak, other times I feel like it's a struggle.  It's probably not something people can notice, but I do, and it bothers me.  I think the Lord is teaching me to depend on Him completely and not just on what I know, which is not much, and I'm not being humble.  It was a great time and I got to have some good conversations afterwards.  After speaking, I hugged everyone and headed up to Pawley's Island to Carrie Turner's.  Her family is awesome and I feel like I'm at home when I'm around them.  Her family grew up in the same place that my dad did so they share a lot of the same.  Her dad tells the same type of jokes my dad tells, it's great.   urlLink Josh Turner  is Carrie Turner's older brother, he's a country singer.  I said it like that because everyone always says, Carrie is Josh Turner's sister.  I want to be special.  His tour bus got in a wreck right before we went to church, but everyone was ok, and the man whose car was in the road, walked away with only a scratch.  (He is blessed!).  I had a great time with them and at their church.  Her church had a bbq for her and she raised lots of bling bling for a mission trip to Costa Rica!    All and all it was a great weekend, not to mention that it rained the whole time, and of course, no top on my Jeep.  I love pulling up beside people and watching them laugh.  Sometimes older ladies say, "i'm sorry darlin."  It's quite amusing.  Rain feels good this time of year!  This was a random blog and somewhat out of my personality.  I just hit my head on my motorcyle while I was trying to fix it, it is currently swelling up above my eye and this could have something to do with why I am writing a blog that describes most of my weekend and could help give evidence into why I just wrote a paragraph run-on sentence.  The Lord is good, All the time. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        "Simon, Simon, Satan has asked to sift you as wheat. But I have prayed for you, Simon, that your faith may not fail. And when you have turned back, strengthen your brothers." (Luke 22:31)  I think this shall by my theme verse for the past few months.  You have Jesus, sitting at a table with his closest friends, u have arguing over who is the greatest amongst the disciples, and then you have Peter.  Peter told Jesus that he would basically do anything for Him, he would go to prison with him and he would also die for Him.  Jesus replies with the above verse. Anytime in the Bible when God really wanted someone to hear something, He would say their name twice, "Moses Moses"  "Abraham Abraham"  "Saul Saul"...and now Jesus does it with Peter by calling him "Simon Simon."  It's neat that Jesus uses Peter's old name and not his new name.  Some people think that Jesus was trying to talk about the "Old Man" in Peter, his flesh.  Boy can I hear this.    To think that Jesus, in His quiet times with God the father, actually prayed for Peter by name.  And not only prayed for Peter, but prayed for what Peter would do once he got his heart back in the right place.  That's love, care, and many more adjectives if I knew more vocabulary.   I feel a lot like Peter right now in my own life.  It's tough going from a place where you are surrounded by believers and constant encouragement to a place in your life where you have to go out and find it.  I'm not saying that I don't have friends that encourage me, I surely do and I'm thankful.  It seems that we get comfortable with our faith and our life and we set ourselves up for disaster, spiritually, and sometimes physically.  I can honestly say that the best times in my life have been when I have been tight with the Lord.  Those times that you will literally do anything for Him, regardless of how stupid you look.  I really miss that.  I've been sifted, and even more than that, I feel like I've been run over by a huge  urlLink John Deere .  The most messed up thing about being in a spiritual slump is that other people suffer.  There are probably countless times that I could have encouraged people and helped, and I missed out because I'm not seeking the Lord daily.  Jesus wanted Peter to go out and help others, to build the church, how I have failed.  It's easy to remember Grace and how awesome it is, but you still can't help but to be mad at yourself for wasted time of growth.    It was pouring rain today and again, I don't have the top on my Jeep.  I'm getting used to rain beating me in the face.  Well it started pouring today so I pulled into a carwash bay to wait it out. I get upset sometimes when my friends make bad choices and feel like they are settling, you want to pick them up and shake them.  You want the best for them, of course, they are your friends.  The Lord started speaking to me in my heart and showing me how He wanted me to come back, He wanted me to make the right choices.  He wanted me to stop living my mediocre life.  I never want to settle.  The word settle must have originated in the pit because it is the worst word.  Never settle for anything, anyone and whatever else fits here.  Live the biggest life you can live and serve the most people you can serve.  We have all eternity to praise God but we only have this earth to tell people about Him.  My fingers are about as heavy as my eyes right now, so nitey, whoever reads this. :)
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There are so many interesting things that happen at Walmart.  In our town, Walmart is like a High school reunion, it's the redneck hang-out, and many more things.  I've come to discover that Walmart stores throughout the US serve the same purpose.  The Walmart in the town I live in now is very close to my house, how convenient.   A few days ago, a friend and I made a nice little trip to that very Walmart.  Strolling around the store, enjoying and coveting all the things you never thought you would need, you know, just another day at your neighborhood Walmart.  Or is that Applebee's?  haha.  My friend Lisa and I are just browsing around and eventually make out way through the toy department and IT happens!    Let me say one thing up front, women are a beautiful creation from the hand of God.  He created their bodies very uniquely different than man's body.  Ok, let me just go ahead and tell you!  This woman was breast feeding in the toy section of Walmart!  Right in front of the power rangers basically, you have a woman allowing herself to be milked!  I'm not trying to be insensitive and I know this is a huge part of life.  But now there are 7 year old kids that are walking around with a scar for the rest of their life because they saw this strange sight.  Walmart is not the only place it happens.  I used to work at an upscale steakhouse and the same thing happened!  Table #1 was drinking something that we didn't sell on our menu!  At Table 1!!! The first table you see when you walk in the steakhouse!  Another time, while working at a hotel, another woman was breastfeeding at the checkin lobby!    Don't get me wrong, each time these things have happened, I have laughed hysterically, but it doesn't mean I want to continue to see them!  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Are we content in God when no one but God knows that we have done what we ought to have done?" -John Piper  A friend of mine sent this quote to me.  I read it three times to really get a grasp on what it means.  Ok, so I read it 4 times :).  There is a suitcase of meaning packed in there.    Lately I think I'm learning how crappy I really am, to put it in a blunt way.  I don't even do the things I know to do, the things I do, I shouldn't do, and I'm learning how much sin is really in me.  You think in your spiritual walk, "As I grow, I'll have less sin."  I'm not sure if that is true.  It seems that the more you grow, the more you realize how far you have to go to be like Jesus.  We'll never be Jesus, but we should die trying to be.    On to other news.  Today was a relaxing day, I spent most of it piddling around the house, working on my motorcycle, a neverending project.  The night was spent eating homemade icecream at some friends' house.  It's amazing what it does to you inside to be around Godly people.  I didn't say perfect people, I said Godly people.  People that genuinely desire to be used by God and genuinely seek Him on a daily basis.  When you aren't around a lot of encouraging Christians, and you get the chance to be, I soak it up.  I really love people.  I love icecream too, but I'm lactose intolerant, can you say, stomach ache?  Dude, my stomach will rumble for hours after a nice blizzard from McDonald's!  It makes noises that sound like someone is actually talking.  It's amazing, doesn't feel amazing though.    Late breaking news:  I love being single.  I'm not saying that I jump up and down everyday and thank the Lord for allowing me to be single at the age of 24, but I am glad and thankful for the things He has taught me.  Being content is probably one of the biggest struggle amongst mature Christians.  Nobody likes being single.  To be honest, I'd luv to have a girlfriend and eventually a wife, but I'm surely not going to settle for anything less than what I think is God's best for me.  You can learn so much by just watching other people and how they date.  You can learn a lot by observing girls in group atmospheres,  I luv it.  You don't have to go on 50 dates a week to see what you like.  Well 1 might help, haha.  It's easy to think that God has 1 person picked out for you.  Lately I'm beginning to wonder.  Ultimately, we know that the Lord knows who we will marry, He is sovereign, He knows everything!  But I think now that He has given us some freedom.  There are many people we could just settle down with and probably be happy.  Is there that one person?  Or do we really have choices in the matter?  All in all, you want someone that brings out the best things in you, and you want to do the switch for your mate.  It's a team, you build each other up right?  When God made Eve, He made her to be "complimentary" to Adam.  A "helper."  It's so neat that marriage was God's idea.  Sex was God's idea.  And bringing animals to Adam right after God says, "It's not cool for you to be alone, i will bring you a helper."  God then brings animals!  Hilarious!  They weren't cool enough, so He made Eve!  Woo Hoo!      
     
    
</post>


</Blog>