<Blog>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          well...life is shitty...just plain shitty! i have discovered this after 17 years of tourture from my family and friends...but its all gravey baby ;)  my theory on life is  "live life to its fullest you never know when its gonna end"   today i'm going to get a tat...lol it should be rather interesting considering that i'm the biggest chicken you will ever meet when it come to pain...but i'm doing it for a very good reason...i'm not sure what it is yet...but i KNOW there has got to be a good reason...  last night my boyfriend and i had a HUGE fight!  about me sleeping with some other guy...a guy that i have known my WHOLE life, someone that is like a brother to me! someone that i have loved forever...but never done anything about because i've been scared...  he was blaming me for sleeping with him...so i said 'you know what i did sleep with him and it was good'...i didnt but i was mad, REALLY mad, and i didnt feel like putting up with anymore bullshit...really, i didnt! so he hung up on me...and then had the nerve to tell me that he 'loves me' i know he does...and i love him too...  i wanted to talk to a friend of mine today (about what had happened last night) ...but friends seem to be bullshit too...just like everything else...friends dont seem to mean anything to me anymore-imagine that right!?!?    ill finish updating this later...so...bye  xoxo~    samantha 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys, this is my new journal, we were obviously all pissed off by William's actions so we found another web-page that is NOT x-stopped for us to talk about our rants and opinions as our day progresses.  Okay, just testing this thing out, I'll start posting more serious subjects at a later time.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well i know its been a while~ so many things have happened latley this could get SUPER long...  recent dicoveries about myself...take a look!           urlLink   What Is Your Best Sexual Skill?        Name:         Age:         Sex:     Male  Female       Sexuality:     Straight  Gay  Bisexual       Flirting Skill Level -  69%                                                                            Kissing Skill Level -  12%                                                                            Cudding Skill Level -  25%                                                                            Sex Skill Level -  95%                                                                             Why They Love You      You are too good to be true.        Why They Hate You      You can be selfish.              This   fun quiz   by  urlLink  lady_wintermoon   - Taken 5772 Times.          New! Get Free  urlLink Daily Horoscopes  from Kwiz.Biz 
</post>


</Blog>