<Blog>


<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's Memorial Day weekend which means that it lasts for three days instead of two.  I've had a pretty decent weekend, but it makes me kind of wonder, is my family being home all day for three days better or worse than two?  Not just my immediate family either, aunts and uncles too.  I spent yesterday afternoon with my dad's side of the family, and all day today with my mom's side.  It's not horrible spending time with them, but frankly I'd rather not.  I love my aunt Bo and uncle Steve, but they are about the only ones I like spending a lot of time with.  I guess it's not horrible, but I think I like it better when it's just me all day and my parents and brother at night.  Speaking of my brother, he's going to be gone tomorrow!  He's going to work with my uncle and spending the night with my grandparents so I won't see him again until Wednesday.  He drives me crazy sometimes, and I'm really glad that he's going to be gone for a few days.  I think I'm actually going to get Bo's car!  She and Steve had already talked about selling it to my parents, but they hadn't talked to my parents yet.  Today I was going to run to my house to get something while we were at my grandparents' and Steve was like, "Here, take my car."  He ended up going with me, I'm not sure why, but he did.  While we were gone though my mom asked Bo if they would make us an offer on the car and she told my mom that they had already talked about it (Mom knew that), and that it would be the perfect car for me.  I really hope I get it.  Not only is it a good car, but it's also good looking.  That Mustang my dad was looking at was so ugly.  Don't get me wrong, I'd love to have an '87 Mustang, but it was such a nasty yellow color.  Either way, the Mustang was bought by someone else, and I really hope I get the Galant.  That's all I have for now, but if you want to see some cool shirts, you might want to check out  urlLink RetroDuck.com .
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, I've been out of school for a whole week now, and the realization that I have nothing to do is really hitting home now.  Today I did absolutely nothing.  I got on the internet and played games and listened to Punk Essentials.  I love listening to that station though.  It plays punk from the 70's to today and it's all awesome.  I don't know why I like punk rock so much, but I do.  I'm not mad at the world like all of these bands that I listen to, but maybe they're the reason.  They're mad so I don't have to be!  Tomorrow I'm actually going to have something to do!  I've got a piano lesson at 8:00, and after that I'm going to Hendersonville.  We're passing out the barbecue that we sold for a fundraiser and hopefully it won't be too boring or take too long.  After we get back Bo should be here and then it looks like I'm spending the rest of the day with my family.  My friends are finally back from Philadelphia.  I talked to Sarah today.  She said she had a good time, but I still don't think I would have liked most of the stuff that they did.  They didn't even get to go to that mall.  She said that they missed the ferry and had to choose between the zoo and the mall.  Personally I wouldn't want to go to the zoo at all.  There's a zoo in Nashville.  I'm glad they had a good time though.  That's about all that's going on though.  I'm already starting to suffer from boredom, and I don't have a lot to do.  Hopefully something exciting will happen and shake up the week though.  If not, oh well, I'm perfectly happy with the internet and FUSE!
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday I went to Hendersonville and spent the day with my grandmother.  We went to see Mean Girls and pretty much just hung out all day.  I had a good time, which is surprising because the two of us don't usually bond like that.  Last night was the first time I got to go to church on a Wednesday night in forever.  I had a good time.  I finally got rid of those cds that I burned for Corey too.  That was when Chris told me I was the best and I told him I already knew that!  After church I played kick the can with Corey and Chris.  It's kind of hard when my partner isn't there, but I still kicked butt!  Today I've done almost nothing.  On Tuesday I layed out and got sun burned pretty bad, but I figured I should lay out a little more today and now I'm starting to regret it.  I'm in real pain right now, but hopefully I'll have a tan to show for it in a few days.  After I layed out I went to my grandparents house and cleaned it.  I hope that means I'll be on good terms with my grandmother when they get back tomorrow.  She was kind of upset when I didn't clean it before they left for New York last week.  Hopefully I'll make some money too.  I leave for M-FUGE in less than three weeks and I'm really going to want some money.  Tonight I get the house all to myself.  My brother is spending the entire week at my grandparents' and my parents are helping Ben with all of the barbecue for our fundraiser tonight so they won't be home until after midnight!  They were like, "Are you sure you want to spend the entire day and night all by yourself?"  I didn't want to say duh, but I don't know what makes them think I don't want to be here all alone for 24 hours.  I'm loving it!  That's about all that's happening.  I know it's boring, but hey, I'm not in school so I'm not complaining!
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tonight we watched  Win A Date With Tad Hamilton .  My dad and brother aren't home so it's just me and my mom spending some "quality time" together.  I like nights like this because we talk about all kinds of interesting stuff.  I was trying to find a picture of a slutty dress like the one Rachel wore to graduation Friday night so I was on the Hot Topic website because I thought I'd seen one similar to it in the store.  I didn't find the dress, but the two of us had a lot of fun making fun of the people on the site.  It's kind of like when we're at the mall making fun of people as they walk by.  After the movie she said something that kind of made me think.  She told me that Corey was my Pete.  We are just friends, but he would like for it to be more.  I tell him and everyone else that I don't want us to be anything but friends, but I know I don't mean it.  I can't understand why I don't tell him my feelings.  I think it's because I've been telling people that it wasn't going to happen for so long that I don't want to admit to them that they were right and I was wrong.  I've thought about before what would happen if he changed his mind and decided that I wasn't worth all the effort and emotion he puts into me, but I still can't bring myself to tell him how I feel.  Hopefully I'll be able to do it soon.  We're supposed to go to the movies sometime soon as "friends" and hopefully I'll be able to tell him soon how I really feel.  I hope I don't let him get away.  I may never forgive myself if I do.  What if he's my fairy tale come true?
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was my first official day of summer vacation.  I can only hope that today wasn't any indication of how the rest of my summer is going to be.  All I did was clean house.  I'm really tired and really sore now, though.  Yesterday we went to the nursing home after church, and after that we went to the park.  All we did at the park was play keep away.  Corey and Chris tried to get the football and the other eight of us tried to keep it away from them!  It made me sore though because when Chris or Corey got the football we had to catch them and then get them down.  It was a lot of fun though.  We played Pictionary after that in training union, and Chris and I decided that, although it's very scary, the two of us think a lot alike.  I had to draw a sniper and even though my drawing was really bad he got it, and after that he drew a picture of scratch and I somehow got it from his weird drawing of a guy scratching his butt.  I don't know that it's a good thing that we did so well with each other in that game.  It kind of worries me!  Allison, Alana, and Sarah are all in Philadelphia.  They got there sometime this morning and I'm sure they're having a good time.  I told them when they started talking about the trip though that I was not going because I wasn't spending a week with those people that I can't stand.  They were all for all of us not going, but then Alana and Sarah had to go, so Allison was sticking with her decision not to go, but her "mom made her."  It seems like we all talk about not doing or doing something, but a lot of times I'm the only one who actually acts and does more than talks.  Oh well, I'm sure they're going to have fun.  I'm glad they're in a room with Rachel and not me.  When they come home we'll have a sleep over and catch up anyway.  That's about all that's going on.  I'm not expecting to have a lot of fun this summer, but I've survived 14 summers before this one so it shouldn't be too tough.  I'll make sure to keep you up to date!
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I started thinking today and I realized that I've really been looking forward to school getting out, but now that it's out I have nothing to do!  I'm going to M-FUGE next month and I'm going to leadership camp in St. Simons Georgia, but other than that I have absolutely nothing to do.  I'm in for a really boring summer I think.  Next week I can't even talk to my best friends because they will all be in Philadelphia on that trip that I didn't want to go on.  Oh well, at least I'll have my music.  I bought New Found Glory and Steriogram today.  I haven't had a chance to listen to them yet though.  We had a fish fry at church today.  We went even though my mom and I don't like fish.  I was surprised at how many people were there.  I gave Faustin her birthday present.  I got her a Queen cd.  I knew she'd like it, and now at least she has songs other than Bohemian Rhapsody to listen to.  I really don't like that song.  After the fish fry we had to go to Gallatin for Amanda's graduation party.  I love Amanda to death, but I hate going to stuff like that because when she's got other people that she likes talking to she leaves me out.  I really like hanging out with her, but because of our age difference it has to be just the two of us or it's not worth it.  That's about all that's happening.  I wish there was more going on, but it looks like the next few months are going to be pretty uneventful.  Oh well, I guess I'll just rest up now for when something does happen!
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For the most part I'm a happy person, but Rachel seems to know exactly how to make me furious!  Ok, I guess I should tell you what happened.  Yesterday, of course, I spent the entire day at her house until we went to school at 1:00.  Yesterday was supposed to be her last session with the psychiatrist.  The last few times that she's invited all of us over I've made up some excuse to not go, but this time I actually did want to go.  I thought I'd finally gotten over everything that happened between us, but apparently I haven't.  Our day wasn't terrible.  We didn't talk about anything in depth, but I don't think we will ever be like we were before where we told each other everything.  I admit we didn't have any really deep conversations, but we didn't have an awful day.  Well anyway, after she left the psychologist yesterday she called my mom.  It's not the first time she's called her, but she seems to only do it when she tells everyone else she's ok.  To make a long story short, she told my mom a bunch of crap, which is all she ever tells anyone, and also told her that all we did yesterday was look at each other.  I called Alana last night after my mom got off the phone with Rachel, and I was really mad.  It wouldn't be so bad if she didn't want everyone to think that she wasn't crazy.  I know she's saying all this junk about suicide attempts and everything, but I think a whole lot of this is for attention.  It drives me crazy!  Mom doesn't want to hear about all of this either.  She was talking last night about the way Rachel was when she talked to her and it sounded a whole lot like the way she was with me when the two of us were fighting a few months back.  She doesn't want to hear what either one of us has to say, and she turns your words around to make it sound like you're contradicting yourself, at least it sounds that way to her.  I told Alana last night that I give up.  If she doesn't want to even try to make this work, because I've tried very very hard, then I don't want it to work.  I give up.  Anyway, I don't like talking to her or about her so I'm just going to move on.  There is a guy that has moved to Gainesboro who is trying to shake things up a little bit.  The guy has an education degree from Harvard and he grew up in Italy.  He's opening an Italian/Greek/Mediterranean restaurant in town as well as a coffee shop.  We had our concert tour today and got to try some of his pizza, and it was wonderful!  I've never tasted better pizza, and I made myself sick because I just kept eating it.  I can't wait until the place is up and running.  I'm more excited though about the coffee shop.  I absolutely love coffee, and I think a coffee shop and bookstore in town would be great.  I'll turn sixteen in November, and I'll be able to stop by there on my way to school which will be great.  It's also really awesome because Rachel's mom is the one who will be managing it and even though Rachel doesn't like me, Kathy does and I would really like to work at this place.  I could work at the restaurant, coffee shop, or the bookstore.  I don't care, but I really hope that I can get a job at one of the places because these places are more like me than any of the other places in Gainesboro.  I think change is a wonderful thing, and I can't wait to see how these places do in such a small town.  Maybe this is exactly what the middle of nowhere needed!
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I know that my last post had links to cool websites in it, and I don't normally do that much, but I've found some more really good ones that I just have to share.  First is  urlLink The Milk and Cereal Song  site.  These are two guys from Virginia Tech who must have been really bored or something.  It's hilarious though.  I think that there was another site, but I can't seem to remember what it was now, so I guess you won't get it until I remember what it was.  Anyway, not a whole lot has been going on.  The car wash was cancelled Saturday, but it's okay because Faustin still got to come home with us and we had a really good time at the FCA thing.  Sunday we went to Ridgetop where my mom was the special music for their revival.  The preacher there was a chalk artist who draws while he preaches.  It was neat, but his message wasn't all that good.  It was kind of cool to do something different though.  Yesterday was my last day of school.  I still have to go some this week, but I'm not staying all day and I'm not in class, so yesterday was technically my last day.  We were supposed to play graduation at Dodson's Branch today, but we were going to have to stay through the whole thing so Debbie just took us out to eat instead and we got to spend the afternoon together.  Tomorrow we will be together all day too.  We are having our concert tour which I won't enjoy, but at least I get to spend the day with my best friends and we get to go out to eat lunch.  Speaking of my best friends, the whole Rachel thing is really driving me nuts.  I've tried really hard to get over all of this and be her friend and become close to her again, but it's really hard.  She says that all of this is over, but she still calls my house every week or two and talks to my mom on the phone for an hour or more.  I really don't like that, but I can't say anything about it to Rachel.  She wrote my mom a letter and gave it to me today to give to her, and while I was at Allison's we read it.  It said a bunch of stuff about how she knew my mom didn't want to know, but she was going to tell her anyway about her last suicide attempt.  I don't know what to think about all of this.  I've tried so hard to put what happened before behind us, but the harder I try the more she's fake around me.  It kind of makes me mad really.  I don't know what to do.  She also said something in the letter about how the two of us weren't as close anymore, and I just wanted to say to her (even though she wasn't there) that there's no way things are ever going to be the same again.  I've tried really really hard, but I don't think things are ever going to be like they were, or that I want them to be the same.  I just don't know what to do.  Oh well, I may just have to give up and let her be fake around me if she wants.  Anything to avoid conflict.  I feel really sorry for Sarah.  She's been having all these problems with Julie who has now apparently quit going to rehab and came to pick her up from school today.  They got in a really big fight and Sarah cried a lot.  Sarah doesn't deserve this.  Her family is just full of problems.  She has never met her dad, her aunt who she was really close to is on drugs, and she's just got problem after problem thrown at her.  I hate that it has to happen to her.  Thinking about my friends' lives makes mine sound wonderful.  Rachel's suicidal and just plain messed up.  Sarah doesn't know who her dad is and has big problems with people in her family on drugs.  Allison's parents are divorced, and Alana's parents are still married, but her dad is never home.  I don't know what kind of preacher he is, but he goes wherever they send him and he doesn't even live with them.  Alana said if he did live with them they would probably get a divorce anyway.  It's really sad to think about all of their problems.  My life is nothing compared to all of that.  I'm so blessed, and I definitely take my lack of problems for granted.  That's pretty much all I have for now.  I can't think of anything else I have to talk about, but I'm thinking about doing a tribute to Sarah on  urlLink Straight From The Horse's Mouth .  She's one of the reasons that my site was so big and had so much on it and even though she hates me for putting all of that out there, I think she deserves a special thank you.  It's still in the works, but I'll make sure to tell you about it here when I get that set up.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've got some awesome websites that are definitely worth checking out.  If you don't feel like wasting your time looking at them you don't have to, but if you're bored and you need some amusement these are great for a good laugh.    First is  urlLink The Wacky Iraqi .  This war is really getting old.  When it started I felt like it was a good idea and I agreed with it, but I don't think we did it right.  We needed to go about this in a different way and get it done quicker, but now we've just dug a hole and made a big mess of things.  Anyway, if you're as tired of this war as I am you might want to visit this site.  I'm not sure who runs it, but they have a humorous way of making political statements and the articles are quite funny.  Next is  urlLink Being Famous .  I haven't had a lot of time to spend on this site, but apparently the people who are members get to be famous for 24 hours.  It's pretty cool.  The Laugh Out Loud section is quite funny, and I'm going to spend some more time on the site because it looks like it will be worth it.  That's all I have for you as far as websites, but if you think I'm done you're wrong!  I'm so glad today is Friday.  School is really driving me nuts.  I just have to keep telling myself, "It's almost over."  I took my last tests today and turned in my books.  I'm so glad to have an empty locker, it's such a wonderful feeling.  I think I'm going to sell all of my Algebra notebooks for about $15-$20 dollars a piece.  I bet they'd bring at least that much and I know some idiot will want them so that they can pass Algebra 1.  It'll be nice to get them off of my hands and make some money off of them.  Tomorrow we have a carwash at 9:00 in Hendersonville.  We still don't have everything we need so we're going to have to leave the house at 5:30 in the morning.  That's ok though because after the carwash Faustin is coming home with me and we're going to go to an FCA cookout.  I'm kind of nervous about the cookout though because this is the first thing Rachel and I have completely coordinated as officers and I just hope it goes ok.  I think it's going to be fine though, as long as it doesn't rain, but the rain is supposed to stop by tomorrow afternoon.  I think my favorite part tomorrow is going to be soap suds football!  It's so much fun and I can't wait.  That's about all that's going on right now.  I'll make sure to keep you updated on things.  I don't think much exciting stuff is going to happen, especially since school is almost out, but if anything does I'll make sure to tell you.  I know you don't care, but hey, you keep reading!
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, I've done the whole online journal thing many times before, but hopefully this one will be permanent.  I need a place that noone who knows me personally will be able to find.  I'll probably talk about a lot of different things and different people, but who knows?  Anyway, this is absolutely necessary for me because I've been known to say stuff that I later regret, but if I say it on here I won't have to regret it because I won't have said it to the person it was directed towards.  Anyway, this is my escape and hopefully you won't be too bored by it, but even if you are, who's forcing you to read it?  I guess now is just as good a time as any to start, so here goes.  School is almost over, finally!  It's been such a long year, and I can't wait to get out.  I know that this year puts me one year closer to being a senior and finally being able to leave Jackson County.  I know some people like the whole peace and quiet thing, but I want to live closer to civilization than we do.  I could be like my parents and drive 75 miles to get to work every day, but frankly I'd rather not.  Either way, my freshman year is almost over and I'm glad.  Next week is the last week and I don't have to go for most of it.  I'm exempt from all of my finals.  We have a concert on Wednesday so I know Mr. Gotcher is going to want us all to come on Tuesday, but I already took my Algebra IA final last semester because I had to be there fourth block and I refuse to go on Tuesday and take the IB final.  It wouldn't be so bad if I could just go and not take it, but if you're in the room Ms. Biery makes you take the final whether it counts or not.  I don't care if Mr. Gotcher gets mad, it won't be the first time, but I'm  not  taking that final!  I don't know why I'm so ready to get out of school.  I have absolutely nothing to do this summer.  I guess anything's better than school though.  I'll have to find something to keep myself occupied, but it shouldn't be too hard.  I'll find something, but in the meantime I have to survive this last week!
     
    
</post>


</Blog>