<Blog>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Testin out a new blog svr
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      **Be warned.This is a cheezed off posting**  Goddamit....drove all of 30 mins to get to town...2 mins away and that stupid friend called and say,"Oh,sorry...am actually with my parents, so it'll be kind of difficult why don't we meetup some other time?" When was she planning to tell me that?Think I wanna go and walk with her folks?She seemed suprised when I said I thought we were gonna go get a drink. Fuq you blardey bimbo aris....I had to make a u turn and come straight home...stupid biatch thinks that I have nothing better to do than go jolly around town and come right home is it?! At 10pm on a working day...she's gotta be fookin kidding me.Why blardey bother to suggest meeting up if you know you cant make it?Think I live right next to the malls is it? Screw you...I dont even want to SEE your bimbostic shadow ever.,,she dared suggest that we meetup tomorrow.Anyway..the reason I even bother going was because those are the kind of things that I do for friends!Especially those I haven't seen for ages due to distance. I think they're all spoilt silly.....so screw-all,  NO MORE  of all this nonsense...grrr!!!No more spoiling friends!  On a cheerier note....superstud pointed me the direction of bonobo: Dial M for Monkey...it's the coolest ever.Super trippy and chill...the kind to listen to whilst worshipping the sun and drowning in your fav keg.Ok.. getting too involved with CJ again...step back baybeh,step back. Can't help myself....damnit and now he tells me he spins indie records and bits of manchester dance! I seem to be in lust with that fact. I don't...I can't have that sarung paaar-teh label stuck on me.I can't.Step back take a breather and chill.  Currently listening to: Bonobo - Funky Monkey 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Superstud CJ's back! Some screw up with the emails...i think n.com is trying to block me off...my reply did'nt get to the shoe factory.Damn.  Got an email full of apologies for anything that he did...if he pissed me off or anything. Strange since it was only yesterday I was moaning about the flakey correspondence.Turned out stupid shoe factory may be filtering me out,cos am still receiving regular correspondence on my mailbox.But anyway,we're back. And we're speaking music talk so I just found the coolest indie band...snow patrol..you've gotta get a listen out of their "How to be Dead" track...awesome.I think I'm in love......with snow patrol.I'm bedding them tonight  Too busy entertaining snow patrol...will elaborate about milk-smell tomorrow.  Oh...made up (sorta) with a girl friend...here we go again.  Currently listening to: Snow Patrol - How to be Dead 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The clan. A whole village of people with the same last name.  We are so used to calling our family as clans.What clan?Dad,mom,grandma and a couple of uncles and cousins running a around? Or gamer's clans...basically gang of bods giving themselves a name to run with just like a band.  How often in this world today do we see huge extended family that lives together in a village?I did.Today.Went back home to where dad was born.Being the urbanite,I haven't been back there in ages.The colors of the village temple,the drunken men weaving about,this guy named Holiday (he's always on hols,jobless you see),another named almond and yet another called milk-smell.   Stepping into the world of firecrackers,milk-smell personas and bottomless beer every festival,it brings me back to me.My roots.I am part of them just like mr. milk-smell is part of me. We are blood.  More pictures tomorrow.Just had to get it out before I forget what I feel NOW.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Let's try this again..Moving blogs,used to be  urlLink here  and now I'm here.Last blogsite was a little more depressing in nature,moans and groans and little crazy snippets on how mad the world's become.  Putting up blogs,someone who you actually mention in them may accidently come across them someday,like mom finding out that I may never ever get married or CJ chancing upon this site,yeps,CJ's a name you'll hear often,at least for the time being.   Opening up my life, whoever that I know in real that comes upon this please do not judge me.Sit back and enjoy the drama of my so called life
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Excellent night out at town..Been neglecting my one true love for music far too long and gettin stuck in R&B joints that ex-friends used to patron...and most of the time it's for the erm...pick-up factors that these places offer.Or the free flow that some idiot always seem to provide.Bah.  In trance we trust-and tribal and house and tech ect ect ect.  Miss those silly guys..remember those raves and silly stoning sessions we had...chased by the maggi mee gorend and nasi lemaks...glad I had a chance to hang out with them again yesterday and ,of course,snapped pix of the silliness....forsee future drinking sessions with them...dead tired today due to my lack of practice in the drinking dept and arriving home at 5am sure made a difference.This is what I call a real ball.....rather than those clubs where you're supposed to rub your booty against some guy..bah again.Well.....another silver lining to my cloud.    Currently listening to: K&M feat. Joy- Pink is the color 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Had dinner with a collegue...it's amazing how people stay so pure and simple in this day of age.How I wish I could be simple and pure...only thing to look forward to is seeing my bf at the end of the week and spending countless hours together.  Is this what growing up in KL has bought me?Very jaded and screwed up.Wary and polluted.Or was it the exposure to the world and me being a sponge?I wish for the days of carelessness and pureness...But then again I've never remember being as such...this is what growing up in KL has done.  Life experiences?Which kinds?I have been there done that...she says its good then I can appreciate my life and still be true to myself.Then why am I so screwed up?Why do I have to start all over again time and time again? Everytime it hurts more and more...but now at least I know I am capable of survival,of pain ,of regrowth.  What do I learn at the end?Why must happiness be a choice?Every morning I wake up and repeat the mantra that happiness is a choice and you are who you choose to be. Why does the simple act of having dinner make me so happy?Is it because of my screwed up-ness I appreciate every gesture,every thought?  I want so much more out of life.Am I going the right direction?I don't know.I don't seem to be if I had to start over and over again on a yearly basis...spring clean my life ever so often.I wish for the day where stable is the keyword .But then would I miss me screwed up life?I think so..this is why I am doing all I can to grab everything that comes my direction.Good or bad,what doesn't kill you make you stronger.Including fireballs and conmen.  But then I am just taking the time for me to grow,to evolve,to be a better person at the end.And if I had to do it all alone....well then be it.At least I know I am a better person.  It's buddah's birthday in HK today...strange.Always thought it was Wesak day?  Currently listening to: Nightmares on Wax -Date with Destiny 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wished I was gonna go watch the  urlLink peas .....bought their album over the weekend and promptly fell in love...its the coolest ever.Even though the purchase part was an accident and supposed to be a gift! Hah...too bad she got me Norah Jones instead. Peas are cool!  CJ and I are progressing to the sms period....strange.  I'm wasting far too much time on him..I need to move on to something more worthy....this will just break my heart at the end unless I keep up at it..  Had a real strange conversation with mom in the morning...she's warning ME! ME! to not go out with married men!! ME?! WTF??I was shocked into speechlessness......totally WHAAAA?They probably think I'm seeing someone and if I don't bring that guy back...and I'm always so free on weekends then that must mean that I'm going out with some dude that has something to hide.What the heck is that with that talk where she's sayin that older married men are more stable and all that...omg.I need a guy soon....before my mom thinks I'm someone's mistress.This is so ridicullious.  Actually, to come think of it...hahahahahah!Totally hilarious ! If only she knew ...This is all due to the fact that she's not meeting the people that I go out with...she usually gets to meet the guys that I am goin out with but I haven't had anyone that I want to introduce to my folks for more than a year. That aint a sin.....what is all this crap bout me gettin the jiggy with married dudes!?Hey...everyone I meet I scan for the wedding ring ok...or a tan line.  Currently listening to: The Black Eyed Peas -Shut up 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We tend to waste so much time caring about unimportant things in life...thus leaving us with less time for more important things in life.I have spent the last month caring and worrying and getting mad at my ex-best friend...and if my conclusion is that she is not worth it,then why bother worrying?Worrying does not bring any value whatsoever in life.If there is nothing to be done,then don't worry just fark-it.  Human relationships are so strange...and we as mere mortals spend too much time worrying about things that brings no value whatsoever.Spend that time worrying about solveable things...or things that will add value to your life.Why bother wasting time worrying about your cell phone bill if no matter how you worry it would still remain the same?There are too many mind blocks that we must go through to see ourselves as what we are; our capabilities and destiny.  It is all so easy to say but not easy to do.I know.Been there done that,trying to get out of it.  This had been a good weekend...maybe because I found my long lost friend the chivas?Nah...gettin out there and meeting new people to fill my life with takes away the need to think and worry about nonsense that pollute my life.  Currently listening to: Thievery Corporation- The mirror conspiracy 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today in Kenya it is Madaraka Day...the day Kenya achieved internal self government.Freedom day.Er..Right  And just because it's June 1st life is good! Birthday is in 30 days! WoooHoooo..Right.CJ's commin over at the end of the month..therefore a huge ass bash..or just me and him.Arh well.Buddy Eve's commin home for good..can't wait to see her.And of course the heaps of  urlLink Victoria's Secret  that she will bring along.  Today marks the return of my clubbing mate...the times when it was just me and her hitting the cirrcuit every friday and saturday is back. When we would stand at the entrance at closing time saying goodbyes thanks for commin seeya next week just like as if we were at our own wedding thanking all the guests.Rather..all friends.My home welcomed me back with open arms and it will to her too.  And of course...weekend of Seb Fontaine,John Askew and Dorthmeister.Whoowhee! Happiness is a choice and well,life is good.Even if it means heaps and heaps to do at work meaning that I'll be home at 10pm tomorrow.  Currently listening to: Beth Orton -Sweetest Decline  
     
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's UK Spring Bank Hols!Yeah...wtf rite? Apparently their version of what we call public hols.Day where banks are on strike?Can't they just call it "I-dont-want-to-work-so-screw-it-hols?"There's a couple each year....there's one in Early May which is the May day or Early May Bank Hols...either name it's still dumb.  Here's a boring interpretation of these meaningless hols:   Bank holidays were first introduced by the Bank Holidays Act of 1871, which designated four holidays in England, Wales and Northern Ireland, and five in Scotland. These were Easter Monday, the first Monday in August, the 26th December, and Whit Monday (England, Wales and Northern Ireland) and New Year's Day, Good Friday, the first Monday in May, the first Monday in August, and Christmas Day (Scotland). In England, Wales and Northern Ireland, both Christmas Day and Good Friday were traditional days of rest and Christian worship (as were Sundays) and did not need to be included in the Act.   Two additional days were subsequently appointed in Northern Ireland: St Patrick's Day (17 March) by a special Act of Parliament in 1903 and 12 July (Anniversary of the Battle of the Boyne in 1690), by the Governor of Northern Ireland in 1926.   The 1871 Act was repealed 100 years later and its provisions incorporated into the Banking and Financial Dealings Act 1971, which remains the statutory basis for bank holidays. The following changes were introduced both then and subsequently:   1971 - Whit Monday in England, Wales and Northern Ireland (which could fall anywhere between 11 May and 14 June) was formally replaced by a fixed spring holiday on the last Monday in May. The last Monday in August was formally made a bank holiday in place of the first Monday in August in England, Wales and Northern Ireland. In both cases, this followed a trial period of the new arrangements between 1965 and 1970.   1973 - 2 January was created an additional bank holiday in Scotland by the 1971 Act. However, the provision did not come into effect until 1973.   1974 - New Year's Day became an additional bank holiday in England, Wales and Northern Ireland, and Boxing Day became an additional bank holiday in Scotland.   1978 - the first Monday in May in England, Wales and Northern Ireland, and the last Monday in May in Scotland, became additional bank holidays.    Stupid part of this all? It is not compulsory but "its a tradition".Assholes.That means legally your monster of a boss can choose for you to work like the dog you usually do.If he does let you go,you gotta praise the lord.  Then again...these lazy bums always ensures that Bank hols always equates to long weekends;its either on a friday or a monday...or BOTH.  Currently listening to: Beth Orton- She cries your name
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Havin yummy popia for dinner...YUMZ.Nothing beats home made popia and birthday mee..Veggies,tofu and crabmeat,slapped with the red and black sauce...its heaven on earth. Combined with yuummy pig stock birthday noodles...is it a wonder that I am abandoning my happy hours appointment with uncle carlsberg for this?  Just wanted to provoke some jealousy..:)  Currently listening to: Groove Armada-Suntoucher
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This inspiring musical journey that I am embarking on is one hell of a trip...its amazing how similar my tastes are with CJ's. Unbelievable how we share the exact same taste. I needed something to learn from him,and I guess this is it.Names keep sprouting from him...and I love it,I love it all!   urlLink Thievery Corporation  is one name that I love...with their chill out funky yet disctinct sounds... urlLink Plump DJs  another and they're slow-ish trance..perfect for getting ready for a nite out.....and they are all of totally different genre,thats whats amazing about this. Most of them sound totally different...but it totally blends in my ears.Differennt, but I love it all!   urlLink Beth Orton's  AMAZING! Totally...very chilled very folksy very early Janis Joplin like.Love her rendition of the old song "Oooh Child".Never heard anything so great yet so chilly."Known as the come down queen due to her popularity in the UK with clubbers tuning in to her after a hard night's work clubbing"   urlLink Lemon Jelly  totally rocks. Happy beaty,sunny sunday happiness choons..Listening it to them raises my happiness level..how crazy is that?All the ducks are swimming in the water? falalalaa..  All this education is gettin me nowhere? Well grab this; conversation with boss:   me :Mornin boss.. boss:hey mornin, you alrite?  me:  Yeps..just listenin in to snow patrol...very "the strokes" like.Heard of 'em? boss: EH?Snow patrol?Funny,was just discussing about that band with my friend.Personally I haven't heard any of their tunes...I love the strokes..they sound alike? Thank you for that...thank you thank you so much.Been sometime since I've heard any new bands.Its a terrible thing.  me:  Well...could burn one off for ya...told you to check that indie record shop...didja?  boss:  No..didnt manage to find it...but hey! Thanks for snow patrol..will try i-tunes snippets.  LOLS.Tomorrow I will impress him with Beth Orton.  Currently listening to: Lemon Jelly- Nice weather for ducks 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sebbie suxed over the weekend....very very progressive...which is totally cool with me but you're like chasing the beat and you DONT get the beat!! HE would change the tune and hey,its a brand new song and you're left wondering wtf happened to the beat?  Peter Kruder...another disspointment.Campier than a row of tents..very very chill...very relaxed I almost fell asleep and had to go drink up with some strange men..whom I dont even remember his name..heck,I went back to Kruder for the sake of the drinks lets face it.  Had a premonition for the whole of friday that I'll be stopped in a road block.Then I got stopped by the cops on the way back.Go Figure  But company's most important...Loved those crazy relaxed guys.Guess music really brings us together  Watched Harry Potter on sat accidently.Jeeze.Was supposed to be Shrek2....someone mistakenly bought tix for Harry and we didn't even notice until the show started with subtittles and such! Very juvenile and unentertaining...dont bother wasting your dough.  Looking forward to my jungle retreat this weekend..need time away from work BADLY.Reminds me...I need to call boston in an hour..  Oh cherrioes folks...
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok...when I started this blog thing,the trick was it was supposed to be my haven...where its me and my innermost thoughts and not wht everyone thinks.Started from strife....people who read my blogs are not supposed to judge me..because most do not know me. For those that know me,well, words here are usually penned in moments of strife,anger and insanity...the insanity moments being the CJ moments.  Its only normal for me to write in times like these...because here is the only place on earth that I do not expect to get judged.This is me...I write things down for the reason that JUST BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE IT AT THAT TIME.No other reasons whatsoever.  But the fellowship has been broken...Words here are not meant to hurt,create problems or instigate issues.  Currently listening to: Mr Scruff-Spandex Man 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Its been a while.Some things never change...like bitchin and bitchy and bitches.Oh well...no point apologizin if there aint no substance in that innit?
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bad bad day...goddammit.CJ lost...came in 3rd.In a super strange way my heart's breaking with that...I was so afraid that I wouldnt know what to say to him...from the pictures it really seemed that he was so dissapointed..but at the award time he seemed ok..oh well,all's fair in love and war. Anyway..he sounds ok with the loss.He'll be off paddling in Guangzhou this weekend so that better be good. And...he don't seem to be making it over for my birthday.Even worse.So feeling kinda down now...this was why he stopped mentioning comming over for the last week or two..now I know why.Apparently some other dude may be comming over instead and anyway it'll be july even if he makes it here.Egg..  I MISS HIM in the most awful way...I think I'm gone.  Currently listening to: BEth Orton- Wild World
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If you wake up in the morning and wonder why are there rice dumplings hanging all over...its Tuen Ng festival today!   Now, why the heck rice dumplings you might ask? Well,the festival commemorates the death of a national hero, Qu Yuan, who drowned himself as a protest against the corrupt rulers of the 3rd century China. Legend has it that the villagers threw rice dumplings into the river and beat drums to scare the fish away from his body in an attempt to rescue him. This is only one of the legend's variation,there are various out there.  The rice dumplings usually contain mushrooms,sliced pork,beans,glutinious rice and a duck egg yolk.Wrapped around tightly in bamboo leaves, these are boiled and then voila its ready for consumption  For those of you that know me, you just KNOW that the next part of Tuen Ng is comming up...the Dragon Boat races.YEpps!  As a very *aherm* knowledgeable person in the arena of Dragon Boating (yeah right!!) my fav site for Dragon Boat races is  urlLink here .  Stanley is a huge, HUGE international dragon boat competition.With over 146 teams this year,most are half drunk even before they touch the water.All in good fun me lass,all in good fun.Apparently the more 'serious' and competitive teams do not compete in Stanley..it's a second class competition.There's one up at  urlLink Macau  too...and thats the more 'professional' one.  Dragon boating season starts from April till July..when I say season,I meant the competitions held that I know about.Obviously winter is off season, but i know one of the better  urlLink teams  who are really good starts practice in January.The purple peeps paddle at competitions all around the world...from Guam to South Africa to Penang and Hawaii. Amazing.They'll be over at Macau for Tuen Ng.  Started off as a national pastime in Stanley during the late 60s,by the 70s the expats have already jumped the boat,so to speak, and joined in the good fun.Due to the tinier sized chinese..(OK not trying to be insulting here  but due to  my good mood,Im laughing my aris off on the implications of that line), the expats are eventually shooo-ed off to create their own category..  Hot sweaty men...chickadees in bikinis...all paddling with a half assed grins on their faces..now can someone tell me a better way to spend a tuesday?Other than stuffing yourself silly with rice dummplings of course.And all the beers that flows from nowhere...  Currently listening to: Baby Mammoth-Black Coffee
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Heh.There just have to be a part two innit?Jeeze,I'm even starting to type like him.This is creeps.  Anyway...the SMS thing is going on again....and he's at the drink and dial (or rather,weed and sms) stage.He fookin woke me up from my afternoon 40 winks with a "hello poppit what's up in KL".And I actually replied...with some answer like I'm nekkid and chasing a footy whilst chilling out to morcheeba...bazzoom.Don't get any funny ideas...I don't take it well when someone wakes me up from my snooze. I need to step back and reevaluate this whole situation.  We're getting too close yet we are not gettin close enough.I don't think the whole wide world goes around calling each other fruit flies,duckie,kumquat,poppit,princess(that is,surprisingly,a name for him).This virtual thing is gettin on my nerves,because I think if it wasn't for the fact that I find him hot,I don't think I'll ever let it get so far..I was not replying to his email after the second or third email that I first received.After finding him hot,this had been going on for 3 months...with a week lapse and a 5 day lapse.  Breathe in,breathe out.Step back and look at the bigger picture girl.But it aint easy to find someone as happy as me! Oh damn..shuttup and put your lardy brains to better use.  That reminds me..I need to reply to the daily email.Shiets.  Currently listening to: Nick Drake- Cello Song
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Rightey ho...it's time to babble about my trip before all is forgotten.  At 5.30 fookin am on a Friday morning...woke up and hazily walked to the toilet...cleaned up nicely and had a quick morning fag.Proceeded to call the cab company and whaddaya know...NO FREAKIN CABS! Asked me to call back in 10 mins time..which we proceeded to do for the next 30 mins.Things aint lookin nice...at 6.30 decided that the shit has hit the fan and had to wake up  a friend to drop us off in chinatown...I don't rememeber the last time I felt so bad!  Nevermind...then had  urlLink chee cheong fun  which totally sucked...got on the bus and whaddaya know...its a fookin minibus!!! For a 4 hour journey..THAT SUCKED!The seats were smaller than the metrobus seats...go figure.And because we were the last peeps up.....we had the worse seats in the bus.Thank god for lethargy...I promptly fell asleep..to be awaken shortly by this two uncles  babbling really loud 3  rows behind.Sigh.Stuffed Lemon Jelly and Morcheeba in my ears and the world's sunny again...the journey has begun.  Next stop: The super dead town of Jerantut.Had a two hour pitstop for lunch...and since it only takes 30 mins for lunch..spent the next hour or so roaming around the town(or rural wannabe town) and chanced upon a really happening spot- the local mall!!! Whoowhee! With 'feng-tau' super loud 'ah-beng' techno blasting from every crevice, where  else in Jerantut can you find so much fun and joy? Zipped through the imitation streetmarket quality merchandise in about...10 mins?Bear in mind that this happening 'mall' is about as big a M&S...wow.Left Jerantut feeling vully vully grateful and appreciative....that I don't live there!  Then comes Kuala Tembeling Jetty...one of the highlights in the trip. Here's where we'll start our journey into the innermost parts of Malaysia..the  urlLink Taman Negara .   Very relaxing boatride...a two and a half hour slow boat ride into the lush rainforest jungle with the river water sparyed on our faces..I fell asleep (as usual) under the hot sun and woke up a few shades short of a bittersweet choc bar.This choc bar would continue to be richer over the next day or so.  Stepped off the boat into a floating restaurant where this Stanley guy in cutoff shorts (I know...it's the campiest thing ever) 'oriented' us on the activicties that are available to us.  One problem  We had no booze!!! Being a predominatly muslim area, they are not allowed to sell booze either.Huge problem.I stopped short of bringing my bottle of vodka due to it's weight...and I thought we could get booze there.Yeah..drafts for  RM16 at the Mutiara Taman Negara resort across the river.Damnit.Started begging Stanley to hook us up with booze..with our lil pathetic faces....  Nevermind...we were all in a not-so-happy moood anyway due to the 5.30am thing...trekked up to our humble abode.It's a frikking trek to go to the room...either that or its just "Smokers...beware,this is what you're doing to your health"  Nice suprise awaits us up at the barely habitable room(ableit the airconditioning)...someone pulled out a six pack!! What bliss!!THat'll last us for the night..or at least an hour or so.Totally exhausted...we proceeded to dutifully line up for the loo for a wakeup shower.  After the refreshing encounter with the never-been-cleaned loo,we all trekked down again for dinner..This would become the norm for the next couple of days.I had never encountered so many staircases before..even  urlLink Batu Caves  is no match for this insanity.  Due to our rather refined tastebuds (yeah..erm..),the food was horrible to say the least..they had beansprouts with heads as big as an assplug.Ok..maybe not,I wouldn't know.One omelette,another kind of vege which sucked too and then an ok-tasting chicken dish,so the highlight of our dinner was devouring whatever's left of the chicken in the chafting dish.Yumz..or so we made ourselves belive in.  Spent the next hour fagging ourselves to death,we haven't learn our lesson with the stairs now have we?Hey,there is NOTHING absolutely NOTHING to do in Taman Negara ok?Couldnt wait for our night jungle walk...I thought we were going to bump into some deers AT LEAST,they were still roaming the area when I was there some 10 years ago.But NO!  We were sweating to the tits even before entering the jungle..it's the middle of the night and due to the 'lush foliage' there is no way wind can get in..I still thought we were going animal a-searching until our trusty Herman the guide announced that we are insect searching.INSECT!??!I walk around with a bottle of Ridsect and I'm comming all the way here to go insect searching?Unbelievable.  But in a way,it was kinda cool..caught a couple of bugs going at it doggy style.Ooh yeah baybeh,do it to me c'mon now.Saw huge one inch ants...frogs,huge arse spiders,walking stick blah...grasshopper.But the best part of the whole walking and sweating was the magic mushies!Glow in the dark shrooms..Now,how cool can that get!!??They're real tiny...maybe the size of an ant.The baby ones are even tinier...can't see them if your torch's on...turn it on and whoa baybeh...it's a disco out there.Wanted to get all high on it...but according to Herman all I'll get is a smotchy ache.Pity.Imagine glow in the dark space cakes.Yumz.  After sweating all the way out of the jungle,we spent 15 mins salivating at the sight of the "Tiger Beer" brolly...debating on whether we should spend 16bux a draft...consensus was to hike back to our hide and spoil ourselves silly with warm beer.  Let me tell ya...its amazing how good  warm beer tastes.  Currently listening to: Morcheeba- Undress me now 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Been sometime since I wrote bout CJ...I'm actually starting to miss him some...the kooky humor and silly banter.How do you end up missing someone for their ability to tickle you pink?I don't get it.My mood's always better when I receive one of  the daily nonsense...not only the daily emails mind you,those I sometimes get quite reluctant to reply.Its the war of wits that I most enjoy..that is undeniable.  Does that mean that at the end of the day the only thing holding it together is the frail tie of ridicullious humor?I can't wait to see him again...to see if we have something to go other than our daily humor....will that humor serve us well when we're face to face stuck with each other for hours.Will the wit still be there...the insanity and silliness?It's all so easy to be all sweet and farpuckingly funny when it's all written down.The eyes intepret what the mind wants to see.  There's a part of him which is oh so private but just waiting to be dug out..I sense all is not cheery and oh la la in CJ-Land.Nothing ever is.How the heck do I go about diggin it up now that's a mystery.  Oh...CJ's on tv.Apparently some publicity stunt on his team's win last year...this year's event is this comming tuesday. First thing his mates sees in the morning is his drunken mug in the bus. Nice.  Keeping my fingers crossed!   Currently listening to: Orbital- The Beach 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      YAY! Birthday's officially over....or beginning?Par-tee at The Ascott this saturday..I pray and hope it'll be good...be good to see chums I havent seen for ages.People I loved,people I cared,people that I've come to depend on...people that I'm starting to get to know,people that have wronged me in the most awful way.  Just hope it will not become very complicated since this is a twin-party with someone else...Don't really know his friends all that well...its ok well...I'll be there early.  Currently Listening to: Chemical Bros- One too many mornings
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Im sad...oh so very very sad.At the thought of turning 24? Or at the thought that I've been played again?
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      God plays tricks on people's heart and soul..what God giveth,He taketh Rest in peace Darren Kang....godspeed.Wished I knew you better...other than one of the two.You have loved and been loved.It's been a wild ride.  Currently listening to: Amazing Grace 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For all ye drunkards out there....here's  urlLink somethin  that might just entertain the heck outta ya..  If you're wondering..this is what's up with me today:  hangover hooky  n .  calling in sick because you’re hungover.  Currently listening to: Chemical Bros- One too many Morning 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Aarghh.......DSL's officially screwed...have not been bloggin for the last coupla weeks due to the crappiness of my beloved DSL..  Anyway....outta ere in 2 days! Hong Kong here I commmmmeee! Oh bars...be prepared to host this hilarious drunk.And hello toilet bowl....we shall meet again my ceramic.  Currently listening to: Depeche Mode -Happiest Girl 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>