<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The New York Times is finally starting to get off the Bush bandwagon ( what  liberal media?).   urlLink  This article   indicates what seems to be an increasing trend - a growing divide between traditional GOP/conservatives and the reigning Bushie/neo-con administration.  At first it was the economy that was irking the country club set (billions shelled out to Iraq? The first time in recorded history taxes were  cut  during a war?) but now it also seems the Abu Ghraib matter has raised wider concerns about letting a failed oilman continue to run his campaign to conquer Iraq unsupervised...
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This happened about 20 minutes from my house.  If it was my discovery I would have just put on my spare hazmat suit and tossed this in the composte heap across the street...      Discovery temporarily shuts down neighborhood   Bethlehem, Pennsylvania-AP -- Here's one way to put a scare into your holiday weekend barbecue.  A Bethlehem, Pennsylvania, man was about to throw lobster and steak on the grill for a wedding anniversary cookout yesterday when he stopped by his bushes to pull some weeds.  Along with the weeds he found a yellow-and-black box about the size of a car battery -- with the word "nuclear" on the side.  He called authorities, and within minutes police cordoned off the block and evacuated his neighbors.  Police determined the box was a nuclear compaction device used in construction. A neighbor had reported the box stolen from his truck.  The fire chief says the thief probably threw the box into the bushes. He says it had the same level of radiation as two household smoke detectors.       
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
        From   This Modern World  &nbsp;:         (Note: this entry posted by  Bob Harris )    You've already heard that Pat Tillman was probably  killed by our own guys . That's all over the news.   But holiday Saturdays are particularly good for releasing intensely unadvantageous news, since nobody's bothering with newspapers. So let's look closely at two other stories that came out today:   The U.S. Army determined that "hundreds of Iraqi prisoners were held in Abu Ghraib prison for prolonged periods despite a lack of evidence" -- last  November 5th .   Meanwhile, the Red Cross gave the Army a detailed catalog of sexual and physical abuse at Abu Gharib -- last  November 6th .   As far as I can tell, you had to read both the  NY Times  and the  LA Times  to get both stories and see the dates line up. But now we know: six months before the world recoiled in horror, the Pentagon absolutely  knew  what was going on. All of it. And nothing changed.   So: six extra months of imprisonment for hundreds of innocents. Six extra months of continued sexual and physical abuse. Six extra months of teaching Iraqis to hate us.   Who's the Commander-In-Chief of the U.S. Army, incidentally? Just asking. Because, gee, I don't know who the hell you blame for something like this.   Meanwhile, this Iyad Allawi guy, the new bigshot in Iraq? A well-known  Baathist and CIA tool , so the Shiite majority is obviously gonna just adore him. Because there's nothing Iraqis like better than having a Baathist in charge. Or a CIA puppet. So this is really the best of both worlds for them.   As  Josh Marshall  has ably chronicled, it's not even clear yet how the hell the guy was chosen, but it's clear that large chunks of our own government seem surprised.   Y'know, I've almost forgotten what it's like to have adults in charge of this country.   In fact... I'm only 40. I don't think I've ever seen it. But I still think we can.   This Memorial Day, as Bush parades himself obscenely before a flag for whose meaning he has neither comprehension nor respect, I'm gonna be really, really angry, at him and this whole unelected incompetent  junta . You might be, too.   But I'm also gonna try to remember that I'm only upset because I still believe in what this country can be.   I hope we all do.   Even now. 
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      On the road today for a holiday weekend picnic.  Gas is $2.03/gallon for regular!   The war in Iraq continues to add cost to our daily lives.   Don't blame me - I voted for Gore...
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Today on Worth1000's photoshopping contest: "Movie scenes you didn't get to see."   Click  urlLink  here   to see the rest. &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Sad but true...&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Wolverclean&nbsp; urlLink     Photoshop run amok. See more  urlLink  here  
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink  urlLink    Not a big fan! Click  urlLink  here   to see the video of Hank chowing down on his first bite of cereal...&nbsp; urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Go Big Al!&nbsp; urlLink     I knew there was a reason I voted for him (well I   think   I voted for him - maybe I voted for Buchanan by mistake)   In a scathing attack on what he termed the White House's failed policies in Iraq, Al Gore called today for the resignation of six members of the Bush administration. "We cannot afford to further increase the risk to our country with more blunders by this team," he said.  President Bush, Mr. Gore said, has brought the United States humiliation in the eyes of the world, not the "humility" he had promised. In the process, Mr. Bush "has built a durable reputation as the most dishonest president since Richard Nixon," the former vice president    Full story  urlLink  here    Watch the video of the speech  urlLink  here    (requires RealOne Player)
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Not-So-Curious George!&nbsp; urlLink     It had better be one hell of a speech tonight.  Bush's approval/disapproval rating is at a record low for a second week straight.   urlLink  CNN story here     
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    This is a picture from a contest called Giants Among Us - people using Photoshop etc. to add giants to everyday pictures.  You can go to the site by  urlLink  clicking here  . &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    I can't stands it!&nbsp; urlLink     See laughing boy by  urlLink  clicking here  
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Dodgers BP - the kid in front of us caught a ball before the game from a Phillies slugger (from the left field side)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Close-up!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Or maybe it was free pretzel night!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    It was Greater Asian Co-Prosperity Sphere Night (or something) at the Phillies game tonight&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    The view from lovely downtown Bayonne...&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Troy - I liked this movie!&nbsp; urlLink      Did anybody else see this yet?  I fixed the comments so you can add yours to my posts.  Just click on the link below this post.  I was impressed on how faithful to   The Iliad   the filmmakers were in the end.  Sure, they removed the Gods from the story and by killing Agamemnon off they robbed Aeschylus of the star of his play.  But overall the story captures some of the key elements - war is a political tool; honor and brotherhood among warriors; and most importantly the rage of Achilles.  Brad Pitt is no thespian but I think he brings a sense of Achilles' constant near-boiling anger.  In this film Achilles is a cross between Wolverine and Riddick.  He does kick some ass, though!  Who'd a thunk   The Iliad   could be an action movie?  Eric Bana is great as Hector, the emotional center of the film. Sean Bean makes a pretty fair Odysseus (though I couldn't tell the difference between this role, Boromir or 006!). The rest of the cast are caricatures - made so as much by the script as well as the acting.  Cinematography and effects all well-done.  I give it a  B+ .  Hi-Res Trailer for broadband users  urlLink  here  .   The New York Times did a great review (best I have read so far)  urlLink  here  .    You can read   The Iliad   online  urlLink  here  .
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Gas is freakin' expensive!  Even Michele has complained about it and you know she hardly gets out of the house!  :)  This guy raises some interesting points on Slate.com:    Why $2 Gas Is Amazing   Three reasons it should be cheaper.  By Timothy Noah Posted Wednesday, May 19, 2004, at 9:17 AM PT    Gasoline is now selling at more than $2 a gallon, which, after inflation, is higher than it's been since 1981. But that's not the amazing part. Actually, there are three amazing parts.  Amazing Part No. 1 is that this is happening during the first time in history when the United States belongs to the international cartel that controls gas prices. A rarely discussed benefit of invading Iraq was that, since Iraq is a member of the Organization of Petroleum Exporting Countries, the United States, which controls Iraq, became a de facto member of OPEC. Since cartels violate U.S. law, Chatterbox figured that the American occupation of Iraq would create legal problems for the Coalition Provisional Authority. (See "Is Bremer a Price Fixer?" and "Has the U.S. Joined OPEC?") But it turned out the United States was too busy violating the Geneva Conventions to give much thought to whatever lesser legal arrangements it might be ignoring. So, until June 30, the date when we turn Iraq over to some sort of sovereign government, we get to belong to OPEC. Why aren't we mau-mauing from within to boost production or, better yet, to dismantle the cartel altogether? Well, there's the fact that President Bush, who is from Texas and formerly worked in the oil bidness, is a bit of an OPEC-o-phile. (Paul Krugman wrote a forehead-slapping column about this three years ago after Bush told a reporter that it was important for the oil market to be "stable and predictable," even if that meant higher prices.) Another complication is that our interests diverge from those of the future sovereign state of Iraq when it comes to the price of oil; Iraq wants it high, while we want it low. Apparently the interests of the future sovereign state of Iraq won out. Clearly, this empire business isn't what it's cracked up to be.  Amazing Part No. 2 is that this temporary colony of ours sits atop an estimated 115 billion barrels of oil, which, depending on who you ask, constitute the world's second- or third-largest oil reserves. Chatterbox knows, of course, that this war was not fought for oil. Still, securing greater control over world oil markets was certainly an anticipated fringe benefit. The oil ministry, you'll recall, was famously the only Baghdad government office guarded by coalition troops to keep out looting mobs during the early days of the liberation. The Bush administration anticipated a short-term spike in the price of oil, but by now it was thought Iraq's oil would flow so plentifully that the post-Saddam reconstruction might pay for itself. Instead, Iraq is struggling to produce as much oil as it did before the U.S. invasion, when the Treasury Department described its production as "erratic." Although Iraq will surely boost production substantially over the long term, its outdated oil technology, which is subject to frequent sabotage, makes quick recovery impossible.  Amazing Part No. 3 is that, before the war began, Prince Bandar bin Sultan, the debonair Saudi ambassador, assured President Bush that "the Saudis hoped to fine-tune oil prices over 10 months to prime the economy for 2004," according to Bob Woodward's Plan of Attack. "What was key, Bandar knew, were the economic conditions before a presidential election. … " On the April 19 edition of CNN's Larry King Live, Bandard clarified that "this was nothing unusual." He had fielded similar requests from Bill Clinton in 2000 and Jimmy Carter in 1979. "We always want any president who is in office to be re-elected," Bandar explained. Presidential challengers are hereby placed on notice.  Unfortunately, as Alan Murray pointed out in a May 18 Wall Street Journal column, "Prince Bandar's ability to keep oil prices below $30 a barrel is shot. … The Saudi government has indicated it will boost production, but the market has shrugged off those assurances." Murray quoted oil expert Daniel Yergin explaining why: Much of the price run-up is caused by the anxiety over the turmoil in Iraq. To put it in terms that supporters of the three Bush tax cuts can understand: Poor planning for the postwar occupation of Iraq is costing you money at the gas pump.   Timothy Noah writes "Chatterbox" for Slate. 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    So true...&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Look at the mushroom that sprouted in our living room!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I have been seeing the old 'don't buy gas on such day' email circulating again:   IT HAS BEEN CALCULATED THAT IF EVERYONE IN THE UNITED STATES DID NOT PURCHASE A DROP OF GASOLINE FOR ONE DAY AND ALL AT THE SAME TIME, THE OIL COMPANIES WOULD CHOKE ON THEIR STOCKPILES.   AT THE SAME TIME IT WOULD HIT THE ENTIRE INDUSTRY WITH A NET LOSS OF OVER 4.6 BILLION DOLLARS WHICH AFFECTS THE BOTTOM LINES OF THE OIL COMPANIES.   ETC.  ETC.    Sticking it to the Bush administration is always a good idea but unfortunately a boycott day will have no affect on the gas companies.   Read all about it  urlLink  here  .
     
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Just sitting outside on my back patio cooking and blogging!  We are having tuna and salmon on the grill.  Ain't modern technology grand?   
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Click  urlLink  here   for my brother Dan's site.  He actually knows HTML so he can do cool pics, features, etc.  Be sure to play the Eagles fight theme while there for the complete experience!
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Da Goddfatha gets tanked after his duties are finished...&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Henry's Christening.  I look like a cigar store Indian statue.  The Godfather has extinguished the Torch of Christ.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Michele is forced into subsidized agriculture by her task-master husband.  She has to bring in income some way...&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Dad & Son 2&nbsp; urlLink     Henry gets to see the world and I get to play PS2 games when he is in this Swedish thingamajig.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Dad & Son&nbsp; urlLink     Imagine how red our faces were when Henry and I showed up at a party wearing the same hat!  Great minds think alike...
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Sending from the phone... 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
          I am emailing this  test...     &nbsp;   &nbsp; 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      My very first blog entry!  I started this to post rants and relevant links regarding matters of import.  I will be posting sporadically so check in every once in a while for updates.  This is the kind of political humor I find humorous:  urlLink click here   There is a great online radio station to be found  urlLink  here    Just getting the hang of How To Blog 101 so expect simple posts at the beginning.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
          By ADAM NAGOURNEY and JANET ELDER          Published: June 29, 2004 in   The New York Times          urlLink     resident Bush's   job approval rating has fallen to the lowest level of his presidency, according to the latest New York Times/CBS News poll. The poll found Americans stiffening their opposition to the Iraq war, worried that the invasion could invite domestic terrorist attacks and skeptical about whether the White House has been fully truthful about the war or about abuses at the Abu Ghraib prison.   &nbsp;   A majority of respondents in the poll, conducted before yesterday's transfer of power to an interim Iraqi government, said that the war was not worth its cost in American lives and that the Bush administration did not have a clear plan to restore order to Iraq.   The survey, which showed Mr. Bush's approval rating at 42 percent, also found that nearly 40 percent of Americans say they do not have an opinion about  urlLink  Senator John Kerry  , the likely Democratic presidential nominee, despite what have been both parties' earliest and most expensive television advertising campaigns.   Among those who do have an opinion, Mr. Kerry is disliked more than he is liked. More than 50 percent of respondents said that Mr. Kerry says what he thinks voters want to hear, suggesting that Mr. Bush has had success in portraying his opponent as a flip-flopper.   Americans were more likely to believe that Mr. Bush would do a better job than Mr. Kerry would in steering the nation through a foreign crisis, and protecting it from future terrorist attacks. Support for Mr. Bush's abilities in those areas has declined in recent months, but the findings suggest that Americans are more comfortable entrusting their security to a president they know than a challenger who remains relatively unknown.   Even so, the poll was scattered with warning flags for Mr. Bush, and there was compelling evidence that his decision to take the nation to war against Iraq has left him in a precarious political position.   As he heads into the fall election, Mr. Bush appears to have much riding on the transfer of power in Baghdad yesterday. The 42 percent of Americans who say they approve of the way Mr. Bush is handling his job is the lowest such figure in a Times/CBS News survey since the beginning of Mr. Bush's presidency in January 2001; 51 percent say they disapprove.   Over the past 25 years, according to pollsters, presidents with job approval ratings below 50 percent in the spring of election years have generally gone on to lose. Mr. Bush's father had a 34 percent job approval rating at this time in 1992.   Similarly, 45 percent said they had an unfavorable opinion of Mr. Bush himself, again the most negative measure the Times/CBS Poll has found since he took office. And 57 percent say the country is going in the wrong direction, another measure used by pollsters as a barometer of discontent with an incumbent.   Yet the survey found little evidence that Mr. Kerry has been able to take advantage of the president's difficulties, even though Mr. Kerry has spent $60 million on television advertising over the past three months.   Nationwide, Mr. Kerry has the support of 45 percent of registered voters, with Mr. Bush supported by 44 percent. When  urlLink  Ralph Nader  , who is running as an independent, is included, he draws 5 percent, leaving 42 percent for Mr. Kerry and 43 percent for Mr. Bush   In the 18 states viewed by both parties as the most competitive &mdash; and thus the subject of the most advertising expenditures and visits by the candidates &mdash; the race was equally tight. Forty-five percent of voters in those states said they would support Mr. Kerry, and 43 percent said they would back Mr. Bush. Indeed, on a host of measures, the poll found little difference in public opinion between the nation as a whole and that of voters in the competitive states.   The tight race indicated by the poll reflects how aides to both Mr. Bush and Mr. Kerry have described the overall state of play for weeks. But other polls have, at times, shown Mr. Kerry or Mr. Bush bumping ahead. A CBS News poll taken last month found Mr. Kerry with a lead of 49 percent to 41 percent over Mr. Bush.   The nationwide poll of 1,053 adults, including 875 registered voters, was taken by telephone June 23 to June 27. It has a margin of sampling error of plus or minus 3 percentage points.   For all the signs of opposition to the war, Americans appear prepared to stay in Iraq until the situation becomes stable. The poll found that 54 percent of respondents said that the United States should remain in Iraq "as long as it takes," while 40 percent said the United States should withdraw "as soon as possible."     
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Outside the Spider-Man 2 premiere - a Faux Spidey?  &nbsp; urlLink     A picture taken outside the theater in  NYC for the Spidey 2 screening.  Spider-Man was charging $7 to get your picture taken with him. I declined. I was becoming suspicious that he might not have been the real deal when I noticed his black Reeboks...  Movie was great, BTW. I thought the romantic angst scenes seemed to slow the pacing down but the CGI/fight scenes were much better than the first movie. So it balanced out. If the first movie was a faithful adaptation of the Steve Ditko Spidey circa 1964, than this movie is a good rendering of the John Romita Sr. Spidey circa 1971. Oh yeah, I went there! 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
                   
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Commuter Photo Essay&nbsp; urlLink     This guy did a really cool photo show that you can see  urlLink  here  . Definitely worth checking out if you have ever had to slog in and out of Manhattan...
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
                 Private rocket ship&nbsp;breaks space barrier  
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      June 25th at a theater near you!       Short Trailer can be found  urlLink  here  !   The long form trailer is available at the  urlLink  movie site  .  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
           
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
              urlLink       Panel Says No Signs of Iraq, Qaeda Link  
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Blogging will be sporadic.  I did see Kevin McDonald from the Kids in The Hall walking down the street down by the Skydome.  Awesome!  I didn't stop and yell his name so i deem this a successful celebrity sighting.  I can see the CN Tower from my room!  Only geeks get excited about these kind of things...  Off to the Blue Jays game tonight, versus the Diamondbacks.   Should be a good seat and I will be tossing back some Molson Canadians in honor of fallen homies.  
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Off to Toronto for another show.  Hopefully I will get to blog a bit this weekend... 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
        I have been remiss in updating my trip to Chicago.&nbsp; Last weekend was the annual Book Expo America, the premiere show for the U.S. publishing and bookselling worlds.&nbsp; It was a good show - we were very busy in our booth with meetings and floor traffic so I didn't get much chance to walk the floor.&nbsp; Here is a list of the celebrities I saw first-hand (I'm not counting 'real' authors as I see them all the time):            Marilu Henner  - the Taxi chick stopped at our booth!&nbsp; She must be 55 at least but she looked younger than me.&nbsp; Now I need to meet Catherine Bach (Daisy Duke!) to complete my list of 70's ladies that welcomed me to puberty...      Julie Andrews  - she walked by our table at dinner one night.&nbsp; Looking more like Victor than Victoria at this point.      urlLink   
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      from Gizmodo blog today:  &nbsp;        urlLink       Damn you, Apple, I was about to take a nap! Apple just unveiled the Airport Express with AirTunes, a plug-mounted mini version of their popular Airport Extreme 802.11g base station that ups the digital hub ante with the simple addition of an eighth-inch stereo out that turns the Airport Express into a streaming music outlet that interfaces seamlessly with iTunes. Maybe I'm not explaining this so well: plug in an Airport Express, attach it to any stereo (or powered speakers), and automagically stream iTunes music anywhere in your house.   You can already do similar things with devices like the Roku Soundbridge, for instance, but the addition of the simple $129 device from Apple is notable. There's also a  Firewire  USB port (and Ethernet, obviously) on there that might be useful in the future. The Airport Express can also serve as a wireless bridge for easily extending the range of your existing 802.11g network. And since AirTunes works via iTunes, it looks like an update (version 4.6) is just around the corner (between now and the mid-July launch date, for sure).   urlLink  Read   [Apple via  urlLink CoolHunting ]    Update: More links, plus there's a rumor going around that this may only work with other Airports as a repeater, and not with any old 802.11g networks. We'll see. Also, iTunes to be updated later today.    urlLink  Read   [ThreeBase]   urlLink  Read   [MacMinute]    Update update: MacWorld is saying the iTunes update won't be out until later this week, and are implying that the Airport Express should work just fine as a repeater with non-Airport WiFi (I would be very surprised if it didn't).    urlLink  Read   [MacWorld] 
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Back from Chicago!  More on that later...  Boy, that "liberal media" has really been giving Ronald Reagan the business this week, huh?  They have been crucifying him for Iran-Contra, coddling Sadaam, etc.  Sarcasm now turned off...  Lest we forget during the canonization ceremonies on TV noting the passing of the 40th President this week, Reagan was the arguably the most divisive leaders in American history.  He polarized the left and right in this country and is almost solely responsible for the current political climate.  Since returning home this afternoon I was catching up on internet news and found many articles I could point you towards explaining some of the things that have gone unsaid in the glowing television coverage.  My contempt for RR was basically what molded me into the right-wing bashing guy I am today.  In deference to that small piece of gratitude to Ronnie I choose this Slate article by Christopher Hitchens to give a slightly more balanced look at why RR was such a horrendous President (GWB excepted!).  Click  urlLink  here   .
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       In Chicago!  BEA notes to follow during the next few days... 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Going to Chicago this week for the annual BEA.  That's Book Expo America for those in the real world.  I'll be posting sporadically from my cell & Pocket PC when I can.   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Italian peace activists feign being victims of a bombing. &nbsp; urlLink       Anti-Bush protests in Rome         //  //]]>    Wednesday, June 2, 2004 Posted: 9:41 AM EDT (1341 GMT)         ROME, Italy (Reuters) -- Opponents of the war in Iraq unfurled peace flags from Rome's bridges, put hoods on statues and chanted "Bush Go Home" two days before the president makes a controversial visit to Italy.    The demonstrations took place in various parts of the Italian capital Wednesday as political leaders attended the annual Republic Day military parade under tight security.   The demonstrators, who have dubbed themselves "The Disobedient," held their own march nearby but police in riot gear were on hand to keep them away from the parade route.   Protesters, including some leftist parliamentarians, chanted "Peace Now!," "Troops Out of Iraq!" and "Italy hates war."   Bush told Italian state television he valued freedom of speech and was not afraid of protests during his Rome visit.   "I have no problem with people who say they don't agree. I think it (demonstrating) is a healthy thing," he said.   Some 25 people were detained in Rome after minor scuffles with military police. Further north in Bologna, violence escalated as police wielding batons beat back protesters who broke through barricades at an anti-war demonstration.   This year's Rome parade, in which military, police and volunteer units marched as planes flew overhead, has taken on added controversy because of the war in Iraq.   Italy is braced for violence over Bush's visit and Interior Minister Giuseppe Pisanu has said he was "concerned but not frightened" by what he called serious threats during the 36-hour visit that starts Thursday night.   Most Italians opposed the U.S.-led invasion of Iraq last year and there have been many calls for Rome to withdraw its some 2,700 troops, the third-biggest contingent to U.S.-led occupation forces in Iraq after the United States and Britain.   "It is shameful, a provocation, for Bush to come here. Italy does not want him, he is a friend of the Italian government, not the Italian people," said Margarita Gaetani, a 57-year-old architect who wrapped herself in a rainbow peace flag.   She pledged to return Friday to protest against Bush.   Plumed soldiers marched on Via dei Fori Imperiali (Way of the Imperial Forums), the broad boulevard that wartime dictator Benito Mussolini built over ancient ruins to review troops.       Hood protest   At the same time, demonstrators unfurled peace flags from ancient bridges and pulled a black hood over the statue of an angel to protest against the prisoner abuse scandal in Iraq.   They re-enacted scenes of the prisoner abuse which has inflamed the Arab world and embarrassed the United States by revealing the ugly side of its occupation.   Other banners read "Liberate Rome from Bush." Bush's visit will mark the 60th anniversary of the liberation of Nazi-occupied Rome by allied forces.   Security chiefs considered the parade, which was attended by President Carlo Azeglio Ciampi and Prime Minister Silvio Berlusconi, a dress rehearsal for the Bush visit, when about 10,000 uniformed police will be on hand.   Some fear a repeat of the violent clashes that marred a G8 summit in the northern city of Genoa three years ago when one protester was killed by police.   Opposition to the Iraq war grew after 19 Italians died there in November and a security guard was killed in April. 
     
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Kerry reporting for duty!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
            $241 Million in Cash Flow              July 30, 2004       &nbsp;   &nbsp;     Variety  reports that Turner Broadcasting has revealed that Cartoon Network had cash flow of $241 million last year on $650 million in revenues, making it more profitable than the CNN group. &nbsp;  It accounts for 17% of Turner's revenues, vs. 14% for news. &nbsp;      &nbsp;     Cartoon Network has a great audience of 12-24 year old males, drawn especially to Adult Swim programming. &nbsp;      &nbsp;     Turner also revealed some of the reasons for Cartoon Network's profitability, which go beyond the prices advertisers are willing to pay for CN's attractive audience. &nbsp;  They include licensing of its characters through Warner Bros. consumer products division and the equity stakes of 2-4% that CN takes in ancillary revenues of shows it purchases from outside suppliers. &nbsp;      &nbsp;     CN also keeps its costs low by producing its own programming, drawing from its huge animation library, and making good deals for the outside programming it runs. &nbsp;      &nbsp;     Future plans include adding ads to spin-off network Boomerang and putting cartoon episodes on chips that can be viewed on Game Boys. &nbsp;   &nbsp;      &nbsp;    Cartoon Network's influence on retailers goes far beyond the licensed products based on its own shows -- it's also a huge venue for popularizing anime, which drives sales of DVDs, manga, and licensed merchandise. 
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      From another email account...  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Test from Pocket PC  The first entry sent entirely from my Pocket PC via Wi-Fi card.  I will try to duplicate this feat from the road in  NYC  tomorrow...
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
         Park ranger threatens to arrest Eldred for handing out free Waldens         Yesterday (July 8, 2004) I took the Internet Bookmobile to Walden Pond in Concord, Mass. It was the 150th anniversary of H. D. Thoreau's book "Walden." The Thoreau Society had a dawn to dusk reading.   After an hour of having readers print and take away free copies of "Walden," I was asked by the Walden Pond Reservation police to pack up and leave and threatened with arrest. I left.   The park supervisor (Denise Morrissey, 978-369-3254) told me I could not pass out free literature without a permit. And she would not give me a permit because, as she explained, the state park gets money from a concession by the Thoreau Society, which operates a store that sells "Walden"--and I was competing with them by giving away free copies.   There is no place to park at Walden Pond except in the state parking lot, for which I paid $5.    Link     urlLink Related...  
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        If this is true than the Bush administration is going to have a tough time explaining why they could not get these HVTs brought to justice by now.&nbsp; To play politics with American security in the post-9/11 era has always been the worst sin imaginable to the Bushies.     urlLink  http://www.tnr.com/doc.mhtml?i=20040719&amp;s=aaj071904        PAKISTAN FOR BUSH.     July Surprise?   by John B. Judis, Spencer Ackerman &amp; Massoud Ansari            &nbsp;     urlLink             Post date 07.07.04&nbsp;|&nbsp;Issue date 07.19.04                      ate last month, President Bush lost his greatest advantage in his bid for reelection. A poll conducted by ABC News and  The Washington Post  discovered that challenger John Kerry was running even with the president on the critical question of whom voters trust to handle the war on terrorism. Largely as a result of the deteriorating occupation of Iraq, Bush lost what was, in April, a seemingly prohibitive 21-point advantage on his signature issue. But, even as the president's poll numbers were sliding, his administration was implementing a plan to insure the public's confidence in his hunt for Al Qaeda.    This spring, the administration significantly increased its pressure on Pakistan to kill or capture Osama bin Laden, his deputy, Ayman Al Zawahiri, or the Taliban's Mullah Mohammed Omar, all of whom are believed to be hiding in the lawless tribal areas of Pakistan. A succession of high-level American officials--from outgoing CIA Director George Tenet to Secretary of State Colin Powell to Assistant Secretary of State Christina Rocca to State Department counterterrorism chief Cofer Black to a top CIA South Asia official--have visited Pakistan in recent months to urge General Pervez Musharraf's government to do more in the war on terrorism. In April, Zalmay Khalilzad, the American ambassador to Afghanistan, publicly chided the Pakistanis for providing a "sanctuary" for Al Qaeda and Taliban forces crossing the Afghan border. "The problem has not been solved and needs to be solved, the sooner the better," he said.   This public pressure would be appropriate, even laudable, had it not been accompanied by an unseemly private insistence that the Pakistanis deliver these high-value targets (HVTs)  before  Americans go to the polls in November. The Bush administration denies it has geared the war on terrorism to the electoral calendar. "Our attitude and actions have been the same since September 11 in terms of getting high-value targets off the street, and that doesn't change because of an election," says National Security Council spokesman Sean McCormack. But  The New Republic  has learned that Pakistani security officials have been told they must produce HVTs by the election. According to one source in Pakistan's powerful Inter-Services Intelligence (ISI), "The Pakistani government is really desperate and wants to flush out bin Laden and his associates after the latest pressures from the U.S. administration to deliver before the [upcoming] U.S. elections." Introducing target dates for Al Qaeda captures is a new twist in U.S.-Pakistani counterterrorism relations--according to a recently departed intelligence official, "no timetable[s]" were discussed in 2002 or 2003--but the November election is apparently bringing a new deadline pressure to the hunt. Another official, this one from the Pakistani Interior Ministry, which is responsible for internal security, explains, "The Musharraf government has a history of rescuing the Bush administration. They now want Musharraf to bail them out when they are facing hard times in the coming elections." (These sources insisted on remaining anonymous. Under Pakistan's Official Secrets Act, an official leaking information to the press can be imprisoned for up to ten years.)   A third source, an official who works under ISI's director, Lieutenant General Ehsan ul-Haq, informed  tnr  that the Pakistanis "have been told at every level that apprehension or killing of HVTs before [the] election is [an] absolute must." What's more, this source claims that Bush administration officials have told their Pakistani counterparts they have a date in mind for announcing this achievement: "The last ten days of July deadline has been given repeatedly by visitors to Islamabad and during [ul-Haq's] meetings in Washington." Says McCormack: "I'm aware of no such comment." But according to this ISI official, a White House aide told ul-Haq last spring that "it would be best if the arrest or killing of [any] HVT were announced on twenty-six, twenty-seven, or twenty-eight July"--the first three days of the Democratic National Convention in Boston.   &nbsp;    he Bush administration has matched this public and private pressure with enticements and implicit threats. During his March visit to Islamabad, Powell designated Pakistan a major non- nato  ally, a status that allows its military to purchase a wider array of U.S. weaponry. Powell pointedly refused to criticize Musharraf for pardoning nuclear physicist A.Q. Khan--who, the previous month, had admitted exporting nuclear secrets to Iran, North Korea, and Libya--declaring Khan's transgressions an "internal" Pakistani issue. In addition, the administration is pushing a five-year, $3 billion aid package for Pakistan through Congress over Democratic concerns about the country's proliferation of nuclear technology and lack of democratic reform.   But Powell conspicuously did not commit the United States to selling F-16s to Pakistan, which it desperately wants in order to tilt the regional balance of power against India. And the Pakistanis fear that, if they don't produce an HVT, they won't get the planes. Equally, they fear that, if they don't deliver, either Bush or a prospective Kerry administration would turn its attention to the apparent role of Pakistan's security establishment in facilitating Khan's illicit proliferation network. One Pakistani general recently in Washington confided in a journalist, "If we don't find these guys by the election, they are going to stick this whole nuclear mess up our asshole."   Pakistani perceptions of U.S. politics reinforce these worries. "In Pakistan, there has been a folk belief that, whenever there's a Republican administration in office, relations with Pakistan have been very good," says Khalid Hasan, a U.S. correspondent for the Lahore-based  Daily Times . By contrast, there's also a "folk belief that the Democrats are always pro-India." Recent history has validated those beliefs. The Clinton administration inherited close ties to Pakistan, forged a decade earlier in collaboration against the Soviet invasion of Afghanistan. But, by the time Clinton left office, the United States had tilted toward India, and Pakistan was under U.S. sanctions for its nuclear activities. All this has given Musharraf reason not just to respond to pressure from Bush, but to feel invested in him--and to worry that Kerry, who called the Khan affair a "disaster," and who has proposed tough new curbs on nuclear proliferation, would adopt an icier line.   Bush's strategy could work. In large part because of the increased U.S. pressure, Musharraf has, over the last several months, significantly increased military activity in the tribal areas--regions that enjoy considerable autonomy from Islamabad and where, until Musharraf sided with the United States in the war on terrorism, Pakistani soldiers had never set foot in the nation's 50-year history. Thousands of Pakistani troops fought a pitched battle in late March against tribesmen and their Al Qaeda affiliates in South Waziristan in hopes of capturing Zawahiri. The fighting escalated significantly in June. Attacks on army camps in the tribal areas brought fierce retaliation, leaving over 100 tribal and foreign militants and Pakistani soldiers dead in three days. Last month, Pakistan killed a powerful Waziristan warlord and Qaeda ally, Nek Mohammed, in a dramatic rocket attack that villagers said bore American fingerprints. (They claim a U.S. spy plane had been circling overhead.) Through these efforts, the Pakistanis could bring in bin Laden, Mullah Omar, or Zawahiri--a significant victory in the war on terrorism that would bolster Bush's reputation among voters.   But there is a reason many Pakistanis and some American officials had previously been reluctant to carry the war on terrorism into the tribal areas. A Pakistani offensive in that region, aided by American high-tech weaponry and perhaps Special Forces, could unite tribal chieftains against the central government and precipitate a border war without actually capturing any of the HVTs. Military action in the tribal areas "has a domestic fallout, both religious and ethnic," Pakistani Foreign Minister Mian Khursheed Mehmood Kasuri complained to the  Los Angeles Times  last year. Some American intelligence officials agree. "Pakistan just can't risk a civil war in that area of their country. They can't afford a western border that is unstable," says a senior intelligence official, who anonymously authored the recent  Imperial Hubris: Why the West is Losing the War on Terror  and who says he has not heard that the current pressures on Pakistan are geared to the election. "We may be at the point where [Musharraf] has done almost as much as he can."   Pushing Musharraf to go after Al Qaeda in the tribal areas may be a good idea despite the risks. But, if that is the case, it was a good idea in 2002 and 2003. Why the switch now? Top Pakistanis think they know: This year, the president's reelection is at stake.    Massoud Ansari reported from Karachi.     John B. Judis   is a senior editor at TNR and a visiting scholar at the Carnegie Endowment for International Peace.   Spencer Ackerman   is an assistant editor at TNR.   Massoud Ansari   is a senior reporter for  Newsline , a leading Pakistani news magazine.    &nbsp;   &nbsp; 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
                George W. Bush,  August 2nd 2004 : &ldquo;Let me talk about the intelligence in Iraq. First of all, we all thought we&rsquo;d find stockpiles of weapons. We may still find weapons. We haven&rsquo;t found them yet. Every person standing up here would say, 'Gosh, we thought it was going to be different.; As did congress, by the way. Member of both parties. And the United Nations. But what we do know is that Saddam Hussein had the capability of making weapons. And ... umm &hellip; but let me just say this to you. Knowing what I know today, we still would have gone on into Iraq. We still would have gone to make our country more secure. He had the capability of making weapons. He had terrorist ties. The decision I made was the right decision. The world is better off without Saddam Hussein in power.&rdquo; 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>