<Blog>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Living After Pentecost  Pentecost, what is Pentecost? Well, the Greek word means 'fiftieth', as in the fiftieth day after Passover.    Lev. 23:15-17, 21   All kinds of Jews were in Jerusalem for Pentecost, and the sect of the Nazarene was huddled together in a house. Anyways, in comes a strong wind blowing and tongues of flame appeared on the heads of all the people in the room. Of course, God wouldn't use this sign nowadays. We use too much hair spray and other hair products. Our heads would get burned off.  So.. back to the story. God's Spirit poured out on all the people and they were speaking in foreign languages they hadn't studied.   Remember Jerusalem was full of out-of-towners, so this greatly helped in the proclamation of the new agenda God was declaring. This was a great place for a 'regime change' of the highest order.  The Spirit-filled believers were preaching and telling forth the truth of the life, death, and resurrection of Christ to everyone within hearing distance. And they were hearing it in their native tongues.  All right, the next part is what I think is kind of a weird exchange in the New Testament. Some people are saying, “These guys are drunk!” Peter stands up and says, “They’re not drunk! It’s only 9 AM.” Like they would be drunk if it was 9 PM??!! Then Peter proceeds to give the first sermon in the history of God’s Church. Man, what a dignified start for this great institution.   Acts 2:14-41   Jewish people love to tell and hear stories. We all love a good story. We need to be reminded.  So, Peter tells a good story.   •	vv. 16-21 First, this occurrence (the tongues and prophesying) was prophesied by Joel some 400 years ago. (v18 – men and women will prophesy) •	vv. 22-24 Jesus Christ was and is the Messiah of God, and you were part in His killing. •	vv. 25-28 But He didn’t stay in the grave. It was IMPOSSIBLE for death to keep its hold on him. •	vv. 29-35 Even King David died, and we can still visit his grave, but he prophesied about the resurrection and exalting of our Lord Jesus Christ. The Creed: “Let all Israel be assured of this: God has made this Jesus, whom you crucified, both Lord and Christ.” The Call: Brothers what shall we do? “Repent and be baptized, every one of you, for the forgiveness of your sins. And you will receive the gift of the Holy Spirit. The promise for you and your children, and for all who are far off– for all whom the Lord our God will call.” The Count: “Those who accepted his message were baptized, and about three thousand were added to their number that day.”  Whoa. What a story Peter tells.  And what of us? Do we need to hear stories that will inspire us and give us the strength to carry on in this faith battle which we have entered. I know I do.  Nathan, your family can remember you as a small child, recall your bruises, boo-boos and owwies. They have loved you for all of more than 19 years. They have been preparing you for this very instant and for many that will result from it.  You have not, fortunately, finished the story of your life. You are just now beginning it.  In these weeks and months before you go to college take time to relive your story with your family, because it is out of your life story that you will find strength and encouragement to keep the faith in college.   Friday they dedicated the WWII memorial in Washington. I hope to get to Washington sometime to see the shrines to our nation’s history.   But I think the WWII memorial is especially important now, belated as it is.  Some 800,000 American troops died in that conflict for the world.   This current war has claimed the lives of roughly 800 American soldiers since its start last spring.  If we don’t remember the stories of the Revolution, the Civil War, World War I and II, Korea, Vietnam, and all the lesser conflicts through our history, we may as well close up shop and disassemble our union, for there’s no reason to go on.  I know that I live in a generation that has never fought in a major war, been drafted, or buried scores of brothers. I’m glad, but I lament the lessons we have missed.   The church could, aside from God’s guidance, could be just as doomed.  We must look back on the story of THE Church and of our church and root ourselves there if we are to build God’s Kingdom into the future and for future generations.     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, It's a Friday morning, and I'm supposed to be sitting here writing a sermon in my office. I picked my own topic, and I chose to pick the topic of Pentecost, since it is, after all, Pentecost weekend.  Why the heck didn't I pick veteran's or memorials or graduates? I'm a total idiot. Jeez.  Anyways, my dad's supposed to be here sometime this morning. I guess I'll see him whenever he gets here. Whenever that is.  I'm thinking about scrapping any conventional sermon ideas and going with something a little less orthodox. I'm allowed to do that, I think. Who knows.  Maybe I will just start writing here, and see if it works for me.  Pentecost, what is Pentecost? Well, the Greek word means 'fiftieth', as in the fiftieth day after Passover. So, what significance does that have for us? Nothing. Until about the year AD 35, when Pentecost became the birthday for the church.  All kinds of Jews were in Jerusalem for Pentecost, and the sect of the Nazarenes was huddled together in some upper room. Apparently this was a favorite custom of theres. Anyways, in comes a strong wind blowing and tongues of flame appeared on the heads of all the people in the room. Of course, God wouldn't use this sign nowadays. We use too much hair spray and other hair products. Our heads would get burned off.  So.. back to the story. God's Spirit, as we later came to understand this occurrence, poured out on all the people and they were speaking in foreign languages they hadn't studied.   Remember Jerusalem was full of out of towners, so this greatly helped in the proclamation of the new agenda God was declaring. This was a great place for a 'regime change' of the highest order.  The Spirit-filled believers were preaching and telling forth the truth of the life, death, and resurrection of Christ to everyone within hearing distance. And they were hearing it in their native tongues.  Peter stands up and says, Brothers, this Jesus Christ, whom you have crucified, God has exalted as Messiah and Lord.  And so starts the church.  Jewish people love to tell and hear stories. We all love a good story.  Nathan, your family can remember you as a small child, recall your bruises, boo-boos and owwies. They have loved you for all of more than 19 years. They have been preparing you for this very instant and for many that will result from it.  You have not, fortunately, finished the story of your life. You are just now beginning it.  
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday Amy finally got her shipped anniversary gift. I ordered her piano music for "Come What May" from  Moulin Rouge . She loved it. It took a while to get here, though, and she was beginning to wonder if there really was another present in the mail. Anyways. We then went to the church to play that song together. It was fun.  After that we ordered some pizza, picked it up, then came home and watched  Texas Chainsaw Massacre  with Randall. It was okay.  Today I'm helping Timm with setting up his banquet for tonight. It's always fun to hang around and help with the banquet over here, since there's is bigger and nicer than ours.  Anyways, it's almost time for me to go.  
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    This is me holding two thirty pound carp&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, there've been a couple of days since that gray day I posted such a sad post. I feel a lot better now. I went golfing yesterday with a few youth ministers here in town. It was supposed to be a Youth Worker Alliance activity for bonding/fellowship. It was actually four of the maybe ten youth ministers in town. What the lick. So, we played a four man scramble. It was worthwhile, if only for the hang time with the few guys who did come. Then I took Micah fishing. He caught three fish on his little pole. It was great when he said, "Let's catch another one!" After I'd just taken a fish off his hook. Last night Micah and I slept in the tent in the living room. It was pretty fun, except that wears my back out quite a bit. Ouch. Well, I don't have anything profound to say. 
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey, today isn't all that bad. I'm just saying. Yesterday was fun. Yesterday I was cooking out, got a little sunburn, spent some time with my high school friends, watched a baseball game. That was yesterday. Even just night I went to the mall in Jackson with Amy and enjoyed myself shopping. I bought some new sandals and a new summer outfit. But that was yesterday.  Today the consequences of some sin in my life come crashing around me. But I wanted to be found out. It's just maybe not in that way. I knew I was going wrong, but it had such a strong hold on me, I didn't seek help. Now maybe it's too late. I don't want to see my world come crashing in around me.  That's today. Yesterday was better. Today isn't so great.  Well, you say, what's going on? Well, I'm not entirely sure I can answer.  Suffice it to say I've gone wrong, terribly wrong many times in my lifetime.
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have just been at a baseball game for about the last three hours visiting with high school kids, cooking burgers and giving away free sodas. I'm so tired and sunburnt. I probably should have found some air conditioning to hang out in a while ago. But who knows. Maybe I'll have a tan now from hanging out in the hot sun for the last who knows how long.  School is done for the year at Caruthersville High School. They've all gone on to their summer plans. We'll start Diet YL next week. Probably next monday. In fact, I think I'll send out and email to tell all the kids that on Thursday or Friday.  Yeah.   The air condition in here is freezing me since I was about to pass out from a heat stroke. Oh well, it probably good for me.   Yeah, I wonder if I write better in my physical journal than I do on this cyber version??   I should look for a book now. Oh, by the way, I'm at the public library freezing since I have a committee meeting at 5 here in Cville. I shouldn't drive back and forth unnecessarily with the high gas prices.  
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, I started my day by writing out and working on memorizing the Prayer of St. Francis.   Yesterday I found out it was my friend Jerome's 40th birthday today. So, I had Amy make him a cake and brought him to the office.  This is the first birthday I'll remember. You see, Jerome is a recovering alcoholic and drug addict. This is the first birthday in a long time that he has/will be sober enough to experience his birthday. Thanks be to God!  Anyways, enough about him, let's talk about me.  I'm headed to DCHS to visit some guys for lunch. These particular guys have been coming to TSC for a while, but I just haven't connected with them. Visiting their school should open them up a bit more and allow me room to step into their lives.  Well, this post is short and not that interesting, but I need to go.
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The Prayer of Saint Francis     Lord, make me an instrument of Your peace.  Where there is hatred, let me sow love;  where there is injury, pardon; where there is doubt, faith;  where there is despair, hope;  where there is darkness, light;  where there is sadness, joy.  O, Divine Master,  grant that I may not so much seek  to be consoled as to console;  to be understood as to understand;  to be loved as to love; For it is in giving that we receive;  it is in pardoning that we are pardoned;  it is in dying that we are born again to eternal life.    At the Heifer Ranch there is a peace garden with a statue of St. Francis and a sign that has his famous peace prayer on it. I want to commit to memorizing it and praying it at least once a day, Lord willing. 
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was teaching this morning, and really thinking this week about how dependent we are/should be on God.  God has given us everything that we are and have. And what should our attitude be? Thankfulness, of course. It's as if the very sentiment of thankfulness was created to describe the proper attitude toward God.  Well, after yesterday's lack of a carwash, I of course went fishing. It was enjoyable. 
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, here I am at my office on a Saturday morning. I have no business being here. Amy and I went out to Outback last night for dinner for our anniversary. Today the youth were supposed to have a car wash to raise money to send water buffaloes overseas with Heifer Project International (www.heifer.org).  But here I am in my office two hours after we were supposed to start. It's rained most of the morning. That really stinks. I thought we had a chance to do a great thing together today, but not now. If it's raining all day people won't come to get their cars washed. That much is sure. I don't know much else.  I am listening today to  In The Name of Love , a collection of Christian covers of U2 songs. The songs are even more powerful in that context than they ever were to me in the normal U2 context, which gives me a greater appreciation for U2's art and work.   The best song on their is Chris Tomlin's rendition of "Where the streets have no name". It is powerful, especially when you consider the cd's point, raising money for worldvision to do AIDS/HIV relief in Africa, and the origin of the song.  So, that's a part of what we're called to as Christians and Americans. Not to deny or ignore the pain in our world. But to respond to it and embrace what it is making us as a people. Maybe I didn't make that up. Desmond Tutu talks a lot about that in  God Has A Dream .  And that's what I'm doing here. I obviously live out of my pain a lot. And I expect we all do, just as archbishop Tutu said.
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      May 14, 2004 So, Amy and I celebrate our fourth anniversary today. It’s hard to believe it’s been that long that we’ve been married. It seems like just yesterday was our wedding day. Well, maybe not yesterday, but the day before. I’m sure of it. Anyways, we’re going out to eat at the Outback tonight for our anniversary. That’s a favorite restaurant of ours. I’m reading Fil Anderson’s Running On Empty: Contemplative Spirituality for Overachievers. It is challenging me about how I view my own spiritual growth as primarily my job instead of simply resting and letting God fill me, which is my only job.  And so, I’ve rewritten my summer schedule to have more time to rest and relax, not as an activity on my schedule, but as a rule of life. That’s interesting that I used the same phrase there that Tony Jones spoke of in his book SoulShaper.  That’s what I really need: a general guide to my life that points me toward Christ, not away from Him.  
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, I haven't posted in here in a while, and I finally wrote again in my physical journal. It felt weird to go back there.  Anyways, not much going on. I'm thinking about starting a new blog that will be a work of fiction.  The blog of a fictional character in a fictional life.  I'll post the url for that when i start it.
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Amy and me enjoying our time away from the kids. North Carolina- July 04&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Posting the three previous photo posts was my way of telling myself, and anyone else who might read my blog, that I am serious about this blogging thing.    Journalling has been an important part of my life since I was 15. For me to be able to anonymously journal with text, photos and fonts online is a great thing.   Anyways, I'm going to get back on top of this thing.   
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The people of the church minister to us in song. New Mexico- Jul 04&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Our group posing for a silly photo. Windy Gap, North Carolina- July 04&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Micah and Alexis asleep on their Grandma. Nebraska- July 04&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>


</Blog>