<Blog>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      heya, &nbsp a cold and chilly night it was in the city.. spent about 2 hours in school library studying just now.. no more assignments to rush or do.. brandon jio go coffee in the city. i agreed without much hesitation as no immediate work is at hand..  &nbsp sat at a coffee place call Jimmy's from 9pm - 130am. brandon left at 1130 leaving only jason, hsin and me. we talked about travelling, relationships, and even talked about which direction should you wipe your ass from. i do it from back to front, and the last step front to back. while jason is back to front and hsin is front to back.. &nbsp we were thinking like.. if a girl wipes from back to front, wouldnt some of it be trapped inside the.. erm.. valley? :] &nbsp saturday night in the city is not as boring as it seems.. we saw Autins Powers walking past us, rabbit girls, and many more people with funny clothing. best of all, we withnessed a gay dispute which resulted in 10-11 policemen chasing them! &nbsp 4 police cars and a Aussie style Lo Ti Chia (bread van.. a police van in singapore) drove past us, in the middle of queen street. &nbsp being a proud singaporean myself, i decided to be kaypo and take a peek at whats going on.. then i saw this 2 gay men throwing pussy punches at each other! wow they can be quite rough.. both had short hair, quite well built, wearing shirts and jeans. they were screaming and pulling each others hair.. things were getting rougher and they broke apart and 1 of them took out his shoes and threw it at the other guy! WOW!... &nbsp  i mean.. would you take out your shoe and throw it at another person in a fight? Man!..  &nbspthen, out of a sudden, the police pinned down 1 of them, another 3 policemen were scolding and securing another one sitting on a garden bench. then they were loaded roughly into the policecar. THEN wat happen was most shocking..... the 2 guys in the car start kissing!!!....    nah just kidding.. :D hahahaha.. only the kissing part is not true.. teeheehee    these few days hasnt really been fantastic for me.. from the signs that god gave me, it didnt turn out that bad after all.. hahahaha.. well,.. i ask god again this time..  "oh god, .. what can i expect from the next few days? ... show me something... something nice.. and im not looking up into the clouds anymore... "      urlLink     hmmmmmmmm...... i wonder....  ;] 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hi all,  have been busy with my assignments lately.. so dun really have time to write stuff in my blog..   recently, one of my schoolmates lost her wallet. luckily, only money was lost.. ID, credit card, student card all was kept elsewhere.. so is she considered lucky? or unlucky? ... &nbsp i have been to the casino a few times now.. so far, lost more than $600.. only went home from the casino once with winnings of $42 dollars.. the rest of the times, i walk away about $100 poorer.. unlucky? &nbsp have been doing a programming assignment recently.. spent 6 hours trying to debug 1 single error. and at the end of it, still unsolved.. the next day, when on the way to school, just like that, the codes came into my head. immediately when i reach school, i tried it. and it works... unlucky? or lucky? &nbsp  god.. are you picking on some of us? am i really that unlcuky sometimes? how do i know whether i will have a bad day, or a lucky day? please god, show me a sign that i will have a good day tomoro... please please..    &nbsp;  urlLink        hmmm... guess its not going to be a good day for me... haiz... 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hi all, just wanted to share this funny flash site i got from my friend. it really crack me up and i kept laughing.. click on the horses one by one :D    urlLink  stoopid horseys    the tunes still ring in my head after some time.. :D:D
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      love... something which i will never understand. whats the difference between loving someone, and liking someone? is love a commitment? can you love many people at a time?   thinking of a girl, every hour, every minute, thinking of her smile, her looks, her smell, her voice, her laughter, .. is it love?   feels uncomfortable when she is not around, just want to see her, touch her, feeeeel her, hold her, hug her,... is it love?   mood swings when you see her with another guy, not picking up your phone call, ignoring you, at some other guys house,... love?   i dont know what love is.. if you ask me, ill say those above are obsesssion, lust, and selfishness.. although i feel all of the above before..  does love always associate with pain? ....    well, i know what i like... i like girls.. i like nice, trimmed, cute pussies.. teeheeeheee :D got a photo of a few of my favourites below..            urlLink       cute right? hahahaha   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      it was late at night. the leaves moved as the cold wind blew, the bats flying around squeeking as they glide through the air, it was dark, with only the street lamps and the city night lights. i was in my balcony, on the 4th floor. plus level P1-P3, im actually on the 7th floor.. as usaul, i was lighting up my dragon and admiring the night sky of brisbane, peeping over to my neighbour, checking whether they are alseep at 2am in the morning.  then suddenly, this glaring white circular light shine into my eyes. so bright that my eyes strained and automatically, i raised my hand to cover the light..   "wooow... "   wondering what the hell it is, my eyes slowly got used to the light and i can finally see it..    CHIEH!   its just the moon...  but it was the biggest moon i have ever seen.. so round, so bright, so white.. back in sing, i can never see such beautiful moonlight, shining over me, as i slowly, draining the dragon.. after a while, my eyes got used to it, and you can see shapes on the moon. then i saw a rabbit... im serious. it really is a shape of a rabbit. to convince myself, i told my housemates and they came out to the balcony too, to witness this amazing moon, with rabbit tattoo on it. jason then took a photo of it but cant see the tattoo though..   urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      theses 2 days has been quite boring.. last night, friday night, watched coyote ugly, follow by aliens 4. then went for coffee with hsin, edalene, ray, dave and jason. it was pretty cold.. but bearable. it was fun having coffee and chit chatting about stuff.. chatting mainly about my buddy though..   my friend, brandon, is slowly becoming a superstar.. his every move or action is being watched by paparazzi.. and words about his whereabouts and hanging out with whom gets around pretty fast. he is like in a reality show, where he is being watched by people all the time.. hahahaha :D   just now, as stoopid Man-U is winning the FA cup, i uploaded   SOME   pictures into my friendster.. do go and check out   SOME   of my pictures in friendster ;) teeheehee :D      this photo is taken on Mount cootha in brisbane,australia. its 10min drive from my house and it has a great view of brisbane city. the stars are also brighter when you look at them from the peak.   urlLink    oh and i wasnt trying to act cool hor.. i was having headache and all the flashes from the digital camera was making my head worst.. so i wore the sunglasses to avoid the powerful flash from affecting my head. anyway the photo turned out pretty well huh? ;)  take care people..
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey yall, was busy the whole day yesterday. working my ass off an assignment that require countless nights of doing, weeks of research in library, and effort equivalent to chasing a beautiful girl for months to do.. and the worst thing, it is only worth 10% of the final marks.   &nbsp &nbsp went to look for brandon to smoke with me yesterday evening. i went into his lab and take a peek what the hell is he doing for his Engineering degree. &nbsp  he was programming a little robot to play soccer.... &nbsp  he briefly explained to me what he is doing and demostrated his robot. the robot will spin a few round on the spot to locate the ball, then it slowly moves to the side of the ball and pushes it towards the goal posts.. &nbsp i was pretty amazed by it when it actually kicked the ball.. then suddenly, the robot started banging the wall.. &nbsp &nbsp   reverse... BANG! reverse... BANG! reverse.. BANG! &nbsp &nbsp  then i look at him and ask &nbsp &nbsp "how come your robot fucking the wall?"  &nbsp &nbsp then ah bran say &nbsp &nbsp "orh.. cos still got bugs.. haven't prgram finish mah.. haha" &nbsp &nbsp   Information Technology can be quite boring sometimes.. all we does is face a square box which emmits lights from one side and we are suppose to stare at the light to do our job.. our practical lessons, hands on lessons, are ALL just playing with the keyboard and mouse.. that sucks man.. the robot ah bran was programming looks interesting.. cant wait to see his finished, bug free, fully functional product.. &nbsp  &nbsp  &nbsp  this photo was taken slightly before i was commisioned as an officer of SAF. the suit im wearing is call Number 2.   urlLink    look good eh? ;]
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      after i publish my blog to everyone, first thing the girls in my house say was  &nbsp &nbsp "why dun have us inside wan?" &nbsp &nbsp  so.. to shut them.. nah cant say that.. To make them happy :), i put up the photo of me and all my housemates.. the girl in red is weijun, the other girl in black is iris chai.. and the guy in white is jason.       &nbsp   today was quite exciting in school actually. my group mates and i were late and on our way to school to meet our lecturer to dicuss about our assignment.. we took a lift from level 2 to level 7, through the corridor, past a door, saw our lecturer and a queue of people waiting to see him regarding the same matter as us. as we were thinking how long we need to wait, the fire alarm sounded.. &nbsp  its a daaaaaaamn irritating sound, but its not constant. it goes something like this &nbsp &nbsp  "beeeeeeeeep beeeeeeeeeep beeeeeeeeep!!" &nbsp &nbsp  then it goes like "tuuuuuuUUUUUUUT!.. tuuuuuuuuUUUUUUUUT!" &nbsp &nbsp  and then "BEEP! BEEP! BEEP! BEEP! BEEP!" &nbsp  its just like a freaking car alarm with varying sounds to piss you and irritate the hell out of you.. &nbsp  so, like the rest, we evacuated the building. we follow closely behind our tutor so as to not lose him.. eventually, we came back to level 2 and walk towards an open area where my lecturer and some punk coursemates who were slightly there before us absorbing valuable information from the tutor bit by bit. sucking him dry of all the hints..  &nbsp i was abit excited and was kinda hoping to see some action. but nothing happened, just people crowding around waiting for things to happen. &nbsp  the fire engine came, drove right infront and between block S and Z.. QUT students would know where is that.. then with the loud haler.. one of the fire fighters said &nbsp &nbsp "PAAAA MAAAAAA BAAAAAAA PAAAAAA MAAAAA!!" &nbsp &nbsp i was like.. "huh?¿?"  &nbsp &nbsp then judging from his hand, waving us to move back, i assumed he was trying to chase us furthur away from the building.. then, suddenly, the alarm just went off.. and lecturers and staffs, were waving to all the students around to go back to class.. i looked at my watch, with just 10 minutes left before my next tutorial lesson, the punks left and at last we get to suck the tutor now of information.. due to time constrain, the help he gave was pretty brief.. but valuable.. assignments due in 3 days.. heres a funny picture for those who are as stress as i am to relax abit.. ciaoz.. &nbsp &nbsp  urlLink    &nbsp ooOOooOOOoooo... now THAT must hurt..  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      head giddy, nauseous, running nose, jelly body, balls itchy,.. were how i felt last night when i was down with slight flu.. amazingly, i was cured almost instantly with a magical chinese herbal drink. its has things like luo han guo in it. and just like that, i was back with full health. &nbsp &nbsp the coldness of the wind chills at night is starting to get on my nerves.. literally.. as i step into my balcony for a "before sleep" cigg, i could notice the beautiful stars in the clear night sky. a friend told me how to see the group of stars call scopio here. there is like 3 stars in a row forming the body of a scorpion, its not the orions belt by the way. with another 3 stars placed slight curved forming the tail of a scorpion. oh and when i was admiring the beautiful stars above, the wind chills at 12 degrees gave me the shivers. the iced cold floor of my balcony is giving my feet an ice massage.. which i mentioned earlier, is getting into my nerves through my feet..   &nbsp&nbsp "Brrrrrr.... f..fuc.. fucking coold.d..d.." was all i could say.. &nbsp&nbsp and they say winter is worst.. with daytime temperature at 7 degrees.. shitz..   &nbsp &nbsp   urlLink    &nbsp &nbsp  this picture above is one of my latest picture taken on 2nd May 2004 here in aus. im on the right. the guy on my left is my best buddy brandon. we were getting ready to go to a club call family in brisbane. DJ Tiesto was in town that night.. and we had a hell of a time that night ;) leaving the place only when the sun is out.. Tiesto@family rocks! &nbsp &nbsp &nbsp wish DJ Paul Van Dyke would come.. 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    my necks sore, body aching, thigh stiff, stomach growling, head giddy, penis throbbing, all due to playing basketball yesterday at UQ... except for the last one.. i just woke up hehehe.. second exercise since i came here. first was party from 11-6am with TIESTO@Family.  &nbsp the air here is thin.. i didnt do any warmups and just went in straight to play a game. my throat was soon super dry and unbearable.. i guess im not used to the weather here yet. we played against mostly thais and a few taiwanese, japs.. i think they were japs. the thais are good and they are really funny and friendly people.. .. we played a few good games with them.. although we lost most of the games.. &nbsp anyway, this pic above was taken at Byron Bay, near gold coast with my roommate jason. there was one friday night, after i watched 50 first dates with some of my friends here, we went for coffee and chit chatted a while till abt 2am. then people were like asking &nbsp "go where now?" &nbsp then suddenly, we all decided to go watch sunrise at Byron Bay. and after about 2hr 30min of driving, we reach the place. we reached at abt 430am, sunrise is 1 hour away. we chatted, walked, smoked, and eventually, the sun rose from the sea. it was truely an amazing sight. the sky was covered with clouds but was unable to ruin the view of the strong and powerful sunlight.  the rays that were reflected over the ripples of the sea was an art. the wind was strong, the rocks were all so artistically created. and best of all, we could see dolphins racing to the shore, jumping out and doing a dive with each wave. &nbsp  a new day begins.... &nbsp &nbsp &nbsp&nbsp oh.. still got throbbing problem to settle.. haiz.. =|
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    hi all. &nbsp just want to start off by uploading a photo of me. this photo however is one of my nicest. im the one on the left by the way :Þ  the other guy is my buddy TK. &nbsp &nbsp &nbsp  bought a new sweater today. its a white nike pullover. plus the one i bought yesterday, i spent $140 on sweaters these 2 days. went school to do my assignment. &nbspas i sat in the library to try to do my work, my classmate said to me,  &nbsp &nbsp "hey check out that japanese chick! shes just my type!"  &nbsp &nbsp i looked over and saw a colorfully dress jap chick with a trench coat and socks that look like mittens covering her white ankles and shin. her face was heavily cover with hard dust, they call it makeup. with her was 2 guys and a gal. the 2 poser guys look like hongkees to me. they have fluffy hair, demented faces and a weird sense of dressing. true enough, i overheard their conversation and they were speaking cantonese.  &nbsp &nbsp "wah the guys are crap man! lets go over and talk to the gals!" said my friend..&nbsp &nbsp "LAI! lets go! kia le bo ji nia.." i said..&nbsp&nbsp "har.. mai lar.. i scared.. hahaha " he said.. &nbsp thus ending the most exciting part of my boring day.. &nbsp life in brisbane is kinda boring.. silly things like this keeps me going. &nbsp &nbsp
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this is my first blog.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok.. back track abit..  on sat after my last paper, i met up with my blind date aris, and brandon. we were looking for a present for our dear friend sharyl. its her 22nd bday. so we bought her a necklace from Oroton. as we were scrolling down to have coffee by the river, we stumble across an adult shop. so we just went in to take a look..  ... yes i took my blind date aris into a sex shop on our first date..  anywayz,.. we looked around and decided to buy sharyl a vibrator as a prank :D we choose the cheapest, ask the counter girl to test it for us, paid and we were on our way again.. test it as in put battery to check whether it is working and not *ahem! :P   then the day went and we were at sharyl's house at 730pm. after having some pizzas and cut cake session, we made her open up all the presents infront of everyone :D   urlLink     after which she try to attack us.. with it. hehehe.. after some struggle, the dildo dropped on the floor while it was sstill on...  "drrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr.... "  then it started bouncing on the spot! WAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA :D:D it was fucking funny when it happened! :D  kekekekee.. hope she did enjoy herself that night.. brandon was acting gay to entertain everyone..  hes not gay by the way.. :)  &nbsp urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      6 months ago, i only had about 10-20 friends in my friendster list. i was damn bored, so i browsed other peoples profiles in friendster. then i decided to be funny and msg all the chiobus,.. all writing the same thing..  "hi, can we be friends?  hanny" i sent to about 15-20 chiobus in friendster.. and only a handful reply me.. one of them is Aris..    urlLink     that time i put my Mooooost handsome picture. but when aris viewed my profile, the following picture was my primary picture...   urlLink     warrau.. heng i put this picture man.. else she wont reply my msg..  then we started msg-ing one another. after about 3-4 replys, we just stopped msg-ing.. i added her in msn but she was never online..   then recently, while i online one night, she came online! we talked awhile, and she said she became an air-stewardess and will be coming to brisbane on the 26th june! the last day of my examss!!! YIPEEE!! :D:D but of course, first thing i ask is if she can tapao something for me... Marlboro reds.. :D  the day came, after my exams about 2pm, i called her and waited for her to come down from her hotel room... was quite nerveous cos this is my first time meeting internet people.. heng ah bran was with me.. i too scared to meet her alone.. hahahaha :D:D   hsin and edalene also came to company us for cofffee by the river.. :) the girls like become good friends as the day goes on to night.. even took hello kitty photos ...   urlLink     hee :) andy must be saying "like that also can?" right? :D yeah man.. im shock too :D kakaka and best of all, she bought 2 cartons for me :D:D  2 singaporeans meeting up for a blind date in Australia....   funny leh... hehehe  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      my final paper is out of the way.. HOLIDAY BEGINS! WooOOoOoOOOooHOOooOOooOoO!! :D:D:D studied hard for this mornings paper, so i am pretty confident of getting a grade 5 and aboove for this subject.. possibly a 6. grade 5 is >65%, grade 6 is >75%.. my dream grades is getting nearer after this paper.. to get straights..4 5 6 7 :D:D:D hehehehehe :D:D  then after my paper i went for a so-called blind date, with someone from singapore. a singaporean meeting a singaporean for a blind date in Australia... hmmm.. more info will be added after i get the pictures from brandon..   then at night we went for sharyl's birthday at her house. hmmm.. more will be talked about after i get some photos also.. :D:D  in the mean time, heres something to think about... &nbsp   urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      took my most feared paper today.. got 18/36 for my mid term,.. because of eye-power.. else i would have gotten lower..  2 assignments amounting to 9.75/10.. mainly due to my hardworking coursemates..  so i basically knew nothing much about this subject.. after much reading and question/topic spoting... i think i can make it through todays paper.. :D:D:D:D hopefully can just pass it.. 1 more paper to take this saturday. think this paper i can make it..   self-confidence and friends i agree are valuable.. On the basis of my definition of love, i have yet to find it.. hmmm.. think i need to work on my self-confidence also..     &nbsp urlLink     well, got this  urlLink interesting website   about a person from singapore.. im SURE he has lots of SELF-CONFIDENCE man..   
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nature, plants, trees... never fail to amaze me sometimes..  i love nature. i love to take a walk in the park, look at trees, plants, flowers, and the grass everywhere.. its just so comforting and relaxing when you try to blend in with nature... the birds, bees and insects just enhances the beauty of nature..  i had lots of experince with nature actually.. sleep, eat, piss, shit, in the jungle before.. but what i saw yesterday really shock me.. maybe its just me but i saw this perticular tree in Brisbane south bank, which really caught my attention. it was a pretty small tree and the bark just so sooooo soooooooooooo reminds me of something.. something,.. erm... nice and warm,.. something which i usually see on the internet often,.. something which the japanese always censor away in "Art" movies..   i'll let whoever read my blog be the judge to that...     urlLink     please leave a comment if you know what it looks like or watever it looks like.. thanks..  ... ... ...  FUCK MAN! Really lar... DONT YOU THINK IT LOOKS LIKE A FUCKING CH***YE?!?!?!!  phew.. needed to let that out.. :D:D:D but seriously lar.. dont you agree?!   nature never fails to amaze me...  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today i took a ride on the fastest pussy in the city... it was beautifully shaped, has nice and warm insides, and i'll say, is a clean pussy as well. not smelly, else it would be a ccb.. :D it was my first time getting on such a wild pussy... got me all excited as i zoom into it and out from the front... ( hmmm... ;] )  anyway, it was pretty windy and my housemates and i took a few pictures while we were on it..     urlLink     &nbsp   urlLink      we were on our way to the cinema to get tickets early for the show at 825pm.. Shrek 2.  Wow! i enjoyed the show to the max! hahahaha... love a show with a pussy that is sooOOOooOOoo cute~! :D especially when it is in boots.. ;] *wink! :D teeheehee :D   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Exams are just around the corner.. In fact, my exam will start in 7 hrs 19min. After a week long of torturous study schedule, my mind now is in an ecstatic state.. Just couldn't wait for the exams to be over.. It has been such a long time since i felt so distraughted and eccentric.    But i am now ready for it.. I am ready to face the vicious exams that comes one after another for the next 1 week..  This motivating picture below inspired me.. I not only want to pass my exams, but i will try to attain relatively good results..  All my life, I have always been classified as lazy rather than hardworking..   .......   well, im working on that :P    anywayz, i will do my best for my exams tomorrow.. hopefully do well for it too.. ;]   &nbsp  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've never been such a BEAST today more than any other days of my life...  The appearance was so delicious that I could taste it off my lips.. The size of the tender object of desire is almost close to the surface area of a woman's breast (36F).. The thickness of it was closely matching to the width of my mouth (if you know me well enough, you would know I have very wide, succellent lips).. Blood was oozing from it, driving me to a maddening, delirious state.. The gory and the triumph of owning a piece.....   :]  "Mmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm........."  :]        "Rib-Eye Steak with Bone" ... medium rare.  And, what were you thinking?   I think I understand the urges of Hannibal Lecter now. I am certainly not crazy enough to cannibalize my own kind, but to taste meat so raw and so fresh is undescribable.   This piece would've been classified RA (Really Atrocious) if it was the way it was in Singapore. Its classified RD (Really Delicious) here in Australia.  As I tore off the last of what was left with my bare hands, I couldn't stop myself from gnawing the bones till it was completely done with.    :]  "Mmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm........."  :]    It was by far my  best  steak yet. I never knew near-raw flesh could taste so bloody good...     
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      heya!  Germany draw with Holland 1-1... I WON MONEY@! WOOHOOOO!! :D:D   win 50 cent nia.. hahahahaha :)   first paper in 2 days.. about 49 hours left.. have been sleeping at around 8am, and wakeing up at 3pm.. day is night, night is day to me now.. have to re-adjust my sleep timing to suit the paper soon..   below is just a picture that makes me smile.. just thought of showing whoever comes to read my blog..  urlLink      what is the meaning of life? i wonder.. why am i living in this world?   came across this picture which i find quite meaningful... things in life that destroy a person.. although i feel all of the things mentioned below before, i feel that it will really destroy a person if one does it to the extreme.. a little bit of each is alright lar.. hor? ... :)    urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      England lost to France 2-1... haiz.. they were leading by a goal for a long time.. &nbsp  Gay boy beckham then got a chance to shoot a penalty.. he missed... haiz.. &nbsp  then in the last 3 minutes, france scored 2 goals.. haiz.. &nbsp  freekick given by hesky, zidane scored.. haiz.. &nbsp  gerrard gave a farked up back pass to henry, keeper tackled hard, penalty.. france scored.. haiz...   haiz...   like jason said, england's downfall for this match was caused by 2 Liverpool players.. haiz.. &nbsp  being a liverpool fan myself.. i even more haiz... :(   like what jason said again, France did a Man U on England.. haiz...   but i will stay loyal to Liverpool always..     "you will never walk alone.. "  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      story below taken from my beloved housemates..   2am.. jason, iris and weijun was at home at their computers. the girls share a room and the windows in their room leads to the balcony.. the night was silent and cold..   "THUMP!"   the girls heard a sound hitting the wall just outside the balcony... they looked outside.. there was nothing.. they then went over to my room, where jason is, and asked if he was playing a prank on them... nope. jason was in his room the whole time.. then they became paranoid and imaginations were running wild... i guess they told many ppl abt it and were a bit scared..   the following is my side of the story...   i came at about 5am, prepared the potato salad and smoke in the balcony as described in the blog below... i woke up at 2pm to take picture of the city again which is visible.. then i changed and prepare to leave to watch Harry Potter, which opens today. i went to the balcony and took my socks which was on the rung.. then i saw stains on the wall... brown stains..   urlLink          i wondered.. then i saw a banana on the floor..  urlLink     first thing that comes to my mind was   "aiyo.. how the girls eat banana can throw until all over the floor man.. haiz.. "   then i went in and told them about the banana which spilt in my balcony... hmm.. abit corny hor? :D:D wahahahahaha :D:D  then there was a sense of relief after hearing that the THUMP was cause by a banana..   judging from the stains, the banana most probably was thrown from the opposit building.. WTF man..   well at least there wasnt any bananas flying into their windows... think i will throw a durian into their house soon... heh! :D  
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      studied till late last night.. at the wee hours of the night, i left for the last bus in the city. which leaves at 0010 hrs.. i reached at 0000 hrs.. waited, smoked, walked around,... till 0030 hours.. then i check the timetable of the bus on the board... the last bus left at 2340 hrs.. fuck.. Fuck.. FUCK!!.. fucking bus timetable of brisbane buses are not as accurate as i tot.. fiakz!   after another ciggarette, i walked back to school and study. my mind switched off at around 3am.. surf net, check mail, watched Ong Bak,.. in school's 24hr lab.. finally decided to leave at 5am.. took a cab back..   reached home, unpack a bit, started making my famous Potato Salad! people who know what Oliver's supersandwiches will know what salad im refering too.. ;) it is dave's birthday today and i made him potato salad.. which only contributes to a smaaaaallll portion of his Fabulous Buffet he prepared.. mmmmm... Delicious!! love ya dave :D   anywayz... after i finish preparing the ingredients, i went to my balcony for a smoke.. then i look towards the city and i couldnt see the city..... it was cover by the fog.. wooow... second time i saw such foggy skies.. first incident was blog down at  urlLink jason's blog . well after i woke up in the afternoon, i took another picture of the city.. which is visible now..      urlLink     urlLink    you can never see this scene in singapore manz.....  
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      it was late at night, i was studying in my school library's 24 hour lab as exmas are in 13 days.. as i was desperately trying to print the lecture slides into my head, my mind tends to drift.. and it drifts daaaaammnn far.. scenes from Young and Dangerous 2 were in my mind.. and the next minute, images of my army life.. after a few different scenes, i will doze off...    when i wake, i will whisper to myself   "fuck! cannot sleep! ... must study..."   then from my white adidas bag, bought from china, i will pull out my bars of chocolates and start eating them.. to stay awake... everytime i doze off, i will eat a bar..   then i decided to take a piss.. as i walk to the toilet, my mind was thinking should i smoke after i piss? or should i wait for brandon then smoke together.. i entered the toilet and went to the cubicle,   ....   i was thinking to myself... "how come got sanitary bins next to the bowl?"   THEN.. i realised.. i was in the girls toilet!.. fuck man!... i quickly walked out, doing a side step into the guys toilet. i heard giggles when i do the side step into the next room, with my left hand covering my mouth.. i quickly peeed and walked back to my seat, calmly,.. acting coool as i walked..   i went back to my seat, tapped brandon on the shoudler.. he removed his headphones and i told him about the incident...   He laughed sooo hard he almost fell off..!! nbcb..   second time in my life, i went into a girls toilet.. well, the first time i pissed finish then i came out..   it was a good experince though... oh and there was no one inside at that time.. so not that bad.. hehehehe :D:D:D
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      does all girls have a cheeky side? mischevious image? or does all girls just want to behave entirely different for 1 day out of 99 days? ... well,.... i dedicate 1 entire blog entry to this "very cheeky" friend of mine, Hsin! :D   my impression of her is nice, clever, sweet, cute, beatiful, attractive and fun girl. well, after she transformed into the "Very cheeky" mode, and after she virtually gave me the finger,.. with a sweet smile :) ,.. my impression of her changed slightly..   it still contains all of the above, plus cheeky and mischevious! :D    to hsin: well, since you showed me your looOOooOOooong finger,.. i figured you wouldnt mind me putting it up on the blog.. ya? :D:D:D teeheeehee :]  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      dressed in navy blue pants, whites short sleeve shirts, white converse shoes with white socks, long hair till just above the ear, 1cm slope at the back, and combed centre parting. i wore big glasses with metal frames and i was skinny.. oh! and plus a ultra man school bag.. as dorky as it seems, that was how i looked like ..   it all started through david, my friend and classmate. i got to know a girl.. david knew another girl call serena.. who brought a friend. she was about 1.7, slim, with shoulder length hair. plain, but nice and pleasant, with an amazing warm smile always on her face.. her name is alfi...   we used to go out in groups.. alfi, serena, brandon, eric, ivan, lam kei and me... just to name a few that i remember.. we would all be in school uniforms, hanging out in town, tampines mall, far east? there was once, if my vivid memory serves me correctly, serena and alfi came in a cab to bedok house (david's another apartment). serena left her wallet in the cab! just as i was about to run for the cab, david ran for it instead.. well, he wasnt say very fast last time, so he didnt managed to catch it.. eventually, the cab driver returned it another day..   some of us reading this will remember bedok house.. i for one will definitely remember bedok house alright.. we were all playing truth or dare in the house.. come to think of it.. most of the dares were all planned ahead.. hahaha :D planned by the girls ar.. not us guys.. we were all underaged, drinking beer, smoking, having fun...... :)   that was all 8 years ago...   8 years later, today,.. brandon and me managed to meet up with alfi!! and of all places, brisbane Australia! we didnt see each other for 8 f**king years man!~... she changed alot. she became more mature, more feminine, more beautiful.. she say i changed quite abit also.. but she say brandon never change at all. wahahahahaha :D   we were having coffee in the Brisbane city. alfi, brandon, hsin and me. we talked, did lots of catching up.. and best of all, she bought 1 carton of ciggarettes for me :D:D:D hehehehhehe...   well, come to think of it.. its pretty amazing how we got to see each other again after all these years.. coincidence?.. luck?... fate?...   the beautiful girls in the pic below are alfi and hsin. alfi's in white and hsin's in red :)   urlLink     oh and the handsome dude in black is brandon :D and im in white. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      monday... may be the blues or just me, i had another boring lecture in the evening.. as i slowly slide lower and lower from my seat, i started to day dream. my legs were stretched out and my right hand supporting my heavy head, eventually, i started dreaming.. images and scenes from the movie "day after tomoro" was in my mind.. then.. suddenly..   "AAAAAAAIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIII!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!"   i heard a scream. i jumped slightly and opened my eyes and saw a angmo just walked away from the lecture door.. the room was silent for 5 secs.. then everyone started laughing and giggling.. well, that sure woke me up. it was weird.. and everyone's faces were like "???" ..   well, all i can say is that studying in Brisbane, is definitely an experince all right..  angmos... heh! 
     
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i only brought 1 pair of glasses to australia.. my one and only pair of spectacles.. has become my   3   and only pair of spectacles...  i am so farked...    urlLink     how i broke it is even more unbelivable..  i was walking down the city one day with my converse cap, as i try to take it off from the back, it hooked onto my glasses and dragged them off my face and down to the floor. which jun jun land directly where my leg was going to step on next..  "PIAK!"...  "thats it man... im farked....." shaking my head...  curently using blue tack to temporary hold the lens in so i can walk around at home.. i still have 40 day supply of daily contact lens left.. a pair of   CHEAPEST   specs you can get here is  $170 .... haiz..   jin eh si sway gao laosai man...   (really is unlucky until like diahorrea) :P
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      have been thinking about what im going to do after the year ends.. will i study somemore? will i be back home working? or will i be here in aus working?  ....  mom ask, "study finish liao what you do huh?"  "come back work lor... " i said..  "NO! Dun want you come back!! go study there somemore!!" she said..  :|~ "........." i said...  now too lazy to give it a serious thought.. so just pushing this decision back a few months... see how later...  if i did do my masters, it will be 1.5 years in UQ.. where jason is.. the only course that i find interesting and relevant to what im studying is Masters in Technology Management.. which is available at 2 campus.. one is here in brisbane australia, St lucia campus. where jason is.. the other, is Singapore Institute of Management (SIM) in singapore..  ... hate making this kind of important decisions... poly i took IT also quite chin chye choose one..  haiz..     urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      had a drinking session on friday night. i missed drinking.. miss the burning effect of drinking straight shots. my toot housemates were gone that night.. light weights.. sia sway chasely apartments.. she puke on her own bed and blanket.. si beh jialat..  weijun made a new friend as well.. her na... erm.. its name is toilet bowl. they were hugging each other all night looong.. hehehehe iris, was lying down whenever possible. blocking people in our narrow corridor.. jason wants to take a picture of her and ask her smile..   "i dont want to take picture~!!" iris said..  then she smiled, raised her left hand and posed.. haiz.. indra was also gone.. lying in the living room with his arms outstretch and say  "i can feel my head throbbing.. THUD THUD! THUD THUD!!" :D:D:D  hahahaha.. and kelvin was gone pretty early snoring away like a dinosaur in my room.. makes me appreciate jason as my roommate...   im too lazy to upload all the photos.. pictures can be seen at   urlLink jason's" blog .   overall, it was a good night.. hehehehe.. maybe will hold one again soon..   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      just to let you all know, my results was out almost 2 weeks liao..  my grades are as below..    subject &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Grade &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp; Percentage &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  Software Development 3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 81%  Network Technology&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 73%  Internetworking&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 58%  Information Security&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 58%    GPA&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 4.75    trying to increae my grade 5 to 6. so my GPA can be 5 and not 4 point something..  just 2% nia... hope i can cham xiong with my lecturer...&nbsp;  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      didnt had time to upload these.. a bit old liao.. but nonetheless, i want to put in my blog to show you all...  this pic is taken from mt cootha. just 10min drive from my house in brisbane to the top. the view is magnificant.. and ah bran's camera is really power. with flash still can capture all the city night lights and us.. good good..  urlLink     this is the lighthouse of byron bay. always have to do some funny shot whereever i go..   urlLink     sunrise at byron..    urlLink     just some more pictures...   urlLink     we manage to see whales... but all we saw was the whales, hardly visible, squrting water out like a fountain.. when we saw, we were like..  "WHOOAA!! LOOK!! WHALES!!! WAAAAAHHHHH~~~!!!!.... "  sua koo singaporeans...  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      these few days, i have been feeling very weak.. restless, no energy, just wanna sleep and rest.. today, i might have found the cause. abt a week ago, after my housemates left for sydney, i saw chocolates next to the bin, decadence chocolates... i tot it accidentally fell from the table and landed next to the bin. so i picked it up and ate a piece. few days ago, i ate another 5-7 pieces... last fews days was super restless, easily tired, just simply lifeless... today, i asked my housemates about it, and i took out the chocolates and ask them wanna eat anot.. then they were shock and showed me the obvious green plants, moulds, growing on it..   ....  i didnt feel very good after that... no wonder i laosai the other day.. no wonder my tummy feels weird everyday.. no appetite to eat.. all shag out..  wanted to take a picture of the mould and let you all see... but the gals threw it away liao..  haiz...  ...  fuck.. 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      we were suppose to be at movie world's door when they open. suppose to pick up ah bran at 9am, but we all only woke up at 9am. hehehe. well, movie world was fun. all the rides which i took before are slightly different now.. new rides were Scooby doo ride.. alright lar.. lethal weapon is still the same.. it was brandons virgin ride on lethal weapon! hahaha.. he sit in front somemore..  overall, it was enjoyable and fun at movie world. at least cover up the bad zoo trip the day before..    urlLink     brandon like his to be well polished... hee :D  urlLink     doing the famous sam war cry... " AH BU AH~!!"  urlLink     the same chair we took pictures with 3 years ago when me and jas came here with raymond and kev  urlLink     it the super hero photo shooot! batman, robin, batwomen, hornyman and sweetgirl.   urlLink      ah bran and aris bugging each other at a bugstop waiting for a bug..   urlLink     sorry bout the late upload, cos i busy trying to complete my FFX2 in 5 days.. as i need to return the PS2 liao.. got deadline to meet.. now 60% complete liao.. hehehe  ok seeya guys!  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      first, lets have a look at how red my hair is..    urlLink       urlLink      my wallet sure feels good when its still alive..  went to the zoo with jason, hsin, brandon and aris. hoping to see Steve Erwin, the Crocodile Hunter!! the zoo sucks man.. its more like a crocodile farm cum mini bird park, plus a few roaming kangaroos..    urlLink       urlLink      while in the zoo, got this farker tiao me.. ccb. then i tiao back...   "kua simi kua!... narbeh...."    urlLink      maybe because i was caressing his gal on the grass...    urlLink      saw nigger kangaroos in curumbin wild life park 3 yrs ago.. now in Australia zoo, we manage to take a picture with a WHITE kangaroo..    urlLink      the zoo's a really boring place.. abit regret going there.. but nonetheless, we had fun and we manage to take a picture with the Crocodile Hunter afterall.. hehehe    urlLink       urlLink       stay tuned for my blog on movie world and byron bay!   to be continued....  &nbsp; &nbsp; oh and thank you Hsin for my wonderful glowing hair! :D:D    
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hiyall, this is how i look like moments ago.     urlLink     hsin, jas and me were having dinner at sunnybank. we were walking around and came across a pharmacy type shop. immediately, jason spotted cheap hair dyes.. so we bought a color each.. i bought "Intense Pure Red" color..   hsin, prior to this has no experince in helping people dye hair, offered to help us do it.. so me and jason stoopi... erm.. happily agreed to it.    so off we go, straight home to get our hair dyed.   it was a bit rough.. but bearable still.. it hurts when she put it at the roots and massage it.. and its no fun making the hairdresser laugh when she is putting dye on your hair.. laughing and dragging your hair along with it.. oooOOooooOoOoh man! sensation,.. istemewa!! :D:D  well, we managed to piss her off a little and she started hammering jason on the head!  BAMM! BAMM!! WAAPAAH!!  ...   urlLink     after i started laughing, i got whacked up too! i touch the back of my head to see whether isit out of shape, and all i see was blood...   urlLink     thats my head on the right... can almost see my brains man... hahahaha :D  well, thats all for now. going to sleep soon.. 5hrs of sleep left before aris arrives and all of us going to see Steve Erwin doing his crocodile shows! me jas hsin bran aris.   urlLink     stay tuned for my new look tomoro!! :D:D  
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      heya, sorry havent been blogging recently.. holidays in brisbane isnt that fun after all.. especially when everyone is at singapore, sydney, melborne, etc. and only me and jason and brandon is left.. things to do everyday is very limited. either warcraft 3, coffee, or ps2.. manage to borrowed a ps2 from my friend and now just started playing final fantasy X 2..  tomorrow going to watch 'whole 10 yards' with jason. friday going moreton bay, hoping to see whales. next week is bettered planned.  my blind date, aris, is coming to brisbane again. but not to work, not here for a day, but she is coming here for a holiday. :D:D since im so free also, will bring her around brisbane and goldcoast. :D:D oh and my school results not out yet.. QUT slow.. UQ, jason's uni, results are all out liao.. jason did not too bad.. got a distinction. me hopefully can get a couple of distinctions too.. hehehe :D my results will be out on the 14th.. sianz..   &nbsp urlLink     dont you think the girls in this pic are chio? ... warrau.. arent you impress with computer graphics these days? the game play is even better i tell you... :]   "no matter how dark the night is, morning always comes..."   lulu - final fantasy X  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      on monday, 5 days ago, there was an Asian party @ family. named Klub Kandy. like mambo in zouk, this is klub kandy in family. this is the second klub kandy i have been to since i came here.. not as fun as tiesto, but can do lar.. 90% asians. we were upstairs most of the time, playing silly games like, 7-up, 007, superman, etc. hehehe..  but i miss playing with the pros..  yes im talking about all you bitches in singapore :P gary, kev, tk, ivan, beng, muscle, andy, yang, apes, G, and all those that i missed out..  but it is always fun playing with newbies :D:D kakakaka.. ah bran didnt go though.. he went to see sunrise @ byron bay.  tried a new drink. 'absense'. think thats how you spell it.. contains 80% alcohol.. taste like shiiiiiiiiittt...... but its all good.. :D miss flamo.. miss 'shitty' long island..  but i manage to get on 4 girls in family! :D  &nbsp urlLink     hehehehehe :D:D:D   urlLink     from the left, iris, weijun, handsome dude, hsin, grace, another handsome dude. grace is me and jason's new daughter. now we got 3 daughters liao.. all are good girls.. hehehe     "whosse your dadddddyy?"  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     "The Da vinci Code" Dan Brown Chapter 74 page 411  "He gave her a moment. Admittedly, the concept of sex as a pathway to God was mind-boggling at first. Langdon's Jewish stuidents always looked flabbergasted when he first told them that the early Jewish tradition involved ritualistic sex.  In the Temple, no less.  Early Jews believed that the Holy of Holies in Solomon's Temple housed not only God but also His powerful female equal, Shekinah.   Men seeking spiritual wholeness came to the Temple to visit priestesses--or  hierodules -- with whom they made love and experienced the divine through physical union.   The Jewish tetragrammaton YHWH-- the sacred name of God-- in fact derived from jehovah, an androgynous physical union between the masculine jah and the pre-Hebraic name for Eve, Havah."    for those who have read the book, you will know what Hieros Gamos is. Sex ritual. i have finished the book and this perticular sentence above really caught my attention..   "Men seeking spiritual wholeness came to the Temple to visit priestesses--or  hierodules -- with whom they made love and experienced the divine through physical union.      hmmmmmmm.... men wanting to commune with god goes to the temples? with the help of the prostit.. i mean priestesses, they will reach their climax and be closer to god? wooww...   do YOU see God when you climax? or do you see anyone at all? what were you thinking when you climax? or were there any thoughts going through your head? for me, everything just goes blank... just the sensation that overwhelms my whole body.. ISTEMEWA.... :D:D hee    interesting book. highly recommmended.. gives you a whole new concept of the bible and the Holy Grail.. and also jesus and mary's history..   
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      went to the strawberry farm that day. my image of a strawberry farm is like chest level bushes, where i can stand up and pluck it off and just throw it into my basket behind my back or something... and to my supprise, its more like a strawberry plant..    urlLink     had to kneel down to pluck them.. some nice big red ones are really well hidden. have to go low to spot them. hehehe.     urlLink     my nice berries.. hehehehe    urlLink     my whole straberry plucking crew.. notice anything under my ears?   urlLink     a close up of my new fresh earrings.. hehe    urlLink     strawberry plucking is definitely an experience. 1 whole plastic plate of it only cost me $4.40 . eat until siao.. after that we went Glass House Mountains walk walk.. cos nearby.. there was no glass, no house, no glass house, on the mountain. the view on top reminds me of thailand.. how i use to go up hill tops and examine rounds fired onto another hill....   urlLink     my Taichi pose..    urlLink     it was fun.. although most of my straberries are not as sweet as i thought it would be.. and some are really sour.. dammn..   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      remember my grades for ITB627 Network Technologies? i got 73%, grade 5. hoping to appeal and get 2% to become Grade 6. so my GPA would be 5 and not 4.75? well, i had an appointment on friday morning 9am with my lecturer to discuss this.. but when i woke up, it was 9am already... fuck.. after i decided to skip it, i slept for 30secs and decided to rush for it instead.. upon reaching school, its 915am already. i ran to the ticketing box and realised i had only $1.40 with me.. minimun parking $2 for an hour.. CCB..  oh what the heck, i ran up ignoring the parking ticket and found the door of my lecturer locked... fark.. think he left after 15min thinking i put him aeroplane.. sianz.. so i went into a lab and email a 'sorry' mail to him hoping to make another appointment.. after i send it, i went to check again, this time, he was there! but a indian girl was waiting outside for him so she got him first.. so i waited.. at 10am, she left and it was my turn. oh and throughout, i overheard the whole conversation about her asking about her exam paper, well, she did dammmn bad.. failed every question man..  anywayz, i talked to him and i just couldnt find any marks for him to add.. i just need 1.5 marks to get the 2%!! fark!! so finally i decided to send in for a remark of the whole paper.. hoping to get 1.5 marks.. haiz.. when i reach the car, i saw a ticket at my windscreen.. ccb..    urlLink     knnbccb... $37.50 fine.. ccb.. i now financial crisis liao still fine me.. narbeh.. haiz... 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>