<Blog>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today was the first day that actually felt like  summer . I woke up on the couch at about 1PM, laid there for about 2 hours, staring at the ceiling... It's nice not having anything to do. Oh. -laughs-. You have to hear why I was on the couch...   So last night, we come home from dinner. I walk in my room, kick my shoes off, look over, and there is this  HUGE  spider on my bed... I froze (like it was gonna jump the 6 feet from my bed to my door and EAT me! haha). I started looking for things to smash it with that were in my immediate vicinity, and said to myself "Screw this, kill it with the damn pillow." So I grabbed the pillow, but it ran! It went into the folds of my comforter so I flipped the comforter off my bed (Probably launching it into the ceiling) and lost sight of him... I'm mortally terrified of the fact of a spider being near me when I sleep... So I took my comforter and my pillow out on the back patio and flipped them in the air for about 10 minutes.... BACK TO WHAT I DID TODAY.  Well. I didn't do much else... Went to the pool. Got in the water... Didn't have much else to do seeing as I'm not the social type. I sat down at my chair and opened a book entitled  The Mystery of Flight 427 . I read about half of it last christmas when I got it, but it started getting too deep into politics, and kept getting farther and farther away from the part of the plane crash. I only took it with me so I'd keep myself occupied. I'll probably buy a new book on Amazon tonight.   It's 6:30PM and I still haven't eaten... That's another thing I commonly do over the summer. I just don't get hungry, ever. We're going to Zaxby's tonight (>     Sunset in Dinosaur Valley, Saskatchewan    A flower in Nassau    Sunset as seen from a hill near my aunt's lakehouse (Saskatchewan, Canada)    My little sister in the process of getting her hair braided (Nassau, Bahamas)    Sunrise as seen from a tiny bay in the Bahamas    A mighty sunrise shrouded in clouds (Bahamas)    Sunlight glinting off the surface of the ocean    The ice that sent everyone home from school early    
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      As I sit here typing this, a determined mosquito continues to heave itself into the Liquid Crystal Display of my iBook.  Today was boring. Didn't get up till mid-afternoon. On the way to my mom's house I very nearly hit my dads car, a road cone, and my NEIGHBOR. -laughs- well... that wouldn't have been so bad.  Thanks rina for the comments, and you're right. The picture is too big, but as of now i'm a little too lazy to mess with it. I got 200 bucks from my parents for straight a's, and very little is left over. I'll probably go shopping or something, since (BAM! killed the mosquito!) I don't really have anything big to save for. The SciFi channel is on. How annoying.  EDIT: Okay, so I will mess with it.   It's the stud!  -laughs- I found my lost post from Monday. It is below.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'm finally free from the burden of school... I got a 92 on my math final, thus giving me straight a's (First time since 4th grade). I also got my iPod today... It's wonderful.  Yesterday we were at Hilltop and my dad's car battery died. His friend clamped some small jumper cables to the battery and this little box (Which we later discovered to be a cordless drill battery) and after a minute or two the car started! It was neat.... As I write, i'm waiting for the last of 8 cd's to save to my hard drive so I can put the songs on my iPod. It takes forever...
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It's Monday. What more can be said? I checked out photobucket, but the picture is too large. I'm still pretty new to this place... so yeah. I've got a lot to learn in the area of posting and such.  Huh... I think I did sorta o.k. on my math test. My grade is constantly going up in that class, yet I have turned in nothing new. Weird... I got up at 5:45 this morning to organize my Health notebook. It had to be done... AH! The highlight of my day was definetly when my crazy Lit teacher said I could exempt her exam... The requirements are that you have above a 90 and have missed 3 or fewer days. My grade is a 94, and i've missed 9 days. Spot the error? Hope she doesn't. I also took an IQ test and made a 126... It mentioned something about my linguistic skills and blah blah. That I was a good writer...  'Whatever'. It's like the universal phrase that can get you out of any confrontation when you've dug yourself a hole that you can't or don't want to get out of. BLAH. Some people make me so mad... The random thoughts are spewing about, which usually means I don't have much else to say that is relevant... So until next time...
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'm sitting here worrying about a math test I missed on Friday. I woke up  very  late, and after a bit of manipulation, I got my way and stayed home... Oh well. It shouldn't be too bad... My math grade is strong enough to sustain the hit of a bad test, but I think i've got what it's on under my belt. Even if I don't, I realize that i'll just have to deal with it.  I finally got around to packing my PS2 that I sold on ebay. I hate packing, all types. I am proud to say, however, that it is not budging... Or at least I hope!  I got everything I had hoped to get done today done. I packed my PS2, did my laundry, made my lunch, and cleaned the living room, among other things. I'm exhausted and struggling to keep my eyes open among rude comments from my "friend" that i'm recieving via IM, so I think i'll tell her off and go to bed.   Oh! Before I go, (If anyone is reading this) do any of you know a site where I can upload my picture for use in my profile? I find it rather stupid that you can't just upload your picture straight to the site but oh well... We're not perfect. Bye!
     
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yesterday I got the bad pump at the gas station, and got gas all over myself. Today has been pure nothingness. Sitting around... Not anything anybody really wants to hear about.   Next week is our last week of school... Thursday and Friday are both half days for finals... I didn't turn in my early release form on Friday, when it was due (I was absent), so I hope they let me turn it in Monday. I'm not the board-cleaning computer-moving type they're looking for... I can't wait till we get school over. It's been fun, but it's time for it to be OVER!   I'm still saving for my iPod... Any monetary donations are welcome:) I'm almost there, though. I think I'm gonna get mine at BestBuy, where I'll also get the two year warranty against anything that goes wrong. I got that with my cell a few years ago, and had to replace it twice. It helped.  My friend Nicole is at the Chastain Amphitheater in Atlanta as I speak, at the Fleetwood Mac concert. She's SO LUCKY! I hope she's having a good time... I wish I'd known about it when she got the tickets. That would've been great. 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'm so mad. I'm not even gonna get into it.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      -laugh- probably some weird error. Notice how the thing that's usually directly to the upper right had corner is at the bottom? Strange...
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It's 6:08 and i've got nothing to do. Went to bed at about 11 and have been up since 2. I think i'll go to work with my dad today... I think I pissed off a few friends tonight. One (not you Blake) has annoyed me forever, and it's finally over between us. I made a comment that prehaps I shouldn't have in Blake's live journal, and she thinks i'm offended. I'm not, at all. This is America, and you're free to believe what you want to believe. -yawn-. But now i'd think Blake is gonna be mad at me... I really hope not. The mall was TONS of fun, and I don't want to lose her... ugh. I think about stuff too much. 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ... why is 'seafoam green' green? Isn't foam from the sea white?
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ... why is 'seafoam green' green? Isn't foam from the sea white?
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Got up really early this morning and cleaned my room... Then the kitchen. When dad got home from golfing, we went to Taco Mac and his Buffalo Wings were undercooked so they picked up the bill. Thank god. Then we went downtown and I spent $40 on a bookbag that I wanted to take with me on my trip... But now I hate it. The store I bought it from accepts no returns and I don't like the way it feels on your back at ALL... My dad flat out didn't feed the parking machine, and we got a ticket. Didn't realize it was under the windshield wiper till we were flying down the highway though... Then we pulled over in the Taco Stand parking lot (I love that place) and got it. ohh. Right when I sat down to type this, I saw somehting floating in the air next to me... It was a spider... Right next to my head. I threw down my computer and ran out of the room yelling... I still don't know where it is.   I hate bugs.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
          How to make a Ryan        Ingredients:   5 parts friendliness  3 parts ambition  5 parts         Method:  Add to a cocktail shaker and mix vigorously. Serve with a slice of sadness and a pinch of salt. Yum!        Username:       urlLink Personality cocktail  From  urlLink Go-Quiz.com   Can't say I completely agree with my results, but it's fun anyways. I'm dying to know what that 3rd ingredient is...
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today me and Blake went to the mall. Had a great time... We went to Rich's, because I was looking for a new cologne. I decided to get Lucky You, and for 47 I could buy one bottle. I opted for the 52.50 tin box, with a big bottle, a small bottle, and some body stuff... ALSO i get this crazy huge bag and a stool/cooler as a free gift... Insane. got some new shorts at AE, and got Blake her b-day present early (at Pacsun)  Speaking of Pacsun...  We got there and the person working behind the counter was  very  friendly.... not to mention good looking. haha. We kept making eye contact... Might have been something between us -laughs-. That's all I'll say about that.   Then we went to BestBuy where I got my dad the Jet CD for Father's Day. Then I went home. sounds a little boring, but I had tons of fun... Right now I sorta have that feeling you get when you've passed up a big opportunity unwillingly... grrr
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Wow.... a blank page. I think  that's what's inspires me most. A big ol' page to fill up with my thoughs.  We went to the lakehouse again yesterday. I think Amy has the hots for Jonathan (or me, but she'd be wasting her time!) I really hope Amy doesn't read this... It rained for about an hour and a half and it was so geat hanging out, watching the dock swing side to side and watching the lightning bolts hit trees on the Georgia side of the lake. We got home around 10:00p.m., and by then I had been up for 30 hours straight. I fell asleep on my bed reading my bank statement. Never have I been so tired in my life.  I talked with one of my once (and still) close friends. we've drifted apart recently due to conflicting beliefs I guess... It's sad really. I have some good memories, but sometimes people just cant accept one another. I think it's because of her religion (hint: starts with C) and the ideas she was brought up with.... I wish I could erase what was said between us and start over. (Cheer for me, I didn't capitalize at the beginning of the sentence!)  I'm looking forward to my trip. It'll be nice to get away to a life totally different from mine. I'd really like to be listening to music right now but I left my headphones back home. Maybe i'll plug in my FM Transmitter and get my kid sisters purple boombox to play it on.... there aren't any other small radios around.  -30 Minutes Later-  There. I took my last idea and ran with it. I got my little sisters boombox and have it hooked up... it's playing "Smile at You" by Fleetwood Mac...   I had a million other things to say, but nearly every one left me when I was struggling to plug in the charger for my iPod under this huge-ass desk. One thing I remember is that REALLY long posts like this get boring quickly, so i'll kill it. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The past few days have been a blur. Sunday we went to the lakehouse and had a blast. Rode the jetskis, fell off numerous times... got burned... It's all fun. Last night I booked my plane tickets to Saskatchewan. I'll be flying Northwest Airlines, and I have a connecting flight in Minneapolis/St. Paul. Hopefully I won't get lost...  I made banana bread today (my FAVORITE)...now i'm kinda tired. My mom called me and woke me up at 10:30 to tell me to check my email... I had to set a PIN number for my Aeroplan account. (Aeroplan is the frequent flyer program for Air Canada) Surfed the net a bit from bed, then fell back asleep at like 11:30. I had a weird weird dream... Dreamt I was at my new school and that it was some kinda military base where all the officials were convinced Vancouver (and the rest of Midwestern Canada for that matter) were full of terrorists. They were getting ready to nuke 'em too... Then I walked through this hallway, out the door and it was snowing. I walked on to a street and fell, and just laid there in the slush next to an orange VW Minibus... Very bizarre. The UPS guy woke me up. I didn't answer it because I was only half-clothed and my arm was asleep, thus making it immobile. I felt like i'd been thrown from bed. Tomorrow I have to clean the  whole  house... Definetly not looking forward to that...  Since i'm meandering, I think i'll wait for my songs (purchased from iTunes legally!) to finish downloading and catch some Z's.  In case you're wondering, i'm downloading   Fit but You Know It by The Streets  100 Years by Five for Fighting   I'm so happy that I remembered the HTML tags for bullets! -laughs- Well... I've nothing important to say so I'll head out. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>