<Blog>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Sixth Sunday of Easter at St. Timothy's Church in Warwick, RI Affectionately known as the "Roundhouse"  Processional hymn: All the Earth Proclaim the Lord (Ditsy-Deiss) Psalm 67: O God, let all the nations praise you (Tone 6) Alleluia: O Filii et Filiae (Mode II, arr. Page / Verses: Tone 2) Offertory hymn: Come, Holy Ghost (Lambillotte) Eucharist: Mass of Creation (Haugen) Communion hymn: Let There Be Peace on Earth (Miller/Jackson) Recessional hymn: Alleluia! Sing to Jesus! (Hyfrydol)  PROGRAM NOTES: The Sixth Sunday of Easter is usually the Sunday before Pentecost where you hear such lines as "The Father will send you a Paraclete", meaning the Holy Spirit.  This explains my choice of "Come, Holy Ghost". Incidentally, on "Come, Holy Ghost":  Has anyone ever seen a piece of muzak called "One Spirit, One Church"?  It has "Come, Holy Ghost" incorporated as verses to a refrain that sounds like something that can be plunked out on a toy piano.  To boot, CHG (the real hymn) is 3/4 - CHG (the verses to 1S1C) is 4/4.  Do yourselves a favor, all, and stick with the REAL "Come, Holy Ghost".  It is the true Lambillotte, and has stuck to congregations for a couple of centuries. "Mass of Creation" (often referred to as "Massive Cremation") is something I'm stuck with for a bit here, at least till next year, unfortunately.  This Fall, I will be teaching Richard Proulx's "Community Mass", should I still be at the Roundhouse.  Otherwise, not much Haugen-Daas from this organist. "Let There Be Peace on Earth" (often referred to as "Let There Be Peas and Carrots on Earth") was not my choice.  The pastor preached on world peace (mainly in light of current events in Iraq and other countries where terrorism seems to be the norm).  Till next post, nanu-nanu! BMP
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Greetings! My name is Brian Michael Page.  I've been a church organist for 23 years, and a composer of sacred music for 20 years.  To boot, I've been a singer in churches for 29 years.  Currently, I'm serving as music director and organist at St. Timothy's Church in Warwick, RI, directing an adult choir of about 15 voices.  I have a wonderful wife named Ann - she really is the love of my life, my support when I'm down, and someone to put my in my place when I'm "too up". :-)  I also have what I consider the four best kids in the world - Christopher, Jessica, Brian Robert, and Brittany.  My favorite mentors outside of my family include my high school chorus director, Mrs. Nectar Lennox, a friend who I sang under back in 1975, Mr. Reuel Gifford, my former pastor, Fr. Kevin Fisette of Holy Name Church in Providence, RI, and, not so directly, the late Dr. C. Alexander Peloquin, renowned composer of sacred music and longtime director of music at the Cathedral of Saints Peter and Paul in Providence.  Former churches I've served are (in reverse chronological order): Holy Name of Jesus, Providence, RI Saint Teresa of the Child Jesus, Pawtucket, RI Saint Benedict, Warwick, RI Precious Blood, Woonsocket, RI Saint Mary, Cranston, RI Sacred Heart, West Warwick, RI Our Lady of Loreto, East Providence, RI Saint Sebastian, Providence, RI Sacred Heart, Woonsocket, RI Our Lady of Victories, Woonsocket, RI Saint Joseph, Cumberland, RI Saint Aidan, Cumberland, RI  In further blogs, I will be posting stories of my present and former parishes, other cool musings relating to liturgy and liturgical music.  All of this is in the context of the Roman Catholic Church.  See you all soon!  BMP  -If the music is good and the spoken word is bad, it's a concert. -If the spoken word is good and the music is bad, it's a talk show. (Alexander Peloquin, 1918-1997)
     

    
</post>


</Blog>