<Blog>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      situs islam terkini ; tragedipalestina.com, bangsamusnah.com, keajaibanalQuran.com
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      teah banyak kritikan, "kok pake b. ingris seh?" yah itu hanya untuk ebih universal. mahi mohon maaf bagi kawan kawan yang  DISAPOINTED
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      maaf bila site terlalu lama terbuka karena kapasitas antara komp centre dgn provider sangat signifikan berbeda,thank's........ 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
         
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      DO FISH FLY?  Flying fish don't fly with wings like birds, but they slide on fins that resemble a bird's wings. They travel about 56 kilometres (35 miles) in an hour. These small fish can move faster in water by spreading their fins and lifting their tails out of the water. In this way, they slide swiftly in water.  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      DO FISH FLY?  Flying fish don't fly with wings like birds, but they slide on fins that resemble a bird's wings. They travel about 56 kilometres (35 miles) in an hour. These small fish can move faster in water by spreading their fins and lifting their tails out of the water. In this way, they slide swiftly in water.  THE HERON  The heron displays great skill in catching fish. It stands up spreading its wings in an umbrella shape above its head. This produces a shadow and prevents reflections from the surface of the water. Now, the heron can clearly see its prey under the surface of the water. The wings of the bird form a circular shadow on the water's surface, and it always fishes inside this circle.  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      MIRACLES OF THE QUR'AN  The Qur'an was sent to mankind 1,400 years ago, but there are some facts related in the Qur'an whose meanings we have only been able to uncover recently.   From the planets to the stars, human beings to animals, Allah created everything in the universe. Our Lord already knows everything we have not discovered so far and He informs us about some of that in the Qur'an. We can only learn these things when Allah permits us and then we realise that they are miracles of Allah.    How the Universe Came into Existence   He is the Originator of the heavens and the earth… (Surat al-An'am: 101)  The universe came into existence from nothing 15 billion years ago. In other words, the universe suddenly came into existence from nothing.   Only the science of the twentieth century enabled us to attain scientific evidence of this great event. Therefore, it was impossible to know this scientifically 1,400 years ago. But, as is also mentioned in the previous verse, Allah told us this fact when the Qur'an was first revealed. This is a miracle of the Qur'an and one of the pieces of evidence that it is the Speech of Allah.    The Expansion of the Universe  In the Qur'an, which was revealed 14 centuries ago at a time when the science of astronomy was still primitive, the expansion of the universe was described like this:  And it is We who have constructed the heaven with might, and verily, it is We who are steadily expanding it. (Surat adh-Dhariyat, 47)  The word "heaven", as stated in this verse, is used in various places in the Qur'an with the meaning of space and universe. Here again, the word is used with this meaning. In other words, in the Qur'an it is revealed that the universe "expands". And this is the very conclusion that science has reached today.  Until the dawn of the 20th century, the only view prevailing in the world of science was that "the universe has a constant nature and it has existed since infinite time." The research, observations, and calculations carried out by means of modern technology, however, have revealed that the universe in fact had a beginning, and that it constantly "expands."  Orbits  Many of you know that our world and the other planets have orbits. In fact, not only do the planets in our Solar System have orbits, but also all heavenly bodies in the universe have their separate orbits. That is, they all move in very precisely computed paths. This scientific truth that scientists have only recently uncovered was revealed 1,400 years ago:   It is He Who created the night and the day, and the sun and the moon. They swim along, each in an orbit. (Surat al-Anbiya: 33)  As is also seen in this verse, Allah informs us about a scientific fact which was only discovered recently. At the time the Qur'an was revealed, people did not know that heavenly bodies moved in constant orbits. But Allah knows everything and tells what He wills to His slaves.   The Roundness of the Earth  The understanding of astronomy of the time, when the Qur'an was revealed, perceived the world differently. It was then thought by some that the earth was flat, and others had different theories. But the fact that the earth was round was not then generally known. However, from the Qur'an it was understood by implication that the shape of the world is round. The relevant verse reads:   He has created the Heavens and the Earth for Truth. He wraps the night up in the day, and wraps the day up in the night… (Surat az-Zumar: 5)   The Arabic word "takwir" is translated as "to wrap" in the above verse. In English it means "to make one thing lap over another, folded up as a garment that is laid away." The day and the night wrapping over each other can be true only if the earth is round. But, as mentioned above, the Arabs who lived 1,400 years ago thought that the earth was flat. This means that the roundness of the world was hinted at in the Qur'an, which was revealed in the seventh century. That is because Allah teaches the truth to mankind. This matter, indicated in the Book revealed by Allah, was verified only centuries later by scientists.   Since the Qur'an is Allah's word, the most correct words were used in it when describing the universe. It is unlikely that a human could know and choose these words. But because Allah knows everything, He can make these facts available to man at any time He wills.   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      blog ini adalah up date dari mahlil.blogspot.com, berhubung blog yang lalu masih longer little web, kali ini sudah grow up. trim's............
     

    
</post>


</Blog>