<Blog>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   A week ago I was laying in bed and heard a "pop-pop" my knee felt like a rubber band being stretched as far as it would go then being snapped. I tried to buy a ghetto brace from Krogers and deal with the pain so I wouldn't have to go to the doctors again. Last Friday the pain got to the place I couldn't take it. My knee was making a crunching/grinding noise not the normal cracking I hear from my arthritis. So Saturday I send countless hours at the ER. They do x-rays and say nothing is broke. Damn it took a bunch of x-rays to tell you that? I need to become a doctor! I stated over and over again I didn't twist it and I could move it. So the doctor plays with my knee for a while scratches his head and says I think you might have torn ligaments and cartilage. So he dx me with internal derangement of the knee, gave me some pain pills, a brace which makes me have to hold my knee straight at all times and some crutches. He gave me a number to an orthopedic doctor to call and said to call them within the next ten days. So first thing Monday morning I called the number the ER had given me and they say you can't make this appointment you family doctor has to call us first and refer you. I made the mistake of thinking this might be easy! So I had to see my family doctor. He plays around with my knee for a while and says he agrees with the ER and wants me to get an MRI then he will call an orthopedic doctor for me. In the mean time I am suppose to keep the God awful brace on and continue to use the crutches. So tomorrow I go for my MRI. In the meantime I have had this stupid brace on my leg which has a steel plate down the back so I can't bend my knee so now when I try to bend my leg I can't at all. So no matter what the original problem was I will end up having to do physical therapy to get my leg working. I know I won't get the MRI results until mid next week so I'm really frustrated right now. There's not much I can do with this brace on. The pain sucks but I try to work through it. My fear is I will have to get surgery and I am not looking forward to the at all. I think "the wolf" has me pinned down for now but soon I will be back on my feet and kick his ass!  The Lupus scares me a little more everyday. I am 26 looking at knee surgery because of it. I am in a support group and I hear all the stories of the woman in the group. Most of them have had countless kindney problems and many have had kidney transplants. I don't like to spend to much time thinking about my Lupus but somedays I do get stuck in fear of what next. I don't fear death for myself but I don't want my kids to grow up without me. I don't want to be a burden to my family and I often feel that way already. I take pride in doing things on my own and not depending on anyone but every year it seems I become more dependent on those around me. Whether it's for someone to open a jar or for someone to carry things down the stairs because for that day my body isn't working. I hate the fact that some days I just can't do things normal people do. I push myself as far as I can but sometimes my body won't do what I tell it to do. I understand it could be worse but these are my pains I know no worse pain then what I am feeling. To not be able to go out a toss a ball with my son or not be able to brush my daughters hair because my hands hurt doesn't seem fair to my kids.  

						
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So much time spent on things that don't matter, so much time spent on others. We don't take the time to care anymore. We don't take the time to love anymore. I lost you a long time ago but it took me this long to see it. All these years just a faded memory. Why are we still here? Is it because once in a while we get that old feeling back? For the kids? Maybe because it has become comfortable...  My heart is still in your hands but your mind has drifted. You don't look at me the same. You are too busy to notice. Maybe my health has turned you away from me. Maybe the years have made us change so that we can't find common ground anymore.   I'm tired of being that painting on the wall you notice from time to time. I'm tired of being in the same room with you but still alone. I'm tired of feeling nothing. I miss the passion. I miss the friendship. I miss the butterflys I use to get when you kissed me. I miss the way you use to look at me.  You pour your heart out to others but have nothing to say to me. You stay up all hours of the night with your buddies but it's lights out at nine with me. You are closer to people you have never met then you are to me. You don't even know who I am anymore. I bet I could ask questions about your online buddies and you would know all the answers. Do you even know of my dreams? Do you know my fears? Do you know anything about me anymore? Do you even care?   So many times we said forever but now that seems so far away. I'm not sure I see forever anymore. I can't live my life like this. I can't beg you to love me. I can't beg for you attention. I want you to love me. I want you to want me. I want you to notice me but not because I asked you to.  So where do I go from here? What is best for the kids? What is best for me? What is best for you?  Maybe you would rather not having me around? Maybe I add too much stress to your life? Maybe we just got lazy? Maybe we figured we would always be here for each other so we don't have to work at it? Maybe we have taken each other for granted? Maybe we just don't care anymore? Maybe we don't think we deserve any better? Maybe love isn't forever?        

						
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I am mom I am wife I am a homemaker At times I feel very useless At times I feel nothing To many people think if you don’t bring home a pay check you don’t work To many people think if you don’t have a 9 to 5 you are lazy Where is my life going? What will I become? I had many dreams I had many plans Now I dream of nothing Now I don’t make any plans I am only a mom I am only a wife I am only a homemaker   

						
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So my dad calls today to let me know my Grandma's sister died. She had bone cancer and I know she's better off. So knowing this makes it all better right? No not really. Growing up me my brother and sister were the poor white trash of the family. Everyone knew what an asshole my dad was so either people took pity on us or wanted nothing to do with us. There were few people who gave a shit. Opal (my grandma's sister) was one of those people who cared for us not out of pity but just because she had a good heart. She also took great care of my grandma. So she was old and full of cancer so I should buck up and be happy that she's gone I guess...Most of my pain is for my Grandma she is about the only one left from her family and the years are getting to her. She feels very alone and I can't handle seeing my grandma in pain and I know I have to stay strong for her this weekend while we bury her sister. My grandparents are the world to me and I know their time is coming. I've lost many people but my grandparents were my hope when I was a kid they are the ones who taught me about love. Before Steve and the kids it was only my grandparents. Now my life is full of love but I know some of that love will be taken away soon.  I know I will have to see my dad for the funeral. People always say to leave the past behind you. I try everyday to do this. I get sick just looking at my dad or hearing his voice. I start to feel sick to my stomach and end up with a headache. I would love to find forgiveness in my heart for him but he doesn't want it. He won't own up for the times he knocked around my mom. He won't own up for all the hate he gave us kids. Most of the time people who don't understand baggage have never had any of their own. I love people who have no clue what we went through say I should let it go and move on with my life. I have moved on with my life but the drama from my childhood will always be there with me. It reminds me to never let myself turn into the asshole my dad is. I know the pain a parent who doesn't love their child can bring so I make sure my kids know everyday I love them. Every time I see or talk to my dad my past and present meets. There's no moving on or shoving it aside it is there and I have to deal with it for the moment then when I see him in anther six months I deal with it again.   My leg is still hurting me. I go to the orthopedic doctor next week. It looks like I'm heading towards surgery. All my ligaments in my knee are torn apart. So I'll either get some plastic in my knee or parts off a dead person. Kind of weird to think about having a dead persons body parts. I just want it over all ready I am sick of the waiting game.  So today is a shitty day. The good thing is there's only so much shit that happens before good things start to happen so soon my ship should come in right? 

						
</post>


</Blog>