<Blog>


<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Mondays suck. I always feel tired, more so than usual. Today we finished STAR testing for the fifth grade. I'm so glad that testing is over, but now I have to start my multiple measures. There is quite a bit of work to do at the end of the school year. I think it is the most stressful time of the year, at least for the teachers. Just my thoughts on Monday.
     
    
</post>


<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Man oh man where does the time go? It is already Friday, May 21st. 2004 This was the fastest week I can remember in a long time. School is almost over, and summer will soon be here. I am so looking forward to surfing, kayaking, mountain biking, motorcycle camping and of course just doing nothing. My cohort and I finished packing the STAR tests for ouur district today. We finished early, so we graded writing for our classes. Work was easy today. I have to admit the 500.00 I'm getting for being a STAR test coodinator was the easiest 500.00 I have ever made. Anyway tomorrow is Saturday and I am hoping for a sunny day with some fun surf. If not I'll take the sunny day and call it even.
     
    
</post>



<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today is the eve of the last day of school. What an exhausting week this has been. The kids are so ready for summer, but then again so am I. I had a good year with some really good kids in my fifth grade class. The last day of school is always a little emotional. The kids, even though they are ready for summer, they still give you that look as they leave, "I wish I could be in your class again. " I try to keep a strait face, but sometime it is difficult. IT is the eve of the last day of school, what a wonderful time of the year for teachers. 
    
</post>


<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was the first day of summer vacation for me. I am a teacher living on the southern coast of California. It is pleasant for the most part, except we have what is known as, "June gloom." Basically it is overcast and drizzly all day long. So evn hough it is very nearly the official start of summer, we have temperatures in the low 60's. Today was sort of stay at home and drink coffee, sort files and organize my desk, i.e. a nothing kind of day. I hope to catch some good surf tomorrow, if not I plan on riding my mountain bike with my friend Walter. There is always something to do here in Ventura. Summer 2004!!!!!!!!!!!
    
</post>


<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today is tyhe first day of the Birankai summer camp here at San Francisco State University. I rode my motorcycle here, which wasn't all that bad. In fact I enjoyed it! Anyway I didn't  train the first calss today. I was a little burned out from the drive and I was ready to just lay down. Well not much more to write. 
    
</post>


<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was the first full day of training. The mat that we trained on is meant for wrestling, and it was especially hard on my knees today. I liked all the classes and I feel ready to have dinner, a few beers, and then time for bed. Each instructor definitely has their own style, all are awesome. I'll have to come back to edit this once later. 1 day done, 4 more to go.
    
</post>


</Blog>