<Blog>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Regarding my last post about informed consent.  I just thought about the fact that she was still covered under her parents insurance.  Why, then, shouldn't the consent need to come from them?  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My cousin recently had surgery for endometriosis.  During the procedure her Gynecologist found an inguinal hernia.  He took pictures of it and informed her about what he had found after the surgery.  My cousin was 22 years old at the time of her surgery and was responsible for giving the consent required to perform the repair of the hernia.  Her mother had been with her at all of her doctor appointments and was there in the waiting room of the hospital during the surgery.  When my cousin heard about the hernia and that her doctor had not tried to fix it at the time she was very confused.  She did not understand why her mother could not give consent for her.  The doctor had said that it could have been taken care of at the same time if they had had consent.   I understand all of the legal issues surrounding her case.  I know that, had they gone ahead with the surgery without her consent, they could have faced a heafty law suit especially if something had gone wrong.  My question is this; why don't physicians or the hospital offer the option to give consent for such a procedure?  If they had found cancer they did not have consent to remove it if possible.  Hospitals and patients alike could benefit from such provisions.  Many patients may choose to avoid having surgery again due to the associated risks.  Had they been able to fix two problems at once the insurance companies would have to cover both procedures, but only one hospitalization.  In her case, the hospital would have saved, at the very least, $10,000 due to the medicine that was required for her to undergo both procedures.  Is it on the part of the doctor that the second procedure was not performed.  Was this a ploy to have her come in again in order to be reimbursed more for a second opperation?  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The case of Paradise Hills Medical Center presents a serious ethical problem which faces administrators and providers alike.   On one hand, the physicians' viewpoint of withholding the information in the best interests of the patients seemed acceptable.  Informing the patients may very well cause the patients to refuse treatment that they require, or induce symptoms by the mere suggestion of them.  However, as the story progressed, the underlying issue of the oncology department and hospital as a whole losing business because of the negative publicity this issue would bring, seemed to outweigh the concern for the patients.  In my view, the patients should have been informed of the incident.  It is the responsibility of the hospital administrators, physicians, and other providers to disclose to patients any information regarding their health.  If the outcome would have resulted in litigation, the hospital had already taken an initiative to prove their concern by ordering the resignation of the medical physicist, whose responsibility it was to calibrate the equipment.  The patients have also signed informed consents to authorize the treatment.  If anything, I feel that the outcome would have been positive for the hospital, because they took responsibility for their actions.  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So this is what a blog is.  I've been away on business all week and finally got a chance to set up my blog.  I hope this works and everyone sees it alright.  Anyhow, I know this exercise is supposed to be somewhat of a journal for us, so here's my first entry. After returning from south Florida I stopped into work to see how everything was going at my home store, (as many of you may know, I work for a restaurant chain as a corporate trainer).  I found out that the GM at this particular store just got dismissed.  Reason being...he went out and had a couple cocktails with employees after work.  There is a policy about managers "hanging out" with employees.  Personally, I think it is a pretty dumb policy.  It's kind of hard not to form a friendship or some type of bond with employees that you manage.  I think what you do after work shouldn't matter, as long as those actions don't affect what is going on at work.  I'm sure the policy was implemented for those "just in case" situations, but it shouldn't have such a stiff penalty.  This individual has been with the company for fifteen years, and because of a bad judgement call he has no job.  Anyone have any thoughts?
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I came across a pretty good article concerning healthcare ethics and the death penalty.  A story in Reuters news stated that lawyers in New York hope to charge doctors with professional misconduct for participating in executions.  The article brings up a good point.  Other than the fact that the patient involved is a convicted criminal sentenced to their punishment, how is their death any different from assisted suicide?  Although it sounds like I agree with the lawyers in this matter, I in fact am riding the other wagon.  Just because the patient is a convicted murderer, is that any reason to deny him a humane death.  If doctors are not allowed to administer the lethal injection or assure that the prisoner is not subjected to a "cruel" punishment, then society is no better than the ones being executed.  These prisoners have no choice in the matter, they have been sentenced to death.  Not to allow them a painless death would truly be inhumane.    "The idea that physicians who have taken the Hippocratic Oath to take care of and preserve life, are taking part in executions is alarming and it is another sign that the death penalty tears at human rights," said Michael Stark of the Campaign to End the Death Penalty.  I agree that the death penalty tears at human rights, but unfortunately, its a part of our society.  Are the condemned any less human than the rest of us...some would argue yes (usually the victim's friends and family).  However, they ARE human, and they DO have rights.  I agree with attorney Kenneth Baum, who also teaches medical ethics at Yale University, "If a physician wants to be there and the condemned person wants them to be there, the physician's primary responsibility is to the patient."    Reuters News. (2004). Death Penalty Poses Ethics Quandary for Doctors. [Online Source].      Available: http://health.yahoo.com/search/healthnews?lb=s&p=id%3A59401  
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My blog for this week sort of adds on to last week's topic.  Although, instead of focusing on pharmaceutical companies, we're going to focus on third party payers.  The reason I want to add on to last week's post is that I read an interesting article in USA Today (http://www.healthscout.com/news/68/519371/main.html).  The article summarizes a study which found that the use of life saving drugs decreases when co-pays increase.  These drugs, called statins, have been proven to improve survival in patients with cardiovascular disease.  "Among patients whose co-pay was less than $10 a month, 50 percent remained on the drug after four years; in contrast, 50 percent of patients whose monthly co-pay was more than $20 stayed on their statin for only one year (USA Today)."  I know there are many different plans and many different factors in producing prices and co-pays, but I think there should be some kind of regulation on prices when research finds these kinds of statistics.  If a certain drug is proven to save lives, wouldn't it be in the best interest of the insurance company to offer these types of medications at a low co-pay?  It would save them money in the long run.  Even though the pharmaceutical companies set the prices that insurance companies ultimately pay, third party payers should regulate their prices that reflect the money they would save from these life saving drugs.  
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As my group and I sat down for dinner and our meeting on Thursday, we had an interesting conversation.  Shelley and I got into a discussion about the differences between the Canadian and American health systems.  We spoke in particular about prescription drugs.  As we have learned in some of our classes, the Canadian government negotiates with pharmaceutical companies concerning the pricing of drugs in Canada.  Obviously, there are many issues surrounding our governments decision not to regulate drug prices within our borders.  In my view most of these reasons are based on political agendas.  When it comes down to the matter, is it ethical for pharmaceutical companies to charge the inflated prices that they do in the United States, just because they can?   Are the drug companies inflating the prices in the U.S. to make up for profits lost in a socialized system? Probably!  What does it really cost for these companies to produce these drugs?  I know most of them blame research and development for the outrageous prices, but is this really the issue?  Most of these drug companies now use the media as a means to advertise their drugs.  How many times do you turn on the t.v. and see a commercial for a drug that does not even inform you of what it is for?  Air time is very expensive.  Even though I am aware of the process and how difficult it is to introduce a new drug, I refuse to believe that this is the primary reason for the costs of certain drugs.     Some people cannot afford the ridiculous prices put on these drugs, therefore cannot receive the medications that they need to get better.  How can pharmaceutical companies not have an ethical concern about denying sick people the medications that they need?  I feel that our government needs to exercise their power to negotiate with drug companies as the Canadian government does.  Also, if Canadians are allowed to come to America for healthcare, why are Americans getting grief about going to Canada for drugs?  As a side note, I will leave you with a quote from one of my Canadian friends..."We're just unarmed Americans with healthcare :)"  
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've been reading that campaigns aimed at increasing organ donations are not going so well.  There are many people in the United States alone that need organ transplants, but unfortunately, there are not enough organs to cover each patient.  The American Medical Association called for a study of incentives to increase people's willingness to donate organs (Kahn, 2002).  Some of the proposals seemed outright unethical to me.  One proposal is so-called presumed consent, a practice in which organs are collected after death unless individuals or families object.  Now this can't be ethical...it would probably help the organ donation cause tremendously, but the means is quite questionable.  This would be no better, in my eyes, than those doctors in the 1800's that stole corpses in order to study the human body.  It had been done with good intentions, and the medical profession probably benefited from the research, but the costs were unethical.  Providers must manage this issue with integrity and not compromise their ethics in the process.    Kahn, Jeffrey. (2002). Making organ donations a better deal. [Online Source]. Available:       http://www.cnn.com/2002/HEALTH/06/25/ethics.matters/index.html 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In case you wanted to read the articles, here are the references for the previous post...  CNN. (2004). Western diet hikes stroke risk, study finds. [Online Source]. Available:      http://www.cnn.com/2004/HEALTH/diet.fitness/07/02/western.diet.reut/index.html  Utton, Tim. (2004).Mums-to-be warned off Atkins diet. [Online Source]. Available:      http://www.sundaytimes.news.com.au/common/story_page/0,7034,10030463%255E949,00.html  
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am going crazy hearing about Atkins this and Atkins that.  People going out to dinner just to order a salad, in fear that their carbohydrate count may be too high.  I have had my suspisions about the diet and how safe it might be.  I feel that too much of one thing and not enough of another, could be pretty unhealthy.  You need balance in your diet, as well as your life.  It has been drilled into our heads from a very young age that we should follow a diet according to the food pyramid.  Wouldn't you know it...the base of the pyramid (the biggest group), which requires 6-11 servings a day, is the very thing that Atkins has said to cut out of your diets.  I can't stand the fact that restaurants, grocery stores, and even beer distributors have jumped on the low carb band wagon.  It's nuts to think that everyone is following a fad, not truly understanding what its consequences may be.  I've come across a few articles that discuss some of the dangers that a low carb high protein diet may have on a person on Atkins.  Health experts already say a diet high in animal fat, especially red meat, and low in fiber, fruits and vegetables has been linked to the risk of stroke; therefore, dietary modification may be an important way to reduce the risk of stroke," said Teresa Fung, an assistant professor of nutrition at Simmons College School for Health Studies in Boston, who led the study (CNN, 2004).  Some interesting research has also tied the diet to infertility.  A study found the diet's emphasis on meat could overload the body with protein, which could hinder the early development of an embryo.  It also could double the risk of genetic problems, making the possibility of a miscarriage significantly higher.  The latest warning comes after the high-fat, low-carbohydrate regime was linked to increased risk of diabetes, brittle bone disease, depression and breast cancer (Utton, 2004). With all of these perceived risk of the diet, is it ethical for corporate America to exploit the fad for what it is?  How ethical is it that corporations are backing the diet because it is what's popular, even though the risks are out there?    
     
    
</post>


</Blog>