<Blog>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Another weird site i found during a random surfing occasion...in this site there's a clock that counts how many seconds left till u r dead...stupid huh...but,well it;s kinda interesting so how about if u just move ur cursor 2 the link below and click....well at least it'll remind u that life is short.....when i tried it said that i'll be dead in july 2061...well there's still a lot of time....spare some and check this site  links:  urlLink Death Clock  
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I kinda found this pic when i was freakin bored.....but when i got a second look at it...kinda give me the creeps......so since it does give me some chilling feeling i'll just gonna leave it here...the link that is   urlLink Mysterious pic  
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      [Collected on the Internet, 1998]   A teenager is driving his girlfriend home from a date. The boy had been playing around earlier about the car running out of gas as a means to make out with her. Well, it doesn't work and she's mad. He starts up the car to take her home, apologizing all the way, when lo and behold they actually do run out of gas. He pulls the car over by some trees. It's very late and the area is secluded and wooded. The boy tells his girlfriend that he saw a gas station a couple of miles back and since going ahead would take even longer, he tells her to stay in the car with the windows rolled up and locked and he'll get back as fast as he can, no sense in both of them going, right?   Well, the girl waits in the car. It's been about 20 minutes when she hears a faint scratching noise. It starts to bother her, but she blows it off as the tree branches hitting the car, it had been windy that day, She decides to turn on the radio to listen to some music so it won't freak her out. Well, now it's been almost 2 hours and she's starting to get worried. Her boyfriend was a jock and could have easily made it there and back in under an hour. A half hour later she's very worried and decides to turn off the radio and look around. He had told her not to get out under any circumstances so she tries to peer out the window, she sees nothing. To her annoyment the scratching sound is still there. She decides that she will get out just long enough to break off that damn branch. She gets out and notices the gas can on the ground near the door. She immediately turns around and sees her boyfriend hanging upside down from the tree, throat slit, and his fingernails dragging across the top of the car making a scratching sound. Of course, had she been listening to talk radio instead of music, she would have known a maniac had escaped from the asylum near the woods where they were parked.     -------------------------------------------------------------------------------- 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Claim:   Two men each lost an arm in a grisly tug-of-war contest.  Status:   True.   Origins:   On 25 October 1997, a mass tug-of-war contest was held at a park along the Keelung River in Taipei in celebration of Retrocession Day (the 52nd anniversary of the end of the Japanese colonial rule in Taiwan). Over 1,600 participants joined in the contest, exerting over 80,000 kg of force on a 5-cm nylon rope that could bear a force of about 26,000 kg at most.   WARNING: The picture below is a gruesome photograph of this incident and will not automatically display. If you want to see the picture, hold the mouse pointer over this text to make it appear.  p/s:i didn't place the pic in case someone doesn't want to see it,but to those who's interested.Go to this link:  urlLink No hands   (not recommended to the weak hearted)   Within seconds the rope snapped, severing the left arms of two men (Yang Chiung-ming and Chen Ming-kuo) below the shoulder. (The severing of the limbs was believed to have been caused by sheer rebounding force of the broken rope rather than the men's having wrapped the rope around their arms, as was sometimes reported.) The victims were taken to Mackay Memorial Hospital and underwent seven hours of microsurgery to reattach their arms.    
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Have u ever thought that bush was a lying,sadistic cruel bastard.....well u have a chance to watch his groovier side...in this site...wow ur gonna get shocked when bush does his splits and moonwalks..  Click this link  urlLink dancing bush  
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Forever --------------------------------------------------------------------------------   "Edmund Kemper solved it all"   "He fooled the shrinks"   "Fooled the shrinks"   "It then apears the proclaimation"   "He fooled the shrinks"   "Fooled the shrinks"     "Edmund Kemper solved it all"   "He fooled the shrinks"   "Fooled the shrinks"   "It then apears the proclaimation"   "He fooled the shrinks"   "Fooled the shrinks"     "The fortress of forever"   "Been forsaken"   "Man made promise"   "Polluted with blue dye"   "Air, water, design"   "Man made promise"   "Polluted with blue dye"     "Can we tamper"   "We have gained"   "Outerspace, outerspace"   "A million years"   "The devistation of"   "Outerspace, outerspace"     "Can we tamper"   "We have gained"   "Outerspace, outerspace"   "A million years"   "The devistation of"   "Outerspace, outerspace"         "The fortress of forever"   "Been forsaken"   "Man made promise"   "Polluted with blue dye"   "Air, water, design"   "Man made promise"   "Polluted with blue dye"     "Fortress of forever"   "Been forsaken"   "Man made promise"   "Polluting of the sky" (x2)     "The fortress of forever"   "Been forsaken"   "Man made promise"   "Polluted with blue dye"   "Air, water, design"   "Man made promise"   "Polluted with blue dye"  
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Woohooo.The loooong tests have finally ended,no more sleepless nights,no more staying up late at night,and no more Studying..Hah finally rest.Well since the long three weeks has ended..i'm kinda wondering what to do in the coming holidays.....well first thing first IM GONNA GET SOME SLEEP....which should be starting now..oh yeah i did a search on my name on the internet and found out i have the same name as an american fitness model...gosh...didn't know my name could be linked with so many people.i placed the pic below for all of u....gulp...  
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well on this day,i was playing kompang for the old pengetua of my skool on her retirement.Well that day was just like a normal day except i need to wear a baju melayu.And the pengetua is retiring.Well i don't have any fond memories of the pengetua sice i'm quite new to the skool..i joined the skool just 2 months b4 i took my pmr.Now in my final year as a student of the skool.....er...dunno what to say......Anyways this is a pic at the time  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      haha im in control
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      MAn can't stand it anymore....staying up for 3 straight days studyin for the freakin test...to make things worst the tests are all freakin hard...it makes the stay ups look worthless.....Is there any slipknot fans out there...i got the newest pics with their newest masks...i don't know if it's outdated or something...but i'll just let it here for the rest to see  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       To All You Basket FAns...Here's an info on one of my favourite streetball player   Name: Tyron Evans   Age: 28  Height: 6'8  Weight: 205  Hometown: Harlem World, NY  Homecourt: 139th and Lenox in Harlem  How did you get your “big break” with AND 1? Vol. 1, although it was Skip’s tape, people were asking, “who’s that other kid?  Practice / training routines: Practice every day, Sunday to Sunday. Shoot 500 jumpers a day  Three words to describe the AND 1 Mix Tape Tour: Exciting, monumental, and success      
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Antoine "Flash" Howard (1975 - 2004)  It is our sad duty to share some news with you about a member of our AND 1 family. Antoine "Flash" Howard has passed away.  Last summer, this legendary AND 1 Mix Tape Player may have seemed to take a back seat to the rest of the AND 1 squad members but not for the reason you might have thought.  Two years ago Flash learned that he had a tumor, and began chemotherapy to treat it. After treatment, Flash's strength prevailed and he came back to join the 2003 AND 1 Mix Tape Tour. He had the strength of heart to bring all he could to the team last summer, yet he was not 100% physically well so he saw limited playing time.  Spirits were high when the tour rolled to Europe this past fall as Flash came on strong and really started to shine on the court again. In February, Flash felt weak while playing in a game and checked himself into a hospital. After finding another tumor, doctors again started aggressive chemotherapy. This time the treatment did not work as hoped and his battle ended.   Flash is survived by his mother, stepfather, younger brother, 3-year-old daughter and girlfriend. Flash was the heart and soul of the AND 1 squad as much as anyone and brought the love of the game and a love for life with him wherever he went. He will be sorely missed. Please keep Flash's family in your thoughts and prayers as we begin to move through these tough times.  To show your support, please send all cards, thoughts and well-wishes to the address below and we will forward them on to Flash's family: 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wohoo,just another week before the exams ends.I'm getting tired of all the reading and late night studying.After the exams the holidays comes in.Yeah finally my long deserved rest.Been waiting this day for a loooong time.Well the 1st week is all about catching up with all the movies and games that i missed.The 2nd week.....well haven't thought of anything yet....but one thing is for certain.....I'm goin to play basketball..Haha sounds like i haven't went out in weeks...it's true i guess...So, nothing is gonna stop meeeeeeeeee!!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Haha.finished ,my 1st ever blogggg.I don't know how did I somehow did this,but somehow I did.Thanks to iglue for giving me the idea of making my own blog.I'm on my exam week right now.So,i'll be kinda busy.Well kinda busy.I've been strugglin for almost forever in achieving at least an A for my physics.Well,i guess i'm just not cut out to get an A for that particular subject.For bio and chemistry at least i have managed to get at least an A2.But for physics.....well I guess let's forget about that for now.Wonder how the other guys are doin in their particular studies....hopefully their facing the same problem as i am..At least there must be someone...Is there??
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wohooo!!!!..for all of ur information square-enix have released the newest addition to it's line of Final Fantasy...and this time it's not a game.....being a FF fan i cannot wait for this movie to come out...here's some screen shots.....      
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nowadays there's been a ragnarok online craze going on...so for all does ro fans here's a piece of info i'll be placing in here...to be frank i'm not such a die-hard fan of ro either..just happen to play it once..well here it is  
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      fuh...finally got me 2 type again...i'ts been at least a month since i last updated my blog...i guess it's something that got to do with the long holidays and the absolute lazyness that's engulfing me lately...somehow after the sleepless nights i've encountered during the examination week,i cannot force myself to even read...chronic huh....well, now with the euro2004 going around...we can expect a couple more sleepless nights don't we......i'm czech all the way....go czech go...u can do it!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      mummy, see what i can do  yayer  -iglue
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ever hit ur mind that the match u saw live is showing one of the best goals in the whole tournament.......y don't u give a piece of ur mind by voting which goal u think is the best...my favourite goal of the tournament is the goal by michael owen....for people that's interested click this link  urlLink Euro 2004  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>