<Blog>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      so you get mad when i ask a question trying to help you? well...shouldn't i have the right to get mad when you try to get me dropped two grades? wake up, mrs landry told me that i was going on thursday, she said a list of names then went "the rest of you will go on thursday." sorry that i didn't think to bring my stuff.  what about the rest of the people who didn't bring their stuff? are they irresponsible also?  i'm so sick of you attacking me.  the way i talk, the way i ask questions.  i'll be damned if i am gonna stop asking questions.  why are you so maliciously mean to me?  do you get off on this?  don't you think i have to deal with this enough at home?  would it make you happy for me to say i keep getting slapped at my house?  does that make you feel oh so better?  i don't need to come to school and deal with people attacking me some more, especially when that person is supposed to be my friend.  i'm sorry i'm annoying, and all that other stuff, but if that bothers you so much, why don't you just leave me alone?! why do you then have to attack me? make mrs landry attack me?! i only try and help you and you humilate me.  now i've got the rest of the day to deal with everyone pissed at me because i didn't bring my stuff today to present, because of your misinterpreted view on things.  do you bring your stuff to class the day it ISN'T DUE? 'cause i sure don't, and if that is an oddity, or irresponsible, then i guess that is what i am, and if you don't like that, don't bother me, but please don't be a bitch about it and make my day even worse.  
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      http://www.epa.gov/OGWDW/
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      this is me checking out this thing  mr p blocked livejournal and restricted diaryland...so i'm kind of left with this
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So Summer has started and i realize how uneventfull it has already turned out.  The beautiful weather that normally inhabits Northern Michigan in summer is missing.  I don't think I'll be making many new friends, or even hanging out with people who i want to.  I am desperately FAR behind in latin, but haven't touched it since break.  i just want to go hang out today, i  believe i am going through human contact withdrawl.   i lack the writing skills i used to possess. i remember last summer talking to Evan all the time and effort i put forth to impress him with my linguistic skills, and at the end of a conversation i was oddly satisfied in conversing in such a manner.  look at me go right now, upgrading my typing just to sound intelligent.  I need to get out.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm a thinker not a feeler i seek to find the birth of this infection to put to words, to stastics a completely new sensation rationalize with chemical reactions what you explain with simply love scientifically undefined from this word i shrink  ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~  You, glowed Radiated a tragically wonderful life  I, cautious never made my move  This, senerio Likes to repeat itself  ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~  Its better to burn  Than to fade away Least thats what they say  YOu made my heart turn In wild rapture of your fire Who knew you were such a liar?  ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~  Pretend to smile The fake plastic look Is fashionable  Your rosey colored apathy  Sickenly sweet Candy to feed the obesity  Be glad you fit The mold The epitome of our generation
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My minutes tick by in such an insanely fast fashion that you almost had to wonder if my brain was periotically shutting itself off to cope with the inevideable tradgety that will ansue. There were only two ways this could end, and neither were pretty. i needed to face the consequences soon, if i hoped to keep my life. But instead i lay my head against the porceline and slept. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>