<Blog>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "The greatest mistake you can make in life is to be continually fearing you will make one." Elbert Hubbard (1856 - 1915)  Are you grown up when you move out of your parents house? When you go to college? When you get married? Have children of your own?  For me, I'm feeling pretty grown up knowing that my parents are coming to my house, the house I own, to stay with me and my husband for a short time. I will be making my parents food, making sure they have fresh towels to use, and generally playing hostess to two people who used to think my poop was cute. Weird. Defintely a turning point in ones life.   No matter how grown up you feel, however, there are always those thoughts, those voices of your parents still in your head. I try and try, but every once in a while I still hear them. My dad talking to me about integrity, or my mom telling me to take myself less seriously. Wisdom, yes. But annoying. Why can't they just get out of my head? Will I do the same thing to my children? What will my voice say to them when they are feeling grown up?  For now though, I'm just getting all excited, waiting for my mom and dad to come see me, bring me goodies and give me lots of hugs. I think no matter how old I get, I'll still need that from time to time. I hope my kids will too.  Older, but not too old, K
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, so after a couple happy sunny days, I'm now sick. Either sick or the worst case of allergies I have ever encountered. Probably sick, uck. I always get sick around this time of year. Should I fight it? Should I be a trooper and just keep on keepin' on and try to convince my immune system that it is being ignored? Or should I just crawl mercifully back into bed, under the wonderful covers with my trusty puppy at my side and sleep the yuckiness away?  What do you think?  ZZZZZZZZZZZZzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz  Ciao *cough* *sneeze*
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Learning to live in the present moment is part of the path of joy. - Sarah Ban Breathnach  I had a great day yesterday. One of those kind of great days that can't quite be contained in only 24 hours. One of those kind of great days that spills over into the next, just so you can soak in it like a lukewarm tub that still has bubbles.   Nothing amazing happened. No miracle occured. I didn't really go anywhere or see anything new or win the lottery. I just spent the day at home with my husband. We actually had a lot or work to do because we are finishing up a complete renovation on our house. It's been a long, hard road with lots of work, but yesterday we just cleaned and hung pictures. The simple transformation of the walls amazed us both and we sat back, a couple times during the day, just to marvel at how wonderful everything looked.   Later on in the evening, we took our dog for a walk around our new neighborhood. We've lived here for about six months now, but with our energies focused so much on the renovation, it still feels very new. It was such a simple, sweet event. One of those moments wrapped up in a day that when explained to an outsider, would seem trivial and meaningless. But when held up to the light of the next day by one involved, it was joy overflowing and contentment.  There are so many times I feel unsatisfied or antsy. Nice to know that days of contentment can come out of nowhere and blind-side you so wonderfully.  K
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Since this is my first blog, I thought it appropriate to say hello, do a little turn, and introduce myself to the planet. I am Kristin. I am 26 years old. I am a happily married woman. I have a wonderful husband and an adorable little dog. My dog's name is Ozzy. He rocks.  Ok, now that the preliminaries are out of the way... I sit here and ask myself, "Self, what do you have to say to the world?" Isn't it amazing how easy it is to get one's own little soapbox in this universe? Just click a few buttons, come up with a password, and you're in! Suddenly you have the ear of the world, or at least any part of the world that might be interested in hearing what you have to say or what you had for breakfast. (I had Frosted Mini-Wheats, if you'd like to know.) So how do we go about making sure that what we present to the world is not merely the same drivel already put forth by others? How do we assure ourselves that our thoughts are of enough import to warrant external consideration? I have no idea.  So, hoping I present a tad bit more than drivel, I submit myself humbly before you all. Good luck with me.   Signing off, K 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>