<Blog>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I had a few thoughts I wanted to write down and share with anyone who's interested so I started this blog today.  -Phil   Ephesians 5:22 and 25   Wives, be subject to your own husbands, as to the Lord...    Husbands, love your wives, just as Christ also loved the church and gave Himself up for her...    As I was driving home from work the other day, I switched on the radio in time to hear a man calling in to a talk show and asking the following question.  "I'm engaged to be married.  At what point is it reasonable for me to expect my finace to submit to me?"  The announcer kind of laughed and said "Never!"  I thought I had stumbled onto some amusing radio skit but I soon realized that this guy was serious.    At first I couldn't believe it but after listening a few minutes more, I began to realize that this man didn't understand two very important things about these verses.  Why Paul wrote them and who he wrote the verses to.  Why did Paul write these things?  Two reasons.  First, these are things we each have difficulty doing.  Let's face it men, we are terrible at showing love and most of the time we have no idea how to do it anyway.  And second, these are some of the most basic needs your mate has.  Men need to feel respected.  It's part of who we are.  If we don't feel respected by someone, then we don't want to be around them.  We don't want to deal with them and we certainly don't want to SERVE them.  Women are the same way about being loved.  Feeling loved is essential to their daily needs.  Sadly, I (and most men) don't understand this very well.  It's a good thing God wrote it down for us.  Who did Paul write these verses to?  It think it's pretty clear!  "Wives, be subject..." and "Husbands, love your..."  He was telling each of us what we needed to be reminded of.  He didn't say "Wives, be subject to your own husbands and husbands make sure that they do it."  THAT'S NOT OUR JOB!!!  Our job is to love our wives.  Their job is to submit to their husbands.  It's very simple.  And yet, we get so involved in what the other person is or isn't doing that we lose sight of our own responsibility.  What's worse is we excuse our failings by saying that THEY aren't doing THEIR job.  "I'd be more loving if she'd just show me a little respect."  That's not how it works.  You don't get to make that call.  God told you what to do.  Now do it.  I think that's one of the fundamental problems with people nowadays.  The "splinter in your eye" attitude.  We delight in pointing out other peoples problems but we scurry into the corner when the light shines our way.    The ironic thing about this, is I've just condemned myself.  I need to learn to love people better.  Even if I'm not very good at it.  I need to worry less about how others let me down and more about making sure that I'm not failing them.    I don't remember much else of what was said on that radio broadcast but I hope they got as much out of it as I did.  I can't forget it.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>