<Blog>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok so for the LA project you need to have a refrence guide and "Cite" all the sources you use. Knowing my school a bunch of people probably lost it so i decieded to type it up. Im pretty sure this is it. Well have fun......or not    urlLink  .:[Refrence Guide]:.     .:[PhAnToM]:. 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Great website for your depression needs:   urlLink Depression Era Facts Site   
    
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok so before I can make a splash\logo for the Phantom Report, I need some help on font choice. Yes its quite stupid but its very crucial, if they font looks bad or off then it just ruins the whole picture. So I have three pre-made choices. If you have any suggestions of your own then feel free to post them up. (Oh and the picture behind isn't necessarily going to be the splash\logo picture)(I included the link just in case the picture doesn't show up for some reason, or if you want to download it or whatever you might want it for)  Ok here we go:      .:[Choice 1]:.           .:[Choice 2]:.           .:[Choice 3]:.        Ya so post your oppinion and if you have any suggestions of your own feel free to post those too. Thanx :)     .:[PhAnToM]:. 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok because this topic is really hot right now and all the smart people are posting in depth looks on the Presidential Candidates, ive decided to post a new topic (so its up top :-p and so more people notice it) Maybe some of you arn't that familiar with the debate right now so hopefully you will be enlightened to the topic.    Ok so here are the posts:   "Okay... Kerry... Hum... He's the only presidential canidate to do something, but say the entire opposite. He voted to go to war with Iraq, but he "regreted" it later. He fought in Vietnam, but then decided it was wrong and allegidly threw out all of his medals (which he still has today). Kerry voted to reduce the CIA's budget, but then regreted that when 9/11 happened. You know, I could support Kerry for president, but I'd regret it later.   http://www.liberalscum.com/pics.html  Oh, and what the heck is this ABB (Anybody But Bush) thing? Are people really that despirate? And another thing, in the polls, Bush is leading in Massachusetts."  .:[Anonymous]:.    "Well Well, Kerry threw out the ribbons, he kept the metal part of the medals. So that is partially incorrect. Anyways, the only reason Kerry is viewed as a waffler is because Bush spent million of dollars on advertising him as being so. Never shall you tell me that Bush is not a waffler. Take this into account, Bush siphoned hundreds of millions of dollars (can't remember the exact #...) into secret war planning without Congress knowing. Does it interest you that Bush spends more time with Condoleezza Rice than Dick Cheney? How come the "Bush Team" doesn't even pretend to be Colin Powell's friend anymore? Did you know that George Bush Senior held ten times more meetings with his executive crew than W? How about the fact that George Bush took along Dick Cheney to testify in front of the 9/11 Commision to "save time"?  Why did the US Army in Iraq raid Chalabi's house? We all know that he was once the president's first pick to run a post-war Iraq. Bush fired his Secretary of the Treasury (Paul O'Neill) and replaced him with a brown-nosing John Snow. Little did he know that O'Neill would write a book on the isolation, egotisiticality, and ignorance of the "Bush Team" called "The Price of Loyalty". Remember when people had bumper stickers saying "No Blood for Oil" ? What about Donald Rumsfield? who dissmissed the prison abuse cases being reported as unimportant months ago? Just think about that...  ABB is pretty stupid, because the only other party other than Democrats/Republicans is the Green Party. Ralph Nader has decided again to run for president. And that just steals votes away from the Democrats, because the Green party is like, Super Democrats.   Bush may be leading now, but in the election, Kerry will come out on top because firstly, Massachusetts is a Democratic state, and Kerry comes from Boston.  Anyways, who won't have a few contradicting votes in a 20-year Senate career?]"  .:[Anonymous]:.    "1) Ribbons, medals, same thing... If your going to get picky, then you should watch Bill O'Reilly. Do you even listen to talk radio? Notice that they call it the "No-Spin Zone"... they give you just the FACTS. O'Reilly even gets guys on to oppose him, and guess what? He TROUNCES them.   2)I haven't seen one Bush commercial yet. I watch the news, CNN, and read online stories. Did it ever occur to you that the media only shows the bad things? I literally had to look up the good things going on in Iraq because I couldn't find them in the newspapers.  3)Bush was never secret about the war. Neither was CLINTON. They both warned the UN about Saddam many, many times. check out this website: http://www.liberalscum.com/pics/arial.gif  it may be a political cartoon, but at least it's correct.   4)Well duh Bush is going to spend more time with Condolezza Rice than Dick Cheney. He has to figure out what the hell he is going to do about the alleged terrorists in the United States and then just run it by Cheney. If Cheney wants to change it or has another idea, then great, set up a meeting. There isn't much for Cheney to do.   5)Colin Powell has been trying to turn the War on Terrorism into a political war, not one for the safety of Americans.   6)You just said that Dick Cheney never had meetings with the President. The fact that he was brought to the 9-11 committee shows that he was important enough and had enough knowledge to testify. Just because he didn't have so many meetings with W. doesn't mean that he wasn't well informed.  7) Yes, Chalabi was one of the President's first choice to be one of the presidents of Iraq. However, that was until Chalabi's house was raided because he was convicted in August of 2003 of embezzling millions of dollars of American money. Does that answer your question?   8)There is a snowball's chance in hell that the Green House will win, just like the Independents. Who cares? And honestly, if you think that Kerry needs the extra 50,000 votes just to beat Bush, your insane.  9)Kerry won't come out on first because people are starting to get educated about him. They are starting to learn that he's a lier and he, himself, is an ABB. Massachusetts may be a democratic state, and Kerry may have come from Boston, but Gore's home state also voted for Bush, so don't make any assumptions you would want to regret.   10)When you belong to a party, you tend to support their ideas. If you support ideas of both parties, you are an Independent. Kerry keeps changing his mind so he can oppose Bush at every turn. Great example - Kerry wanted to up the gas prices to make more of a profit. Now that everyone is furious, Kerry is changing his mind to lower the gas prices.   Anything else I can help you with?"  .:[Anonymous]:.    "Don't even mention the WMD .... check this out - http://www.liberalscum.com/leftwmd.html"  .:[Anonymous]:.    "and kerry is quoted on there too"  .:[Anonymous]:.    "WMD: Bush claimed that he had reliable sources that claim Iraq had them. Later (now) it is found out it is a single source, and fake too.  Bush: How come the Republican National Convention is held so much later than the Democrats'? They can get more money this way, and if you think that Bush needs more money, you must be brain-dead. Although it is said that he has already spent more than half of the ammassed wealth. Finally from Time itself, Bush recieved money from ten times as many CEO's than Kerry. While Kerry recieved ten times as much money from colleges and universities. Really shows what their priorities are, right?  Bush biked into a bush, that's pretty sad. Kerry brags about his snowboarding skills, and he falls many times and blames it on a secret service agent.  (So don't bring those topics in)  I would say more, except I got 2 go sleepy now. =)"  .:[Anonymous]:.    You people should stop posting as Anonymous so we can see the brilliant minds behind these arguments lol  Well Enjoy      .:[PhAnToM]:. 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok so as most of us 8th graders are reaching our graduation in almost 26ish days or somthing like that, many ideas of pranks have come up. Putting all the desks out on the field, having a huge bonfire with all out papers outside, super glueing the doors to the classrooms shut. Now if anyone has the desire to get suspended the last day of school check out this site. A bunch of kids replaced the morning annoucements with a porn tape!?!?!?!?!?!?!?! I highly discourage this act. If you like 8th grade and don't mind spending the year with the teachers again go right on ahead, in any other case......just laugh.....nothing more plz haha     urlLink  .:[School Prank We Shoudn't Pull]:.       .:[PhAnToM]:. 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       YES ITS LAME BUT FANTASIA BAREENO JUST WON AMERICAN IDOL!!!!!!!!! my parents are watching............     .:[PhAnToM]:. 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       IF u ppl want ne music, just email me @ peterliis@hotmail.com or IM me on aim @ alchemicdream, just gimmie the album name and ill get it within 2 days 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       OMFG i just went to Market Basket cuz my sis needed stuff for her science fair project... and the cashier lady 2 aisles away passed out and started twiching on the floor.... she had a seizure.. whats real freakky is that her head started bleeding and she wuz like retarded for a while... lol  
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok so Peter, your always bragging about how Chinese people are soooo smart and soooo cool and stuff. THIS PROVES HOW STUPID U GUYS REALLY ARE. Some Chinese guy SWALLOWED a knife in order to prevent him from getting arrested...........whats worse, death or being arrested??? But then again this does prove that Chinese people are the luckiest little punks ever. Read the article.....laugh at the Asians in our school :-p    urlLink  .:[Chinese Fool Article]:.       .:[PhAnToM]:. 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey this is Josh Infantine  tune into andover radio server    urlLink www.andoverradio.com    
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So, as the story goes, so dad in California didn't want his daugher saying the two words "Under God" in the Pledge of Alligence at her school because she didn't believe in God. Well, guess what this world has come too? He has taken the court case all the way to the Supreme Court. It's two words, she can choose not to say them! No big deal, right? Wrong, people have had so many arguements about this topic for the last couple of months. When the pledge was first written, it omitted those two words, but thirty years later, they reinstated them and they have been there ever sense. It's amazing what parents will do for their children just to make their lives better... http://www.liberalscum.com/cagle00.gif  
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       For the second quiz in science.  KNOW THE FOLLOWING AND BE ABLE TO CONNECT BETWEEN THEM  The 2 laws, Charles and Boyle's know pressure law!!! 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The Social Studies test is coming up tomorow for all C and D classes and just in case you don't have the Cause and Effect chart (maybe you need to study from it) here it is   .:[Cause and Effect Chart For SS]:.      .:[PhAnToM]:. 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok so new addition to the blog. We will be newly offereing hw help, study guides, needed papers that nobody's got, ext, you know the usual. Well anyways ya this should help alot of people. So......enjoy      .:[PhAnToM]:. 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok so i was reading around some news articles a little bit back and i came up apon a very strange one.   A local school in Lakeside, Ohio had a contest and the winner got to throw a pie at the princeiples face. Now the kid who won got SUSPENEDED!!!! FOR THROWING IT TOOO HARD!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!   NOT LIKE THE KID KILLED THE PRINCIPLE. I think we should all go on strike one day, and everyone in like the whole school at a certain time stop talking and plead the fith lol. that'd be wicked funny....even thou it has no relation to anything this article is about lol. if you want to check out the article the links down below   School Punishments suck      .:[PhAnToM]:. 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Okay... Bush... Hum... He's the only president that I know of that choked on a pretzel, acts like a cowboy, and fell off a bike in one term.  Or ever for that matter... 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         President Bush received minor scrapes from a bicycle accident two days before his speech. 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hello. This is Peter. 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       With only 23 days of school left the 8th teachers have planned a ton of events. Just in case you didn't get the dates here are the upcoming events.  June 3rd, 2004  Grade 8 Career Day  June 8th, 2004 AHS Orientation  June 11th, 2004 Andover Middle School Battle of the Bands  June 17th, 2004 Recognition Night for 7th and 8th Graders  June 18th, 2004  Canobie Lake Park  June 21st, 2004 Mr. & Ms. Wood Hill (8th Grade Only)  June 22nd, 2004 Aloha Dance (8th Grade Only) Basically the Semi, except its not a Semi, according to the teachers no formal dress or date needed)  June 23rd, 2004 (Last Day Of School) 8th Grade Breakfast 8th Grade Final Assembly Half Day, Dismissal at 11:00     .:[PhAnToM]:. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
                            .:[Welcome to the Phantom Report]:.                 _=[The Andover Blog Place]=_  Welcome to the Phantom Report. The Phantom Report is basically the Andover News blog. The site will include upcoming events, mentions of new sites, good music, homework help, study guides, ext, and almost anything else that is interesting. Not only will the Phantom Report act as a news site but also a community where conversations will take place and and discussions about everyday topics. Have fun. If you'd like to join out team please contact PhAnToM.     .:[PhAnToM]:.   
    
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       And I think maybe 2 people will ever read this. 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       you bought an N-Gage didnt you? y helo thar buttseckz lolololol 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Interesting......people always say "You scared me to death" or "He was scared to death", but has anyone really been put to death by being scared????? Well according to this article I found someone...or rather something has been scared to death.   A squad of police cars, in China, roared through someones neighborhood killing the lady's 435 chickens.........Chinese people............anyways She's suing the police for "scaring her chickens to death" this just makes me laugh  HAHAHAHAHAHAAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAAHAHAHAHA  Nnow i know why people call people "chickens"  Anyways here is the article, have fun laughing ur ass off   urlLink  .:[Chickens Scared to Death]:.      .:[PhAnToM]:. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       OK so i posted this before but its way too far down for anyone to care about lol. So here are the updated event lists. SCHOOL IS OUT IN....14 DAYS!!!!!!   Oh and before i forget, we all got a slip thing for the end of the year events. The price for EVERYTHING is $35 and the deadline to get it in is by MONDAY, I REPEAT MONDAY!!!!! so get you money in before your stuck with 7th graders.....  June 8th, 2004 AHS Orientation  June 16th, 2004 Andover Middle School Battle of the Bands  June 17th, 2004 Recognition Night for 7th and 8th Graders  June 18th, 2004  Canobie Lake Park   June 21st, 2004 Mr. & Ms. Wood Hill (8th Grade Only)  June 22nd, 2004 Aloha Dance (8th Grade Only) Basically the Semi, except its not a Semi, according to the teachers no formal dress or date needed)  June 23rd, 2004 (Last Day Of School) 8th Grade Breakfast 8th Grade Final Assembly Half Day, Dismissal at 11:00     .:[PhAnToM]:. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok so G8 TA is having a Social Studies quiz on the Confederate\Union States. I thought people might need this so here is the map with all the Union states, Confederate states, Border states, and Union territories. Sorry about my coloring, im not Picasso you know :-/ Well here ya go, good luck on the test.    urlLink  .:[Social Studies Confederate-Union Map]:.     .:[PhAnToM]:. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok so for grade 8 Team A, there is a Social Studies project coming up. I think its due June 16th but im not quite sure. Well anyways here are the outlines for what you need to have on your project. Good luck on the projects....or test if your taking it    urlLink  .:[Social Studies Project Outline]:.    *Note: It may load wicked slow but don't worry itll come up....i have a shitty hosting site......    .:[PhAnToM]:. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
          Hehe, i'd say he's checking "someone" out.     Look, George Bush is showing everyone that he has a perky side too! 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
          Look at those amazing leans toward Kerry. More Bush-Burning!!! 
    
    
</post>


</Blog>