<Blog>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hola peoples! ashes and i had another successful day of ditchin' raymon buahaha. I was just talkin 2 julie and she was tellin' me what eric wrote in her yearbook bout me, its pretty funny.Jack says i should prank call his house since hes never on the computer.haha. my cousin is comin up this summer i just heard. her name is Genie lynn i guess we kinda look alike is what im told but shes a year younger than me, it should be pretty interesting. Ashes and i walked 2 evergreen a bit ago and cuz of the giant bike ride it was packed and we saw some scary people...haha we took 4 of the dogs down 2 get shots today and as we pulled into the vet the slug and his mom pulled in behind us then another 7th grader (i 4got his name) came in then roseanne and another 7th grader showed up, it was like a school gathering or smthn it was pretty funny. well.... later days, rock on, peace out watever, mandy
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yoowwzzzaaa guys! so today was rather interesting... in pe i find out that raymon was plannin on talkin 2 me 2day. then as ashes and i were walkin 2 my class we saw him so we ran off 2 our classes haha. then during lunch we hid from him cuz ashes said she saw him walkin around skewl but we never saw him. Then in art me and ashes had water on our hands and flicked it and a little hit john and he made a fist and threw his arm back and hit me in my nose. so i had 2 go 2 the office and get an ice pack and my eyes were all watering cuz it hurt so bad. now its swelling and gettin shootin pains through it and my dad said i might end up w/ a black eye 2morrow. then ashes wrote tim a note and send it to his class and he came flyin through our class door and was yellin at john for hittin me, he was really upset. john didnt even get in ANY trouble, mrs. lemnah said nothin 2 him at all! then when i got home i went out 2 feed bob the pig and as soon as i step off the back porch it starts pourin then when i finish and get almost back 2 the house it stops!!! haha so 2day hasnt been the greatest....and now i gotta go 2 work so later days, mandy
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yooowwwzzzaaa dudes and dudettes!haha yesterday at work i cut myself and so i went 2 the backroom and got a band-aide and it was so kewl cuz it was clear and u couldnt tell i was wearin it till i turned my hand over and u saw the part that actually covers the wound but it was very intertaining.haha....the small things that i find interesting haha. oh i saw raymon martinez today hahahahahahahahahahaha u probably dont care bout the story so just tell me if ya do haha. me and ashes were listenin 2 music and this 1 song started playin and the words were "ill watch u smile while your sleeping" and we just busted up so now i cant listen 2 that song without laughin cuz most of ya know the smile while sleepin story haha.Ashes and i took lotz of pics of peeps at skewl 2day...some i dont know about..*ahem* trevor haha.....12 more days of school!!!!!i think....haha well i gotz 2 do my favorite pastime...homework haha. Later days, mandy
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yoooowwwzzzaaa dudes! so 2day i have been called a blonde 3 times....by different people.haha. tifa had even changed her msn name 2, if u know mandy then u know a real dumb blonde...or smthn like that...thanx 4 changin it though tifa and remember next tyme i have some blackmail info on you.haha. nobody will be able 2 call me a blonde again once they meet donne(im sorry if ur readin this donne)haha she has never been 2 my house without brakin somthing, she changes boyfriends like weekly(i know i know u and david have been goin out 2 months haha), she went up 2 her parents and told them gullible wasnt in the dictionary haha!(but she really believed it wasnt)etc etc etc i wont say anything else mean bout u donne haha...but u guys will just hafta meet her next month when shes up here haha. Oh and another thingy im thinkin bout just lettin the blonde grow outta my hair and havin it just brown again but what do u guys think?i need feedback haha. so i gotz 2 go get ready 4 work. later days! luvz, mandy 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      howdy! i just had 2 tell bout my "joyous" experience with Bob the pig tonight.haha. well....he decided to dump over his water bucket 4 or 5 times 2day so his pen was nothin but swampy mud and poop (and u cant tell which is which) haha. so i had 2 let him run around the backyard while i was sliding around, raking, shoveling, and splattering poop/mud all over me. then my lovely/kind/sweet/EVIL father comes out and takes a mess of pics....which will never be seen!!!!buawhaha. then bob started chasin the goat and chickens.....then they started chasin back so he ran in the pen w/ me to hide and got more mud/poop on me and made me slide and almost fall in the "stuff"haha. then he didnt wanna go back in so i was chasin him ALL over the yard and i look up to see that people are watchin me.haha. it was........a lot of fun...i hafta admit that as gnarly as it was at the same time it was pretty sweet. oh yeah and 2night at work the slug came in w/ his mommy and asked her to buy him a sports illustrated magazine. Then he got like all embarrassed and tryed hiding it from me.and he didnt think i heard but he was all sayin how he was gonna put the pics on his wall. then he had 2 go 2 the car 2 get some money and his mom picked up the magazine while he was out there and randomly opened 2 a page and it had this like naked woman and she was like "Look at this!!!" and he came back and she told him bout the pic and said just look at the pic ill show you and he got really embarrassed and was all "show me later!!!" it was all very funny. that story was mainly 4 ashes cuz she knows another 1 that kinda goes along w/ that one........if she remembers haha.Oh yeah the evil rooster was killed 2night by my dad.yay!!!!....it was a good rooster....(when it was still in its egg haha) j/k. well im sure this is all rather uninteresting so later dudes haha                 luvz ya'll, mandy 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      howdy peoples! this last week has been like crazy busy. friday while ashes and i were eatin lunch people started comin in the hallway at skewl from outside extremely soaked so we went outside 2 check it out and it was pouring so hard so wat do we do? we run outside and get soaked, we spun in circles and ran through the water comin off of the roof. needless 2 say we were soaked and kinda cold the rest of the day but it was great! saturday the frc bus never showed up at 8:30 but it did at 9 and i went back home at 10 til 9 so i just missed it....so i get 2 take a 2 hour test another day...yay! haha. Last night was the play. it was really good. im sure punk and Gi are glad its over.....just think u dont hafta wear the mustache anymore gi haha.oh yeah and i have blackmail pics.....bwahahaha. sorry had 2 say that haha.i gtg go 2 work....yay!haha     luvz ya'll, mandy
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Howdy peoples!!!!!!! This is my new blog.......cuz jack said i should switch 2 this 1 cuz she did 2. If ya wanna know how jack (aka serena) got her name i gave it 2 her..........but if you wanna know the story behind it ask her! Anyways (see ashes i wrote "anyways" haha) my new blog is rather spiffy dontcha think? i got the privledge of killing John last night......if u know him u will understand.....of course he killed me back.......but that is beside the point! oh and if you were wondering how i am. im just PLUMY!!!!!!!! haha. ummmmi dont kno wat else 2 say sooo bye 4 now but not 4 ever! luvz ya'll, Mandy 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey everyone i've been so busy i havent had a lot of time to write. after the lil dudes left we got 3 more lil dudes cept there were 2 older boys and they kept gettin freaked out by the raccoons and jumpin on me 2 protect them.ha! so i suggested we put in a scary movie and sit in the livingroom next to the glass door w/ the lights off. needless 2 say i scared them every chance i got muahaha. then donne came the next day and they left and it was like old times we got our speacial curly fries and milkshakes which is our routine, and she might be able 2 come back up be4 summer!!!yay! ashes donne termite and i went out on the boat and we all caught fish and went joy ridin it was fun.....cept the sunburn part.i went down to chico with her and her dad. thursday i saw arnold schwarzenneggar (sp?) and he walked up 2 us then a crowd started pushin us and my mom got chostraphobic so we had 2 leave but maya got a pic so shes gonna email it 2 me.then friday me and my mum got in a car wreck.  i remember goin down the road on the way to my great grandparents house and her cell phone rang so she answered it, i realized it was her "new" boyfriend on the phone...i dont dislike 2 many people but i dont like him at all. u hafta know some of the stories behind him i guess... anyways she was talkin on the phone and i had this sharp metal thing in my hand and i looked forward and saw this car turnin but i figured she would stop. but she didnt.i remember lookin at her and seein her face fill w/ terror w/ the realization that we were about 2 hit the other car. then she screamed and dropped the phone then we hit the car and i went forward....and thats all i remember of the accident but it keeps replayin in my head like a movie over and over like a nightmare that wont end or somthing. i was knocked out when i hit the air bag my mom said i screamed then went like dead quiet. she said i started coughin cuz of all the smoke then she was callin my name and pullin my arm and i didnt respond at all. then of course the ambulance and cops showed up etc etc. my face was completely numb all day and i have some bruises and cuts and my mom has some bruises also they said that we were sooo lucky that we didnt get hurt worse and that the metal thing i was holdin didnt stab me when the airbag came out. im sooo glad its over and i neva wanna go through it again. then during the cop questioning i found out some stuff i would rather not have heard in my whole life.   im home now though and im not goin to frc this summer no matter how mad ken is at me! yay!!! then 2night at youth was interesting we were gonna play this game where gi and i were captains and had 2 eat a banana w/ stockings over our heads....cept the stockings didnt fit very good haha. then we played basketball which was fun and now im supposed to be cleanin and walk around the house lookin for raccoons so i better go. later days, yooowwwzzzaaaa, rok on, peace out, wateva -mandy the most famousest eva
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Joe duncan is a crazy/evil person!! haha. John kept comin in the store today and joe told him 2 start calling me pepperger.....so of course he thought it was the best name ever and wont stop callin me it!!! i told him pepper was his name and i couldnt take it away and i tried everything!!!NOTHING worked. Joe also said for john 2 tell every1 else 2 call me it.....like anybody would listen but still haha. Then he was gettin really weird today he kept puttin his arms around me and leanin on me and like touchin my arm and stuff i was like eeewwwwwww icky!!!!! hahaha Then darlene came in the store 2 tell me raymond was comin in to talk 2 me later, so i hid haha, and i made it through the rest of work w/o seein him.YAY!! haha. Then me and kelsie were puttin soap in the guys bathroom and it overflowed everywhere and we were like tryin 2 stop it and it was on the walls, floor everything, it was a sticky icky mess!!! well i betta go b4 smthn else happens! haha peace out rock on later gator, wateva, mandy
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The lil dudes are finally gone.......and the thing is i kinda miss em'. They were fun to play with and tease and stuff kinda like havin siblings.but they are gone and its not like i'll neva see them again haha besides next year they will be stayin w/ us all over again while donny,chris, and eric move here! my dad and me were at work the other day and he started tellin me names of guys that were "off limits" and who werent. i was soooooo embarrassed!!!!haha. giraffe was bein horrid today he kept messin w/ my hair and then pullin me around w/ it, then he would grab me and walk around or use me as an arm rest. he even cut my wrist and made it bleed! Finals week aaagghhhh the horror!!! Donne comes up sunday!!!! i so cannot wait! as long as she stays away from liquid dish soap....ill hafta tell u guys the story behind that later. but im gonna go now so later days peace out rock on wateva, mandy
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The play was tonight it was pretty funny. giraffe was pretty good and of course so was jack. And she had an E string yay!!!! haha. i hafta get my eyes checked cuz they have kinda been hurting me lately so i might hafta wear reading glasses......so no makin fun of me haha j/k. 5 days left of skewl!!! yay!! Michael is a fruit cake!!he wrote that he had 2 tell me he loves me, said 2 call him, gave me his #, and said lets party in my yearbook. This is difficult 2 write as i am being sprayed in the face w/ silly string....ahhhh im hit.....haha oh no i hafta go save jr. from caitlyn kissin and puttin make-up on him haha. later days peace out watever,mandy
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i am sooo glad i was working yesterday because right after i went 2 work gabbi and kaitlynn went into my room and found makeup then covered there faces in it and my room.it was a disaster!!! then gabbi finds scissors.....im sure u can figure out wat happens next.....she cuts some of her hair on the left side off then says,"its okay i have lots more." then i got the joy of having my bed taken over last night by gabbi and kaitlynn gabbi punched,kicked, and used me as a pillow sooo many times during the night....it was horrid! then oilar came 2day after school to look at bob and i had 2 practice my showmanship training by walkin him around the yard w/ a cane. Thats when i notice not only are there the 3 kids but some neighbor kids from next door have come over now there are like 8 lil kids runnin around and climbn trees its like a zoo of kids!!!!!then me and ashes thought it would be safe at school today but we saw raymon and had 2 run away more today than any day so far. Then i was walkin home and i was almost here when i look behind me and see raymon and ryan walkin a little ways behind me, so i casually walk behind a truck 2 block there sight till im home, i really really hope they were just casually walkin down the street, but they never passed my house i think they turned around and went back.haha k well i gotta go 2 work and hope nothin horrid happens while im gone haha, later days, peace out, rock on wateva, mandy
     

    
</post>


</Blog>