<Blog>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well .. i think some people try to be nice because others are nice to them but deep down they just wanna die .. if everyone could be as supportive as my friends then there would be world peace and all the starving little children .. would be .. ahh         non-starving and i could sleep at night knowing theres no crime no war no hunger that cant be fixed ... but no thats not real its only fantasy... the truth is people starve to death everyday people get shot down in the street but I live my life acting like i dont care But I do... i sponsered this little girl her names Ileea  she's really cute and she writes me letters she started school this year YAY for her shes doing well..  she has 3 brothers and her mothers very sick .. but they can eat.. err sometimes  what else.... oh and im wondering why everyone acts like im this big slut... well i guess i do flirt a lot but not enough to be called a slut what does the word slut mean anyway? its just cruel ... i think everyone on icq should grow the hell up and. im just talking away not that ANYONE will read this lol...  hmm what to type .... what to type... My Sister Had her Baby :D she called it Joshua William ... he's so cute!!! she let me hold him im like aww .. then she's like bree maybe you should have one so i gave him back... i dont want no kid .. as much as i love them i dont want one   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           Your Homocidal Rampage! by  urlLink  crash_and_burn        Your name:           Weapon of Choice:    My Voice      Your Favorite Target:    Innocent Kittens      Your Kill Count:    100,000,000,000      Your Battle Cry:    "Die Kitty DIE!"      Years You Spend in Jail:    48      How Much Money In Damages You Cause:     many broken mother kittens hearts        Your Homocidal Insanity Level:: 99%                                                                                             Created with the ORIGINAL  urlLink  MemeGen  !     
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      my real mother got killed by some Italian Mafia dude... and yeh dont know much about her... only that she was really nice she died when i was 9.. not that anyone cares what happens to me :(
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Naz    : shes really funny... and umm.. a good... friend ( naz would run out in front of a truck to save a cat) lol sorry naz had ta     Amy    : umm... shes just my friend OK     Kate    : kate is the BESTEST gurl In the world I love Ya Kate!! lol      Nick    : he's funny.. and nice.. AND he likes  car " STYLE="text-decoration: none; border-bottom: medium solid green;" HREF="http://search.targetwords.com/u.search?x=5977|1||||cars|AA1VDw">car s :)     Nene    : well.. haven't known nene that long but she's really nice .. and doesn't like guys who treat girls like shit.. none of my friends do come to think about it....
     
    
</post>


</Blog>