<Blog>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I wonder what it takes to remove all the fear from my heart?  What does it take to let go entirely into the loving arms of the almighty?  What does it take to give oneself completely to the divine spark that permeates everything?  I can't answer any of these.  I only know that I must find the will, the means, and the honest reflection that should accompany the attempt at finding an answer.  Never mind what has passed before!  Nothing from the past can put a stop to the momentum that has started building already.  I am no longer stuck in a spiralling whirlpool of destruction, but I must remain constantly aware of the dangers from delusion.  I pray that today I will live fully in the moment unified in my movements with all that surrounds me, open to possibility, fully awake, and fully aware of the life I am living.  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Walking along the river this morning with less time than normal caused me to think about the quality of my steps.  How deep can one take it, each step feeling the earth pushing back springing forward with the strength and balance of musculature developed over years of practice and how much evolution?    True, mispractice has shadowed my every step at times and haunts my body still with pain, improper alignment, creaking and cracking such that I'm tempted to self diagnos arthritis.  But whether through misuse, disuse, abuse, or the effects of time itself, I realize that healing is a very real possibility, at least, something that I am commited to doing my part in to make possible.  The set of conditions necessary are not particularly clear to me except that I must be active and at the same time deeply rooted without being stationary.  Now, finally, beginning to sift out the truth through the sieve of experience I see that the remainder is nothing, yet it is everything.  Every grain of sand, every gradient of existence, everything remains as it always was and as it will be.    Placing myself into this mixing room of life and for the first time admitting that I have questions and asking appropriately while remaining open to whatever feelings come when I get the answer.  Because, I know what I want to hear, but I'm often challenged to really listen.  If I want to know the answers, or even understand the question, was it really appropriate, then I've got to listen with full attention.    Today, I will take time periodically to set aside all distractions and focus in on the one true source of our condition, the everpresent, limitless resource of the divine spirit within each of us.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sometimes a vagueness of feeling pervades when distractions invade our lives relentlessly.  They do just that no matter good, or bad, only the results of our conscious actions tell of our intentions.  If commited to living fully in every moment, turning over desire to one loving, guiding spirit-force, matter not, but not anti-matter, with attention focused, only then does action, work, and play spring from the same source.  Living this commitment is likely to deliver more joy and happiness than I could have ever imagined.  Disciplined practice, joyful daily practice, loyal commitment to the path and the source of light, all these I must ingrain throughout my being.  Truthfully, I have yet to fully release myself, but I know that soon the time will arrive and those bonds of fear and denial that I still grip so tightly at times will be loosed then finally and completely dissapated in the mercy, wisdom, and joy of the eternal light within.  I pray, from that time forth, may I take that spirit with me wherever I go, throughout all my days in this life, in these times.  
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My fear is tangible, causing me to question, looking for cracks in the foundation, formulating "what if's" endlessly, rotating incomprehensible scenarios for the sole purpose of meltdown, at least, meltdown was my usual path.  Thoughts should lead to action, or is it action that leads to thought.  I must meditate on that.  Either way, with my thinking, it's best that I act out of my true desire to seek an understanding of God, an understanding of the natural flow of spiritual forces.  I will be asking for guides and for understanding until there comes a point where I must guide and provide some help and still I will ask for guidance and for deeper atunement.  This practice must never end, because that would be turning my back on the source of joy.    If I sense nothing more, may I sense the presence my personal life-force which stems from the ultimate consciousness, the ultimate love and acceptance, and into this embrace may I forever dance and rejoice.  When the time comes, let nothing stand in my way as I pass into the next phase, as I assemble the courage to manifest divine will as handed down through ages.  May I recieve the touch of light from which I have already gained so many blessing.  Divine Mother, I thank you and hold dear the kiss of your redemption.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Everyday I must emerge from my sleep and fully awaken within myself the passion and drive that will permit me to delve deep again.  I must ask for the energy, work to build the energy, cause it to rise up in my own body from the earth and from the sky, from the universe itself.  I will learn to feel the most subtle of vibrations throughout every cell of my being.  I will learn a new life that is true freedom.  I will affirm for myself for as long as it seems appropriate, that I am a child of light, that what I seek lies within and enfolds me with all forms of existence.  Immerse me in the light, I am ready for the baptism of fire that seers only a flame in my mind to hold a fixed point and feel the energy expanding, feel the joy expanding, feel the life force expanding ever outward, circling, spiraling ribbons of light and energy.  Perhaps I've been a bit optimistic, but perhaps this is the way, the truth and the life, perhaps it does much more than balance out the inevitable entropy?  I will continue to seek truth, and god will light my way if I look for the sign.  It will not be far and the darkness will lift in waves of triumph.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There is an insatiable hunger within me that can't be fed anymore with false desires, that can't be stuffed, loaded, drowned, or filled with anything but pure essence - energy from the source of all light.  It's not a stretch to imagine the freedom from delusion, freedom from desire, but god.  Our desires are real and one must eat, but eat well, one must always deal with desire for sexual gratification, have sex with love then.  Because it is in love that all our desires can truly be fulfilled.    I can't help but feel that the daily enactment of this story, that I am a child of light seeking to unite again from that which I came, can only bring me greater freedom, joy, and energy to accomplish anything I set my mind to.  I'm taking steps inward to open my heart and mind to the infinite.  As I ask, so shall I receive and the familiar breeze of awakening gently kisses my consciousness.  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Studying the waves of my thoughts, so much of which cycle endlessly, repetition that coicincided with the abuse of my body and my body and mind have suffered.  The effects on my body are profound, but so is the body's capacity for healing.  The body, as a receptical, or a transmitter of energy, has infinite resources for transformation.  Still, physical contact must be initiated first in order for deeper inner experiences to emerge.  What is this physical contact?  I believe it is a connection to a spiritual family where one is commited and loyal.  I'm not about to turn my back on the simple beauty and joy that can be obtained this way because of some ambiguous fear!  Fearfullness be gone!    Just like a preacher, ha!, but I am no preacher, nor a teacher, but I'm not opposed to learning, in fact I thirst for learning that will take me beyond myself, infuse me in the light everywhere lest I catch glimpses of myself in that cloudless manifestation.  Infuse me in the temple of my longing, may it serve to open the heart of the universe in me, measuring nothing, over and over, hurdling the void that reassures me I am as much as you are and that together we make a force that is only reconciled in freedom, joy, happiness, and love.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Like the fool who listens then acts contrary to the truth of the words he has heard and builds his house upon sand, I too have had my foundation blown, washed, and eroded away right from underneath me.  I see this as good.  I can build again on rock.  Take action now to reinforce a solid foundation, take action that will instill an attitude of egoless service.  This will bring me joy.    I place all hope for my future endeavors in this world on the broad and accepting shoulders of the divine.  Mother, Father, Friend, our God make us ever one with thee...the wholeness I have sensed but always pulled away from, ran away from, deadened myself to...I realize now it is unescapable, one need not escape at all...but acceptance, humility, willingness to submit your own will to that of a higher calling...well, it only takes place through patient commitment to daily practice with energy focused on christ consciousness.  The eyes truly opened to the light of eternity.  Every cell awake and ready. 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In a society girded on all sides and from within by violence it should come as no surprise when reports of the most heinous acts emerge from the belly of the beast.  Yet so many act surprised that a culture of rape prevails in the military.  Well, no wonder!  "Don't ask don't tell" is the kind of policy that essentially condones violence against female and male bodies.    In such an atmosphere it becomes increasingly clear to me that in order to make any sense at all, in order to find any happiness or joy, that I must trust in the path I have begun to walk, a path that delves ever deeper inward, not in isolation, but in understanding that transcends the physical world and makes ever more apparent that the tragi-comedy of life is purely meant for our enjoyment.  The more I trust in the path, the more I yearn for light to infuse my core, growing, increasing energy, spilling over with spirit that is not self-righteous, but of service to others.  I know that for violence to end I must first understand and deal with my own violence.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I will succumb to the realization that my life will be used and that I can learn to like being infused daily with the light that is eternal and utimately is the essence of even these transmitted digits.  Circumspect, I know, but without a doubt an important moment in my transformation, or recognition of elemental worth from wich to enrich and grow a life of my making.    No longer will I sit on the sidelines threatening to take my own life while everyone sits by pretending right along with me that everything will pass and brighter days will encompass a new beginning.  But along with the fantasy comes the reality of a world that loves deception, that loves to wear blinders, that begs to believe what hurts worst only makes one stronger.    I'm begging you to believe that what is done is done and that from here on out, love, compassion, forgiveness, humility, patience, a fragrant balance of the finer attitudes in life that allow us to cooperate, compromise, validate, and agree to disagree, going seperate ways free of anger, directing violence neither outward, nor inward.  Still, getting to this point of clarity is unlikely to remain clear if I don't continue to clean the windshield of my mind.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have a choice to make everyday...do I stand tall in the light, facing my fears, courageously approaching each moment with deep reverence, or do I stray...I do stray, but now I quickly return to reverence, to mindfulness, to conscious commitment...each breath an honor and a blessing to behold...benefits of breathe outway anything material...concentration helps to intensify devotion to the divine eternal personal life energy spark...I honor that spark in all creation...come to me spirit of forgiveness and grace, come to me spirit of healing, spirit of wisdom, come to me great masters, I will always need guidance...
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I discovered something about myself the other night on the car ride home from a wonderful wedding in Kalamazoo...I'm afraid of liberation, of accepting joy, of opening my heart completely...but, everyday it is part of my prayers...let my heart be open and accepting of a spirit of joy.  My intent and my conscious will are focused on eternal light/energy/personal cosmic transformative force, ebbing and flowing, but always growing, expanding, engulfing the chasms that were created to keep myself from myself.  Bridges, built to withstand any soulquake, divine light is present in every structure, both animate and inanimate.  Diversity is nothing but different aspects of the eternal one, only meant to bring interest and humor while we're looking past into the fire of life, making a home there, pondering ancient truths with scientific techniques connected back through the ages.  I thank those who came before me, those whose lives, wills, being, were entirely focused on the everpresent eternal, their commitment has laid bare the path before me...may I approach fully aware, each day a step toward yoga.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So tragic!  Dead at 25!  That will keep me ever mindful of divine grace, grateful for the opportunity to walk in divine light, grateful for the chance to breathe deep again, seeking understanding, connection and healing in every step.  Life can be so deadening if you've never been taught how to look up into the light of the soul.  I'm learning a series of techniques and I'm applying them daily.  I'm not locked into a routine, but I routinely remind myself to allow for time to practice and I find the time.  Meditation is beginning to free me, deep devotion will eventually free me completely.  I want only to know divine will.  
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Deepening commitment to the path requires that I set aside completely my thinking and rest comfortably in the precious, voluminous, ever-refreshing, all encompasing and inspiring embrace of the infinite.  Daily doses of meditation and physical exertion are beginning to work through the years of encrusted denial and abuse.  My body is transforming and healing at the same time that I am mentally, emotionally, and spiritually healing...all words to describe the wholeness of my being.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My outer actions have rarely reflected my inner intent.  The time is now that inner intent and outer action coordinate and balance, reinforcing each other fluidly.  Though I may fail.  I now know that it is not God's will for me, ultimately my failures are stepping stones on my path to success.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just as we take a step toward freedom, some of us turn and run as fast as we can from it, and that is exactly what I have done.  As much as I want freedom, connection, love, companionship, I ran away from it all because I let fear stand in my way, I let shame stand in my way, I let regret of the past stand in my way.  But today is a new day!  I can breathe the chill morning air again, I can stretch and gain energy from each breath, from each step, from each chant.  I can lift my eyes into the light again and ask for the help that only divine energy can give.  Why would anyone turn away from that joy?  Why would I make myself work so hard to bring that joy from within to all my relationships and situations outside?  Well, that just seems to be the way.  Yes, I continue to work on simplifying and clarifying, continuing to attune myself to the ray and things will get easier, maybe even seem natural.  I don't know.  They seem natural this morning.  Everything is the same as it ever was, but everything has changed.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Some days you wake up and just know that things are going to get better, but it starts with a concerted effort.  Mine started with a bit of reading and as I opened the book The Path by J. Donald Walters the chapter I left off on started with a discussion of what failure means.  Failure is merely stepping stones on the path to success.  I found this passage deeply inspirational and was glad that I made the effort to open that book this morning.  I will take the time today to thank God for giving me gifts of inspiration and joy.  I will commit myself again to immersion in the light of the eternal.  I wll employ all the means necessary to live in the light, freeing myself with every step from the darkness that can so easily surround me.  Nothing on earth can hold me / Rise oh my sould in freedom / Nothing to fear anymore...so long as I place my trust fully in the love of God asking that all the great Masters, Saints and Sages of all the ages direct me in my course.  This I have done today and will do tomorrow and so long as I follow this path I can truly find freedom.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      October 26, 1985-2003, An 18-Year Prayer on Meditation                                                                                                Rob Curtner       Circle of Love and Light,  First Mother and First Father,  Presence of the void,  Over, around and within all that is,     Divine oneness so simple,  We sit in quiet disturbance,  Letting go of more than we hold on to.  Give us peace and vision.     Bring these truths into focus,  Keep them in our minds.  Let our thoughts and actions  Go to God.  Give us those loving eyes.     Deep within the heart of hearts,  Beyond form and time,  Beyond the beginning and the end,  The always already watches all.     In the room where nothing is everything,  Where oneness counts most,  Let our thoughts be prayers,  Bringing all into alignment.     In deepest dreaming, watching still,  Watching all we do, all we are,  Removing limits on what can be.  Free thoughts leading to freedom.  Every breath a universe, a day and a night.     Wholeness, holy place every where the same  Complete, all in one, offering peace.  Guide us to this place inside,  Sitting on the mountain still.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nobody could ever really care as much about this as me.  It's really just an outlet to remind me as often as possible that I am fallible and capable of sabatoging my best efforts.  It is an opportunity to come to terms with the mental battle I have sometimes between doing what is right and what feels good.  Ultimately, I know that what feels best is to be in the warm and loving embrace of the eternal light-force-energy that is all pervading.    It will be my daily goal to remain in conscious contact with that force, to actively seek that power, to allow it to manifest through my daily living in all the choices I make.  Everything I do should be infused with the vibration of Aum.  Though parts of my mind still tell me to resist, still tell me that I can't possibly follow the path with all my heart, I know that I must.  So, I recommit daily and ask that my steps be guided by that commitment to God, to the great masters and to all my fellow humans struggling to make sense of this illusion.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Each day reminds how deeply I must commit myself, no devote myself, my entire being to the ongoing transformation to a spirit filled existence.  I'm far from perfect.  In fact, I'm likely to make mistakes, but if I allow those mistakes to be learning experiences then I have done my part in growing into a new way of life.  If I keep making the same mistakes over and over again, then I have little to offer anyone, including myself.    My heart is continuing to open, my body continues to change with age, my mind continues to play tricks on me...but the more I focus on God, on incorporating christ-consciousness into my daily moment by moment living, then I know I am on the right path.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night I felt the crushing blow of depression, the agonizing depth of sorrow that stems from the same longing for connection to spirit and knowing that I am of this world.  I tried not to wallow in it.  I tried not to let it take me into despair.  I chanted over and over, "divine mother, my divine mother".  I prayed for the touch of kindness and forgiveness that only divine spirit can give.  I know that today I can't stay in the darkness and I ask for the light to come, I know I can't dance with depression, so I ask for joy and release in the rain soaked day.    May it become ever more clear to me just how important it is to stand up to fear, anger, denial, depression, misery, torture and to boldly say, "NO MORE!" and to mean it with all my heart, to believe that by invoking this that I have renewed my efforts at living in the light, fully in the moment, prayer in motion, poetry in hope.  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There is nothing beyond the blazing of the third eye, the fire that incorporates divine feminine and divine masculine in a unique combination that equals a perpective and a nuance of feeling complete in itself.  Not reaching out for more of one than the other, never shedding fully the clothes of imeasurable quantity, not knowing the depths of microness, nor the vastness of universalities, in each way expecting nothing and receiving everything in return: the eternal gift that circumscribes all of the components of an organic machine that eats cosmology and shits astrology.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tapping into the everlasting source of inspiration, renewal, and healing, receiving the gifts of our very essence; why have I waited so long to turn my gaze toward the light?  Still, I look away, look to the world of material gratification, lust turning to pure thanks for all life's diversity, curves and scents.  Mostly I look longer, linger where I should not, ask myself why, try to accept my feelings and the energy of my sexuality.  I take it upon myself to learn to respectfully and inwardly work through the many encounters that grasp at desire for more than the reality...there is nothing but god, there is joy in respect and service to others is the key to happiness.  My energy will forever be infused with the desire to incorporate work, worship, play with the most fulfilling presence of mind, that state of mind centered in the third eye, giving ever more awareness, awakeness, and effort towards all my actions, continuing to open myself to alignment and expansion throughout the sacred spine's chakra. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This human body so racked with desire unfulfilled, seeking to release it all into the light of eternal awakening, seeking to release all earthly want to the vast expanses of divine joy.  But my body calls me back with vision that stops and stares and takes in hungrily anything sensuous, carnal, lustful and wants to romp there, gladly soaking in the sweat of another, the scent of another, the taste.  If I linger too long, spend too much energy on the fantasy, it is entirely possible, no probable that I will eventually fall prey to the illusion, that I will seek out that which is unattainable.  Except for returning inward there would be no escape and though pleasure comes, pain follows quickly...today I've still got to convince myself that I seek the higher road, that I don't need to indulge my selfish desire, that I don't need to wallow in the excess of flesh and rush of blood.  Today I will wash my face in the shallow pools of redemption that have gathered about me in the pits of my former despair.  I will bathe luxuriously in the sweet grace of divine inspirition. 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Looking back it is clear that I was trying to maintain an unsustainable vibration, a chemical buzz that nearly crushed me with fantasy.  Not a place I want to take myself again today, not a place I want to crawl to on my knees, not a place I want to lay myself down in with all that guilt, remorse and shame.  I was trying to hold on to an enlarging gulf, an engrossing divide, widening, leaving me ever more disconnected than the day before.  Even now, the aftertaste is not something that leaves one quickly, nor is it something to cling to, but the memories remain.  I claim all of them, realizing that they can't harm me, that my destiny lies ahead of me, my memories are not barriers, only reminders of the person I was.    I'm making progress, deepening my spiritual commitments, allowing my life to be an ongoing prayer, allowing my life to bleed from the edges, infusing the layers of now with healing light, seeping in and out, breath and breathlessness circling the amphitheatre of my spine.  Bodies align slowly and I will rest in mine learning to look at myself from the inside, sensing, feeling, acting out of a calm spirit-center, engaged in the moments that surround me, filled with light eternal, expecting nothing, but forever open to the possiblities for transformation.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It is only within the intent to let divine energy propel and infuse my life that I find an outlet and a release from the glut of feelings that I would so love to indulge in.  But I've found that indulgence is violence at some level and whether directed inward, or outward will always remain unresolved.  So, indulgence is not an option, at least it never is for very long...please, indulge me for a little while, and we'll see how long the action can be tolerated.    And that is exactly the point! Tolerance and patience are so needed in every moment.  Does there ever come a time where these would not be wise?  Could there ever be enough of these in the world?  In our own lives?  Still, I become lost in desparate moments and spin the wheels of my mind on some delusion, thinking if I could just express this one more time, maybe then...but I am lost and disconnected.  Only be seeing from the inside through the spiritual center, through divine connection, feeling from the inside what vision really has to say about the outside, through the tongue, or pen.  But it must start from this place of surrender to infinite joy.  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't know where I am heading, except into the light, with fear catapulting me into new confusion and risk.  But with courage, commitment, tenacity, wit, and an everpresent desire to seek the core source of understanding and energy, I will dive deep in those moments of stillness.  I will enact a conscious engagement with the unknown, asking only to know it better, know well its healing power, its limitless love and affection; to know intimately these things is all I ask.  Today I will continue to open my heart to the reality of living in this miracle.  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I will stubbornly resist the urge to throw down the towel, to give up and walk away from the one true source of all power.  I will not lay down and be defeated.  I will take responsibility for my actions in the world and for the quality of my inner world.  I will listen, I will actively engage a loving spirit in an ongoing effort to change, heal, grow, forgive, love.  I will use my energy wisely and will remain mindful in each moment of the power of words, thoughts, media, and the necessity to turn it all over to god.    Sometimes I still wish that there was a magic pill, or potion to take me straight to nirvana, or somewhere perfectly alright all of the time, but I know that realistically I must continue to work daily at practicing right living.  For me this is prayer, meditation, devotional chanting, daily meetings.  If I maintain my commitment to these then I know that eventually everything else will follow.  I have faith that I will be shown the way on the path, that it will become clearer and more potent over time.  I have to trust in the way and the light.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was rainy, but needed.&nbsp; The tomato plants were parched, but still they are overgrown, the entire yard is.&nbsp; Still, I wait patiently for the opportunity to present itself.&nbsp; Pruning, weeding, beating the fecundity down so that I can easily walk a clear path.&nbsp;   It is the clear path that I seek.&nbsp; So I look within, because I find myself there, completely immersed in eternal, cosmic consciousness.&nbsp; I'm learning to live from within my body, my being&nbsp;instead of&nbsp;viewing/feeling&nbsp;like some&nbsp;disconnected machine that I'm outside of and incapable of controlling, always wanting to fix, agitated by its slipping.&nbsp; It is the only thing I can control to some degree...my breath, my stretch, my tension, my focus, my intention, my delusion, realizing the edges of my vista and the depth of my soul spiralling off into chaos, returning to union.   
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When I'm feeling filled with anxiety and worry, now I know, that I can't hold on to it, or pretend that it doesn't exist.  I've got to talk about it, bring it out into the light, expose it so that it doesn't hold any power over me.  In this way I come to realize that the only solution to that feeling is to still my mind, center myself in the embrace of the eternal, the light of omniscient consciousness.  If I want my life to be a walking prayer, a walking meditation, a constant comminication with the divine, then I've got to start each day with the commitment and live each moment as if it were my last.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I learned, once again, that my problems are not that bad.  I don't want to compare to others, but some people really have some huge issues to deal with.  Still, I 've got to keep in mind, on a daily basis, what is important...there is only God and his will for us is to recognize that our essence is joy...the same universally.  I'm learning to be awake and ready in mind/body/spirit and feel the wholeness of my being.  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When you're sitting and just waiting for the something to happen it's often difficult to realize that it  is  happening.  
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I want to be vulnerable, cleave my body, turn it inside out, expose everything to the light, let no dark corner go unexamined.  I don't want to hurt anymore...so I turn to the light.  Only there, nothing on earth, only there can I find the salve that heals.  But it is not cheap, or easy, or free, it costs patience, perseverence, dedication, devotion and commitment.  I'm willing to pay any price so that I return only to divine light and never to ignorance.  I trust entirely in the path that leads to light, but I am forever challenged by the veil of delusion.  May it one day be removed.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If you know that song by Public Enemy it starts something like, "picture us cooling out on the 4th of july and if you heard we were celebrating it's a worldwide lie!"  But I know now that there is cause for celebration.  Freedom is worth celebrating, freedom is worth attaining and I will celebrate today and everday because freedom can be a reality on a daily basis.  No need for anything to chain me anymore.  Nothing on earth can hold me, rise oh my soul in freedom!  Unending, unerring, promise of joy, promise of peace, promise of unlimited resources for achieving liberation of the soul.  I only have to turn toward these promises everday, I only need to accept the gifts offered to me, I only need to thank my god and all the masters for their protection and guidance and in this way I will further immerse myself in the blessings of freedom.  Thank you.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Opening my heart, lightening my load, lengthening my spine, pulling energy from the cosmos, pinpoint focus, concentration developing intensity, commitment never to falter, daily rehersal, prayer, devotion, chanting, walking, singing, dancing, swimming, biking, skating, drawing, anything that takes me out of my ego, deriving moments outside of the pain, or rather deep inside the real self that is inseperable from the divine.    Walking this morning with joy in the knowledge, walking from the center of my being, offering up prayers and thanks, aligning my body, stretching, feeling, atuning to the ray of hope that has been offered, to the promise of peace and deep purpose.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Even my mistakes I will give to God.  Everything I do is only through God.  Only through devotion will I find my way down the path toward enlightenment, toward freedom.  It is my true desire to learn to live each day in a way that honors all my commitments starting first with my commitment to walking a spiritual path.  I offer no resistance to this, but I must learn to accept the joy, love and freedom that my soul so desires, yet I still cling to my chains. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>