<Blog>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have received an answer to my prayers, and now I can be confident enough to share my testimony; the story of Christ working his miraculous wonders in me.    My “pilgrimage,” and I use that word loosely, began when 9th grade had just started.  I went to Mark Keppel High School for a week only (long story), and made my return back to the school in which I belonged, Temple City.  The very first day I came happened to be the same day where an enormous Christian meeting was being held in the morning.  A large circle of people were gathered around the flagpole, singing worship songs.  At that time, I had no idea why a crowd of people were singing to a flagpole, but soon enough, I found out.   I forget how many months later I had first asked Eric about that meeting.  We were in Orchestra, and he told me all about them, the Christian Club.  Then, he also began telling me about Christianity itself.  And so I learned the story of Jesus Christ.    Eric had kindly given me his New King James Bible and told me to read John.  Some point around that time, I had decided to attend church.  Around this period, I called myself a  "Christian" but acted nothing of the sort.  I did not know Jesus personally; he was only a mysterious "miracle-worker" in the background of my life.  So naturally, when I went to church, I felt nothing special.  It was just a room where a bunch of freaks held their hands in the air, as if to touch something that, obviously, did not exist.  Delusional psychos, I thought.     Of course, I wasn’t completely turned off by Christianity.  There was always something that lured me into the Bible and the story of the Crucifixion.  And all the while, I always felt that I was missing something; that the day I lived seemed cratered with a hole, what was it?  Why am I not content with where I am?  With  who  I am?    I wanted to go to church again.  But now, my parents, well, my mother, forbid me to go.  She said she didn’t like Christians, and that they were always so pushy, and not the sort of crowd that was good for me.  I burned with anger.  What kind of authority did she have to criticize these people?    At this time, I was still very confused.  There I was, saying she had no authority to bash on Christians, and there I was again, saying they were all psychos.  The best way I can describe how I felt and thought, is that I  wanted  to believe in Jesus, but I did not.  It was still a “fad” and the stories of the Bible weren’t true.    February, 2004, my friends, Stuart and Ben, went on a Christian retreat with Eric and John.  I had planned to go, but my mother said no at the last minute.  When they came back, I was shocked.  Stuart, the once  Kevin-your-gay-and-your-a-homo  had turned into a devout Christian.  Ben, the once  I-almost-made-it-into-wah-ching-but-my-friends-told-on-me-so-I-had-to-do-3-months-of-counseling , had also become a follower of Christ.    Stupid fools, I roared.  (To myself).  How is it possible that they had fallen into the hole of retardedness?  How is it possible they had believed all of this nonsense that is the essence of Christianity?  I did not know, I only knew that they were making big mistakes.    After some convincing from them, I decided to go back church.  Except, once again, my mother said no.  So there I was, talking to Eric about what she said, when John told me that we could all go and pray.  I was uneasy and a bit reluctant because I knew prayers never worked.  When people prayed, they gave false hope to themselves, they were euphemistically portraying the world with someone to always watch over them, but I knew for sure that life was cruel, and no manner of prayer could change that.    Or so I naively thought.    I remember the hallway being very dark, chilly was the weather, and cloudy were the skies.  We huddled around in a small circle, and started to pray.  As I heard each person go, John, Ben, Stuart, then Eric, I realized that these people weren’t my friends.  They were somehow different.  As if innocent, as if "blessed."  The words they spoke were not theirs, it couldn’t have been.  I was becoming very cold, and I could feel the wind start to brush up against my face.    As they spoke, I felt as if I wasn’t there.  As if I was floating around, just surveying the events that were taking place.  Then I felt it.  Something, as if it had life, was bearing over me.  Like I was being squeezed from all sides, I became weak.  When Eric had finished, I collapsed on the floor.  The next thing I knew, I was in the restroom with toilet paper in my hands.  I looked into the mirror and saw my reflection.  I was crying.  But I couldn’t feel the tears rolling down my cheeks. Why?  Why were the tears weightless?  My eyes weren’t red.  Why was that?  I was confused, no doubt.    When I came out, Josh told me that people had started to gather around.  The bell rang, and I was still feeling subconscious.    As I headed for my class, I couldn’t ignore it anymore.  I cried because of Christ; because He is the living Lord, because the presence of the Holy Spirit was felt.  Right then and there, I was absolutely positive that God is real.  That God really did create the Heavens and the Earth.  That God really did send His only Son to die for our sins.    Today, I am part of that "delusional psychos" crowd.  But it's different when I'm at church now.  I feel it.  I feel Jesus, and his sovereign place in the world.  I feel the King of Kings, and the Lord of Lords, just singing along with us.  I feel His glory, it's warm, it's bright, it's powerful.    Today, I am finally content with where I am.  I no longer question what's missing, for the answer is obvious.  The hole that had once been so great and massive has been reduced to nothing, filled by Christ’s love and devotion for me and the rest of humanity.  Today, that mysterious miracle worker is no longer a hidden shadow, but a living, breathing, life force that gives me the strength to carry on.    Today, I pray at least twice a day.  My friends, (Eric, Ben, Stuart, John), and I hold a prayer meeting everyday.  We give Thanks to the Heavenly Father for the magnitude of Grace beyond our imaginations.  We praise Him for his eternal Love and Sacrifice, the deeds He did for people such as us; corrupt in spirit, and lost in soul.    Today, I no longer wonder why 75% of America believes in Christ, but why Christ believes in us.  It's utterly amazing how, we, who are so guilty of sin, who have spat on God's holy name, who have commited deeds so foul, Satan rejoices; Jesus still died on that cross, so that we are no longer guilty, so that God's name remains paramount around the world, so that Satan wimpers in fear, so that the deeds so foul have been forgiven.    Today, God tells me this isn't my testimony.  That the 21 paragraphs about how I met Him are nothing compared to what will happen.  And that the real story of Christ Jesus in me, has yet to begin.  
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Copied  urlLink Eric  in creating a blog for Christ.    If you're looking at this page right now, you're about a release date to soon.  
    
</post>


<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Don't even try to guess the title.  Read the whole thing.  It'll only make sense if you leave descriptive and sincere comments of concern; then and only then will the true brilliance of the Bloody-Eulogy Symphonic Suite shed it's skin, and emerge triumphant in your minds.    Just kidding.  Three topics to choose from:       urlLink Orchestra     urlLink Corporal Patrick Tillman     urlLink Bloody Baltimore        ORCHESTRA     In my orchestra, all throughout the year, the violins always have had a special place in there.  Firstly, because of the population of violins, which out numbers cellos, violas, and bass, 3:1.  Secondly, because of it's nature; it's been known to deliver the melody line, first violins, and the sweet accompany of harmony, the second violins.  When I first started out as a violist, I was a second.  Year after year, I would always have to play the same  rest-note-rest-note pattern ; it was boring beyond belief.    But there was one year, I think 8th grade, when I tried out for first violin, and made it.  Oh how I was joyed to be released from the bondage of boredom and sheer hatred.  I actually knew how it felt to play the melody of different songs, and I never looked back as some of my friends were stuck as seconds.    For our last song this year, however, Mr. Ferntheil has decided to play The Harry Potter Symphonic Suite and The Wizard of Oz.  Wow, I thought, we're playing a piece where the audience will actually recognize our songs.    You have no idea how much I hate both of our songs.  I can't explain to you how much it's an irrelevant part in comparison to the band.  Although, there was this part in Harry Potter where we got the melody for 3 measures--and then it was back to the old useless and boring accompaniment.  I've heard the sound track, and it's nothing like this one.  Strings actually have some melody, and there's a perfect balance between both the band and orchestra; so harmonically in tune, but we're not playing that.  We're playing the "arranged" version by persons unknown.  Damn those people.      A TRIBUTE TO CORPORAL PATRICK TILLMAN     We've seen acts of bravery and courage all throughtout wars, past and present.  But America, sometimes, forgets or does not know about the underbelly line of heroes.  I am here to tell you about one extraordinary man named Patrick Tillman, Corporal.  He and his platoon were ambushed April 22, 2004.  As his troop was taking fire, the Corporal jumped out of the military combat unit, and "moved into position to supress enemy fire."  1   Supposedly, Tillman was killed by friendly fire.  There is still, however, an investigation taking place.  But whether he was killed by Iraqis, or by his own men, his efforts shall not be forgotten; at least not by me.  That's the minimum of what I, no, America, owes him.  He died fighting for freedom, and I can say that not many people do.      BLOODY BALTIMORE     We live in tough times.  Very tough times.  It's one thing when there's inhumanity being born of war, but something else when it's reincarnated in this country.  The city of Baltimore, however, has gotten accustomed to murder.  The Washingtonpost says:    "...Baltimore has one of the nation's highest violent crime and homicide rates. Three years ago, three homeless men were stomped to death on city streets by a pair of teenagers and another young man. Two years ago, seven members of one family died when their home was firebombed after they complained to police that drug dealers were in control of their east Baltimore neighborhood. And two weeks ago, twin infants were found beaten to death, allegedly by their parents, in the trash-strewn basement where they lived."   2    And there's more.  Just recently 3 children died;  Lucero Quezada, 8, Ricardo Espinoza, 9, and Alexis Espejo, 10.  It wasn't strangers that caused their demise; family members did.  Adan Espinoza Canela, 17, and Policarpio Espinoza, 22, are suspects held by authorities.  So far, there are no motives; they've only found a large knife and a club.  But get this; they found one child decapitated,  decapitated , and the two others, "bludgeoned and slashed to death."  3   There were reasons for the prisoner abuse scandal at Abu Ghraib, however weak they were.  There were reasons for U.S. soldiers to die in Iraq.  There were even reasons to kill Nick Berg.  But for innocent children of Baltimore to lay decapitated and beaten to death; there is absolutely no reason.  The murderers are without excuse.     WORK CITED      1  Rueters.  URL:  urlLink http://www.reuters.com/newsArticle.jhtml?type=...     2-3  The Washington Post.  URL:  urlLink  http://www.washingtonpost.com/wp-dyn/articles/A64...     
    
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       On Tuesday, May 25, 2004, a 17-year-old boy shot a 12-year-old boy and fled to the nearby Mark Keppel High School.  The students there were held there for hours until they were let go from the lock down.  Unfortunately, there are no signs of Anthony Castellanos, the suspected murderer. 1     I wonder how it felt to be in the midst of that kind of person.  Knowing that at any moment, Castellanos may burst through the door and start shooting.  I was only in Mark Keppel for a week, so I was lucky; but all of my friends weren't.  They were terrified, but now they're back home, safe at last.    They recalled first hearing about the shootings at Columnbine, of course they were scared also, but nobody had actually experienced the feeling.  I really hope Temple City will never have to.     1  Pasadena Star News. URL:  urlLink  http://www.pasadenastarnews.com/Stories/0,1413...  
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
          Today I came home and saw a delicious hot dog/chip/coke combo on the kitchen counter.  While I was eating it, the sudden thought of Jonh Kerry popped into my mind.  I'm not sure if it's because the hot dog had the shape of a 'dick,' and hence Kerry, or if I psychically discovered John's favorite food.  So I went upstairs and came up with this:   The year is finally coming closer for re-elections.  Now, every president does things that don't appeal to some people, and does some things that favor others, but nothing comes close to the statements, actions, and opinions of John Kerry.  I don't know to much about the delicate "card-house" of politics, but I recognize dumbasses pretty well.  Let's take a look at the evidence:    BEING LED INTO CONTRADICTION NATION        The War In Iraq-  On October 2002, Kerry stated that he is in full support for the war on Iraq.  Exactly one year later, Kerry stated that we should not have engaged in war.  He claimed Bush did everything wrong.  Why the sudden change in opinion?     Behind the Military's Back-  Here is a quote from Mens News Daily, "Kerry now claims he always supported and always fought for the soldiers. Yet when reviewing his book, The New Soldier, much of the text is found to be anti military, including charges that our service personnel committed unspeakable atrocities against the Vietnamese, including rape, torture, disfigurement and murder." 1      "The Biggest Nothing In History"-  In 1971, Kerry called for an immdediate withdrawal of the U.S. soldiers in Vietnam.  He called it, "The biggest nothing in history."  On February 26, 2004, Kerry said he did not regret supporting the war in Vietnam. 2      War Criminal-  Here's a quote that explains itself.    "There are all kinds of atrocities, and I would have to say that, yes, yes, I committed the same kind of atrocities as thousands of other soldiers have committed in that I took part in shootings in free fire zones. I conducted harassment and interdiction fire. I used 50 calibre machine guns, which we were granted and ordered to use, which were our only weapon against people. I took part in search and destroy missions, in the burning of villages. All of this is contrary to the laws of warfare, all of this is contrary to the Geneva Conventions and all of this is ordered as a matter of written established policy by the government of the United States from the top down. And I believe that the men who designed these, the men who designed the free fire zone, the men who ordered us, the men who signed off the air raid strike areas, I think these men, by the letter of the law, the same letter of the law that tried Lieutenant Calley, are war criminals."   3    John, however, is in constant hypocrisy as he relentlessly persecutes U.S. Military soldiers.       MORALLY AND INTELLECTUALLY WRONG       Questions Bush-  Kerry, apparently, questions Bush on his actions to protect the American people from the threat of terrorism and Saddam Hussien.       "The Right to Choose"-  Let's say it flatly; Kerry supports the right to kill children.  He calls it, euphemistically, "The Right to Choose."     Tried to Use Berg's Dad-  I'm not sure if the Nick Berg video is real, but Nick's family is pretty certain it is.  Even so, John F. Kerry was seen entering the Berg house; "This grave robber has met with Nick Berg's father in an apparent attempt to turn him into a campaign prop."  4       A Profane President?-  The president, of any country, should have some superior class.  That includes removing profane words from one's vocabulary; at least in public.  Kerry, however, refuses to do so, and speaks profanity in front of live reporters and video cameras.       THE IDIOTIC, SENSELESS, AND ADMITTEDLY FUNNY      Teresa-  How can the would-be president of the United States not know how to pronounce his own wife's name right, let alone handle all of America?      "...One condo commando asked the candidate where the missus [Wife] was. He used the normal American pronunciation ("Ter-EE-suh”), and so did Kerry in replying that she was up in Daytona Beach, though he warned that we’d be seeing more of her...Problem is, as ace columnist Michelle Malkin noted in the March issue of NewsMax Magazine, the Massachusetts Democrat’s highfalutin foreign-born wife calls herself 'Teh-RAY-zah.' The Eurotrash pronunciation is no doubt part of the ketchup queen’s inability to identify with all things American, even her hubby."   5        Not a Very Nice Man-  John Kerry called his secret service agent a "son-of-a-bitch" when the agent accidently went in front of John, causing Kerry to fall over.  Afterwards he said to a reporter, "I don't fall down, the 'son of a b*itch' knocked me over."    A Lying Irish-  John Kerry said before that he wasn't Irish, and he always corrects people when they say he has an Irish ancestry.  The Globe, however, has reported many instances where his staff openly acknowledges that he is in fact, Irish.  Only after the public knew about it, did Kerry change his opinion.  It's not a big deal about his ancestry, but to lie about such a small thing?         HARD TO BE WITH       Officers Told Kerry To Leave Vietnam- Thomas Wright, once a soldier in the same platoon as Kerry, told reporters that the would be Democratic president had bad behavior problems, and thus at Wright's request, was assigned to another platoon.    "I had a lot of trouble getting him to follow orders," Wright recalled. "He had a different view of leadership and operations. Those of us with direct experience working with Kerry found him difficult and oriented toward his personal, rather than unit goals and objectives."    And if that weren't enough, only some time later, "Wright referred to the three Purple Hearts awarded to Kerry, which allowed him to leave Vietnam for the U.S."  6       WHY IS KERRY EVEN RUNNING?        It's one thing when the American public doesn't vote for Kerry, but the democrats also?  Yes it's true, a group called the "Democrats for Bush" support the current president instead of Democrat Kerry.  What does this bring into question about Kerry's choice of actions?  With the supporting evidence above even more questions rise.  For instance, WHY IS KERRY EVEN RUNNING?    So anyways, that was fun.  Let's hope someone brave enough to withstand America's scrutiny will rise and challenge Mr. Bush, not that he's a bad president, but just to redeem the presidential election honor; after a man like this, we're gonna need a darn good runner-up.     WORK CITED      1  Mens News Daily. URL:_________.    2  North Texas Indy Media Center. URL: urlLink http://www.ntimc.org/newswire.php?story_id=530&media_type=IMAGE     3  John Kerry, on NBC's "Meet the Press" April 18, 1971.  URL:  urlLink http://outdoorsbest.zeroforum.com/zerothread?id=201012&postid=2315600     4  Free Republic.  URL:  urlLink http://www.freerepublic.com/focus/f-news/1135006/posts      5  News Max.  URL:__________.    6  World Net Daily.  URL:  urlLink http://www.worldnetdaily.com/news/article.asp?ARTICLE_ID=38483        
    
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       When I first heard about Nick Berg, the 26 year old American who had his head cut off in Iraq, my heart nearly dropped.  I became even more horrified when I heard how he was decapitated; a thick knife through the right side of his neck, and then the left in the midst of his screaming.    What really got me, though, was a picture of Nick's dad and brother on the front lawn, crying.    But when I was finding more stuff about Nick, I found tons of articles stating his decapitation is a fraud.  Here's what I've found so far:    MILITARY BEHIND THIS?   There are alot of suspicious dates that have been lied by the U.S. Military.  Many sources say that the "Beheading of Nick Berg" is nothing more than an attempt to swerve attention away from the naked photos of Iraqis.       Descrepancies- Here is a quote:   "Berg's last known whereabouts was in U.S. custody. On April 1, Beth A. Payne, the U.S. consular officer in Iraq, sent an e-mail to the family of Nick Berg. It stated that Ms. Payne had located Nick, and he was currently in custody of the US military. She wrote, "I have confirmed that your son, Nick, is being detained by the U.S. military in Mosul. He is safe. He was picked up approximately one week ago. We will try to obtain additional information regarding his detention and a contact person you can communicate with directly. This is distinct from the next point... The US military has stated that Berg was never in US custody and that he had been in custody of the Iraqi police. The Iraqi police adamantly deny he was ever in their custody. (See again: The Unanswered Questions of Nick Berg's Murder.) If this is so, we have to conclude that either the email from Ms. Payne was incorrect or that the US military has been lying." -Break For News      Similiar- There are alot of pictures that have dragged attention to a white chair; both in the photo of Nick Berg in the hands of the "terrorists," and in the photo of the U.S. Military prison, Abu Ghraib.  In both photos, the wall colors are of the same hue.  And, in the video, you see a glimpse of a military hat and sweater.    Here is the article: http://aztlan.net/berg_abu_ghraib_video.htm.         THE VIDEO      Dates- The military reported they found Nick's body Monday, May 10th.  But the video itself is dated May 11th.       Dubbed- Screaming starts while Berg is not moving and before he is touched.  Here is a quote:   "Whatever the mismatch in the speaker and video, videotape cognoscenti have said the scream was amateurishly dubbed into the tape. The writer of this K5 article reviewed this issue closely: The screaming starts (at 4:31 - on the copy I viewed, not the time stamp) about 5 to 6 seconds before Berg is touched (at 4:36) and he is moved to his side. He is just sitting there like a lump. While the screaming commences for (1 - 2 - 3 - 4 - 5 seconds), his head doesn't move and his mouth doesn't appear to move (though the tape is blurry), nor does he seem to be physically screaming at any time. Yet the audio plays a loud vigorous screaming. The exact same dubbed screaming continues after the long time jump and a bit of a time gap with silence and after some cutting on the head, during which Berg is not moving. This screaming seems clearly dubbed and is highly incongruous with Berg's lack of activity." -Break For News      Time Stamp- There is a big jump in the time stamp that goes from 2:44:40 to about 13:45:47.  The first time is when Nick is reading his statement, and the second one is when his head was held up.     The Time Itself- The time itself is in Military time, and not Arabic.     Different Men- The man who was doing the cutting, the one in all black, was not the same man who held up the head.  In the video, however, it shows the man who was doing the cutting to be the same man who picked up the head.  Obviously there is some descrepancies here.     Sneakers?- This one is more funny than credible.  There's one guy in the video wearing white tennis sneakers; and these are supposedly terrorists?     OTHER EVIDENCE   There's to much to type, so here's another quote:   "Berg shown in video wearing orange jumpsuit known to be of U.S. issue. The orange jump suit "appears" to be identical to the jumpsuits used at Guantanamo. (Compare with pictures at Guantanamo.) The orange jumpsuit was standard US military issue to men in custody. It is unlikely Berg would continue wearing a U.S. custodial uniform if he had been released by the military as they claim. The fact he was still wearing the suit is both anomalous and suggestive. One wonders: Was there an immediate transfer of Berg from the US military to unknown persons, preventing Berg from discarding his US prison garb?   When Berg is decapitated, there was almost no blood. If Berg were still alive at this point, with the cut starting at front of throat, blood would have been spraying everywhere. Berg's severed head, the floor, Berg's clothes, and even the hand of the 'Arab' who decapitated Berg had no visible blood on it. When the executioner holds up Berg's head immediately following what is represented as an actual decapitation of a living person, there is no significant blood flow from the neck or blood splatters showing anywhere on the executioner.   Berg seems limp just before the beheading. It is not clear if he was moving after the time skip in the tape. While on the ground, Berg's body didn't seem move except in response to the captors movements. Although held down, Berg would have tried to instinctively wiggle and writhe away from captor's grip and use of a knife. (That is unless he was long dead after the cut in the tape.) A surgeon would very likely testify that the beheading did not cause the death.   The lack of spurting blood and lack of movement suggests Berg was already dead at the time of the alleged decapitation. During the beheading, Berg's eyes are not seen. Camera angle made it impossible to see if Berg's eyes were open or glassy. Berg very probably was killed before the staged beheading. Did the captors have no stomach for the beheading of a living person?"    CONCLUSION    To tell you the truth, I'm just as confused as anyone else is.  I really have no idea whether to believe Nick Berg was beheaded by the al-Qaida group, or the U.S. Military.  Maybe it's just my longing believe that there can't be people with absolutely no moral values at all.    I really hope this is all a fraud.  Not so I can bad mouth the Military, but so Nick Berg can come home.  But I think that's already to late, since we already have found his body.  But then the question remains, because he's already dead, who did it?  I think we owe it to Nick and the rest of the world, to find out for sure.    NOTE: You can now comment, even though you're not a user.     Articles To Read:     urlLink http://aztlan.net/berg_abu_ghraib_video.htm     urlLink http://www.rense.com/general52/anom.htm     urlLink http://www.kuro5hin.org/story/2004/5/15/22827/0477     urlLink http://marc.perkel.com/archives/000233.html      
    
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       After  urlLink Eric's  post on the new Blogger look and fresh templates, I just had to try it out.  I was amazed at how much work had been put into Blogger's redesign.  Even more amazed to see the new templates in store.    I don't know why I signed up for an account in the midst of my already active (well not active per se) synik account.  Maybe it's just the nice templates that have drawn me here; I really have no idea.  What even puzzles me more is my relunctancy to get my own domain.  I think I'm just lazy.  And that would probably explain my absence from blogging or web designing.    Well let's see, it's been around 4 months (I made that number up) since I last updated, and alot--I mean ALOT--has happened.    Let's start at the beginning of the school year.  The TCHS School District found out I lived 8 feet (I made up at number too) too far away from the TC School area, and thus I was forced to attend a school near my father's place: Mark Keppel.    There, I was influenced by alot of people in almost every aspect of my life.  Marijuana was commonly seen at lunch, cigarettes were usually smoked behind shadows, and I can guarantee you almost 80% of the school's students are--or were--involved in gang related activities.  Every single day during lunch there would be the "Oooooo" from everyone who had just witnessed something like a loud sneeze.  Then one person would say just let the sneeze go.  And then there would be a fight.    However, in spite of all the idiocy, I made some close friends.  My lawyer said I had a strong case in getting back to TC because of my orchestra background; but now that I had adjusted to my new friends and my new life style, I just didn't see the need to go back.  But there was that conviction, that ecstasy, that compassion from my lawyer that changed my mind.     I went to court, told the 12 judges my story, they cried (just kidding), and unanimously voted me back to TC.  The first day I got back was a wednesday; and it was there that I saw a mass Christian meeting taking place near the flag pole.    A month later, my friend Eric told me about Christ.  I becamer a follower from then on.  And it was strange how my perception of Christianity changed when I really dug deep and found the truth.  It's so different and unique in comparison to other religions.  In no other religion, does a God come onto earth and make Himself nothing; and then die just for our salvation.  In no other religion do the Scriptures--the foundation of the religion itself--come backed with historical evidence beyond belief.  In no other religion do prophecies be made and fulfilled.  In no other religion have I changed my complete assumption of life and so on, and in no other religion have I felt so loved.    So here I am, 5 weeks before freshman year ends.  But I know this is only the beginning of a lifetime I still have to finish, so see you around.    
    
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       You all know, by now at least, the title is completely irrelevant to the entry.  But now that I have your attention...well you know the drill.       urlLink Free! or Am I?     urlLink Electric Guitar     urlLink The Terminal     urlLink Many More Days To Come        FREE AT LAST, OR AM I?    I still remember the first day I stepped onto TCHS grounds, and that's alot since I can only vaguely remember what I did this morning.  So, I conclude, this year has only passed in the time span of less than 4 hours.  Just kidding.  But anyway, the last day of school sort of just crept by; I didn't even know, until Thursday night, we had no school the next day.  I think it was because of the finals, but luckily that's all over and we have the rest of summer to kick back and enjoy.    Well, for some people at least.  If you're like me, you have summer school.  I think the word  summer  is great, I think the word  school  is alright, but when those words unite, who would have ever thought it would be so horrible?  I mean, you add 3 and 4 (two very good numbers; and they're good only because if they weren't, my analogy wouldn't make sense), and you get 7 (a fabulous number by the way).  You don't get 1 (which is a horrible number, and again it's horrible because then my analogy works).  So, obviously then...summer school must be defying the laws of numbers!  Yes, I realize there are no "laws of numbers" that make one number better than another.  But whether the laws exist or not, summer school is still illegal, and hax0rs always get logged out.      ELECTRIC GUITAR     I was looking at some guitars the other day and came across this  urlLink one .  The price is only $109.99, 110, so I figure if I get $10 bucks a week, for allowance that is, I'll have to save for 11 weeks, or 3 months.  Not bad, not bad at all.    Then my dad came along.  Now, he's usually a tough one 'cause no matter what I say, he  thinks all I need in life is nothing but the bare necessities.  Which is true, but it's not like I'm hitching a free ride here; if I want something from that guy, I gotta work my ass off.    "Hey, dad, can I show you something?"  "What?  Your report card?"    Oh great, that's just great.  Now he's expecting something good on my report card, and I have to let him down with the idea of an electric guitar.    "No, no, that's not coming until later.  But take a look at this."    I showed him the giant image of the guitar.   "Wow, that looks good."   "Yeah, it looks really good.  It comes with an amp, the guitar itself, 3 picks, a cable, the case, and a chord book.  A guitar, alone, already costs, at minimal, $115.  This package has everything you need already for only $110.  So I was thinking, if I save for about 11 weeks, I could get it.  But it  is  the summer, and I'd really like it if I could play a little before school starts.  So you think you could give me an advance?"    "You already have one," he said.  And those words almost made me lose hope.    "Yeah, I know.  But there's two types of guitars.  And acoustic, and an electric.  They both sound different, and this offer is just too good."    "Well, fine.  Only, though, if you do my laundry, the dishes, iron my clothes, and vacuum the house every week, for let's say...a year.  And when you get your first job, you're paying me back $110."    "What?  I thought you were giving me an advance, why do I have to pay you back?"    "The $110 is not for the guitar, it's the extra fees I'm charging you for an advance."    "You're turning into a corrupted bank."    "Don't make me change my mind."   "Yes, sir."    Wow, I can't believe I am that lucky.  A little work here and there, but in the long run, it'll all pay off.  How will it pay off you ask?    ......  Yeah, anyways, it's going to pay off, whether I can answer you right now or not.      THE TERMINAL (THE MOVIE)    I'm going to pretend today is sunday.  So "today" I went to church at about 9:30.  Worship songs, yadayadayada, hypocrisy speech, blah blah blah, bible study, erghhhtheyuaa, and then a gourmet lunch at the built in restuarant.  (Chicken and rice at the cafeteria.)    Afterwards, me and some people,  urlLink John ,  urlLink Stuart , and  urlLink Ben  (who I believe now owes me 7 bucks), went to the movie theaters on Atlantic, 'cause Temple City didn't have  The Terminal , and we waited for an hour until the movie started.  And if you haven't caught on, the movie was  The Terminal .    It was, just flat out, a good movie.  Creative; a nice fresh breeze of change from the  man has this much alotted time to save the world and catch some chicks on the way  movie.  Honestly, who could have ever thought of a movie about a guy stuck at an airport terminal?  And to make it good too!?  Geniuses I tell you.  I highly recommend it.      MANY MORE DAYS TO COME...    Have a good summer everybody.  Unless you have summer school, then I guess...well, don't have a good summer.  Unless you like summer school, then, by all means, have a horrible summer.    And remember, buy candy from Ben and Stuart; they're raising money for BS.....S.  On the market, each item costs $1.  Mention my name, and they'll give it to you for half price.  If at first, they say no, be persistent; it's a code I worked out with them.  You have to at least ask 3 times.    Okay, bye now.  Oh yeah, and if you see me running and if they're close behind, you have to jump in and stop them.  It's another code, and they'll give you free candy bars.   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The title has absolutely nothing to do with what I'm going to talk about.  It was merely to get your attention.  Now that I have it, you can do nothing but read the whole thing and leave a comment.     urlLink Study     urlLink Cannibals     urlLink Deodorant     urlLink Questions     urlLink Assignments        STUDY    I did nothing but study this weekend.  Well, I'm not  going  to do anything but study this weekend; it's only sunday and saturday counts as a weekday because I say so.    1.) Work on Pathways Final.  An email interview with Professor Don Thorsen of Theology from APU.  Should be very interesting.  I have to write a report and do an oral speech.    2.) Make an English Portfolio.  Benchmarks, essays, and stuff go inside the folder.  I also have to write a "Dear Reader" letter.  Gee, like people can't read essays without proper instructions from the author.    3.) Study for Spanish.    4.) Study for Math.  5.) Study for P.E.    Wait, what?      CANNIBALS    I watched Hannibal on USA yesterday.  Spoookkyy.  Anyway, I wonder: Could any one we know be a cannibal?  Are you born a cannibal?  After thinking awhile about the movie, I came to the conclusion that all cannibals are evil psychos who get off watching people scream in pain.  But, then, I thought about the 3rd world countries who have ancient tribes or whatnot that practice cannabilism.  And it occured to me that the Greeks and Romans practiced cannabilism too; and they certainly are not evil psychos who get off watching people scream in pain.    On the contrary, they were quite civilized; we actually owe alot to the Greeks.  They gave us theater, philosophy, politics, democracy, and so on.  So my conclusion now is that canniblism is instinct; rather than a murderer's desire, it's a cannibal's need.  They know no other way to survive, so obviously they eat people.  Still a scary thought though.      DEODORANT    On a lighter note, I had a dream I married deodorant.  Old Spice Pure Spirit to be exact.  I think it was because  urlLink Andrew  and I were discussing the origins of deodorant for like 5 hours.  And how it actually came 20,000 light years away from the sun on a planet called Eath.  Not Earth, Eath.  Interesting, yes?      STUDY QUESTIONS    1.) Why do you think saturday is actually a weekday, and not a weekend?  Keep in mind that I am right, and the calendar of the whole world is wrong.    2.) Are you a cannibal?    3.) The Greeks invented democracy.  Who invented the toilet?    4.) Where does deodorant come from?      ASSIGNMENTS    1.) Write a full thesis on why toilets keep the Earth and Eath in order from total civilization chaos.    2.) Form an outline on the full thesis.    3.) Write an essay based on the outline.    4.) Due Monday.     A NOTE   I wonder why I'm demanding homework from what I write in my blog now.  I swear, the finals are getting to me.  Good luck guys.  And remember summer is just over the scantrons.  Oh great, summer school starts the week after.  One of these days I'm going to die, and they'll ban finals.  I'll be a hero.   
    
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I wonder why we're all in the timeline of great tragedy and sorrow.  I can hope that in future wars, death casualities will never match to D-Day.  I can always hope that the people who haven't died yet, would come back from the war, alive.  And I can always hope that future leaders of such compassion for America, will remain well.  But then the heroes would be forgotten; forgotten in the midst of hope for future persons, and not remembered as the past heads further and further away.         urlLink 60th Anniversary of D-Day     urlLink Another 5 Die     urlLink Remember Reagan        60TH ANNIVERSARY OF D-DAY    Today is the 60th anniversay of D-Day.  On June 6, 1944, Operation Overlord commenced with a landing of over 5,000 ships, 11,000 airplanes, and 150,000 service men. 1   After suffering hell on the beaches, more than 4,000 Allied Forces were dead.  But after the shock had hit the troops of the blood massacre and death, "Fortress Europe had been breached."  2     Operation Overlord was a mission against Nazi Germany.  It was a mission for freedom against Adolf Hitler.  Against a tyrant who loved his people, and put his morals on the line for them.    Adolf Hitler killed off more than 1,000,000 million Jews.  America saw that as wrong, and the soldiers acted upon it.  They fought not only for America, but for people half way around the world.  There's something extraordinary about these men, and I can't quite put my finger on it, but the word comes close to 'miracle.'    ANOTHER 5 DIE    Five U.S. soldiers were killed  when their vehicle was attacked near Sadr City. 3   I don't know why the news sources, including the LA Times, didn't show the names of the people who died.  It's the least they could do, seriously.    The total death toll is about over 600, with the death of the five soldiers. 4   Why?  Why did they put their lives at risk?  Why?  I can't imagine the amount of bravery, patriotism, and self-neglect even if you told me.        REMEMBER REAGAN     Our 40th president, one that has attracted great amounts of popularity, has died.  June 5, 2004 is his passing date, and shall his memory never be forgotten.   It was Alzheimer's that took his life.  It first starts off with memory loss.  Then it gets worse by progressing to a more higher stage of memory loss; forgetting common words and phrases, and objects, and names.  Then, the concentration of the person is affected.  It becomes increasingly difficult to pay attention.  All the while, the memory keeps getting worse until he or she has lost the ability to respond with the environment.   5     That is what happened to Mr. Reagan.  By the time he died, he didn't know of his immense contributions towards pushing America to where it is now.  He is credited with ending the Cold War, which stopped communism from spreading.  And:    "In 1986 Reagan obtained an overhaul of the income tax code, which eliminated many deductions and exempted millions of people with low incomes. At the end of his administration, the Nation was enjoying its longest recorded period of peacetime prosperity without recession or depression."   6     There were alot of other things he did.  But that is sort of out of place here.  I think the main point is to remember him, period.  He is one of the few presidents I admire most.  His speeches were not of this world; there was an audio recording on KFI the other day, and it was absolutely amazing.  Here is an excerpt from Ronald Reagan's speech on commemorating D-Day:    "Forty summers have passed since the battle that you fought here. You were young the day you took these cliffs; some of you were hardly more than boys, with the deepest joys of life before you. Yet, you risked everything here. Why? Why did you do it? What impelled you to put aside the instinct for self-preservation and risk your lives to take these cliffs? What inspired all the men of the armies that met here? We look at you, and somehow we know the answer. It was faith and belief. It was loyalty and love."   I will always remember yesterday, as the day America lost a little bit of it's soul; the soul Reagan worked so hard to make truly great for us.         WORK CITED      1-2  D-Day Memorial Foundation.  URL:   urlLink http://www.dday.org/html/d-day_history.html      3   King, Laura.  "Premier of Iraq Calls for End to Insurgency."   Los Angeles Times , 5 June, 2004, p. 1.      4   Newsday.  URL:   urlLink http://www.newsday.com/news/nationworld/world/ny-woiraq053834682...     5  Alzheimer's Association.  URL:  urlLink http://www.alz.org/AboutAD/Stages.asp     6  Whitehouse.gov.  URL:   urlLink http://www.whitehouse.gov/history/p...     
    
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I hate jokes.    Well, at least the ones that are brain stumpers.  For example, me and  urlLink Ben  were talking after the orchestra concert--which was a disaster by the way--and he asked me how to spell 'spot.'   Me:  S-P-O-T, Ben...   Ben:  Okay, what do you do when you see a green light?  This was it I thought, the point in time where I was going to show him I'm no idiot.  I mean, what kind of question is that?     Me:  I stop.    I looked at him with a triumphant gaze, but all he could do was give me one of those "you're a stupid moron" looks.  And then I realized what he meant.  SINCE WHEN DO I STOP AT A GREEN LIGHT?    I hate jokes.     
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Here are some pictures from a couple of weeks ago.&nbsp; We were at John's house, apparently doing nothing but acting stupid:&nbsp;  &nbsp;    &nbsp;   I don't know what Stuart was doing here; I think he had a high fever with an acute case of idiot, and thus the forehead contact and retard-expression.&nbsp;      &nbsp;   I, being the normal person that I am, was playing an F chord on the guitar. Ben, on the other hand, was pretending to kill space zombies through his "virtual-reality module," which was actually a pair of ear muffs.      &nbsp;   Do I even need to explain this one?&nbsp; Lovely, isn't it...? &nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;  And, just to prove that I really have fried my brain cells:&nbsp;       This is Stuart without his medication.&nbsp;   That's enough mayhem for today.&nbsp; Now, if you'll excuse me, I must go study for the test I'm going to inevitably fail.&nbsp; So long.&nbsp;     
    
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Either I'm terribly troubled by some unknown force, or I'm just crazy.  I'm going to put my friend,  urlLink Andrew , on the spot light while I tell my sad, sad tale.  Or is it his sad tale?     I was situated at the corner of Temple City and Lemon, strutting south toward the little green man without a face.   urlLink John  was with me, and we'd just come from summer school.    "KEVIN HUYNH!"    I looked to my right and saw Andrew's head peeking out of his car, smiling.  He always does that, I thought.  I grinned widely for no apparent reason.  Then my heart nearly skipped a beat, or maybe it did, how can you tell?: A larger than normal sized truck came skidding past, which sprayed water from the puddle that was not there, made from the rain that didn't exist.    When the truck finally past by, the only thing on the road was Andrew's head.  It was rolling on the floor with that same happy expression, it was still smiling.  It would  have been less horrible without the crimson red blood dripping from his "decapitated" head, unfortunately, the blood was there, and at the next moment I was at his furneral.      Strange, the casket was open, and Andrew's body was in a suit.  He was wearing a silky black jacket with a nice white dress shirt.  His head was still missing, and even more strange, his neck was bare; no bandages.     (The picture above was taken from Eric's  urlLink blog .  He doesn't know yet, so don't tell him!)   I arrived home and headed for my room.  When I opened the door, I recieved the shock of my subconscious life.  There, right on my bed, lay a fish bowl with Andrew's head in it.    Still f-ing smiling.     In an attempt to save my dignity, I will say that anything Andrew does ends up, in one way or another, making me laugh.  So it's no surprise that when I woke up from the dream, I was not screaming in horror, but laughing hysterically.    But you must think, Why, Kevin is a mad man!    Indeed, I am.  Maybe even, a morbid mad man.  Is that an alliteration?  Kevin, the alliterating morbid mad man.    Okay, anyway, that's enough fame for Andrew.  Don't want to spoil his mind; the whole world will know his name.  He's far better off away from those things.  There, there, Ben, after all, it's not really good bye.  He'll be at Hogwarts soon enough.  Good bye, Harry Potter--the boy who lived!   
    
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Today is actually the 7th.  But I put the entry date back to the forth because I hate you.    It was not the usual alarm clock that woke me.  Why the beep-beep-beep didn't go off at 7 o' clock sharp, I still am not sure.  Perhaps it has formed a mind of it's own; a cynical one at that.  But its "efforts" (if a hypothetical alarm clock-mind has  efforts  at all) were in vain.    For I was awakened by pigeons.    In my room, I have two windows; one big, and one very small one.  The more larger of the two is facing south and my bed is located directly beneath it.  Now, Saturday night turned out to be quite hot, so the AC was running.  But at about 1pm, my dad turned it off and said it was because he wanted to save electricity.  Like America is in need of power saving anyway.  So I opened my window and let the cool breeze in.    "Coo-Coo-Cooooo," was the first thing I heard Sunday morning.  But you know when you're half asleep and you don't really know what's going on?  Yeah, that was me.  I invented that feeling.  So I went back to sleep because my alarm hadn't gone off, naturally I thought it was still before 7.    It's funny how friendly little pigeons can suddenly turn you into a rampaging psycho.  They could've stopped making that noise.  They could've flew away from my window ledge.  They could've  fell  off my window ledge.  But no, they relentlessly pushed on.  And on.  And on.     Screw it, I thought.  Getting up earlier wouldn't harm anyone.  It couldn't be to far away from 7 o' clock anyway.     I checked my clock, and it read 9:15 am.  The numbers seemed more lively today; like they were taunting me.  Laughing at my folly, laughing because I wasn't going to make it.  And it was then, I felt a sense of determination and conviction; I  was  going to make it.    Wierd, it was just church.    I managed to get there in time for Sunday services.  We sang a couple of songs, and heard some prayers; particularily David Chui's ( urlLink John's  older brother).  He talked about other countries and let his heart pour out.  It made alot of people weep.  But don't get the idea that I cried.  Shut up.    After that, we had bible study (Book of John) then lunch, you know, the usual deal.  Then my dad took me to Barnes and Noble because he wanted to get this book,   urlLink Guns, Germs, and Steel , which is something his co-workers have been raving about.  He ended up also purchasing Bill Clinton's  urlLink My Life .  I doubt he's ever going to read it, though.  And lastly, he talked to me about my doing nothing productive except playing guitar and sleeping.  So, he got Michael Behe's  urlLink Darwin's Black Box  for me (a yucky science book, the biochemical challenge to evolution to be exact).    Okay, moving on.  I came home to sleep and get ready for fireworks later.  I ended playing PS2's True Crime.  At 4pm I went to Stuart's house and waited for people to come over.  Let me tell you, the worst decision you can make in your life is to enter Stuart's room...with him in there (that is, without a safety buddy to call 911).    Ben wasn't coming for another hour, so I had no choice.  We started playing a little guitar here and there, then he got bored.  So I moved to his desk chair, and let him sleep on his bed.  After awhile my stomach roared with hunger; maybe because I digest faster while being held captive.  I told him I was hungry and that we should go to Carl's to get a bite to eat.  He said, "Okay, give me a hand up."  I willingly obeyed.  I pulled him up on his back and started to pack my guitar.    Then he fell back down.    At least six times I had to prop him up.  On the last time I stayed behind him to hold him there.  Dammit, he's freaking heavy.  I gave up and retreated back to the much safer chair.    I never thought he would start to throw things at me.  But I'm naïve, so my thoughts don't count.  First line of fire was his guitar case.  It wounded my eye, and one of my contacts fell out.  Suck it up, Kevin.  I took shelter behind a book shelf and returned fire.    I was hurt, but I wasn't down.  Years of training had prepared me for this and through out the battle I kept in mind what my commander once told me: "Always expect the unexpected from Stuart."  I let my guard down in the beginning; I wasn't going to make the same mistake twice.    Then my stupidity caught up to me.  I was right under the damned door knob!  I manuevered my way out of the door and left the battle grounds for good.  I was on his territory, he had an advantage; leaving was the only wise thing I could do.    Then his mom made fried rice for the both of us and we sat outside to eat.  The mindless chatter of the TV was on, and it set the mood of  good karma .  But this time, my guard was up, I was thinking clearly.  Somehow, I knew he was plotting against me.  Even as I was chewing down on the rice, I knew.    Rice, as it had been known to do, has a way of stealing your thoughts and transferring them to some other bowl of rice.  For today, it was my intelligence officer.  I don't think Stuart knew how to harness the powers of the grain of rice, so now, the tides have changed and I was swimming in my own bathtub again.    Oh, if Ben hadn't knocked on the door that instant, Stuart would not have lived.    Well, I've been going on and on, so I'll try summarizing.  We went to buy fireworks, lit them, and then I went home.  Stuart tied a smoke bomb at the end of my bike and told me to ride it.  Awesome.   urlLink Eric  came later with his brother and a whole bag of fireworks.    That's basically, well maybe I'm 1300 hundred words too late for  basically  but whatever, it.    It's wierd, I've been getting déjà vu alot lately.  Maybe it's because of my growing up, memories tend to stack on each other, and therefore repeat.  I'm not certain.  But I'm always uneasy when it happens; you never know if Stuart might be lurking behind a corner laughing with his new creation of  déjà vu zoo .   
    
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This morning,  urlLink Eric  passed on a story to me.  It talks about the age old dispute between atheists and theists on "Does Evil Exist?";    The professor of a university challenged his students with this question: "Did God create everything that exists?"   A student answered bravely, "Yes, he did."  The professor then asked, "If God created everything, then he created evil."   Since evil exists (as noticed by our own actions), so God is evil.  The student couldn't respond to that statement causing the professor to conclude that he had "proved" that "belief in God" was a fairy tale, and therefore worthless.   Another student raised his hand and asked the professor, "May I pose a question?"   "Of course," answered the professor.   The young student stood up and asked: "Professor does Cold exists?"   The professor answered, "What kind of question is that?...Of course the cold exists... haven't you ever been cold?"   The young student answered, "In fact sir, Cold does not exist. According to the laws of Physics, what we consider cold, in fact is the absence of heat. Anything is able to be studied as long as it transmits energy (heat). Absolute Zero is the total absence of heat, but cold does not exist. What we have done is create a term to describe how we feel if we don't have body heat or we are not hot."   "And, does Dark exist?", he continued. The professor answered "Of course". This time the student responded, "Again you're wrong, Sir. Darkness does not exist either. Darkness is in fact simply the absence of light. Light can be studied, darkness can not. Darkness cannot be broken down. A simple ray of light tears the darkness and illuminates the surface where the light beam finishes. Dark is a term that we humans have created to describe what happens when there's lack of light."   Finally, the student asked the professor, "Sir, does evil exist?" The professor replied, "Of course it exists, as I mentioned at the beginning, we see violations, crimes and violence anywhere in the world, and those things are evil."   The student responded, "Sir, Evil does not exist. Just as in the previous cases, Evil is a term which man has created to describe the result of the absence of God's presence in the hearts of man."   After this, the professor bowed down his head, and didn't answer back.    Some people have said that the boy was Albert Einstein.  No one knows for sure.     
    
    
</post>


</Blog>