<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The graphic blogger uses for the posting in progress page is cool. Thank you, that is all.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'll finally be getting a degree. While this comes easy for some people, it hasn't for me. I've been working full time +, while trying to figure out what I wanted to actually go to school for. This turned into a 5 year adventure, for a 2 year degree. Hopefully my pace will increase while I go for my B.A. this fall. Best of all, I don't have to do the job hunt thing. Now I just need to finish up my Microsoft MCSE. Me and my motivation...
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      In two weeks I start a new job as Director of Technology at a local organization. Yey! I can't wait to start.   I'll be overseeing the current network of computers, telephones and security systems, as well as programming new billing software.  In other news, I starting looking for an apartment last week. Three bedrooms sure can be high and hard to find. Wish me luck.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'm mavrck. I tend to start a lot of projects at one time, so we'll see how much attention this gets.  Stay tuned!   -mav
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Last weekend, in Dayton, I saw Ben Folds (Formally of Ben Folds Five), Guster and some other guy. The Quick rundown is: Ben Folds was very funny, but sucked musicly; Guster was cool, I bought their cd; and the other guy was horrible and I walked out and left. I have Guster's cd in my computer right now, it's not too bad. This week I also purchased Switchfoot and Hoobastank cds. w0rd.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I don't remember when I've seen a group of people working so well together as we all are over at DL. Everyone is lending a hand. This is great. Thanks guys and gals.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Coding VB6. I'll have the billing project I'm working on done this week. Next project, website. Yey.  In other news, I activated my XM Radio account Saturday. Kick ass. I can't stop listening to it. I highly recommend the service.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I spent the weekend in Dayton to watch a concert and shopped a bit on Sunday. It was nice to be away for a change. Next month I'll be doing a 3 day weekend in the great state of TN. That should be fun as well. 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      What items would you like to see on DesignersLounge? Here's  my  list...  - Profile Pages (Like Yahoo Profiles or the old CV pages) - Better News/Hineline System - MySQL Resource Database (From Nicoles Flat List) - Elect Tutorial Person and Finally get a good tutorial database  give me your thoughts!
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      There's one thing you can count on, no matter what time of the day, where you find news, you'll find some mindless newscaster giving a rundown of bad stories of the day. God forbid you watch more than once, as you'll see the same crap once again. They should replace all of the news with better programming. Since I'm on the topic, they should replace replace all of the reality crap also.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Man, I love work now. This is so cool. I'm programming in VB, Which I don't like but I'm still having fun. Now I think I may close my personal business to focus on the new job and still give me extra time through the week. It's just so hard to turn down money though ;)
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Thanks to Novell Netware I lost my whole weekend. I was called to fix a computer, only to make it worse my using ghost on it. Tech Tip: Never try to use ghost on Novell Netware. I learned this one the hard way (killed the thing). Novell should crawl in a hole and die.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Now that my mind isn't tied up in school, it's already been wondering around. I think that this is the first break that I've had in 2 or 3 years. The first time I've not been overwhelmed or been self overbooked. It feels strange. Now I've been thinking about what activities I want to pursue. I think that I'll make a Saturday morning tee time each week and I think I'll try to devote some more time to the GOP. Of course, I can't leave out developing things I've been forces to overlook at  urlLink DL  as well. Any other things that I should try?
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Sometimes a want to buy a five pack of  urlLink these  and wear them around everywhere I go. People can be funny. I wonder if I was a doctor if people would stop me on the street to fix their problems?! So, then if I was a porn star would I get stopped my people for my 'services'? That's borderline to being one of SNL's deep thoughts.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'm on my third day at the new job. I love it so much! I'm still in the process of fixing up my office, but when I'm done I'll post some pictures for all to see. I know I've not said anything about it before, but a few of the added benefits of my job is free membership to the pools and health/rec building. So now I can start to get back in shape also. Don't worry, I'm not big, so there won't be a  urlLink DBM transformation .
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I think I'm depressed. I'm worried that I can get this way too easily. 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'm a wimp. I stayed up for 24 hours, got 4 hours of sleep, I'm at work and now all I can think abouit is going home and jumping in bed. Well, that and blogging I guess. 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Last weekend, while on vacation, I burt my hand while cooking a frozen pizza. I don't understand it, I've cooked hundreds of pizzas before, yet when I go on vacation I burn my hand. Isn't that moore's law or something?  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>