<Blog>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm bored out of my mind once again my plans failed and I'm sitting her disappointed I missed the movie I wanted to see because my mom wanted to plan games. Everyone in my house can take a peaceful nap but I take one and then people want to wake me up to do stupid crap. Its ridculous on the flip side last night I talked to my ex boyfriend I'm friends with his sister and me and him are still friends it was nice talkin to him catching each other up on each others lives. It was real nice. I told him of my fiancee and how wonderful he is and how much I love him and can't wait to be his wife. I'm really excited about all that. It was nice talking to someone I normally don't talk to but he's a real cool guy I think I'm going to keep in touch with him when i go to college that would be even better. So much as my fiancee and I what to say one minute we're on cloud nine the next we're at each other's throats but I'm going to try something new and see if it works. Hopefully it will. Lately it just seems like everyone i know is getting pregnant. I'm jealous but only a little because I know that I will have my day and until then I have some things that I have to accomplish before I start my family. Sometimes I wish that I could just start my family right now though. It would be nice. At the same time i want to be a little wiser and older I think I'll start having my kids around 22 after I gradaute college. But it's storming so i'm going to enjoy it................ 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was an ok day. I thought it was. The past week I've been going over his house in the morning his being my fiancee and waking him up so that he could go to work on time. Wed I had to go to work at 9 in the morning so I go there at like 6:50 and I put my pajamas back on and fell right back asleep in his arms I woke up looked at him and smiled. Thinking damn I'm about to spend the rest of my life with this man he's so beautiful. I don't know I think he's absolutely drop dead sexy. hehe you thought i was going to say sexy huh? But I think that he's amazing, then again I see him in a different light then most I"m the on that he complains and talks to as well as it should be. But Laying there with him was so fufilling and I get to do it for the rest of my life YAY. Spending this much time with him is absolutely heaven. I haven't really done too much else and thats fine with me. I can't wait to create all the memories with this guy. Hehe it's all good.  
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm still wondering why no one told me graduation didn't feel like anything? It wasn't exciting or anything. I just looked at my diploma like 4 years in this hell hole for this funky little piece of paper. That's pretty messed up. My family and boyfriend were there to watch me walk across the stage. I'm just happy that it's over with. Anyways I've just been kicking it with my bay since graduation it's all good most times right now we're mad at each other I hate that feeling. I hate that he has that much power I hate that I give in just so I don't have to argue. I'm just tired I guess cause the same shit just keeps happening over and over again I just wis things that you wanted could changed by a wiggle of the nose despite me being upset I don't want comfort from anyone but him. Even though he's not my favorite person right now I still want to be in his arms and only his arms. GRRRRRRRRRRRRRR .......... until tomorrow.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Today was very tiring mostly enjoyable but not the entire day. I walked out to my baybee's house and woke him up washed the jeans he needed washed for the lunch we were preparing for with Elighie (his professor). Then I took a shower while he was still sleeping. I don't know what it is about a hot shower but it's soothing like a bath especially long hot showers makes me think a lot about everything and it's there I try to comprehend the things that I haven't yet. I'm not slow or anything just takes me a little while to understand so call it what you want. Then I walk around because I don't want to disturb him. I lay at the foot of the bed he shifts so I have to I move to the side with the most room his back is facing me so I scratch it and we talk of a couple things it's funny how we both have trouble sleeping all the time. Anyway he locks his leg around mine I love the physical contact with him anything holding hands everything kissing caressing my face I love all of it it makes me tummy do cartwheels. It's the best feeling ever!!!! Does he know that? I hope so I hope that he feels the same way. Anywho we went out to lunch with his professor not before getting into a lovers spat (that wouldn't be the only one of the day)before we got there generally giving me an attitude. I try really hard but it just seems like Evan knows the right combination of buttons to push sometimes, I enjoyed lunch he held my hand for a couple of seconds... Which was comforting. We ran some errands then went back to his house where I attempted to clean his room. I accomplished a little we can see the floor. Oh yeah I was cleaning because I was making him write his letter to Monmouth otherwise he would just put it off and continue to do so. Somewhere when he came back there I wanted to spend some q-time with him whether it be laying together or running around the house playing like little kids. It didn't matter to me I just wanted some attention that's all.Some generally I got mad when I didn't get it. He took me home, I chilled for a bit then I went up stairs in hope to clean me own room I was sadly mistaken, Evan called and told me to be there early. He signed me up for League fun stuff.... I got there and our attitudes were different from earlier which was nice. We bowled three games won the first 2 lost the last one. And in the last one we got into another spat. He always makes me feel like I'm wrong and an idiot I know that's not his intention ya know? But it just happens like that... The entire car ride home was silence until we got into my drive way where we semi talked and I kissed him apologized hugged him and he told me that he loved me which is always nice to hear my friend taliah who dropped me off was suppose to come back and never did she didnt start calling until 930 by then I was like F*@$ it. It didn't matter. But it's all good I guess I'm use to that. Then she calls at like 1245 to see what happened to me. Whatever that was a lost cause don't you think but whatever. I watched you got served the corniest movie but the dancing was HOT. Newho lets see what I thought about today... Many things I'm an extremely Jealous person but not all the time, just sometimes grrrrrr I'm working on that, was thinking about my family how much I love em but I just got to get away quick fast and in a hurry.Friends always know how to disappoint you no matter what it sucks but what can ya do ya know... Until next time.....
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was my last day of high school. In a sense it was one of those I can't believe that it's over type deals. I'm really happy that it's over now time for the real world, well semi- real world. Where I make all my decisions what to do? I'll be an adult with responsibilites, it's weird but at the same time relievinng.It a wonderful feeling but at the same time it's sad because everything goes so fast. When you're younger you look forward to high school when it's over then you look forward to college after college some go right into the real world for others it's off the grad school or medical school after or during you get married and have a family and some where in between there I'll grow up. Right now just isn't that time. It's just so crazy how things fly by so fast and you don't even realize it. I'll probably cry I know that my mom probably is. I love her to death she's a wonderful woman but very controlling at times. I know her and my father are proud of me. I took a lot of pictures none of my by myself really. It's just weird how I was sitting in my class it felt like just yesterday that I started high school amazing I've waited for this day for what it feels like centuries. I spent time with my Other Half today his name is Evan, when he came and got me I just looked at him and smiled, amazing how much you can love one person and the feeling you get when you're with them. I still get the butterflies the tingles all of that good stuff, eight months and I get the same feelings but now it's ten times stronger. I never imagined someone making me feel this good. Don't get me wrong we've have our fair share of bad, but the good comes out on top. He's wonderful I wish there were words to describe how I felt about him there are but I'm just not that great with writing about things such as love my friend La'teasha is great at that and so is Evan he's a wonderful writer. The other night he told me that bowling was his thing the one thing that he was good at and I'm thinking that's not the only thing you're good at you're good at loving me and putting your everything into us, all the free time you have that is. See me and my boyfriend come from two different worlds, it's hard to compromise my world to fit around his sometimes but I do because I love him. Not that our worlds are so completely opposite just they're different in many aspects. On that note see you when I have more thoughts   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       This is my first blog, we learned about this is class so i thought that it would be kinda cool to start one of my ways people can read my thoughts whether they're stupid or insightful. I have both. Tomorrow is my last day of high school and then it's off into the semi real world which is also known as college. But I've been told college isn't reality it's after college that you have to worry about. I guess. I'm excited about a lot of things as dorky as that sounds being able to vote, being out on my own all that goos stuff, being able to make my own decisions. Believe me  I think I'm anything but grown and far from it still I know some things but so do other people I still have a whole lot of learning to do which is cool. I have wonderful people in my life to guide me so it's all good. I don't think I'll cry tomorrow I'm tired of all the drama that goes on in high school it's absolutely ridiculous not that I  imagine college to be too much different. Me and my friend adam were talking the other day and he said he loved college and that the only difference in college is that the most of the idiots are filtered but there are some idiots that slip through the cracks that's ok I guess. I'm just ready to close this chapter in my life, that's sounds so corny but that's really how I feel. Well I'm going to go for now............. until then
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I haven't written in quite sometime.. where shall I start? I don't even remember the last time that i wrote in this blog thing well  I had a slight interruption my baby called. He is so wonderful and can in the midst of all choas always put a smile on my face. He doesn't know that and I don't always let him know that but it's alright I guess.I went through this extremely unhappy phase for a little while, why? To be completely honest afterward I never know why I let myself be unhappy for that long. But now that I'm happy and perky I haven't the slightest clue why i was unhappy oh yeah my mom could have something to do with it lack of communication with my significant other could have something to do with it. You know the other day he told me that he thinks that his dad knows that he's going to marry me, well my parents know that I want to marry him... And my mom said that he's growing on her and little does he know my dad likes him which is wonderful. The night before my graduation party Evan came over to get an Dvd and I gave him cheaper by the dozen when he got home he put it on to watch and text message me and said i'll give you nine kids.. And i you wonder why i love you so much.. there's so much to look forward to with you and that's one of the many reasons he then said give me nine more and i did. Some days that's the only thing that cheers me up that there's someone out there who loves me as much as i love him. but anyways. Family life hasn't been a complete buzz kill, my brother is so cool as hell my mom hasn't been nagging lately and my dad has been pretty cool.  It seems like the closer it gets for the time for me to leave the more my sister and I argue and sometimes it's just like alright already but i just for some reason can't give in sometimes but other times it's not so easy. I've been pretty content with doing nothing really I have before that would have driven me absolutely wild but now im content with watching a little tv writting in my journal reading talking to my other half and then just sleeping I crave sleep now a days I'm tired so this is enough for this time...........
     
    
</post>


</Blog>