<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      .. don't know why I chose that as a title.... I can't stand Megadeth.  Bank Holiday Monday here in England... no work (got all week off anyway), haven't done any drawing... nothing much to say other than:  Countdown to new tattoo: less than 24 hours!  Be seeing you.    Listening to: nothing! 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's Sunday so I have done bugger all. Had a nice day with my girlfriend and her family and spent tonight playing Command & Conquer: Generals, so now I'm gonna do some research... and read some comics :-D  Countdown to new tattoo: 2 days  Be seeing you.    Listening to: nothing. 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Another sketch of Storm Shadow:   urlLink      I took a bit more time on this one, sketched it out with a 6H pencil, lined out the details with a HB and then used a 2B to finish it off. I also... shock horror... used a rubber (or eraser to you Americans reading this :-D). When I was at college (1995-1998) I got stuck in a mind set where I didn't like using rubbers, I preferred to leave all the pencil lines on the page so people could see how the image was built up.  I'm more pleased with this sketch than I was with the last, but already I have noticed a few things I don't like, mainly the arms and the pose itself, it's not too bad but it's not as "dynamic" as I was aiming for, I guess that will come with more practice.  Also, as soon as I finished it I realised how much it looks like how Andrew Wildman used to draw Ninjas in the GI Joe comic... no surprise really since he is one of my favourite artists. I assure you this was total coincidence, although if I saw this picture I would instantly think it had been (badly) copied from a Wildman picture.  Got the whole of this coming week off work so I shall hopefully get more and more sketches up including some of my own comics' characters.  Be seeing you.    Listening to: Dimmu Borgir - Puritanical Euphoric Misanthropia (Excellent Scandinavian black metal. Within the black metal "scene" they are seen as being quite poppy and commercial, but I love 'em!) 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Paul and Jonic are getting together on Monday to put together ideas for the webcomic we are doing, so I should be able to start drawing stuff up for that next week.  Today, comic wise, all I have done is posted on Newsarama about weather Rob Liefeld's artwork is any good or not. Poor guy was once one of the "hottest" comic artists in America and now everyone just bashes him. Personally I like his work in the same way I like films like Piranha and Gone In Sixty Seconds... mindless entertainment that is fun and is easy to follow. If every writer and artist was "deep and meaningful" then the world would be boring! So thanks Rob (and Fabian) for doing some cool entertainment, I can't wait for the new X-Force series.  Ah, last day of work for 9 days! If the weather is nice this weekend me and my lovely girlfriend are going camping, Tuesday I get my new tattoo (a pic will be up asap after it's done) and the rest of the week I will be relaxing and drawing :-)  By hook or by crook... ;-)    Listening to: VAST - Nude (Good to chill to on an afternoon) 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Quick post: I'm tired, fed up of my job and frustrated. Might try and "ink" the Storm Shadow picture tonight. Needs more blacks and less shading. I keep looking at it every few hours and spotting what's wrong with it, so I my do another one from scratch and take some more time over it.  Yes, this is a pointless post and I'm only doing it to keep up the fact I've done one every day since i started this Blog.  Be seeing you.    Listening to: VAST - Nude (Excellent album, reminds me of Achtung Baby and POP-era U2) 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Storm Shadow  This is a quick sketch I have just thrown together of GI Joe character Storm Shadow in his classic Cobra outfit.  It's not a bad sketch but I'm not pleased with some of the proportions and the pose isn't as dynamic as I would have liked, but it's the first time I have properly drawn in a few years so I'm quite pleased with it. The "shading" is terrible though, something I need to work on. Maybe I will ink the piece and see how it looks with solid blacks.  A bit more time and practice and I'll be more confident about drawing my own comic. I'm not a big fan of a lot of modern American artists who all seem to be "influenced" by Manga (most of which try too hard to copy the style of many manga artists but lack the actual skill) or draw far too cartoony for the books they are on. Recently I've been looking at more British and European stuff, mainly people like John Cassady, Bryan Hitch, Frank Quitley and the guy who draws the French comic XIII (recently seen in the UK for the first time in a computer game), sadly I'm not too sure which guy is the artist and which is the writer, either way the art on XIII is amazing.  So, yeah, more practice is needed, I'll probably sketch a few different GI Joe characters in different styles until I start to feel happy about committing pencil to paper for my own stuff.  Be seeing you.    Listening to: the news on BBC1. 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tuesday is band night, so no work at all on the comic side of life today.  Be seeing you.   Listening to: the sounds of the office.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Quick post tonight, not much to add to be honest. Been a bit busy tonight so haven't done much except for scribble down a few ideas in my "ideas book" and read some comics (It's research! Honest!).  Be seeing you.    Listening to: Kiss - God Gave Rock & Roll To You II (been stuck in my head ALLL night!) 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Action Man!  What am I doing?   That is a question to myself. It's Sunday afternoon, been a really nice day and I spent most of it indoors playing on the computer!  This morning me and my girlfriend set up our new tent in the garden to see how fast we could get it up and down. She then went home to revise for some exams so I sat in the garden for a bit with the cats enjoying the sun and then came in and played Command & Conquer: Generals. I know I wasn't gong to turn this Blog into a "personal diary" but the above reasons are why I haven't done much today in the way of comics. I've done a few sketches and roughed out some more plots, but that's it. I was hoping to have a few pages fully drawn by now when I first started this comic thing back up a few months ago.  So, instead of procrastinating so much I'm gonna play on the computer a bit more and then get down to some serious writing. Once I have fully plotted out my first few stories then I *will* start to draw the damn thing!  Be seeing you.    Listening to: Nothing, the TV is on and it's some "drama" about an earthquake in New York. Good background entertainment! 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Added a links bit down the side now, thanks to the help of my lovely girlfriend who showed me an easy way to do it using some Bloglines thing or something.  I really should start designing an original page for this instead of using one of these templates, since my day job actually is "web designer" I feel like I'm cheating using a template. The comics themselves will have actual web-sites, this Blog is just for me to use to keep track of the "journey".  Anyway, I keep talking about this "journey" but haven't actually shown much in the way of comic stuff I've done myself. I'll try and get some stuff up within the next few days.  Be seeing you.    Listening to: Kiss - Crazy Nights (The Darkness? Who are they then...? Stuff the Darkness, listen to Kiss!!!) 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Snake Eyes!  Just installed this "Hello" software thing so I can upload pics directly to my Blog easily.  That Is all, be seeing you.    Listening to: my eyelids saying "go to bed". 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Well, the weekend doth approacheth and that means some time to really kick things into gear! Going to go through all my sketches and start tightening up the character designs for my own comic. The first 12 issues are "roughly" plotted out, most of the first issue is scripted and the first few pages have been roughed out as thumbnails. Once I finalise the actual character designs I shall start drawing the proper pages.  Not much time to write at the moment, still at work, so I shall go into more detail soon!  Be seeing you.    Listening to: Nothing at the moment, although it was Hatebreed :-) \m/ 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, the little webcomic I'm doing with some other guys is starting to come together already. Paul and Jonic (the writers) are putting together a few scripts and character profiles for me to use to design the characters.  Meanwhile I'm currently putting together "reference" materials for my own comic. Collecting photos and things like that, mainly of New York City and of people I want to base characters on. The book is going to be something along the lines of Strangers In Paradise/Slice-of-life kind of stuff mixed with The Authority/The Ultimates style action and ultra-violence. My super-hero team is going to be more military based than most comic book super-teams, and the slice-of-life stuff will be based more around the life of Brian (hmmm, good title there ;-) ) and his friends. I'm also basing a lot of the plots involving Brian on things I have experienced in life, nothing too exciting but it's something I can write easy (I hope) and I suppose it will act as a bit of a catharsis.  I've taken a lot of ideas and sketches I did when I started this book years ago and... scrapped most of them! I'll get more ideas and plots up soon, along with some sketches and stuff.  Be seeing you.    Listening To: Mudvayne - The End Of All Things To Come (I think that's the full album title, the case is at home so I can't check. Don't even know the name of the song (track 6). It's not a bad album, enjoyable and interesting in places, but verges a little too much on nu-metal for my liking. Probably put Hatebreed back on in a minute) 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow, 2nd day and I'm already making my second post in one day.  I've had a new idea, one to run along side my other ideas (which I havent really posted about yet, but I will). Panini publish loads of Licensed comics in the UK, based on cartoon characters. So, the plan is to try and break in through something like that. They accept submissions and if you are any good they will give you a job, anything is worth a try.  A lot of my favourite artists started by working for 2000AD, so that might be worth a try as well.  Also, a mate of mine has contacted me after reading this and has asked me to draw for his upcoming web-comic, this will be in more of a cartoony style than how I usually draw, but I can't wait as it should be cool :-)  So, as it stands I have:  My own full on 22 pages an issue super-hero-soap-opera which I will publish online for free, just cos it's a story I really want to tell. And hopefully if its good enough it will get published properly.  My idea that I want to work with another artist on (this involves Zombies, Godzilla sized monsters and men in radiation suits).  Submitting stuff to companies her ein the UK like 2000AD and the Panini stuff.  And last but not least, the web comic which will be more of a traditional 3-Panel style thing.  Be seeing you.    Listening to: Raunchy - Confusion Bay (Crap band name, but awesome band from Denmark, fast and heavy but very catchy. Remind me of SYL crossed with Soilwork. ROCK \m/) 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Not really much to post this morning, I was out last night practicing with my new band (no name sorted yet, but we are thrash-metal sort of stuff), but I'm going to try and post something here everyday regardless.  Might as well get a bit of history out of the way: After school I went straight to York College to study art and spent 3 years there, passing 2 courses (GNVQ Advanced and BTEC Foundation, both specialising in fine art). I had been into comics since I was a little kid and was always drawing my own but didn't get chance to do anything like that at college.  I applied to Leeds Met Uni to do a Graphic Design: Illustration course, where I was told they did comic art. I wasn't too keen on going to Uni but I went on the basis that my parents would support me and if i didn't enjoy it i could drop out with no hassle. So, i started the course and found out the teachers who specialised in comics had left the Uni and wouldn't be replaced.... instantly I knew i didn't want to stay.   I gave it a few months and then moved back home where i started to draw my own comic. It was about 2 guys, Brian and Phil, who shared a flat. Phil was "normal" but Brian had super powers and was the son of one of the most famous super heroes in the little world i created. Brian, however, didn't want the life of a hero and wanted to live normally, but was constantly made to feel guilty by his super powered brother who led the local "team" of heroes (kind of like The Avengers or the JLA). I planned out a few issues and drew the entire first issue. I put together a full proposal and sent it to a few American companies. Basically, my stuff was crap and I got turned down. I put all the art and story ideas aside and gradually forgot about it all.  Then a few months ago I dug it all out again and started re-planning it all, changing some stuff and adding to it. So , my current plan for world domination is this: Writing and drawing my own series, based roughly on my proposal involving the characters Brian and Phil, and i shall publish this online for free, and i also have a few story ideas I'm going to flesh out more and then find an artist to draw with the plan of submitting these to other publishers.  That's the plan anyway, and the purpose of this Blog is to keep a record of what i do (or don't do) and the journey I take.  Be seeing you.    Listening to: Hatebreed - The Rise Of Brutality (Simple but positive music! LIVE FOR THIS! IF YOU DON'T LIVE FOR SOMETHING YOU'LL DIE FOR NOTHING!) 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Righty ho then, just set this thing up so expect the look and feel to change over the next week or so until I'm happy with it.  This Blog has one basic reason: to chart my "progression" from bored web designer to *cough* "super-star" *cough* comic artist.  I shall gradually add more "about me" type crap to here, mainly my back ground in art, how I first tried to become a comic artist after I left college, how (and why I think) I failed and why now, at almost 25, I am going to try once more.  Oh, and I love music and I'm crap at spelling.    Listening to: Heaven Shall Burn - Antigone (currently track 14, an amazing cover of Not My God by Hate Squad) 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Finally got some more stuff scanned up, spent most the weekend doing Judge Dredd sketches, I think I'm finally happy with the helmet, and I can pretty much draw the outfit without referring to any pictures now.  So, here is a few Judge Dredd images:   urlLink    This is Dredd and PSI Officer Anderson.   urlLink    Quick sketch of Judge Hershey, a random sketch of the Judges outfit and a head sketch of Judge Joe Dredd himself.   urlLink    My favourite of the sketches, simple bust shot of Judge Dredd, I think I'm finally finding my feet with a style that uses a lot of shadow but balances it with detail. I'm tempted to ink this piece to see how it looks.  Here are some sketches I've done for the web comic. Still not happy with "Paul", I'm pleased with how "Jonic" has come out, but I've spent ages trying to do sketches of how Paul should look but I still cant quite get it:   urlLink      urlLink     My hand is killing me now, so I think I'll call it a day!  Be seeing you!    Listening to: Nightwish - Once and Century Child (Awesome albums!) Would be nice to listen to Skid Row and Motley Crue... hint hint Paul :-p 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Spent a lot of the night doing sketch after sketch of Judge Dredd, trying to nail down the costume and the right look, each time though I seem to get the head too small!! Aggghhh!  Early night now though... Totally knackered, gonna read some comics and then sleep. Lots.  Be seeing you.    Listening to: Lots of Nightwish! 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think I have just about got the 2 main characters for the web comic sorted. To be honest I'm still not 100% happy with these, problem being that I cant put my finger on what is wrong. Anyone got any comments or ideas on how to improve the characters look? (Baring in mind they are based on 2 real people)   urlLink     The "look" is there, but I don't know what's wrong. I'm going to draw up a decent tight version, scan it and then colour it and see how it looks then. Maybe it's just the "finish" that is the problem.  Onto my own comic: Had to rub out and redo all the background of the first panel cos I got the perspective all wrong which was annoying.... so I set up some GI Joe figures and took various photos to get the distance and perspective correct, which I think has worked. Should have the page finished on Monday night, then I really want to get on with my Submission for 2000AD, don't know whether to do Judge Dredd (the obvious) or Rogue Trooper (my favorite!).  Also been working on my bands website. Originally me and the singer from my old band were just going to reform the band with a few new members, but for various reasons we are using a different name and totally new songs (so nothing to do with the old band really, except a few riffs we had lying around that we liked). You can see what I have done with the site so far by clicking  urlLink here .  And I've noticed the time on this thing is wrong, think I have set it right now! :-)  Be seeing you.    Listening to: Sepultura - Arise \m/ 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here is a scan of Issue One, Page One of my still untitled comic. At the moment, in my head, I'm calling it "Intermezzo" but I think that will change soon. I'm also looking into the cost of publishing it properly, on paper, instead of online.   urlLink    Issue One, Page One   Once this page is finished I shall start work on the first webcomic written by Paul and Jonic. And I also have some websites to work on and update, not too sure how I'm going to fit everything in my life! Ah well, going to Paris again in 6 weeks, wooo!  Be seeing you.    Listening to: Nightwish - Once (Awesome symphonic, female fronted metal band. Evenescence only wish they could be this good!) 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here are 2 quick character sketches I did the other night for my comic. The top one is Diamond (yes, I know there is a character of the same name in Powers, but I named mine first in 1998 the first time I started this comic! :-p ), real name Stuart Shultz, he is the brother of Brian.  The bottom sketch is of ??????? who will appear around Issue #12 of the comic.    urlLink    Diamond and ????  As I type I am taking a break from drawing my first full page of the comic, might put up a scan when it's about half done. Then I'm going to get on with some work for the web comic I'm working on.  Be seeing you.    Listening to: Nothing. 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Been a bit busy the past few days so I haven't posted, I have however got some pics to scan to put on here once I've finished "rebuilding" my computer (at least once a year I wipe the thing and start again, keeps the thing fast and tidy)  Be seeing you.    Listening to: the news. 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here are a few sketches of the two main characters in the web comic I'm working on. Paul and Jonic are writing it and are also the basis of the two main characters (Jonic is the skinny one, Paul is the one that is my evil twin).   urlLink       urlLink      It took me a few pages of scribbles to get to these images and I'm still playing around with the look of each character, so in no way are these final.  I haven't really done any cartoon style stuff for about 10 years and I forgot how hard it is to make a cartoon look good (I'm having enough trouble getting realistic stuff to look good!).  Should hopefully have some more sketches up later today.  Be seeing you.    Listening to: Nothing. 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      No scans today, extremely busy day so I'm winding down by playing Morrowind.  Scans and stuff tomorrow, I promise!  Be seeing you.    Listening to: nothing. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, it's nearly the weekend, and after that I will be back at work. Nothing scanned in yet but I've done a load of sketches for my own comic and also designed the 2 main characters for the web comic, gonna practice them a bit and then ink them up and scan them. Then I'll have a play around with what style of colouring to use.  Anyway, back to the drawing board...  Be seeing you.    Listening to: Eastenders on the TV. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just a quick one: done some sketches of characters for my comic, started ideas for the web comic with Paul and Jonic (have 8 or 9 scripts so far from them, damn funny stuff, just hope my drawings are as good as the scripts!). Got one character sorted for the web comic but the other is proving a bit harder (will put up some scans soon).  Be seeing you.    Listening to: Nothing. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bought some new pencils and pens today, did some sketches, sooo tired.... going to bed...  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink      Here is a picture of my fat hairy body and my new tattoo! Will maybe write more about it in the morning, just got home from practice with the band and I'm knackered!  Be seeing you.   Listening to: Nothing.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Just got back from a lovely holiday in Paris with my lovely girlfriend, it was.... lovely :-)     &nbsp;   And now I'm back at work and its crap. I've been looking at the page and half of my comic I have done and they are crap. But I'm determined.... practice, practice and more practice until I'm happy... and then I'm gonna sort something proper to send to 2000AD. Really need to put a plan together of what I'm going to do.     &nbsp;   Something that hasn't helped is that when in Paris I bought some more French comics, one has art by American Artist John (Planetary, Astonishing X-Men, Capitan America) Cassaday.... I've spent a few hours sat looking at the art (don't understand half the writing as its in French, I'll have to buy the American version) and I just keep staring and thinking "how will I ever be this good?". The other stuff I bought by French artists is equally as good, the art is amazing and just makes me jealous.     &nbsp;   *sigh*     
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here is the final scan of Page One of my comic. I'm about 60% happy with it, I can see a lot of room for improvement and I think the best practice is to "do".   urlLink      I scanned the pencils, duplicated the layer and then set that layer to multiply which gives an almost "inked" look.  I've started in page two, it's gonna be a slow process since I'm doing the lot on my own.... ah well, back to the drawing board ;-)  Be seeing you.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Next Monday I shall be 25 years old.... 25!!!!!!!!!!  I'm still stuck here in my crap job where no one cares about pushing the department forward (which would bring them more profit and hopefully more wages for me!) but I do have an interview on Tuesday for a better job (the day before I go to Paris for a week, wooo!).  My dream of being a comic artist isn't really much nearer. I have finished the pencils for the first page of my own book, and I have it plotted out in detail up to about issue #15, the only problem is finding the time to draw.  Not too sure what's going on with the web-comic thing, I've mailed the guys a few times and had no replies (and Paul STILL has my Skid Row and Motley Crue CD's :-( ) so I'm just going to concentrate on my own stuff for the time being.   Also very busy with the band, practicing every week, sorting gigs and stuff, and we are booked to go in the studio in early August, which should be cool.  My lovely girlfriend is currently moving house so won't be visiting me tonight so I think I shall use the time to do some more drawing. I find it hard to motivate myself into doing it, but once I start I really get into it. Also, reading a damn good comic helps motivate me :-)  That is all for now :-)
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, here we finally have a colour image of the characters for the Web Comic!  Didn't think I'd get any time to draw today, some gardening needed doing and I spent all afternoon doing that, which turned out to help with the comic! Inspiration comes from all sorts of weird places, and today it came from my neighbour. By coincidence he looks a lot like me (sans beard), he is big with a shaved head, and Paul (the real life Paul whom I was having trouble turning into comic Paul) is also big with a shaved head. So, as I'm chatting to our Neighbour I was suddenly hit with inspiration on how to draw Paul, so after I finished in the garden I came in, did a quick sketch and it looked right, so I inked it up, scanned it and coloured it and I think I'm finally happy with the look! The only problem with the picture is that I forgot Jonic's eyebrows!! Ah well!  I'll let the guys see the pic and if they are happy with both designs then I can finally get on with it!    urlLink       Listening To: Unearth (new album which I've forgotten the name of! Very \m/ though :-D ) 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Not much to post right now, been busy finishing my band's site which is now live at:  www.daiatlus.co.uk  And now i'm dragging myself away from the computer to refine plotting out my comic a bit more.  Be seeing you.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>